<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR798*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Ryan.</P>
      <P>Thanks for you letter. I am so exciting that I have won the first prize. I will give you all information you need and ask some questions.</P>
      <P>I could only travel on July. As you know, I am a student and the nearest holiday is summer holiday. But I have booked a flight to home at the beginning of Auguest. And also I would like to go on summer.</P>
      <P>The accommodation I would like to live in tents. Because I never live in tents before. I think it is great and I want to try it.</P>
      <P>I like doing sports. I would like to play basketball and golf when I am at the Camp. I play basketball a lot and I am a member of our college term. But I am not very good at golf.</P>
      <P>And also I want to ask some questions. What clothes should I taken? How much money should I taken? And how could we meet at the airport? I am looking forward your reply.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>As our class is going to mark a short video about daily life at college, I write this report to suggest some lessons and activities which should be filmed.</P>
      <P>1. English lesson. Because all students in English class are from all over the world. We can talk everybody's feeling living and study at a foreign country.</P>
      <P>2. Computing lesson and computer room. Nowdays internet makes us closer and closer. We can get all what we want on internet. It's one of the most important things in our life now.</P>
      <P>3. Liabrary. We not only borrow books from liabrary but also study at liabrary. Library is very important in our daily life.</P>
      <P>4. Canteen. Everyday we go to canteen have lunch, no matter you bought food from there or you take your own food.</P>
      <P>5. Football. What do you do after class? Joging or doing some sports? You can't forget football.</P>
      <P>These are what I think should be filmed. If any of you have other suggestion, we can discuss again. But I think these five lesson or activities are most common in our daily life at college.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
