<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR160*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Madam Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I have received your letter yesterday. I really thanks for your organisation has given me the opportunities to go abroad U.S.A.</P>
      <P>The date that I would like to travel, that will be nice to go on 1st of July. Because my summer holidays break is start at end of June. And I need few days to prepare my stuff.</P>
      <P>Regarding to the accommodation, I would prefer to stay in tents more than log carbins because I have a lot of experiences of built up my own tents. When I was in highschool I used to be a member of the campfire.</P>
      <P>The activities that you have listed forms. Some of the them I really interested in it, especially painting. Since I was young, my dad he alway took me out to have live drawings, so now it became my hobbies. And I think, it is nice to draw the beautiful landscapes of the place. Beside drawings, swimming is my favourite as well. When I was in highschool, I have joined in the swimming club. And I also participated in a few swimming competition. Although I'm not the best, but I have a lot of confident in it.</P>
      <P>At last some of things I need to clarify, that is, what type of clothes and money do I need to prepared.</P>
      <P>Thanks again.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>I agree! Sometimes shopping is not always enjoyable. For most of the people might think, why would I say that, because shopping is a very good entertainment especially for female, as me.</P>
      <P>But, when during any peak season, like Christmas, holidays or even during weekends. Then I can say I'm definatly doesn't feel any enjoyable. Because of the crowd. For me I think, it is not shopping that is kind of suffering. Especially, queue up for twenty minutes for just paying the money or waiting for the salesgirl getting your the right size of clothes. So sometimes I don't think shopping is enjoyable, and if there is any big festival, I would rather stay at home and watch television.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
