<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR37*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dir Madam</P>
      <P>I'm writing to you in reply to your letter. I was really suprised when I opened it. I look forword to going to the Camp California in the USA. I would like to travel only in July because my family is going to visit me on August and I will have to look after them. I prefer staying in tens to staying in log cabins. Because it remainds me my childhood. I used to going with my friends to the camp, wich was situeded on a seaside.</P>
      <P>We had always enjoying ourselves. Never had I got such a great time. From your's list of activities I choose sailing and climbing. I'm keen on sailing, it is my favourite sport. I find it very atractive. I have been sailing since my father had bought a boat in 1980, when I was only five years old. However, I have never taken part in any competitions connected with this sport. For me it is only a hobby. Last year I took up climbing and I want to carry on learning this sport.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask what kinds of clothes should I take with me. and I wonder if prizes are high there.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Angelina</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>I used to like shopping, but recently I came across many disadvantage of this activity. Most people think that if they have got money they will buy everything what they want. It isn't true. Nowdays we have many big shopping centers. We like them because everything is on one place. The most suitable time for shopping is weekand when parents don't work and children haven't got a school. Because of that shopping centers are over crowded. You can't buy something in peacful and calm athmospher. In addition in such kind of shops prizes are very high, of course not all of them. However such centers are very useful and necessary. I my opinion the worst thing which may happened is extremly hugh queu to the changing room. It is really exhausting. Afterwards you are all in. Nevertheless sometimes shopping could be enjoyable. If you bought something goregous, you would be very happy. On balance I think that shopping should be a nice thing so if you have bad mood don't go shopping.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
