<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR787*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam</P>
      <P>I'm writting to you to complain about the musical show that I saw when I went to the theatre on my holidays in London.</P>
      <P>First of all I had read in the advertisement that it would start at 19:30 and that I would have some discount, but it started at 20:15, what means that I had to wait for forthy five minutes, and there wasn't any discount on tickets.</P>
      <P>For my surprise Danny Brook never apeard. There was a different actor instead and it put me very nervous. He is my favorite actor and I pay to saw him not to saw a different actor.</P>
      <P>Finally at the end of the sow I decided to went to the theatre restaurant but it was closed because it wasn't been repeard yet. I think you must told people about this in the advertisement.</P>
      <P>I was a bit disappointed because you told that it would be a perfect evening and it wasn't.</P>
      <P>I enclose my postal addresses and I will be looking forward to a completly refound</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Fashion of the Future</P>
      <P>We could see all over the human being How the fashion change in its colours and styles, Since the first men on the earth started to wear kind of clothes because they were a bit cold</P>
      <P>Asking people about the Fashion of the Future you realise that there are different opinions. Adults think that new coloured clothes, that young people wear are horrible an very untraditional. Most of them believe that they are kind of crazy or ievel. They think that in the future they will change and start to wear more formal clothes.</P>
      <P>On the other hand young people believe that in the Future things'll be very different. Carol, 16 years old girl, said "I imagine clothes in the future very strang. May be they would have many colors and they would be very thight. They would be sinthetic clothes, I think made of plastic or something similar."</P>
      <P>Most young people as Carol believe the same and use their minds to imagin the variety of clothes in the future. After wear they'll be the ones that dicide How the Fashion of the Future will be like.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
