<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR446*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>My name is Steven. I'am very serpride when I get the letter from you. And heard that I have win the prise. Goging on a camp California in the U.S.A. for one week.</P>
      <P>And you need some imformation from me. About when would I like to go? And I think I love togo on July. Because is good time for camping and the weather is lovely at this time of the year.</P>
      <P>And the most important reason is because I' am still a student. And I study at London International School. So July is my end of year holiday. So I be happy to go on july. And about the accommodation at camp. I like to stays in tent because it have more feeling about adventure that's call camping. And in the letter that you send to me also whant's me to choose two activities to do while I was at the camp. So I will choose two activities that I good at and not good at. The first one is the one that I good at is Basketball. I use to play basketball at school and play for school team. And the second activities is the one that I not good at or I never try it before is surfing. I love to try surfing because it is a very interessting sport and use a lot of power and enigy so now is the end of the letter. And I want to know more about the money can you give me more imformation about the money that I need to bring whith me</P>
      <P>Thank you for every things</P>
      <P>Your sincerely</P>
      <P>Frank Steven.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>Now let's start whith shopping at Beverley Center. Beverley Center area is the place that the teenager like to go shopping the most. But some teenager like to go to Bolton-Market. Because every one havebeverley center if you there every day or every week for a shopping you well get very boring because some time is to much people every where like in the resturant and shops. It's make you feel want to go home. And about the traffic some times it makes you feel don't want to go out because of the traffic. And if you never know money or you have less money shopping is not enjoyable for you I'am choue. And shopping in the market is one think that I' am not going to do. Because all the smell in the market is alfrell is the smell of the meat and durty water black and smely water all over the market street. I think of it it's make my shopping enjoyable. And that's why some time shopping is enjoyable. Because the place and people.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
