<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR581*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen</P>
      <P>I am writing to thank you for the first prize in your competition and reply to your letter.</P>
      <P>First of all, according to your letter you asked me my prefered travel dates. If it is possible, I would only like to travel in July because I am going to go on my holiday in July.</P>
      <P>On your letter, you are going to provid me one of tents and log cabins with accommodation at Camp California. I would like to be in tents because I can find it being in tents more comfortable than being in log cabins.</P>
      <P>I am very happy because I can have a chance to do activities while I am at the camp. I would like to take part in the Golf and the sailing. I am not goot at both of them. I have been interested in them so I would like to turn up them on this chance.</P>
      <P>Finally, I would like to know something about travel. Could you let me know whether I need extra money or what sort of clothes I need. I would also like to know whether someone will be at the airport for me because this will be the first time in the U.S.A.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim</P>
      <P>I was happy to get your letter. I haven't writen a letter to you for ages. I'm sorry about that.</P>
      <P>On your letter, you want to hear about my experience at a pop concert. I'll tell you my experience about helping the pop concert.</P>
      <P>At first, I applyed for the volenteer at the pop concert and then I got a responsibility for control the audience. I had to make the fan to keep a queue. I also make them find their seats. It was very hard working. For example, I always spoke loudly and run fast.</P>
      <P>However, there was something good to me. I saw a lot of singers and entertainers. I didn't need to pay enterence fee because I was working there.</P>
      <P>Plus, I got a authography from a popular singer. I'll give you the authography for present. It is valuable of keeping on your suvinier</P>
      <P>I'll tell you more experience on next letter.</P>
      <P>Looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Best whishes</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
