<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR968*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs. Ryan,</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to thank you for this prize and the fact that you wrote me asking for my preferences about the Camp.</P>
      <P>About the information you needed, I have to tell you that I can only go in July, because of work reasons. Once there, I would prefer staying in tents, because that is a way to remember my childhood as a boyscout and go against the routine.</P>
      <P>From the list of activities you sent me, I stay with the, from my point of view, most relaxing activities available: painting and photography. One of my hobbies is the photography, so I think I am rather good at it, but I will take painting only to learn, because I am not very talentive at it.</P>
      <P>I also would like to know if I have to take money and what kind of clothes are suitable for that location. Please reply soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>David Brian</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>You are not going to believe what I am about to tell you! A couple of months ago, I was told that Britney Spears was coming to perform in our city. When I knew this, I managed to get a job as one of the kids that prepares the stage during the concert. I was really excited.</P>
      <P>The day of the show I worked so hard that I couldn't see the spectacle. And I didn't even got paid. But it was worthy. I found my reward when the concert finished. After been carrying stuff like lights, microphones, wires and some other equipment for about three hours, I was eshausted. But when Britney came out of the stage, she passed by me, saw my tired face and invited me to her personal changing room. We talked for about half an hour and when she said goodbye she gave me a kiss. I won't forget that moment ever. Write me soon to tell me your impression about what happened to me. Bye.</P>
      <P>With love</P>
      <P>David Brian</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
