<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1095*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>31-40</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>13th June</P>
      <P>Dear Ms Ryan</P>
      <P>I am so grateful and I can't believe I am so lucky to receiving your letter in which said that I have won the first prize in your competition, for two weeks camping in California in the U.S.A.</P>
      <P>I am writing to inform that I can only go in July, the summer holiday, because I have got a place in the university and it will start in August. Is there the time I request available? I would also like to ask accommodation you offer are in tens or log cabins. If I can choose I would prefer tens. I like to sleep on open land and see the sun come up in the morning.</P>
      <P>In addition, I choose painting and sailing for my activities. I can wait to do my painting for the rising sun, and can't imagine how wonderful sailing along the rivers.</P>
      <P>Finally, can you tell me what kind of clothes I should bring with, and how much spending money will be need.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>JUAN LILY LEE</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>13th June</P>
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable. I don't really like shopping. Sometime when I'm boring and can't find something else to do. I go look round shops. When I see some clothes in the window I like, I would go in and try them. But I always finds it not look nice on me. The other thing I don't like going shopping is in the weekend. All the shops are full of people, and people treat the articals like rubbish. Hang them every where after they tried and that was not suit them.</P>
      <P>Also in the weekend shopping. You do can't find some where to sit down comfortaly to have a cup of tea. Mc.Donnals, K.F.C, the all full of people.</P>
      <P>However, shopping is nice to spend you leisure time and give yourself to relax sometimes, but suggest that never in the weekend.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
