<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR140*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thanks for your letter, I am so glad that I have won first prize in your competition. And thanks again for offer me two weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A.</P>
      <P>As you asked, I think I'd like to travel only in July, because I am quite busy with my job. July is the only free time that I have. And I prefer tents to log cabins, as I know tents better than log cabins. I used to sleep in tent once on my holiday, and tent is more suitable for camping.</P>
      <P>It is very kind for you to give me the chance to do two activities while I am at the Camp. I'd like to have climbing and sailing. Actually I am quite good at climbing. I often go climbing in my town. For sailing, well, I haven't try it before, that is why I want to have a try. I think it must be fun.</P>
      <P>As you said, all accommodation and travel costs are paid for, but I am sure I still need some money with me. How much do you think that I will need. By the way what kinds of clothes do you think I have to get with me? And is there anything eles I have to get with me?</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable</P>
      <P>I think most people will agree with "shopping is not always enjoyable". Because so far as I know nothing is enjoyable all the time.</P>
      <P>Some people might say women just love shopping, they couldn't stop thinking about doing shopping. Yes, it is true, this is only because nowadays people have more money than even before, and some women don't earn money, they have no idea how diffcult to earn the money. Women just love spending money in shops. Just imagine if one day their husbands lost their jobs, will those women still thinking shopping is enjoyable! So it is depend on different case.</P>
      <P>For me, I don't think shopping is enjoyable at all. I even hate shopping. I only go to shop unless I really need something. Shopping is just like a nightmare to me, I think I will never understand why people love shopping. How can you face the same goods at the same shop all the time. I think most men have the same opinion as I do.</P>
      <P>Some women spend their whole life doing shopping, and most of times, they don't buy many things. In my eyes they are wasting their lifes, they are hopeless.</P>
      <P>Those are only my opinions, you don't need to agree with it, but one day you might found out that what I have said is not totally wrong.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
