<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR197*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear, Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for the prize at camp California in America.</P>
      <P>For the time that I would like to travel must be on July only. This is because my A-levels exams is coming up so I really need times to revise, and July is the only month and time that I am free.</P>
      <P>An accommodation, I prefer to stay in a tent. This is because it is my first time to see an outside world by myself so I need to gather up new experiences. I have never ever stayed in a tent before but some of the people I know said that it is fun and much more exiting.</P>
      <P>As I am a person who is love and doing activities, so I would like to choose to do sailing and photography. Once I used to take a photography course at my school and my teacher taught me well about taking photo. Also I tried how to sail before, but I am not perfectly good at it, but I love to sail more.</P>
      <P>Finally, I would like to ask about what kind of clothes do I need to bring? and the money, do I need much of them? Please, give me a suggestion about these.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear, Kim</P>
      <P>How are you? I have written to you to tell you about the greatest experience that I ever have.</P>
      <P>Last week I offered myself to help the others at the concert and it was amazing. I couldn't believed how close I was to the band. There were so many youngsters at the concert, but because I was the youngest in a helping team so I guess that I was the luckiest at that moment.</P>
      <P>A concert did very well and I enjoyed it so much. Later on the band took a break for ten or fifteen minutes, so I served them with glasses of fizzy drink and chocolate bars, biscuits and sandwiches. You will not believe how close I was to the singers.</P>
      <P>After a break, the bank have to carried on the concert for another one hour and a half. People at the backstage including me were helping to clean up all the stuff and ready for the end of the concert.</P>
      <P>The time has come, when the band finished the concert, we have to served them drinks again and helped to clear up the stage. Afterwards, I have a chance to took photos with them and have their autographs etc.</P>
      <P>It was the enjoyable time in my life and wished that you were there with me. From this letter, I am sure that you should be able to share this experience with me.</P>
      <P>Lots of Love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
