<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR203*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>I am writing to thank for the letter with the result of the competition and also to ask some questions.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I would like to inform that I prefer travelling in July to travelling in another month. The reason for it, is that, July is the only month in which, I am on holidays so I will not have to miss any classes. Next, I would prefer stay in tents rather than stay in log cabins because I appreciate having straight contact with nature. Therefore, I have chosen climbing and swimming as the two activities on which I am good at. I can say I am good at swimming, because in the club I used to be the first in all the competitions and climbing I used to climb trees, walls everything in my childhood without falling.</P>
      <P>Since I am going to travel I would like to know how much money would be adviseable to take and what kind of clothe I should take.</P>
      <P>I look forward an answer from you.</P>
      <P>Yours Faithfully</P>
      <P>Adriana</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>I am just writing to tell you about my experience about helping at a pop concert.</P>
      <P>Wonderful, Breathtaking, Fabulous, these are some adjectives to describe just a little bit how my experience was. Starting with good points, I could say that you can talk face to face with the pop stars. Moreover, you have the unique opportunity to take pictures with them, to have their names written, on your notebook by themselves. Despite of being tiring, it was rewarding because I noticed that all the singers are ordinary people who want to see their fans happy and satisfied and that is true I experienced that. Another thing is that they pay you for you job and it is a good money. Don't worry because you don't pay your ticket it is "free". From my point of view, there were not disadvantages.</P>
      <P>Kim, summing up it was the most interesting experience that I have ever had. I'm looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Lots of Love</P>
      <P>XXXXX</P>
      <P>Adriana</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
