<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR234*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about a musical show that I saw in your theatre.</P>
      <P>First of all, Danny Brook was supposed to act there, but he was replaced by another actor. This situation made me feel very disappointed.</P>
      <P>Secondly, the show should have started at 19:30 p.m., and it began fourty-five minutes later.</P>
      <P>Moreover, when I went to buy the tickets no discounts were avaliable.</P>
      <P>Furthermore, I wanted to have a coffe after the show, but when I tried to get to the theatre restaurant, it was closed. A police officer who was there told me that the manager of the restaurant was ill and that he didn't allowed anyone to open it.</P>
      <P>This was the worst night that I had during my stay in London.</P>
      <P>For all that reasons, I want you to refund the cost of the tickets and to send the money back to my house.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. Her school's class-matters were going to give their friend Maria a party and it was going to be a surprise to her. They organized everything. The event was going to take place in the garden of Paula's house. Some of them were in charge of bringing music. The others had to bring food. That day afternoon they arrived at Paula's house in order to decorate the place. Ballons and coloured lights were put in all the trees. A table was laid with a lot of delightful food and a beautiful cake was in the centre of it. Some time later all the things were finally prepared. The garden was wonderful. The children were very enthusiastic because they thought that Maria was going to be very happy with this surprise. But things didn't happen as they had been planned. Because when Maria reached the house, they realised that she had been told about the party and they supposed that Pat had done this.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
