<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR782*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan</P>
      <P>I am very happy to know that I have won the first prize in your competition. Now I can realize one of my dream.</P>
      <P>I can give you all the information that you need. I prefer to travel in July because it is the only month I can have two weeks holiday.</P>
      <P>For the accommodation I prefer to have a log cabin because I have some problems with my back and I need a bed to sleep in. I can do two activities during my stay at the camp. The first one I choose is swimming. I have a good level in swimming and I have done some competitions last year which I have won. For the second activity I choose photography. I have take a photography course the last two years so I am able to do some beautiful pictures.</P>
      <P>One question, I just want to know what kind of clothes do I take with me? And how many money do I need?</P>
      <P>I thank you in advance.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>You want to hear about my experience in helping at a pop concert. You can't imagine how funny it was! You could do so many things because you received a free-pass which allowed you to go where you wanted and it was what I had prefer about this experience.</P>
      <P>I really enjoyed to serve the drinks to the pop-stars. You could speak to them and you could see that a lot were very cool and the other ones were still in the sky. And you heard the concerts too.</P>
      <P>After the concert I had to clean the area and it took a long time because people were like pigs. But I was chatting and laughing with other workers.</P>
      <P>One more word! If you can have the chance to do it too, do it! It was a very positive experience. I didn't regret it and I want to do it again!</P>
      <P>Write me soon.</P>
      <P>Love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
