<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR27*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>13th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Ms Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>Competition Organiser</P>
      <P>I have just recieved the letter, which lets me know that I have won the first prize. I am proud of winning it and would like to say how thankful I am. I am therefore writing to give you my further information.</P>
      <P>First of all, I am a student and would like to travel in July. Because I intend to take examination in Septenber. So I can afford to go on holiday only in July. Secondly, I would prefer to stay at log cabins rather than tents. It will be my first time to experience to stay there and I am interested in trying new things which I have not tried.</P>
      <P>The next consideration is the activities. Actually, I used to play basketball for 6 years and am quite confident of it. And nowadays, I have been practicing tennis as school activity. Therefore I would like to choose basketball and tennis.</P>
      <P>Finally, I am considering about what kind of clothes I should wear and how much I need. I would be most grateful if you could give me further advicable information.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>Hello! I hope everything around you is alright. You might not believe but actually I helped at a pop concert last month and I really enjoyed it so much. So I'm now writing to let you know how grateful it was. All work I needed to do wasn't very interesting. which I must have set thousands chairs correctly and after finishing I put them back nicely. The reason I enjoyed it very much is that I could meet the vocalist on setting chairs just before they started practicing. I was asked if I wanted to sit down in front of stage. Naturally I agreed and I could enjoy their gig as audience. It was absolutely fantastic. I had ever never sit down there. Additionally, you couldn't believe, but the vocalist said "All the chairs you are sitting down were set from him," pointing at me!! Actually I was a bit ashamed but it will be my brilliant memory.</P>
      <P>Anyway it was so interesting time that I didn't even feel tired after that. Finally, I suggest you should try as I did if you have any opportunity. You must like it.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to seeing you soon. Can you send me the letter back writing what happend to you recently.</P>
      <P>Bye!</P>
      <P>Love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
