<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR242*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/ Madame,</P>
      <P>Today a recived your letter, it is the most wonderful news I here in a long time. I am so please that I won this prize, that I can not explain how greateful I am. I wasen't expecting this prize because was to good to be true. My family decide to visit my grandmother in Orlando, because she got some problems with the swiming-pool, she.</P>
      <P>Because this situation I be very busy on the first week of july, and I apreciate if you can give me the choice to start my "Camp California" from July 10th. About the Accomodation I would prefer to sleep on the tents, because I never been in one, and it is a lot more fun than log cabins.</P>
      <P>Because I seen my father playing golf since I was a child I am very kind on this sport, and also I love photography because I got a great Camara.</P>
      <P>I am really looking forward to see you soon.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>When I was a child I never like to go shopping because my Mum spend so much time on the shops that I remember going shopping with her, was a nigthmare. It is ameaising how people change during the years, for example now shopping for me is one of the most entertaining things, and every week I have to buy something. I enjoy so much fashion that my life change completely since I start to study clothes designer and I discover that fabrics, colors, are really enjoyable. But in this days shopping is not always enjoyable, because if you decide to buy a very expensive designer and you pay full price, on the end of the season it is half price, I find very anfair for people who pay a lot of money on their clothes. Anyway, shopping is allways a satisfation for rich people, because they can afforded and they don't main to spend full price on their clothes.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
