<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR251*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms Ryan</P>
      <P>I am very astonished that I won this competition! It is great and I will say thank you for the two weeks at Camp California already. I have never been in California yet.</P>
      <P>Now I will give you the further information: I have to travel in July because I had to make sure that I can have holiday this year and it is the only possebility! I am sure you can take attention on this.</P>
      <P>I decided to have the accommodation at Camp California in a tent, because there you will have lots of fun. You can feel the fresh air and listen to animals, this will be a great oportunety!</P>
      <P>I am pleased to choose two activities, because now I will be able to learn SINGING and SURFING! I am not well in both activities, but it will be a pleasure to try it espacially surfing, I would like to feel the air in my hair, and enjoy how quick the board goes over the sea.</P>
      <P>Another question I have; the live there, is it as expensive as I think? And the weather are they only sunshiny days?</P>
      <P>In the other hand it is not as important, the main reason is I really look forward to go at this Camp and one more time, thanks a lot!</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>L. Schwartz</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable</P>
      <P>We have recently had a discussion in our class about this statement, we have had a great argueing. Certainly it is great to buy new clothes and have a great variety at home, to wear, but mostly you will have allways not enough.</P>
      <P>When I decided to go for a shopping, first I will make sure that I have enough time. I am not a typical women because I hate shopping! I am lucky if I will find something which fits.</P>
      <P>The main reason I hate, there are too many people who are always standing in my way (or maybe I think in that way) and I begin to be angry, normally I am looking those people with evil eyes!</P>
      <P>I mean, it is too crowdy, you have to wait such a long time before you can pay, and mostly all the things are too expensive! Even before you will find a color you like or the right size of the trousers, you were looking for it a long time, has gone!</P>
      <P>Lastly, you can see, my opinion about shopping is not very good, then I think shopping is never enjoyable!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
