<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR254*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/MADAME,</P>
      <P>I am writting you because yesterday I went to the musical show "Over the Rainbow" and I had a bad evening.</P>
      <P>First of all, in the advertisement says that the starring were different actors, and there weren't different one, so that can not.</P>
      <P>Also in the advertisement says, that the show will begin at 19.30 and it started at 20.15; that mean that I have to cancelled a date that I had at 21:00, because I coudn't make it. If you present a show you must be on time.</P>
      <P>Another thing that happened was that the tickets did not have discount and the advertisement says the will have. So, how is possible that you present an advertisement and you don't make what it say?</P>
      <P>Finally, it supose to have the restaurant open, and it wasn't, because they didn't have electricity to cook, so they close it.</P>
      <P>I am really made and I want my money back, please call me to the number 23456789, I will be waiting your call. Thank for your time</P>
      <P>your sincerelly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed your daily life?</P>
      <P>Modern technology have change my daily life in many aspects.</P>
      <P>First of all at work; computer are really amazing, you only need to turn it on and start to write; your work is more clean and you work faster.</P>
      <P>Also change my free time, they had invented great games like play station, and you can have a really good time with your friend playing. In the early day, on a raining day you couldn't play because most of game were outside the house but now with the technology you can make many things in your house.</P>
      <P>Another aspect is, on the house artefacts, microwaves, laundrymachine, make life easily.</P>
      <P>In my opinion technology have made human life easily, funier and more comfortable.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
