<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR258*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan. I'm so glad to hear I have won first prize in your competition - two weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A. Thank you for asking me some details. I'd like to travel in July. Because I am a university student, I have got classes until the midle of June and I have to attend to a 'Development and Research Conference' at the end of June. Otherwise I have to work at a business department office as a assistant from the beginning of Aguest. So I will be able to travel in July. Accommodation is very important for me as well. I would prefer staying in log cabins. I've got some skin trouble and I can't sleep very well in tents. I have ever slept in tents when I went camping. That time I had to sleep in tent. Whole night, I felt backache ands shoulder ache so I couldn't sleep very well. And I've never stayed in log cabins. It sounds wonderful! Could I have the chance to do two activities while I am at the Camp? I'd very much like to do painting and swimming. I am quite good at painting. Especially I love water-painting. I really want to paint the countryside of California. It will be fantastic experience for me. Actually I can't swimming at all. I'm afraid of water. That why I couldn't have swimmed yet. I think this chance is very good for me to learn to swim. I expect to join above two activities. I want to know how much money I need. You pay for all costs. But I think I'll need some money for clubing or evening events. And please let me know How the weather is. I'll buy some clothes, shoes and a hat. So I must know if it is cold or hot. I'm looking forward to hearing from you as soon as possible Your sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>Whenever I walk in the street, I always want to go into the every shops. I always want to buy T-shirts, Jeans, Skirts, cosmetic, hairband, accessories, ring, earings, bracelet, shoes, hats, bags, fancy stationeries, interior stuffs and CD. But it is impossible to buy everything at the same time. I have to chose some of them and I have to give up buying most of them. Before I go out home, I make a plan. What is I want to buy and I decide to buy some items.</P>
      <P>But when I stand at every shops, I can't stand my desire. If I have got enough money to buy something what I want to buy, I can buy them and it will be no problem. However, If I haven't got enough money, I will not be able to buy what I want and it will be very big problem. I feel depressed. Shopping is not enjoyable any more. I'll think why I'm so poor. But I can get over. I go window shopping. Insead of buying something, I buy some fresh food and Ice-cream. They make me happy and rich. I can try every shoes, clothes, hats, accessories and jakect on. They are mine!</P>
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>But if you think positive opinion about shopping, It will make you the happiest and the riches man in the world.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
