<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR261*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir and Madam</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter. I'm writing this letter to tell you some further information that you need.</P>
      <P>First of all, I'd like to travel in July because I have to work except that month. July is the only month that I can be free.</P>
      <P>I prefer staying in tents because it is unusual experience for me. Also I'd like to have the chance to play tennis and sailing at the camp. Talking about tennis, I used to play it for about five years when I was a child. I think I'm much better than a beginner. But I never had a chance to enjoy sailing. I'd like to try this time.</P>
      <P>Now, I have two questions about camping. First, what clothes should I bring? Is it hot enough? I've never been to California, therefore please let me know about the weather there. Second, how much money to I need? I haven't a clue about it. I'd like to know some examples.</P>
      <P>I'm waiting for your reply.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim</P>
      <P>It was so nice to hear from you last time. Thank you very much.</P>
      <P>As I mentioned before, I really enjoyed helping at a pop concert last month, the artist's name was "Bonny Pink" who is famous in my country. I could enjoy her music very much.</P>
      <P>My job was looking after her when she had a break time. I guided her to a rest room and served her a cup of tea, and so on. I thought it was most exciting job. Actually, I could have a chance to ask her about music, her favorite artist and her hobby. I was impressed when I heard that she liked playing puzzle alone. She seemed to be very active woman when she was singing but at the same time she had very gentle attitude when she spoke to me. I became a fan of her.</P>
      <P>It was very interesting experience for me. I wish you were there. But don't worry Kim, I'll send you a copy of her CD for you. I hope you can enjoy.</P>
      <P>Anyway it's the time to go to bed. Take care of yourself, Kim. I'm waiting for your letter.</P>
      <P>Love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
