<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR279*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Miss Ryan.</P>
      <P>I am writing to inform the further information about myself. I was very glad to hear that I won the competition.</P>
      <P>First of all, I can only travel in July. I have a summer holiday from at the end of June to at the begging of September as I am a student, but I am planing to work in August as a part-time job. So that's the reason why I can not travel in August. I prefer to stay in tents rather than log cabins, because I have had a camping once and I stayed in tents. It was great to have a fun and also it was very good memorise. As you said I will have the opportunity to do two activities. I am quite good at singing and I have a talent about singing that I can entertain people by singing. In addition I am keen on swimming but actually I am not very good at swimming because I have just started to learn swimming but I have really been enjoying it and I think it will be good chance to improve my swimming.</P>
      <P>In fact, I have some questions that how much money I will need, what else I have to bring with and if I have a emergency what you can do for.</P>
      <P>Once again, I am very happy to have such a good opportunity and I hope this letter can bring what you want to know about me. Thank you for your attention.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Lee. Han</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>These days, there are so many people like shopping that it is one of the important part in our life. It is not, however, always enjoyable that there are both advantages and disadvantages.</P>
      <P>First of all, there are quite many advantages of shopping are that it can be the solvation of our stress and boring. When you are under stress or when you are bored, if you go to shopping, then at least it can be motive to change your mode. Also shopping makes people happier by using a lot of money and it influnce even economic situation more flexably</P>
      <P>There are, in contrast, disadvantages at the same time. When we are having a shopping, we often find that the place where people often go for a shopping is too crowed and it makes us more tired. Also there are plenty of dangerous that lots of people have wallet stollen because it is a public place and there are too many people. In addition shop owner often cheat their customers by increasing the cost secreatly. The customer can never know what price is the normal unless they have a same shop or same thing.</P>
      <P>To sum up, shopping is very important part of our life and we can have a lot of fun, however it is not always enjoyable which means we can not find only advantages from it.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
