<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR327*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Miss Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you because I am very glad for my first place in the competition, I am going to tell you the things that you ask me on your letter.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel on July because is the perfect time to go to the camp and is summer.</P>
      <P>Accommodation at camp I would like to choose cabins because I think I would be protected from the animals and the cold.</P>
      <P>Furthermore for the activities I want to select Tennis and Basketball because I haves been playing tennis since I was young and basketball because I played for the team in my college like the capitan.</P>
      <P>I want to ask you one more thing I do not have any idea about how much money and clothes I have to bring would you give me an advice to know how much I need to bring</P>
      <P>I look forward to heard from you</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I'm writing to you to tell you about my experience when I was helping at a pop concert, well first let me tell you that my job was helping the artist if they need something, for example give them water or snacks.</P>
      <P>It wasn't very exciting job but you can knew a lot of pop Artists that was the good thing because they gave their t-shirts also I could chat with them for a few minutes. another good thing was that all the people wants to be in your place and they were very jealous about me.</P>
      <P>any way, this was my own experience working at the concert, if you have any oportunity to help at any concert you should help because you have a lot of fun as well ok.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Best wishes</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
