<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR343*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Thomas West</P>
      <P>24 Kingsberry place</P>
      <P>CS4 1XD</P>
      <P>Tuesday 13th june</P>
      <P>to Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>Competition Organiser at Camp California</P>
      <P>Dear Madame,</P>
      <P>thank you for your letter, I've been so happy to receave such a good news that I can't already believe it.</P>
      <P>To answer your first question, I would like to travel on july if it's possible, because I'll be on holiday and because a friend would be able to come with me at this time of the year.</P>
      <P>In the accomodation at Camp California, I prefer to rent a tent, he is going to be more funny, I think, but are the tents singles? I would be pleased if you could give me details about this question.</P>
      <P>I can see in the list a lot of interesting sports! But I think (it's difficult to choose) I'll choose golf and basketball, golf because I'm quiet good. I finished 5th at the England Golf tour junior in 1999, and basketball, because I would like to discover this sport I only used to play at school.</P>
      <P>I've got other questions: wich type of clothes do I have to bring? Can I change money on the campus? Are some party organized during the holidays? Is there only one teatcher for each sport, and how many are we in each group of activities?</P>
      <P>Thank you for all informations you could give me.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hear from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Report about which lessons and activities we should film.</P>
      <P>First, I think we can't shoot a film only about lessons or only about breaks, because this two elements are representative of a daily life at school aren't they?</P>
      <P>First, we should film some lessons because everybody know (or remember for the growns up) that it is the activity that to be the most of a student time at school.</P>
      <P>Just after, to make a contrast, we may film the break, because it's the other part of a daily school! It's the place where you can meet your friends, where you can talk free, there are no teatchers, it could be a good contrast to the serious of the lessons. To come back to a strict subject, I suggest that we film the sport lesson, doing that will allowed the spectator to see how does the students behave when they are all together and in small groups.</P>
      <P>Finally we should film the lunch, which is also a moment to relax for the students, and for the teatchers, we mustn't forget to film the teatcher room because if a school is made of students, it's also made of teatchers.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
