<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR373*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>To whome it may concern,</P>
      <P>I am writing to tell that I had a very disappointing evening regarding a musical show at your theatre. There are some things that I was not completely satisfied with and I would like to point them out.</P>
      <P>Firstly, the advertisement told that Danny Brook was going to starr in a musical but it turned out a completely different person which was very disappointing. It was very unprofessional of you to had printed a wrong starring name on the paper. Secondly, according to the advertisment, the musical was supprsed to start at 19.30 but it actually started at 20.15 which caused me a trouble. As for my ticket, I was expecting to get a discount as a student, as it said so in the advertisement, however, it was not actually available which was very disappointing again. Then, I was hoping to have a meal at the theatre restaurant which was recommended in the advertisement, however, it was not possible for me to do so as the restaurant was closed due to the stuff vacation which I thought was very unprofessional.</P>
      <P>With all the dissatisfuction above, therefore, I would like to ask for some of my money back as my evening was not what it would have to be.</P>
      <P>I hope that you will consider this letter seriously and try to improve your service.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. How did we know that she was that kind of person? Well, it all begun when Pat's friend, Molly, went down to London...</P>
      <P>Molly went down to London for shopping and as she was walking the street. She found familier faces on the other side of the street. It was Vance and Sally whom she had not seen for ages. Pat, too, are friend of them and has seen them time to time.</P>
      <P>Molly, Vance and Sally had a quick chat and said good-bye to each other as, to Molly, they seemed to be in a hurry and as Molly knew that they have been dating, she wanted them to enjoy their own time.</P>
      <P>After Molly went back home in Aberdeen, she told Pat that she had met Vance and Sally in London. Then suddenly, Pat's face turned to look confused and said in a small voice, 'Haven't they broken up long time ago? Sally must have a new boy friend'. As Molly didn't know this, she was so surprised and tried to ask more about it. Then, Pat realized that it was supposed to be kept as a secret but it just came out of her mouth! She didn't mean to do so, but this kind of thing happens a lot. Now Pat is feeling so guilty about what she has done because Molly isn't good at keeping secrets either! Everyone is going to know that Sally has been cheating both on Vance and her new boyfriend and the Poor Vance is always the last person to know it. </P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
