<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR9*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>17th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I would like to complain about a musical show. I was very disappointing a week holiday for me because I had got a lot of problem with the show.</P>
      <P>I had seen the advertisement that the actors were Danny Brook and Tina Truelove, but it was not Danny Brook. I was really disappointing because he is my famous actor.</P>
      <P>The musical should started at 19.30, but it started at 20.15. When I went to asked for the discount of ticket in the cashier desk they told me no discount available for this. I had seen the advertisement say that discount available.</P>
      <P>After the show I decide to had dinner in your theatre restaurant, but I couldn't because it closed. It closed at 10 pm but the show finished at 10.30 pm.</P>
      <P>This was not perfect evening for me, so if you don't give my money back, I will tell to the newspaper about it.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hear a good new.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Boo Sersuwan.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>I think in the next 100 years people will wear the space clothes with small engine in the back. because of the atmosphere. The atmosphere in the earth now starting badly every years.</P>
      <P>The carbon dioxide are growing very fast and people cut more trees, therefore not enough trees to such carbon dioxide and produce oxygen.</P>
      <P>The designer will have a lot of idea for how to make very nice and useful clothes. I think if we wear thistoevery wherespace ships. This mean.</P>
      <P>I think somebody will make a very big area to grow plant because they can sell the oxygen. This is a new business.</P>
      <P>I think I can win this price, because this clothe will produce in the future soon.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
