<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR417*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I went to your show called "Over The Rainbow" and I was really disappointing in many points.</P>
      <P>Firstly, you spoke about two actors Danny Brook and Tina Truelove, instead of them we had two others and they were really bad. So I was really surprised. In addition to this you started the show 45 minutes late. It was boring for everybody. How could we appreciate the show properly.</P>
      <P>Moreover, in your advert you spoke about discounts available but it was not the case. No discounts were available. Then you offered people to visit your theatre restaurant after the show but it was closed because there is no staff to welcome the people. You offered something impossible to do. I did not have a good time for all of this reasons and I would like you to give my money back.</P>
      <P>I hope your understand my request and you are going to reply as soon as possible. Thank you.</P>
      <P>yours sincerely</P>
      <P>O. Labro</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. The nightmare started at this time. I though she was a really good friend but I made a mistake. She couldn't keep my secret and everybody knew which boy I was in love with. She didn't tell me yet but when I came in class everybody was looking at me and this boy as well. I looked at her and she became pale and suddently left the class. I followed her and caught her to push her on the ground. I was ready to fight but somebody stopped me. I couldn't go back to the class so I went home. My Mum was at home and I told her all the story. She said that I had to be strong and didn't care about them. So I went to the class and everybody was laughing at me and the boy told them to stopped because he loved me and wanted to be with me. At this time all the girls became jealous and stopped to laugh.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
