<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR541*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>41-50</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear manager</P>
      <P>I went to the theatre to see a musical show "Over the rainbow" and had a very disappointing evening.</P>
      <P>According to your advertisement, the actor should be Danny Brook, but infact it was different person. My ticket was for 19.30, but it started very late, it started 20:15. When the show finished, it was too late to catch the train to home. I had to take taxi. It costed me £30. "What a waste!" By the way, I didn't see any discounts for buying tickets. One more thing, the theatre restaurant was closed when I get there for a glass of drink, I don't know why, there was no written notes or information about that. I am not sure that I did have a perfect evening out.</P>
      <P>Would you consider to give my money back? If the refund is available, it would be grateful.</P>
      <P>I would look forward to hearing from you as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. Pat is one of my colleges in the office. She works with me. We get on very well. She is a single mum. She always talks about her private life to me, and I thought we understood each other, because when I talked about my private life to her, she seemed very understandable.</P>
      <P>Last week, I missed work on Tuesday, so Pat had to work harder because she was all alone. I appreciated her and she wouldn't mind. I told her the reason that I had to miss the work. My son was in prison. I had to go and see him. I still don't know how it really happens to him. All I know is about drug smuggling, that he involved. I asked to her not to tell anyone, because I didn't want others know about this. I am very private person.</P>
      <P>Yesterday morning, I went to toilet, I overherd two people talking about my son I felt pity on myself and I burst into tears. I quickly got out of toilet. I don't remember how I finished work that day.</P>
      <P>Nowadays, it is hard to trust people. No one is perfect. Everybody make mistakes. I decided to forgive my friend Pat.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
