<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR47*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Sir manager,</P>
      <P>I am writing in order to complain about what you have written in the advertisement on the newspaper.</P>
      <P>I am disappointed because of the horrible evening I have had, I was on holiday in London and I did not have time enough to spend there, but when you said that show was the best I decided to go. When I bought my ticket I asked for a discount and they said it was not available. At first it was not a problem because if the show was going to be the best it would cost what they said.</P>
      <P>I arrived at the theatre in time and the musical show started later than I expected so I was getting nervous because I dislike very much the impuntuality, but that was not all.</P>
      <P>When the show started the person who was acting it was not Danny Brook and he seemed not to be an actor. Really he was bad. Afterwards I decided to go for a meal in the theatre restaurant but It was closed. So you can imagine how I felt because of the irritating evening out I had.</P>
      <P>I am letting down because of your behaviour. You wanted to cheat me, so I will be very pleasure if you could give my money back.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward your answer.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>I think technology has changed my life and the way of living of almost all people around the world.</P>
      <P>First of all technology is very useful nowadays but really I dislike it because in some ways we are becoming machines too.</P>
      <P>Since the creation of PCs, people - and me too, of course - are making different things.</P>
      <P>For example we can buy food, clothes and whatever we need by internet or by telephone.</P>
      <P>I can know what is happening in differents parts of the world in a few minutes.</P>
      <P>A very good point of this change is that women have more freedom to have a job because before reaching the technology they have to stay at home doing housework but now we have laundries and a lot of machines like microwave oven.</P>
      <P>In my case I dislike computers. I don't know how to use them but I know I have to change because they help us to make our lives easier.</P>
      <P>On the other hand what will happen with us in the future? Our life will be managed by robots and they will replace us in our jobs.</P>
      <P>So, what are we going to do?</P>
      <P>Something that I note about technology is that we are loosing green places and there are a lot of pollution, so we have to be careful.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
