<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR86*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Clark,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you because I would like to give my personal opinion about the 'international arts festival.'</P>
      <P>First of all I have to say that the whole festival was a greatful success and I also think you chose an appropriate title for the leaflet. However, there are some points which can be improved for the next year.</P>
      <P>To begin with, you wrote down in the leaflet that stars and artists from around the world could be seen in the performance in fact their were only six countries involved. My suggestion for this point is to invite more people from different countries.</P>
      <P>Furthermore is that some concert halls were definitely to small or in other words to many people attended those concerts. This kind of problem you could avoid when you look for big halls at the begining.</P>
      <P>Another point where you could improve is when you show more plays and films next year.</P>
      <P>Nearly at the end of this letter I have to say that the idea with the weekend ticket was really good because it gave to the people the opportunity to attemp a whole weekend for a cheap price.</P>
      <P>To finish this letter with I would like to give you a good idea for next year. In my opinion it would be nice if you create an exhibition place where the guests can try to play different instruments.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>How can you earn money in your spare time?</P>
      <P>I think everybody will ask himself this question one day or has already asked it. Anyway the people where asked this question probably found out that it isn't so easy to earn money or that it is sometimes to much work.</P>
      <P>A traditional way to earn money, in the spare time, is to bring newspapers or magazines to the families in your town or village. The problems that you have here is the weather. For example when it is rainy, because then everything get wet.</P>
      <P>Another suggestion is that you go to your cinema and ask if they need your help for changing the film rolls, for cleaning the toilets or to do some other small jobs.</P>
      <P>But in the case that you really want to do some interesting work in your spare time you should try to sell something where you're good at, I mean if you're interested in computers you should try to provide your service for other people. Of course in the begining it is hard but you can learn a lot and if you're good at you'll also earn some money.</P>
      <P>Okay don't wait, there where you're good at and begin.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
