<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR584*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Clark,</P>
      <P>The discovery of the ôInternational Arts Festivalö was a pleasure for me because it gave me the opportunity to enjoy onto a really nice environment.</P>
      <P>The proposal of reasonably-piced package including tickets and accomodations, well supported my personal organization: comfortable rooms easy to reach and booked tickets can help you if you decide at last minute.</P>
      <P>As far as the Festival itself is concerned some small improvements could let it works better.</P>
      <P> Different kinds of music is a good idea but some of them need special features. Larger concert halls can allow people to better enjoy the quality of performances.</P>
      <P>Also the introduction of different cultural experiences is a good idea but six countries can't be really considered as world wide representative.</P>
      <P>The aim to satisfy different interests should not let the quality decrease.</P>
      <P>Just a final note: why not more plays and films for the next year?</P>
      <P>Thanks in advance for your attention</P>
      <P>Regards</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Are you young, are you a student?</P>
      <P>Do you want to earn money?</P>
      <P>You are not alone!</P>
      <P>There are ôseveralö opportunities for you:</P>
      <P>- ask for money to your parents (mum is better), is the most traditional way but also the safest one</P>
      <P>- emprove and ask for works in restaurants or pubs, is a good training period for real life too (be patient with demanding people is always required)</P>
      <P>- test your health and ask for an outdoor activity (seting as sandwich-man can also hep to test your pride)</P>
      <P>- check your pal wallet and if you have enough money (a very small amount) you can arrange a trip to reach countries like Phili, Cuba, Zambania, Morocco where people (poorer than you) will offer small wages for ôsmallö jobs.. you might enjoy your summer holidays and ôfind yourselfö</P>
      <P>Anyway, the best suggestion is always the ôbest ideaö, the famous ôsuch a good ideaö that might change your lifeà. O'm still looking for it.</P>
      <P>Good luck!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
