<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR600*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I recently spent a week in London and during my stay I went to the theatre in order to see "Over the Rainbow", - the musical show -. At first, I thought I would have a wonderful night out since I had read the advertisement of the show, nevertheless it has wrong information.</P>
      <P>First of all, the advertisement of the show said that Danny Brook was going to be on stage. However, he did not appear during the show; that disappointed me a lot.</P>
      <P>Appart from that, the show was delayed forty five minutes, consequently, everybody there lost control and became angry.</P>
      <P>Another thing I would like you to know is that there were no special rates on the price of the ticket, which cost me £20. Besides, the theatre restaurant had closed down before I went out of the show.</P>
      <P>Finally I would like to inform you that I had never spent such an umpleasant evening in my whole life. Therefore, I would be very grateful if you - the manager of the theatre - could send me the money back, at least the money I spent on the ticket.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully</P>
      <P>LUCCA CALZARI</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. He was one of my best friends, but all secrets told to him spreaded throughout the school in a matter of minutes. The worst was that he did it unconciously.</P>
      <P>When we were in the primary school, my teacher wanted to surprise Tom (a school mate) for his 10th birthday by preparing a fancy dress party in the school.</P>
      <P>We had been preparing it for three days, we hired fancy dresses, had a cake made by a cook and decorated the gymnasium. Unfortunately, it was me who had to tell Pat about the surprise.</P>
      <P>Later, I realiced it was the worst thing it could happen to me.</P>
      <P>On the day of the party, half an hour before it started, Pat came across with a gang of boys from another course. Since they were going to beat him, he desperately told them everything he knew about the party.</P>
      <P>Afterwards, all of them were around Tim telling him what Pat had confessed.</P>
      <P>Both Pat and Tim were very disappointed that day.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
