<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR646*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Misses RYAN</P>
      <P>I am writing to inquire whether there is possible to have more details about travel and to give my preferences about travel. Indeed I would rather to travel only on July since I'm going to work in august in order to earn money to pay my studies next year.</P>
      <P>Moreover I would prefer being accommodate in log cabins because I can't put up with mosquitos and other insects which risk coming into tents.</P>
      <P>Besides I've chosen two activities from the list: Tennis as I practice this sport regularly and I'm very good in this activity and Golf because I ignore all about this sport and I wish I will discover it thanks to you.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, I would obtain some details about the kind of clothes that I should carry with me and how much money to take</P>
      <P>You don't hesitate to contact me in order to have further information.</P>
      <P>I hope quickly hearing from you</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Dear readers</P>
      <P>As you have already know, your English class is going to make a short video about daily life at your school, that's why I'm writing a report suggesting which, lessons and other activities, should be filmed.</P>
      <P>First of all, he seems obvious that we should, at least once, film a lesson with our English teacher who have had the idea to make this short video.</P>
      <P>Besides I would suggest filming a lunch to the restaurant at twelve o'clock in order that people are aware of the high level of noises inside the restaurant because of babbles.</P>
      <P>At the end, to my opinion, It would be interesting to film a course of sport in order that our parents realise that we improve our body's abilities, and not only our brain's abilities at school.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
