<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR664*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs H. Ryan</P>
      <P>I am writing with reference to your letter and I would like to give some information which I have been asked.</P>
      <P>Because my course finishes at the end of June and I am going to work for a Hotel in August and September, I would like to travel in July. It is the best time for me.</P>
      <P>As far as accommodation is concern, I would like to say that I prefer to stay in tents. I like staying in tents because when we go on holiday with my friends, we always stay in tents, so I am used to staying in tents.</P>
      <P>Moreover, I have also been asked to choose some activities. I would like to choose basketball and swimming. When I was at school, I have been playing for the school team and I am good at swimming.</P>
      <P>Finally, could you let me know what sort of clothes would be better to bring. It would also be useful to know that how much money will be enough to bring.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>To: Mr. J. Y</P>
      <P> Head Teacher</P>
      <P>From:</P>
      <P>Re: Short Video About Daily Life at I.S.O. School.</P>
      <P>FINDINGS</P>
      <P>I have discussed with my friends and school teachers about this subject. Here are some information about daily life at I.S.O.</P>
      <P>Morning Lessons: Although there are a lot of classes, there is special FCE class in which students are being prepared for FCE exam. There are special methods and materials for students.</P>
      <P>Afternoon Lessons: The aim of the afternoon lessons is to be able to give ability in speaking. There are some discussion groups, so students may have discussion on any subject.</P>
      <P>Break Time: We have a lot of facilities for break time. These are computer, video, and sports.</P>
      <P>RECOMMONDATIONS</P>
      <P>In my opinion we should choose break time activities. Because there are a lot of activities which students take part in. It would be much better for video film.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
