<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR694*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>Yesterday, I received your letter. It made me happy and I would like to than you for the opportunity you offer me</P>
      <P>First of all I would like to travel in July. I think that this is the most ideal month for a trip to California. This period the days are sunny and the weather won't prevent me from doing a lot of activities. About the accomodation I would prefer to stay in a cabin. I think that the combins are safer than the tents and they can protect you better in case the weather changes. The two activities I have chosen is swimming and climbing. I selected swimming because this is one of my hobbies and I'm good enough t this sector. In addition I would like to swim in a sea like California's because it is clean and beautiful. I chose climbing because I'm intrested in this sport even if I'm not experienced. I like it because it offers you a lot of adventure and action.</P>
      <P>As a conclusion I would like to ask you about the money and the cloths I must take with. Please drop me a line</P>
      <P>Yours sincierly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim</P>
      <P>Yesterday I received your letter and it made me happy that you and your family are healthy.</P>
      <P>As you asked me I will write you about the experience I had helping at the pop concert. All the children helped as much as they could and that's why the result was beautiful enough. Before the concert I helped in carring and putting in order some chairs on which would sit some special persons. It was very hard and at the end I was very tired. At the concert, what I had to do was to give out refreshments and drinkings to the audience. I also helped to clear up the place after the concert.</P>
      <P>It was really a very beautiful experience. It offered me more pocket money and besides this I had the chance to make a lot of friends because there were many children who wanted to help too. In addition I had the opportunity to talk to the singers and have a lot of autogrammes by them. I will never forget these days and for sure I will take part in activities like this in the future.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully Alexander.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
