<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR93*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson!</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for good programme! We like it very much! But we would like to go to the London Fashion and Leisure Show. It is on Tuesday. We think, that you also would like to go there, when you'll know about it better. There will be showed the latest fashions. Also, we will see leisure and sports wear.</P>
      <P>We know, that you wanted to have another and didn't know which one. If we go to the show, we will see many hairstyles. Maybe it'll help you choose. Also, you'll be glad to know, that for students it is free! So, we think, that it is very good as for you as for us.</P>
      <P>So, we can change your programme a little bit to the best one. On Monday afternoon we have the river trip to Greenwich, as you have written on your programme. On Tuesday morning we go to the show and after that shopping. And on Wednesday morning we go to the national art gallery, but after that we can go to the Science Museum, in the afternoon.</P>
      <P>Our class asks you to think about this programme. We're sure, that you like it very much!</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>It was dangerous, but I knew I had to do it. My best friend told me, she met one boy. She liked him very much. She was speaking about him every time. She told me, that he was hansom, kind, well-understanding (he understood her from a half of the word); the main was he also liked her very much!</P>
      <P>I belived everything she has told me. And said just to be careful. But in three days she hasn't been at home. She disappeared! We called the police. They advised us to wait. But we couldn't just sit and wait! We had to do something. In three days of her disappearing the phone has rung. I took the phone. Someone told me if I wanted to see my friend, I must take 5000$and bring them up to the street. I took any papers, put them to one bag and without saying anything went to my friend to take something like gun. The friend gave me his toy and I gone to the street. There I saw a man and my friend. I showed the man, that I had a gun and money. I surprised that he belived me. Of course, it was better for us. I gave him the bag took the friends hand and we run away. After that she told me, that the man was the boy, which she met.</P>
      <P>Don't believe everyone! Better check, if you are not sure!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
