<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR713*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan</P>
      <P>It was a grate pleasure to hearing from you, that I have won first prize in your competition.</P>
      <P>I am very glad that all accommodation and travel costs are paid, but even though I would like to know how much money do I have to take with me. I would be glad to travel only in July because of family reasons. Other point is accommodation. I would be more than happy if you could have provided me with tent. The reasons as following; better relationship with nature, and grate opportunity to improve my health.</P>
      <P>Also I would like to tell you which activities I would like to chose and why. I like swimming and photography because it will be very interesting to improve my skills at both activities.</P>
      <P>The last thing I would like to know is which clothes do I have to take, even though the weathe in July will be good.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>Almost all of us like shopping! Going in and out of the shops, buying clothes, food and presents, but a few of us who is very happy to spend money.</P>
      <P>Money is a very important thing in shopping, if you have money, is not a problem, but if you don't? So, let's imagen that your credit card is not working, or some one stold your cash from your pocket. We will say unlucky, but no one will help you in that situation. Also it is very difficult to shop if you are handicapt.</P>
      <P>Staying in a que or croude is also unplesent. All people are shouting, stepping on your feet and it is very likely that you won't get the product you need.</P>
      <P>After words you are tiered and have no power to do things.</P>
      <P>After all things that I have mentioned it is clearly seen that shopping is not enjoyable.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
