<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR730*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>I'm writing to you to thank you for the programme you have organised. All students are very pleased and we are looking forward to go to London. We know we are going for three days, but we'll have enough time to use one of the bigger city in the world.</P>
      <P>London is the place to be when always something happening.</P>
      <P>We all very happy with your programme, especially we like the idea of sightseeing by our and National Art Gallery.</P>
      <P>The students in my class have seen an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show, we would like to ask you if is possible to make some changes in the programme?</P>
      <P>The show is on Tuesday the 14th between 10.00- 13.00. We think is the great opportunity to see latest fashion, find about make up and hairstyles. And all of it is free, According to your programme we have the science Museum which is in the morning and then shopping. Would it be possible to go to the Museum and then for the shopping in our free time which is on Wednesday?</P>
      <P>All students will be very greatful.</P>
      <P>your sincerly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>I think for all of us home is something which is a very important. Home sweet home. We call home the place where we live or the country where we come frome.</P>
      <P>Anyway home is always the place to go because is ours we feel save and comfortable. Home sweet home.</P>
      <P>After hard work we want to go home to have our corner where we are all able to rest and relax.</P>
      <P>I think in the future home might be just the place to go to sleep.</P>
      <P>We live in the very busy world! Working long hours, doing plenty of activieties, going out, going on holidays. We even don't spend time with families. Propably in the future we might be to busy to go to our own home and spend some time there.</P>
      <P>But in the end of the day it alway will be place to go! We find our family there and our life. Some of us have been living in one house since they were born. We are sentimental and we have memory from the past. I think it's a part of our life.lf</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
