<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR738*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P> Ms Clark,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you in order to give you some advice about the annual International Arts Festival.</P>
      <P>Last season I spent two days at the Festival. I enjoyed myself very much, but I think that the organization of the next festival could be better.</P>
      <P>First of all, as I see it the idea of an Arts Festival is great because in this way many people can know artists who cames from different countries. Unfortunately, in the last edition there were artists who cames from only six countries, so I think you should invite artists from other countries, for example from Africa.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I appreciated the fact that there were concerts of different kind of music, but in this case the main problem was that some concerts hall were too small, and because of it I couldn't see one of the concerts in programme.</P>
      <P>In my opinion, one of the best things of the last Festival was that there were not only concerts. I saw films and I played ping-pong. In the next edition will be more or less? I hope more. The thing that I liked much more than others, was that I had to buy only one ticket for all events, and it was no pricey.</P>
      <P>It is clear that for me the last Festival was really great, so I have only one suggestion to give you, I think you should do a baby-parking, in fact a certain number of women couldn't see the Festival because of their sons.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="5a">
      <P>I like read very much, because every book that I read shows me a different world. What I try to explain is that in every book there are characters or situations really different.</P>
      <P>So we can read realistic stories or fantastic, it depends from what we prefer.</P>
      <P>I always prefer read books that are inusual in some way, because they give me the opportunity of escape from the everyday reality. One of my favourite books is without doubts, Wuthering Heights a famous book written by Emily Brontë. The attention of the is focused on the unfortunate love of Heatcliff and Catherine.</P>
      <P>They are the main characters of that book, and what caracterize them is the violence of their passions. In this book you can find only good or bad characters, everything is good or bad. If you look at this book like a painting you can't see afumature of colours, you see only primary colours.</P>
      <P>In other words, when I read a book I want to go in a world where I can find something different from my everyday life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
