<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR792*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson</P>
      <P>Thank you for the good programme which you have organised. There is only one thing we don't agree with you , it is the Tuesday 14 March.</P>
      <P>We have seen an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show. and we would all like to go to this show. It would be very special for us because we haven't seen something like that before. There are four different shows. First there is a show with latest fashions, after they show us the leisure and sports wear and then there are the make up and the hairstyles shows.</P>
      <P>The show is not as expensive as the Science Museum because the entry of the show is free for students.</P>
      <P>You see, the programme has only to be changed on Tuesday morning. In the afternoon we go shopping how you have organised in your programme. In our opinion; it is enough to go one time in a museum and it is on Wednesday.</P>
      <P>Thank you in advance for your trouble</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>your English Class 4A</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>The Home of the Future</P>
      <P>Now, we are in the 21th century. Most of us live in houses or flats and it is most very comfortable. But in which kind of homes will people stay in the future? What will be different and what wont change? We can need our imagination for answering these questions but we will never know the right answer.</P>
      <P>I have further ideas: In the futur, maybe in 2113, there will are houses like now but only with more technical things. The life at home will be more easy because a refrigerator which fill up itself or a bathroom which clean itself. So, people wont have to clean their houses because there are machine for all works.</P>
      <P>But I think that people will altough need a bed and a table with a chair. These things and a lot more went change or wont be forgotten. So, I think. houses only will be more moderne and more practique but not very different from our home in the present.</P>
      <P>This is my idea and we will see!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
