<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR833*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I received your letter this morning and I was very suprised it. It was absolutely fantastic prize.</P>
      <P>I am writting you about your questions. First, I can come there only July because of my examination, I have to take it in June, and my new turm will also start in September. I would like to stay at long cabins because I have stayed at tents many times in my childhood. The most exciting offer is your activities. I have been interested in Painting but I have not had a chance so I would like to do it, and I would like to do climbing. My grand father used to do it when he was a student. After he has got a job, he became busy. However, he retired his job last year so he has had his own time. If I know how to climb, I will enjoy it with my grand father.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask about my clothes and money. How much do I need to bring them?</P>
      <P>I wish I could see you soon.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>How are you? You want to know about my experience at a pop concert, don't you? It was so exciting!</P>
      <P>My main working was take people to their seat because of a concert hall, which was the millenium dorm.</P>
      <P>Do you know it? It's the hottest place in England. Most of people were first time to come there, so they're lost. I had also never been there before. It's a huge building. I also sold a panfulet of that concert, CD and T-shirts.</P>
      <P>The most exciting experience was that I could met a lot of people. I told you before that concert was performed by Elton John, so there were a lot of famouse people. When I saw Jullia Roberts, I was socked. She was abusolutelly beautiful. I have never seen that kind of long legs in my life!</P>
      <P>Did you enjoy my letter? I can't explain you very well. Anyway, it was a wonderful time.</P>
      <P>lots of love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
