<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR761*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Jane Clark,</P>
      <P>I'm writting to you because I've been in the International Arts Festival and it was a pleasure. Let me introduce myself: I'm Mary, I'm nineteen and I'm studying arts. As well, I want you to know my opinion and I'd like to give you my suggestions, because it would be useful to you for the next festival.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I want to congratulate you for the idea, I think that it's very important the development of the arts and that everybody could assist without paying too much. Having a ticket for all the events is a great method because it's an organised way of paying and you win time.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, I must tell you that some concert halls are too small, so you can't be enough confortable to apreciate the event. Other thing, is that the artists come only from six countries, so don't cheat the people by saying that they are from all the world.</P>
      <P>In my opinion, you should call more artist from other countries and have some concert halls bigger or may be change the distribution.</P>
      <P>Well, I think that everything is told but could you tell me, if it's possible, if there will be more plays and films next year?</P>
      <P>I'm waiting for your answer.</P>
      <P> Faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Jane,</P>
      <P>Thanks for your letter, it was nice to hear from you again. I've recently started the classes so all the rules were given to us, like you know, the first day. As you want me to tell you how about the rules are here, I'll start.</P>
      <P>Firstly, in our classroom you can't shout, you must be quite and sat. You must pay attention always because you don't know if the teacher will ask you some question. In exams, you can't talk to the teacher, either you mustn't eat chuingham or take a walkman with you. In my home I can avoid that rules. My mum only doesn't want me to arrive late. However, I can go dancing whenever I want but telling her previously. My mum is a lovely woman and she doesn't know how much I love her because most of the day I'm outside, but that's the true. My father is a bit jealous but agrees with what my mum says.</P>
      <P>So, I'm free when I'm out of the school. I'd like it would be nicer going there.</P>
      <P>Lots of love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
