<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR853*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I address this letter to the manager of the theatre.</P>
      <P>I want to talk to you about an evening I had in your theatre: OVER THE RAINBOW.</P>
      <P>Your advertisement was excellent and it gave me a lot of enthousiasm. But I had a very disappointing evening and it was because many points.</P>
      <P>First point, I didn't see Danny BROOK as starring. I was coming to see him but there was a different actor.</P>
      <P>Second point, the musical show had to begin at 7:30 PM but we have waited for fourty five minutes to see the show started.</P>
      <P>Third point, your advertisement told about "discount available" about the ticket's price but it wasn't.</P>
      <P>Fourth point, after the show, I wanted to visit your theatre restaurant but it was closed and no one didn't know why!</P>
      <P>Well, as you see it wasn't a "perfect evening out!" and I think that you could give to me some money back because I really have the impression that your advertisement is wrong. I'm waiting about your news,</P>
      <P>Yours FAITHFULLY,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>We live in a society where the technology grows up everyday. We can find some everywhere. Then, I think it's interssant to answer the following question:</P>
      <P>How has modern technology changed my daily life?</P>
      <P>My plan will be very simple: a description in a first time and an analysis in a second time.</P>
      <P>Everyday at 7:00 a.m, I am woken up by my radio. After, when I take my breakfast, I use my toaster for my bread and, as I want a hot milk, I use my modern oven too. When I go to school, I can see in many stores the new tools they've just received.</P>
      <P>But I think that the most important is my cellular phone: I can give a call or receive a call from everywhere.</P>
      <P>This little paragraph shows that I depend of technology and, more over, because I'm in an electronic eegenering school, I'm keen on technology.</P>
      <P>I don't know if it is good or bad but we are a generation who's grown up with technologies progress. Modern technology doesn't changed my daily life, it just allows to evoluate in this new world....</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
