<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR859*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I am from Brazil and I recently expent a holiday in London. During my stay I read an advertisement of a musical show being held at The Circle Theatre. As I was reading the advertisement I got very excited, because I am a great fan of Danny Brook, and he was going to be performing in the play. As I got to the theatre I asked for the discounts shown in your advertisement, but they were not avaible. Anyway, I decided to buy my ticket, since I thought the play was going to be good. So I sitted in my chair and waited for 45 minutes until the show started, that is an unacceptable delay.</P>
      <P>Even though I was still excited about the show, but then I sudently realise that Danny Brook is not performing, he had been replaced by an extremely disappointing actor.</P>
      <P>The night had been terrible, but it could be saved by a nice dinner in your restaurant, but it been closed because the heater was not working due to leaking. As you can see it was not the perfect evening out your advertisement talked about. Then, I would be glad if you could have my money back.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed your daily lief.</P>
      <P>Modern technology has brought many discoveries which have made our daily lives much easier. For example, internet has given us the possibility of acessing reliable information very fast.</P>
      <P>I guess science is about solving our daily problems with technological advances. That is exactly what happens to me. When I was younger I remember that when I had to study or to work on a school project I would take a lot of time researching on libraries, looking for old books. Today I can connect to the Internet and find all the information I need faster than you can imagine.</P>
      <P>But technology is not just about studying, it is entertainment too! I can watch pay-per-view films without having to go out to rent one. I can also listen to cds, play the latest games, watching concerts.. everything in a zap. You also have fast food, or food made in the microwave within a few minutes.</P>
      <P>As you can see, technology is about saving our time, so we may have more time to do what we like. In my opinion, technology is making my life much better because of that.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
