<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR869*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Helen,</P>
      <P>It is great to hearing from you. I cannot believe I'm the winner of your competition.</P>
      <P>I'm really very happy.</P>
      <P>As far as some further information you need from me is concerned, I am very glad to give you all the details of the matter.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel on July; that is for me the only possibility because I will finish my course a University at the end of June and I will start to work in September.</P>
      <P>As far as accomodtion is concerned, I would like to live in tents at Camp California. I prefer this type of accomodation because I am used to living in tents during my summer holidays.</P>
      <P>As I am an athletic swimmer and a good surfer too, my choice from your attached list is naturally swimming and surfing.</P>
      <P>I like to travel with light logguage and I have no idea about the weather; could you suggest me what kind of clothes I have to bring with me?</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Hi Kim!</P>
      <P>It's great to hearing from you!</P>
      <P>The last month concert! The singer was fabulous and the musicians played fantastic songs.</P>
      <P>I was employed in the security service. I did it for free because it was a non-profit concert for helping the poor people. It was the first time for me and I consider this experience the best of my life.</P>
      <P>I had to look after people near the stage. The organiser gave me a radio and I had to advise the other staff members in case of disorder. At the same time I could enjoy the music! I think this is what I particularly liked about this experience.</P>
      <P>I suggest you to try this kind of experience. You should be pride of you helping people who suffers, and at the same time you may enjoy yourself!</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to seeing you!</P>
      <P>Love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
