<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR872*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>I am a student of the English class. All my class mates are looking forward to go to London. Thank you so much for organising such a great program.</P>
      <P>I am writing you about changing our plan on Tuesday 14 March. The students in my class have seen an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show and we would all like to go to the show.</P>
      <P>The advertisement saids it is taking place on Tuesday 14 March from 10am to 7pm.</P>
      <P>Since the London Fashion and Leisure Show is not taken place so often and also they will offer the students for free entrance fee this time, if we joined in this show, it would be great opportunity for us.</P>
      <P>For these reasons, we would like to suggest you to go to the show instead of going shopping on Tuesday afternoon.</P>
      <P>I hope I will hear from you soon.</P>
      <P>I am sure that our travel is going to be great.</P>
      <P>Thank you very much</P>
      <P>Sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>It was dangerous, but I knew I had to do it.</P>
      <P> Otherwise I had to keep walking untill the train start.</P>
      <P>Have you stayed at a park during the night?</P>
      <P>When I did that, I was traveling around Japan. It was the very last day of my trip and at that time I was in Kyoto.</P>
      <P>Although I intended to stay at youth hostel, I could not find any place to stay, and also it was too late to buy a train ticket to go back home.</P>
      <P>It was a windy spring day.</P>
      <P>I was sitting under a full-bloomed cherry blossam tree. Inside the dark, I was alone and only the moon light helped me to see the things. I was regretting I risked staying at the park alone.</P>
      <P>Suddenly, strong wind blew up the thousands and thousands pieces of flowers.</P>
      <P>It was like a dream.</P>
      <P>I saw the pink colored snow there.</P>
      <P>Sometimes when we risk a great danger, it turns into a great experience. </P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
