<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR763*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about a musical show, which I have seen in your theatre, in London during my holiday.</P>
      <P>According to the advertisement, which appeared in one of the London's newspapers, I would like to present you some of my complaines about your musical spectacle. Firstly, I would like to say that the cast, which you "offered" has been changed. The man who played the main male role was different than this one, who was mentioned in the advertisement. Secondly, the time when your musical should start has been changed, making your show delayed for nearlly one hour! In your offer I noticed an information about discounts which were supposed to be available - no, they were not! Another "defect" in the advertisement was an "invitation" to the restaurant after the show. For unknown for me reasons, I found the restaurant closed (there was no information telling about a cause of closing it). Finally, you guaranteed "a perfect evening out", but for me it was the worst visit in theatre in two years time.</P>
      <P>To sum up, I am very disappointed about the musical in your theatre. Neither beautiful surranding near your theatre nor comfortable sits will not recompansate my horrible evening. Therefore, I would like you to send my money back, because I think I deserve it as a viewer. I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Technology is very important in our life. Mainly, because it makes it easier and more comfortable. Nevertheless it has some advantages and drawbacks.</P>
      <P>In my opinion my daily life is full of modern technology. I meet her "at every corner": at home, at school, in the backyard and so on. It also changed my life-style for better - I think. Every morning I use a toaster to have my sandwiches done, washing machine which makes my clothes clean again. Recently, modern technology means: mobile phones, computers, internet, super-fast cars etc. These improvements helps me with my ordinary dutes. I can do my homework on computer, prepare for the class test by searching information in Internet and use a mobile phone every time when I want to connect with one of my parents.</P>
      <P>However, technology has a bad influence on us, generally on our healf. Couple of months ago, some foreign scientists noticed that mobile phones make a possibility of getting sick with cancer. Also fast and well-improved car increase a risk of pollution of our air and mainly lead to very dangerous accidents.</P>
      <P>In conclusion I think that modern technology makes our life easier, nevertheless, we should avoid any possible risks connected with these improvements. Then we will be able to say that technology is something we should be proud of.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
