<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR102*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to say thank you to you Mr Robertson for planning to take us to spend three days in London.</P>
      <P>Your programme looks very interesting, especially the River Trip to Greenwich, which I always dreamt of.</P>
      <P>However, we have seen an advertisement on the English magazine for the London Fashion and Leisure Show. It takes place at the Central Exhibition Hall in London on Tuesday March 14 at 10.00-19.00. The show will have latest fashions from top fashion designers in the world. Leisure show will have leisure and sports wear, new make up style and new hair style for next year. The best thing is that it is free because we are students.</P>
      <P>We would like to ask you whether we can change some programme. Our suggestion is that we can go shopping on Wednesday 15 March so on Tuesday afternoon we can go to The London Fashion and Leisure Show. We won't miss any programme that you have planned and we could also have great opportunity to see the show.</P>
      <P>We're looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>"Famous people, such as politicians and film stars, deserve to have a private life without journalists following them all the time".</P>
      <P>In my opinion, everybody wants to have a happy life in our own world, we want to do whatever we want, sometimes we do the right things and sometimes we do the wrong things. We are ordinary people, we work and come home to have activities with our family or go out together.</P>
      <P>The politicians and film stars also want to have a normal life after work. They want to have a private life without journalists following them all the time. Although, their news on the front page of a magazine can catch the eyes of public so that people will never forget them. On the other hand, their story always make them embarras because most of the journalists create their own story base on the true story just to get attraction from people.</P>
      <P>I think, if the journalist want to publish the politicians and film stars private life, they should have asked for permission. They deserve to have a private life as everybody. </P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
