<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR113*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Clark,</P>
      <P>I'm a italian student who has come to the last International Arts Festival.</P>
      <P>I think this festival is a great idea because it's a possibility to see and to love the art, but, I think also there are some things thas could be changed.</P>
      <P>I noticed that the artists were from only six countries insted from around the world. This choice doesn't give many artists the possibility to expresse themself.</P>
      <P>Some concert halls were too small and often people couldn't see the performances.</P>
      <P>There were many events that I think there were a few plays and films. Maybe it would be better put more of them in the programme because they like so much to young people.</P>
      <P>The very about young people, the choice to offer a reasonably-priced weekend ticket is a excellent idea because it brings them to have a contact with all what it art.</P>
      <P>I hope that my opinion can help you to set fro the next year a great internation arts festival alone to young people.</P>
      <P>Thank you and greetings.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>I think a good way to get money it's work in a fast-food.</P>
      <P>Maybe the first impression isn't positive but from my personal experience, I can say that this kind of job is right for get some money. For six months I've worked in a McDonald's restaurant in Italy and I've got lots of money. I worked eight hours every day but in every fast-food you can work part-time, four, three, six hours every day.</P>
      <P>It depends on what you need.</P>
      <P>This kind of job is perfect for the young people who want get money and in the meantime they have to study.</P>
      <P>If you work in a fast-food you can work in the afternoon, or during the night and so you have time for yourself.</P>
      <P>In the staff you can also find young people and getting fun with them during the work.</P>
      <P>What do you want more?</P>
      <P>If you need money and you need time for yourself try a job like that.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
