<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR928*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam:</P>
      <P>Thank you for telling me that I have won the first prize and now I am writing to tell you the information you have requested.</P>
      <P>First of all, I think I would like to travel in July, which will be the only month for me to go. Because my course won't finish until the end of June, and I will have to stay in the college to get ready for the new term.</P>
      <P>Then I'd like to choose the tents for my accommodation when at Camp California. I think sleeping in a tent is funnier than others. However, during my stay at Camp, there are two activities I can choose, one of them I will choose Basketball because it is the sport I play most, I and my friend used to win the first place in school-wide match when we was in school. And the other one, I think painting will be a good idea; Painting is one of my hobbies and I've been learning it since I was 5 years old and now I'm still doing it once I have free time.</P>
      <P>Above are all the information you asked , however, here are something I'd like to know; first is about the clothes, what kind of clothes I need to take with? And another question is what is the prices of things like in there, so that I can make a better buget of my trip.</P>
      <P>Look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim:</P>
      <P>Thanks for your last letter; I knew you would interested at my experience of helping the pop concert last time, now I tell you about it.</P>
      <P>The place we worked was a football pitch; we spent 3 days on setting up the stage, the equitment, and the lights. In fact, there is nothing very important I did, because we are not the right people to do it. I only put the speakers in the right places, or helping engieners tested the lights.</P>
      <P>But at the brakes and after work, I had a chance to talk with the engieners, and I leant something about setting up the equitment.</P>
      <P>The fourth day, the singers and the players have been to there to test. Then I had a chance to speak with them. From that, I learnt more about instruments.</P>
      <P>Finally, the date of concer came. After the concer finished successfully, I was happier than ever because the succeed inclueded my work and that was the most enjoyable moment in my life.</P>
      <P>Anyway, now I have to stop to finish my homework. I'm looking forward to receiving your letter again.</P>
      <P>Best wishes.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
