<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR936*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to giving information about myself.</P>
      <P>Even though I would like to travel, I am only in July, because I am a high school student. Thus I have not got long holiday. I just have one month left. Personally, I would rather stay in log cabins than in tents. On accound to stay in log cabins are as much more interesting than in tents. As far as two activities are concerned I would choose singing and photography. I used to win a number of competitions in singing. I can sing a plenty of songs. which include the english song and the japenese song, and I have part-time job for sining at restaurant. Although the photography is not as good as the singing, I am very interested in it. I have been learning since I was 15 year old. I got third prize in it competition last year and I level is professional now. Futermore, I am going to have competition next year.</P>
      <P>I would like to asking some information about that what kind of clothes I have to wearing and how many your are charge.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable, sometimes have a long quare or a mechine was broken. A lot of circumsenses will have been happening.</P>
      <P>I have unpleased experience. It was in lunch time. Everybody were went to by luch in supermarket, in fact, nobody liked crowe and quare, expecially in the summer time. I was quare in the middle of row. I choose this row because I though it was quicker than other. Although there were finished two people, next was me, something was happened. Suddenly the customer though the receipt was not truth, she did not buy a lot of things but the shop assistant did not make mistake, they argued about this thing. The shop manager was coming solution it. Abviously, I have to chance other row. I was long quare, I have never had.</P>
      <P>Shopping would be enjoyable, if you were good luck. Even though I think it most of time is very interesting, sometimes make people upsent.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
