<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR942*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Sir, Madame</P>
      <P>I passed one week in London and during my visit I had the fortune to visit "Over the rainbow" in your theatre. But I was not very satisfied after my "perfect evening" out. The advertisement for the Musical Show was very good, but the information was not correct. You wrote that the favourite actor will be Danny Brook but there was another one who was really disappointing. In the advertisement was written that the show will start at 19.30 but it started 45 minutes later, at 20.15! Because of the advertisement I thought that I can discount the tickets available but I couldn't. After the show I need to drink something in the theatre restaurant like the advertisement it concieved, but it was closed. And there was no reason why.</P>
      <P>So you can see that it was not a so perfect evening for me then I thought. Now I hope that you can understand my question for some money back because of the trouble I had.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secretes. This was the only reason why that she had not a lot of friends. When Pat came new into a class or a groupe of teenagers there were no problems. But after a few time the others have seen that Pat can't keep secrets. So they stopped nearly immediately to tell her something important. Sometimes it finished like this that the others only said: "Hello, how are you?" and then went away without listening the answer. This made Pat sad and she became very quiet. During the day she worked hard that she had not to think too much. But at night, when it became dark the dreams were coming. She dreamed about good friends, time that was long passed by and she dreamed from someone who she can tell her own secrets.</P>
      <P>Then one day she met this person. It was Katha, a girl who had the same problems like Pat. So they found both the person they dreamed from.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
