<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR948*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P> Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>First of all I would like to thank you the chance to do such a gorgeous trip. We are really looking forward to visiting the city and going to the Museum and Gallery. However, there is one point that we would like to change in the programme.</P>
      <P>We are interested in visiting "The London Fashion and Leisure Show" during our travel. The show is very interesting because we could see the latest fashion, hairstyles and make up, and also leisure and sports wear. Furthermore is totally free for students.</P>
      <P>All this exhibiots are really important and exciting for us because, nowadays, fashion has a huge influence in our lifestyle and we would like to know more about it.</P>
      <P>We think that we could go there next 14th of March, in the eveninng, instead of going shopping. This one could be translate to 15th evening. It is also possible to go to the show in the morning but we are totally agree that we don't want to lose our visit to the Science Museum.</P>
      <P>We truly believe you will consider our change. Please contact us if you have any question.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P> Almost everyone relation famous people with photographers, articles, money, fans,... Normally, one people's dream is to be famous and rich but without that stuff of being without privacy</P>
      <P>Nowadays, there is a lot of people that life only with the money they get in advertisments, reports about their last romance,... but not everyone does the same. On the one hand you find the ones that are well-known and never talk about their privacy. They use the publicity exclusive for their work.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, are the ones that are also respectabled but, appart from their relation with journalists because of their work, they really need to be constantly seek by photographers. I mean, they enjoin being the point of view or the center of everyone, even though it means to see their lifes.</P>
      <P>Communications move the world and famous people use them to improve their work, politicians for their campain and film stars to make famous their last movie. Nevertheless, sometimes communications disturb their lifes in a wrong way.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
