<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR962*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>At first, thank you for your programme. It is very various and interesting. We all enjoy it. But last week we have seen an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show. This presentation will show the latest fashions and the leisure and sports wear. We would be very interesting in seeing the english fashion. At this show we could see different new make up and hairstyles.</P>
      <P>The event is a great opportunity because it is on the 14th of March and it is free for students. For pratical informations, this show start at 10.00 and close at 19.00. It will stay in the Central Exhibition Hall in London. It is not too far and the openning hours fit us.</P>
      <P>About the programme, we suggest to see the show on the Tuesday morning and after to do shopping. As far as we are concerned we prefer seeing the Science Museum rather than the National Art Gallery. We also suggest to visit the Science Museum or Wednesday morning and the afternoon, if some one of us is intersted, we could see the National Art Gallery.</P>
      <P>I hope you won't be too angry for this changing but we would all like to go to the show.</P>
      <P>Waiting for your answer, receive our greetings.</P>
      <P>For the class</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>General speaking, homes will change considerably. They will become less dark and more confortable than today. People's homes will build more economically by using natural energies like solar or wind energy. This improvments will be involved by the lack of petrol and unrecycling energies.</P>
      <P>About the size of hous, I think that in cities houses will be more and more little because of the over population. We also will see very high buildings which contains a lot of narrow flats.</P>
      <P>In opposite, in the suburb or in the land, more and more rich people will build big houses. Homes like this will be build with the latest technologies and very luxurious.</P>
      <P>But about differences between rich's and poor's homes will be the same in the futur. New technologies and facilities won't improve the relationship between people. I think that people will be as alone and julous as today.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
