<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR974*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson</P>
      <P>I'm writing to you to complain about three days programme.</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your good programme, especially for visiting The National Art Gallery. All our class like to see the beautiful pictures which were drawn by brilliant artists and painters.</P>
      <P>We saw an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show and our class would like to go to the show. It starts on Tuesday March 14 and we can go there instead of visiting the Science Museum or go shopping. Anyway we can go to the Science Museum on Wednesday afternoon because we have a free time.</P>
      <P>So on this show there will be the latest fashions, leisure and sports wear, make up and even hair styles. All our class and me would like to see this show.</P>
      <P>You know what else? We don't need to pay, it's for free because we are students.</P>
      <P>It's a great opportunity because in our fast developing world we have to look fashionable and this kind of show happens quite rare.</P>
      <P>I think you'll agree that we have changed your programme.</P>
      <P>As I said we can go to the Science Museum on Wednesday instead of having a free time. I'm looking forward of recieving a letter from you. Thank you very much.</P>
      <P>Bye</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Hello</P>
      <P>I'm going to write about "The Home of the Future".</P>
      <P>We can't say straight away how the people's homes will be different in the future but we can always imagine and create the unbelievable things about future life.</P>
      <P>Of course there will be differences between todays homes and the future ones. I think the houses will grow up on twenty floors up to the sky as more and more people will occupy it.</P>
      <P>I think more and more people will have at least one flat, doesn't matter if you are rich or not. The rooms will be designed in a future fashion like less furniture and everything is compact, even TV-set will be on the ciling. The rooms will be much bigger and wider than now, and you can have up to twenty rooms in your own flat, and even swiching on the light by saying only; "light".</P>
      <P>If course if you have enough money to let your self in such apartments, then you can afford it.</P>
      <P>Now what's going to be the same. Well as I said if you're poor, the government still give you the flat but very ugly one, probably with rats in it. The same problem will be with homeless people who doesn'ta. They will have to stay on the streets as streets is their home.</P>
      <P>I hope and I wish that the future will bring us a good moments of life where everybody will have home and a warm, friendly family relationships.</P>
      <P>Bye.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
