<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR981*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam</P>
      <P>First of all I would like to say thanks for your letter and your care about your customers. I was absolutely threaled to resive news about my win in a competition.</P>
      <P>Your letter contains few questions about detailes of my holiday which I would like to clarify for you. The first is time. I am only able to go on holiday in July, because the other time I have college, which I can't be missed.</P>
      <P>The second is accommodation. I old rather prefer stay in log cabins than live in tents. I don't like night cold and moscitos.</P>
      <P>I so glad, that I will get chance to do activities in the camp. I play basketball and at tennis. I quite good at tennis. What about basketball is. I played in school team, and was one of the best players by the end of this season.</P>
      <P>There is one more thing which I would like to know about. It is clothes and money. Should I have any special, if yes what kind of wear it is. And of course there will be expenses. Can you inform me how much money should I have and can I have some information about prices to visit local places of interests.</P>
      <P>At the end I would like ones more to say thanks for your letter and I look forward to hearing from you by post with all detailes about holiday.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfyly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>I hate shopping but in the other hand sometimes you can have fun at it. In my opinion, it dependes on your mood, your financial ability, off course where you are going to do shopping and what you are going to buy.</P>
      <P>Usualy people don't have time for shopping. You've just finished your long hours at work, you tide, you had row with your boss but you are still going to do shopping. And what you have. There are huge queus to tills, noise, hussle, poor custumer service. You've got more stress, you feel fed up and finaly when you got home you think that shopping is not that enjoyable as you thought.</P>
      <P>For example a lot of people do not like to do shopping in big stores. It takes hours to buy something. There are so many varaity of products, different prices, different quality. You should walk miles around store to find what you wanted. Yes, there is big plus for big store of course. You can find everything in one place, instead of small shops which is specialised on one product. And people spend all weekends walking around shopping cities and high streets in trills to buy something.</P>
      <P>Nower days tecnical progress gets close to us, to usual custumers. Internet is one of the issue at this problem. Without any hussle, seating in your chear in front of your computer you in second can get in at any shop who has internet site, most of the big companies have it, get all information about product, get cheaper price and buy it.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
