<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR983*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen,</P>
      <P>I have just received your letter which made me so happy and I am writing to apply your questions.</P>
      <P>First of all, I can travel only July because my son's school is going to finish at the end of June, so it is impossible for me to travel during on June. Apart from that I work in an international tourism agency and August is the busiest month of the year so July is the best choice for me.</P>
      <P>I would rather stay in tents because I used to go camping when I was a teenager with my family. I have always loved camping.</P>
      <P>My favourite hobby is photography and I think I am very good at it. I have been taking photographs since I was 17. I took some lessons and after that I have really improved it. Beside this, I am very good at playing basketball. I used to play in high school's team.</P>
      <P>Also, I have some questions. I have never been to California before so I have no idea about the climate. Could you please give me some information about it and what kind of clothes should I bring for my holiday. Besides, I really would like to know, approxiametely how much money should I take with me? Is it an expensive city?</P>
      <P>I hope all those information will help you.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I am so sorry that I couldn't write you last week. As you know, I was very busy and excited about a pop concert which I worked as a director's assistant during the last week.</P>
      <P>First of all, it was a very successful concert and probably you have heard the singer's name before who is called Tina.</P>
      <P>As a director's assistant my job was arrangement of the audience's seats and tickets. All seats were brought from a sponsor company. Everyday I worked for two hours in a shop to sale tickets. It was quite enjoyable because everyday I met different people who like listening the pop music so we had lots of things to talk about. I also helped the singer's some special demands which weren't so difficult to do. She was very nice and friendly.</P>
      <P>At the concert night, I worked as well.</P>
      <P>After the concert I was absolutely exhausted but the thing is I will never forget this experience. I met lots of people who were very famous. The best thing was of course Tina. We promised each other to keep in touch and she has invited me her next concert!</P>
      <P>So, my news are finished. Write me back soon.</P>
      <P>Love from,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
