<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR990*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>31-40</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writting to you to complain about the musical show, wich everything was completely different from the advertisement.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I would like to say that I am very disappointed and upset with the show I saw. To begin my complains I can start with the actor - was a different one, not Danny Brook. Tina Truelove performed marvellous, but him I think he is a "street actor" from Covent Garden. Even worse it was the delay, the Show started at 20:15 instead of 19:30, that drove me mad.</P>
      <P>I am a student visiting London for one week only and I asked for discount ticket, I could not get it, it was really unfair, I paid normal price. Also there was another problem, I planned to visit the Theatre restaurant after the show, I could not, was closed because it has been refurbished and redecorated.</P>
      <P>Anyway, I expected to have a perfect evening out however I had just a terrible time, everything went wrong. The only thing to do is: to compensate me, send my money back, I am sending my ticket for that: Hope you'll be fair with me otherwise I am going to take this further.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Márcia</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>"Techno life"</P>
      <P>I am very pleased that I born under such good tecnologies like my parents didn't have the same luck. My life is much easier with all these stuffs above mentioned - tecnology and science.</P>
      <P>Computers have changed people's life, many of them can work from home, they don't need to go to their offices. Internet is very handy, you can buy, send e-mail messages, or even have sex, that is really funny.</P>
      <P>There is ambiguity about technology - can bring good things and terrible things as well. One good side is making life easier - computer, mobile phones, vending machines, etc.... The bad side is to use tecnology for war - missiles, weapons, etc....</P>
      <P>Indeed tecnology has changed our lives, we have become more scepitical and cold. I believe that people should take just good advantages that. Sometimes I think tecnology is not a good thing....</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
