<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1001*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you, because I would like to disagree with your advertisment for the show 'over the Rainbow'.</P>
      <P>I would like to tell you that I was really disappointed with my evening I your theatre. At first when I came I hoped to see Danny Brook on the stage, but there was totally different actor. As it is said in advertisment the show starts at 19.30 but I had to stay outside for 45 minutes, because by the programme it started at 20.15, but that was not the end of the story, in your advertisment it is clearly said that you have discounts available on tickets, that was not true! I was not still very disappointed, because I hoped that I will have a good meal with glass of wine in the restaurant, according to your advertisment but what did I realised, it was closed, because the chef was in the hospital.</P>
      <P>I did not have a perfect evening at all and I would like to ask you to return my money back.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>Sasha Comatova.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Everyday we keep in touch with technology. We have microwaves that help us to do our meal quickly, we have hairdryers to dry our hair in 15 minutes, we have different things that made our life easier.</P>
      <P>I use different technological things everyday. Such as mobile phone that helps me to communicate, with anyone in the world, even if I am not at home, I use stereo, if I want to listen to my favourite music, I use tapes, CDs, hairdryers, ect. I think that all these things made my life much easier. Many years ago people didn't have an oppotunity to use all these things and they had to work a lot. I am very happy that with all technology that we have we don't have to work as much as they did, like to wash plates and cups after meals, my dishwashing machine will do that for me, and I don't have to wash my clothes my washing machine does it better. Of course it is a bit sad that machinery is taking over humans and of course it makes me lazy. However now I have more freedom, free time, and privacy.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
