<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1019*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Jane Clark</P>
      <P>I am writeing to you to "help" you with your festival next year, last year wasn't very good so maybe we can make it more atracite this year?</P>
      <P>the first I think we shoul rent biger hall for that so we could make better sound and give more space for viewers! If we will make one reasonably-priced weekend ticket for all events we can make intrestede more people. We can inaute stars and artists from around the world who will make and prisents all kind of music like jazz, rock, classical ect.</P>
      <P>It should be done show so people can see how people in every corner of the word make theyr own fun. Art exhibitions is good idea too, to introdus how the music is making and show how the instruments lode.</P>
      <P>Afterward we could let people talk with artists so they can get knoe theyr privacy.</P>
      <P>Mr. Jane if you want get more of my suggestions and opinions about it pleace contact with me on my calle phone</P>
      <P> Sincirley</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Simona!</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter it was so nice to hear from you gain and I am glad you have meant this subject.</P>
      <P>It's believed that English schools look different and have different rules then Polish schools but may be we might find sth incomon?!</P>
      <P> What rules do we have in our schools? The first of all it dipends what kind of school it is? Primary, highschool or university! I think that now Polish schools are going foward but they still have lots of bad habits.</P>
      <P>Polish students have to study a lot with books and they have less pracite lessons, sometimes it's hard to get a books or other neaded things to study. Conneat between students and their teachers or principals is very poor!</P>
      <P>During the lesson we are not allowed to have food or stg drink, we can't be late to school</P>
      <P>School supose to be our second home but it's not we work hard and for the end our education we still have nothing.</P>
      <P>You asking me what would I change? I would make schools more unstressfull, added fun cause it's easeyer way to learn and I would gives students more chances to share yo with their fantazy at school.</P>
      <P>Maybe Polish system is not bad, but it's conftyble too. I know that that letter will not change anything but you can see how compliated is Polish studen's life</P>
      <P>Your</P>
      <P> </P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
