<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1028*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson</P>
      <P>I would like to congratulate you for the excellent programme that you have prepared. I think that is such a good programme especially because the places that we visit, like the Science Museum, are very interesting.</P>
      <P>However, the rest of the students and I have heard about the London Fashion and Leisure show that will be celebrated at the Central Exhibition Hall in London where the latest fashions will be shown. There we will have the chance to be maked up or to try new hairstyles, too. And it has free-entrance for the students. We think it will be a great opportunity because it will take place while our visit to London, the 14th of March. We think that, if you don't have any problem, we could visit the Science Museum on Wednesday after visiting the National Art Gallery so that we can go to the London Fashion and Leisure show.</P>
      <P>We are wating for your decision and we will accept it whatever it be.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>"THE HOME OF THE FUTURE"</P>
      <P>From any point of view, the home of the future will be very similar to the homes that we have today. I think that it will has a similar structure but it will include some new technological advantages like having all the house controlled by a computer so that, for example, we can turn on the lights of the bedroom just pressing a button while we are watching the TV sitting on the sofa.</P>
      <P>Although many people think that the home of the future will be something like an UFO, in my opinion the changes won't be very important, they will probably consist on making the houseworks easier. The cleanest example is to compare a house from the beginings of the 20th century with our house Both are very similar but now we have new technologies. In balance then, I think that the houses that we can see on films won't really exist.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
