<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR771*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>41-50</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs or Miss Jane X,</P>
      <P>I am writing to thank you for the annual international arts festival which was organized on 21st-22nd November. I had spent at this festival for two days.</P>
      <P>It was a great idea to organize such festival. I am a teacher and I love music. Most of the events which I had seen were good. I enjoyed dance shows, jazz and rock concerts. I visited art exhibitions. There were a lot of nice pictures, sculptures and other creative works. I was impressed by them. At festival I could talk with writers. It was an excellent idea to make one reasonaly-priced weekend ticket for all events. A lot of people could visit as many events as the they could.</P>
      <P>I was very surprised when I knew that stars and artists were only from six countries. It was too little for this festival. It was pitty that too small halls were used for classical concerts. I like going to classical concerts but at this festival the sounds of music were terrible.</P>
      <P>I have some suggestion for next year's festival. Firstly, it will be great if you invite more famous singers and bands. The second one is to include more musical films and plays. I would like to help you in your interesting job. I look forward to your answer.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Traditional Folk Stories of the World</P>
      <P>There are a lot of folk stories in the world and there are a lot of folk stories in Estonia, I would like to tell you one of them. This story is about a man and his three sons. This story happened a long time ago. The man was old and his sons were young.</P>
      <P>One day the man quarreled with his sons and they left the house trying to find work. They were successful. And they had lived far from their father for two years. They grow up and became wise. They decided to return to his father because he was old and he needed help.</P>
      <P>When the sons were old they began to tell about their life beginning with this story happend a long time ago</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
