<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR772*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>41-50</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>17th Juni 2000</P>
      <P>The manager of the Circle Theatre</P>
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I'm in London first time and I wondered what is interesting on yours stage: I read in newspaper the advertisment about best musical show. In advertisment starring was very interested - Danny Brook and Tina Truelove.</P>
      <P>I desided to go to your theatre but at the beginning was the tranbles. In advertisment was - "discounts available". I'm teacher and in Polan I have discounts but in England no, I know this is other country. I was disappointed because you wrote about it!</P>
      <P>Otherwise, the musical show started too late at 20 15 not 17 30! This was a waste of time. I was very suppresed when I saw different actor, it wasn't Danny Brook. This musical show wasn't "the best". I went out earlier but the theatre restaurant was closed. I had very disappointing evening. I would ask you for money back.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerelly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>"Fashion of the Future"</P>
      <P>What will clothes be like 100 years from now? This is very interesting question for us and maybe very important too. We think and speak about it in our families.</P>
      <P>I saw one week ago on TV 23th the fashion show in Paris and I was very surrprised because of this style. All models had a very strange long shoes made from black skin, the trouses was quite short and the jackets was elegant with blazzend materiell.</P>
      <P>I think the fashion of the future will be very different but suitable for all people. The people will wear clothes from natural materials like silk, comfortable and elgant. The colours will be very good quality and the fashion will be changed very quickly like now.</P>
      <P>Because the world is now a global village the people will wear at least one part of traditional or national clothes (for example peasnt jacket or hat) like now in rural areas from time to time.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
