<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1102*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson</P>
      <P>I am writing to request your permission for us to visit the London Fashion and Leisure Show on 14th March.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to say thank to you for this good programme, especially the decision of going to visit in London. All of us is appreciated that we could have this opportunity. Because most students have never been to London before, also we could visit some famous places which we wanted to go.</P>
      <P>However, we would be grateful if you would arrange a time to visit the show additionally. This show takes place at Central Exhibition Hall on Tuesday from 10:00 to 19:00. In this show, not only can we see latest fashions, leisure and sports wear, make up and hairstyles, but we also can enter for free. Moreover some students think that they would like to do fashion studies in future. If you would accept and wouldn't mind this idea, we would like to visit it instead of shopping in the afternoon on Tuesday.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Nowadays, quite a few famous people suffer their private life from disturbers such as journalists or reporters. I would like to think how media effect to famous people.</P>
      <P>Few years ago, we had a terrible news of death of Lady Diana. She was always been aftering by media. She had no private life even though she wanted to be alone. Finally, after chasing for long time, she was dead because of car accident. It must be a good example of media disaster. I understand she had a good reason to be chased by it. However she definetely deserve to have a private life as one of citizen. Human right must be existed for all people.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, there are few famous people desire to be watched by media. If media stopped focusing the people, they would think as if they are put in a bin like rubbish. Moreover, many people love to watch a gossip programme on TV or in a magazine. It is one of fun in our life.</P>
      <P>On balance,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
