<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1123*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan.</P>
      <P>I can only travel on July because these is the mounth when I have holidays. I've already talked to my manager, and she said that that's the only mounth I can have my holidays.</P>
      <P>I would prefer to stay in log cabin because it must be cold to stay in a tent. I have some problems with my kidneys, so I can't stay in on of the tents, and it also must be very comfortable to stay a log cabin.</P>
      <P>I'm really good at Golf and Tennis, so I would like to choose these two activities. I've been doing these activities for a very long time. I've been playing Golf for five years, and I'm a handidate cup of sixteen, but the problem is that I haven't been playing Golf for a long time because I work every day. I've been playing tannis since I was seven, and I've been studying how to play tannis for a very long time, nine years.</P>
      <P>I would like to know what kind of cloths do I need to take with me, and can you write me back what kind of weather it's going to be there, for the time I will be staying there. Also I would like to know how much money should I take with me, because I'm not sure how much I'll need to spend there. See you Mrs Helen Ryan, and please write me back,</P>
      <P>Ivan. S.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I wish you were there with me helping at a pop concert. I just loved it, I was working with these music system. You know how good I'm at music, anyway I was helping to these pop concert to get the corect sounds, at the bigging I was conecting all these wires into spekers, music system, guitar etc... The particularly bit that I liked about the experience was when I was standing next to the singers and playing a guitar, you know how much I love playing guitar, and all these video cameras were just filming us. I asked on of the camera man when they're going to show these show on tv, and he told me they're going to show it on 10 of June, so turn on your tv on these date chanel three, and must seem me there playing with these guitar AH it was lovely. These singers are going to come next year so I want to invite you to my house for one or two weeks to see these pop concert, beleave me you'll love it and you might use the drums, I told them that you're really good at drums so they want to try you too.</P>
      <P>I'll write you soon Kim.</P>
      <P>Tell hello to your parents!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
