<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1133*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Madam</P>
      <P>I'm very happy to have won in your competition. I'm never going in the U.S.A than I'm very exciting to travel at Camp California. I can to come only July because I have to work the other months of Summer. As accomodation I'd prefer to sleep in tents becaose I like beeing outside and earing the noises of the sea.</P>
      <P>My two activities's choices are Climbing and Surfing. I used to climb and I want to try still because climbing is good for the fit. I want to do surfing too because I like snowboarding and I think surfing make similar sensations, but I have never practised that sport.</P>
      <P>I have one question to ask you. I have a little brother and I want to know if I could take it with me. He doesn't like stay alone at home.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Anton Chevalier</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>I purpose that we should be filmed five topics:</P>
      <P>A math lesson, an english lesson, a swimingpool lesson, the break and the staff room.</P>
      <P>- At the math lesson and the English lesson we could show how the teacher learn at his students. We could be filmed the class room too.</P>
      <P>- In the swimingpool we could been in the water and doing a party of water-polo and then Allan could done acrobatics stands, because he make competitions.</P>
      <P>- During the break we could show the activities of the students. for exemple students who play football or volleyball. We could asked some students about the school.</P>
      <P>- Before the end we could visit the staff room. We could known how this room is and what the Teachers do in this misterious room.</P>
      <P>In the end we could show a comment of each student of our class.</P>
      <P>Anton Chevalier</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
