<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1135*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you after visiting your theatre. Frankly speaking, I was very disappointed after my visit.</P>
      <P>I was displeased from the very beginning, because I expected to get a discount as I'm a student. According to your advertisment I could have one but in reality there were no discounts at all. But nevertheless I decided to go to your show.</P>
      <P>The show started t 20.15 instead of 19.30. I had to wait in overcrowded hall. When finally the show had started I found out that Danny Brook was replaced by another actor. One of the reasons for my visiting your show was Danny Brook's participance. So, you could understand how disappointed I was.</P>
      <P>To make matters worse the restaurant which was mentioned in your advertisment was closed.</P>
      <P>So I hadn't such perfect evening, as was promised in your advertisment.</P>
      <P>In fact there were a lot of mistakes in your advertisment and I would be gratefull if you could give me back a part of my money.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed your daily life?</P>
      <P>In my opinion, modern technologies play the important role in people's life. I think that at present the most important technologies are computer and Internet technologies. Both computer and Internet influence people's life.</P>
      <P>I have to use computer every day. It helps me in preparing my homeworks. Firs of all Internet gives you an access to a great number of different information. On the one hand Internet is often used for entertaiment, but on the other hand it's also used in different business and education process! With the help of Internet technologies I communicate with other people from all over the world it gives me chance to improve my English. From my point of view, Internet can be used in education, because it gives an opportunity to have distant relations between pupils and teachers.</P>
      <P>Though Internet has a lot of positive aspects I think you should be careful with it and not to be depended on it.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
