<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1138*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>First of all I would like to thank you for the perfect organisation of the competition which I luckely won, I have been really very impressed.</P>
      <P>Unfortunately I became your letter with two weeks late so I can travel only between the 5th and the 20th July. In fact I will finish my university's exams only on the first July and after the 20th is impossible because I am going to do four weeks volontary in India for UNICEF.</P>
      <P>If it is possible I would prefer to stay in a log cabins, because, in spite of my love for nature, I am terribly allergic to pollins. So stay in a log cabins will probably evite me a lot of problems.</P>
      <P>Choose two activities from the list has been very difficult but I think I would like to do climbing, sport in which I have many years of experience, and surfing despite I really have any experience.</P>
      <P>Unfortunately I had ever been in the US so I have any idea about how much money I will probably need and about what kind of clothes I have to take with me.</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your attencion on my regard</P>
      <P>Your sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>If you ask at twenty womans what is their favorite hobbies probably the most of them will answer "shopping".</P>
      <P>But why is shopping so popular and loved by so many people all over the world? Why so many people have been contaged by this "psychologic virus"?</P>
      <P>The verb "have" is probably the most used and loved by the human species. We are always trying to have more things, that in spite of care after us family, us future, or other things which are probably more important than a new perfum.</P>
      <P>Always more people, everywhere, are becoming shopping-addicts. Maybe you can think I am excessive but recent studies prouves that this mania can be really dangerous.</P>
      <P>Certenly the only fact of have something can helps people to be more sure of himself. In fact if you have the new Kalvin Klein model for a certain kind of people you are cool, but it is really so important?</P>
      <P>Probably when Oscar Wilde said: "Superficiality is the suprem vice" he was right. We still look at what people look like and not at what they really are.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
