<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1139*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Smith;</P>
      <P>I am writing this letter to make you know the bad points of the theatre.</P>
      <P>First, it didn't start at 19.30. It started at 20.15. We had to wait for 45 minutes. I got bored. Not only me but also the others got bored.</P>
      <P>It was wrote in the newspaper that Danny Brock took place in the play. But it was not Danny Brock, it was a different actor. If there had been a problem, it would have been told us. I wanted to see him but I couldn't see. This was very disappointing for me.</P>
      <P>When I was buying a ticket, there was no discount. But in the newspaper it was wrote to be a discount. I paid £20 to the cashier. I was hungry and I thought I could eat something at the theatre restaurant after the show. But it was closed without any reason. It was very rude. For this, I want my money back. Because I didn't enjoy at the theatre.</P>
      <P>I hope you would not continue like this.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>TECHNOLOGICAL ADVANTAGES</P>
      <P>Technology is the thing that makes our life easy. Technology is in every part of our life.</P>
      <P>We use cars, trains, ships or planes when we want to go somewhere. But if they weren't made, we would have to walk or go by a horse or donkey. With the help of technology, we do our works in less time. For example; in the past people used horses to go another place. And their life passed in the ways. But now we use planes to go far places. It takes less time than going by horse.</P>
      <P>And computers, the most important product of technology. In the world, people spend the whole day by playing computers. Not only as a hobby. They use computers for their works. They connect with other businessmen and do their jobs with the help of computers. Sometimes they don't go to their offices. They write their secret notes into the computers. Computers hold them in their memory. But in the past people had to use lots of note books and they also had to find places to hide them.</P>
      <P>But it has also bad points. For example; wars. Using technology scientists make lots of powerful guns. It is bad for the world's piece.</P>
      <P>I think we should use the technology for the piece and use it for our fortune.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
