<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1140*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to express my dissatisfaction about the show you presented two weeks ago at your theatre.</P>
      <P>As I was spending a week-end in London I took a chance too see the performance of one of my favourite actors, Danny Brook. Unfortunately as soon as I came to the theatre I was told that there had been a change in the cast and Danny Brook was not part of it anymore. Besides, since my girlfriend and I had really to hurry up to reach the theatre on time we hadn't had any dinner, as we had been thinking to have it at your restaurant. You cannot imagine our disappointment when we realised that the show had been posticipated at 20.15 instead of 19.30 and that the restaurant was closed because of restructuring; as a matter of fact, after the show we only ate an hamburger in a fast-food.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, I would like to have the two tickets refunded considering also that there were no discounts available, as instead it was stated in the advertisement.</P>
      <P>Yours Faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. In fact this was the main cause of Mr White's resignation and suicide. Pat was not a very clever teen-ager and while she was attending the Secondary School she had many troubles with Chemistry. I could actually say that if it hadn't been for Mr. White she would have never passed her exam to enter University. Mr White came to our school when he was 40 year-old but still well-looking and all my girls school-mates fell suddenly in love with him; he was always so kind and generous towards his pupils that any girls felt herself loved by him: Pat certainly was one of them. One day while she was walking in Central Park she saw a man and a young girl sitting under a tree. Immediately she recognized her beloved teacher kissing one of her class mate and she run away as fast as she could. She was so angry and felt so betrayed by Mr White that without any exitation she went to the school Headmaster to report everything she had seen. The next day Mr White was charged for abuses and obliged to resign. The trial was long and had a wide coverage by media. We live in a small and old fashioned town and Mr. White was considered a monster: loosing his job was hard for him, but even harder was the loss of his beloved pupils who were not allowed to meet him; so, on a bright summer day he took his final decision and died terrified by the darkness which was nearing.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
