<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1141*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>8 Jun 2000</P>
      <P>Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>Competition Organiser</P>
      <P>Dear Sir</P>
      <P>At the begining I would like to thank You for Your letter - it pleased me much. I have always dreamt about holidays 'in Camp California'</P>
      <P>However there are some problems that I hope to solve. First of all the only suitable time for me to go is July. It is the only time when I am free from my duties - I am a doctor so you see that I can not let my patients down. If we are talking about accomodation then accomodation in tents would be great - I love being close to the nature. I would like You to know also about my two hobbys: swimming and surfing. I am not telling about some kind of achivements in those discipines but It is my big pasion</P>
      <P>I hope to have a chance to practice both of theme at 'Camp California'.</P>
      <P>There is also one thing that I would like to ask You about. The question is: Do I need some extra money and what kind of clothes should I take for this trip?</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Anna Nowak</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Unconectedeverypeoplelifes We buy everything from clothes to food and the only thing that could stop us from this are money.</P>
      <P>As a teenager I must addmit that there is nothing more enjoyable from shopping. It's like "walking in the clouds" you feel like flaing. Choosing gave me such big pleasure because I never have to worry from vere do I take money for my wishes. It all comes from my parents. All I ought to do is buy and choose. I think that "having is a dream'' of all of us.</P>
      <P>However I can't agree with opinion that "Shopping is not always enjoyable'' I think that everybody like to buy but not everybody like to see pleasure in it.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
