<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR777*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>June 13th, 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Mrs/Ms Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I would like to thank you for the prize I won. My name is Manuel P. Martinez and I won the first prize in your competition. I have been informed that all accommodation and travel cost are paid for the company.</P>
      <P>I can only travel in July because I am working as a receptionist in a hotel and they would only let me have two weeks off in that month. I would prefer to stay in a log cabin rather than in tents, because I find it more confortable to sleep in beds, but it wouldn't be a problem if I have to sleep in tents.</P>
      <P>I would love to do climbing and surfing just because those are sports I have never praticed before, that means I do not have any experience on the subject.</P>
      <P>Please let me know the kind of clothes we will be wearing, would I need to take a suit? Are there going to be any formal parties?</P>
      <P>It is important for me to know if we need money and in that case, how much money would you recommend me to take?</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Manuel P. Martinez</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>June 13th, 2000 Dear Kim, As you already know, I was at a pop concert last month. It was great! The concert was organized by the community so everyone who wanted to help was welcomed. The concert lasted for four hours as a lot of small local bands played. My job was to set the stage where the bands played. It was hard and it took me the whole day. I was there at seven a.m and didn't go home until seven a.m the following day. Of course I didn't do it alone, we were a group of about ten guys. After the show we had to stay and clean the park, which was full of empty cans. The part that I enjoyed the most was that I felt I was doing something worthly for the community and also that I got to meet a lot of people. I made great friends with the group I worked with. I think it was a great experience, and I hope we will organize another concert soon. I am looking forward to seeing you. Best wishes</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
