<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR133*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan.</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter. I am so happy to win the prize and come true my dream.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel to California this July, because I can take an holiday from 14th to 27th of July.</P>
      <P>I would prefer log cabins. I have never used it and I think it would be more exciting than tents.</P>
      <P>I have heard that the Camp California is famous for surfing, so I hope that I will enjoy surfing for the first time. Besides, I will take the chance to play golf. It is my only favorite hobby.</P>
      <P>What about clothes and money? I don't know what the weather is like, and you are paid for travel costs, but I am wondering that it is included two activities. Also, I have a dog. Can I go with him.</P>
      <P>Please, let me know this questions as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>I appreciate your competition and I look forward to hearing your answer</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim</P>
      <P>I am sorry. This letter is late, because last week I took exams, so I was very busy.</P>
      <P>To reply your answer, it was realy an nice experience. As you know, I like a pop music so much and singer was one of my favorite singers. Also, in the future I'll want to be an organizer like this concert, so it'll be useful the experience to me.</P>
      <P>I am writing how I got the position and what I did. Firstly, I applied to a concert agency to help, because I had the experience before and I knew how to organize and what to do.</P>
      <P>In the pop concert, there were many people, so before starting the pop concert, I arranged the seats and carried some musical instruments. It was somewhat hard to me. After the concert, I cleaned all the ground with other helpers and we moved the seats again.</P>
      <P>If you have some questions, let me know. I am looking forward to hearing from you</P>
      <P>With best wishes,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
