<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR134*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>41-50</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>I have just received your letter and feel happy about winning first prize. I am now writing to give you all information you require.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to travel only in July because I am employed and will be able to finish my contract in June. On August I am going to apply for a new job.</P>
      <P>Also, I would prefer to stay in a log cabin rather than stay in a tent. From my point of view, log cabins are more comfortable.</P>
      <P>Another consideration are activities. I enjoy playing basketball and golf. Also I think I am good at singing and at dancing.</P>
      <P>I would be most greatful if you could let me know some information:</P>
      <P>- How to get to Camp California from airport?</P>
      <P>- How far from city-centre the camp is situated?</P>
      <P>- How much money I have to take with me?</P>
      <P>- What is the weather in California in July?</P>
      <P>- What kind of clothes would you recommend me to bring with me?</P>
      <P>- Are there leisure and intertainments facilities close to the camp?</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Report</P>
      <P>To: Mr Clark</P>
      <P>From: Sonya Volavkova</P>
      <P>Attituds to the video about life at our school</P>
      <P>Introduction:-</P>
      <P>The aim of this report is to summarize the pupil's attituds about video they have to be made and to suggest which lessons and other activities should be filmed. The report is based on opinion of more than 300 pupils.</P>
      <P>What would the pupils prefer to film?</P>
      <P>According to the answer there are the most important activities pupils would like to film (80 per cent of those questioned)</P>
      <P>- lessons in Mathematics and History, because pupils have very good exam's result.</P>
      <P>- lessons in dancing, because 80 per cent girls attend the Dancing Club</P>
      <P>- competition in basketball, because our school's team won first prize in our gerian.</P>
      <P>- pupils' travel to London, during the last holiday, because it was great!</P>
      <P>- Also they would like to film the pat corner at school, because they enjoy taking care of animals.</P>
      <P>Conclusion: It is clear, that the filming of video is very important event for children, and pupils would prefer to film only positive events of their life at school as I have written above.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
