<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR135*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>June, 13th 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writing in response to your letter which said that I won the first prize in the competition.</P>
      <P>As I didn't expect to be successful, I am very happy about this result.</P>
      <P>I would now like to answer the information you requested. Firstly, I would be pleased if I could travel in July as I already booked this month as a holiday at work.</P>
      <P>Besides, I would prefer to stay in a tent since I have never had the exciting experience to sleep in the middle of the nature.</P>
      <P>I am especially glad about the activities offers, in particular the sports facilities because I was spezialised in sport for my A-levels and intend to become a sport teacher.</P>
      <P>I have been playing Basketball for many years but I would appreciate to improve my skills, in particular the ball-handling.</P>
      <P>Furthermore I am really keen on swimming and can therefore hardly await having the possibility to learn the butterfly as a new style since I am already perfect in crawl.</P>
      <P>I know I have already asked a lot but there is one more thing I need to know which kind of clothes will be appropriate and how much money will I approximately need?</P>
      <P>I trust I mentioned all the requested details and am now looking forward to hearing from you to arrange the exact date of departure.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>June, 13th 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>how are you doing? Thanks for your latest letter - I was really happy about your news!</P>
      <P>Here, everything is as usual: School, studying, eating, sleeping - but did I tell you about my latest job?</P>
      <P>I helped at a pop concert of a newcomer group and you can't imagine how exciting it was!</P>
      <P>First of all, I helped selling tickets and drinks and there I realized how bad my maths is - I took such a long time to give back the change! But at the end I handled it almost automatically. Before the performance I introduced the spectators to their seats and then a instructor showed me how to lead the spotlights. I really had butterflies in my stomach when I was responsible for the lightening! It was marvellous!</P>
      <P>But the cherry on the cake was that I met one of the handsome singers back stage! He asked me what I was doing and so on and finally invited me for his next concert! Of course I agreed - I wouldn't want to miss the chance to gain experience while having fun! Perhaps I could help regularly in the lightening area - it would help me for my studies of photography. What do you reckon?</P>
      <P>I can hardly await your reply!</P>
      <P>Lot's of Love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
