<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR136*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Jun 10/2000</P>
      <P>-Helen Ryan-</P>
      <P>I am really surprise for the information because I won, and I like to tell you thank you for everyting this is why I wrote and send this letter with the information you need, only I can travel in July because it is the only time with I can do it before for my work, really I do not care which accommodation will I can have, I am prefer the accommodation in July I will be avaliabel, I am really apreciated if you can tell to the people who work in Camp California, I choose the Golf and Photography because I think I am really interesting in that object I am no really really good but I have some of studies. I would like to ask you what kind of clothes I need to take for the place and for the weather follow for the money, how much money I need to take? I think it is everyting I like to know. Thank you very much for you time.</P>
      <P>sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>-Dear Kim-</P>
      <P>How are you? I hope you are fine like the same for me.</P>
      <P>I like to apologise with you, because I didn't wrote to you recently, but I like to tell you what hapend to me in the last weak I had the opportunity to help in one of the most pop concert in my city, so imagen, I fell really really good and exating for that I don't have words for describe but I try to do it, OK?</P>
      <P>They need one girl to put make up to the stars of the group, so I do it, I was talking with the manager and the people inside the group so I meet a lot of people and it's good for my curriculum vitae as well but the best for my it's was when one of the group they with me one rose for my work am really proud about them!</P>
      <P>I really enjoy that kind of day what about you? I need to get out know, I keep in touch.</P>
      <P>loves and kisses.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
