<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR137*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you in reply to your letter about my willing the first prize in your competition.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to thank the jury for chosen my work from all the competitors.</P>
      <P>Next, I would like to find out some details about the camp. I need to know if my travel will take place in August. If I had known that I won, I would not have arranged my english course in Britain. Before. The next point is the accommodation. You mentioned that it will be in tents or log cabins. I would prefer staying in tents. I am very close to the nature, so it will be a pleasure for me.</P>
      <P>What's more, your letter said about the chance to do for two acctivities during the camp. I am very interested in tennis, but I am also very good at photography. It has been my hobby since I was a child. I have even won competion once. That is why I would like to continue doing this at the camp.</P>
      <P>Finally, I would like to ask about other things like: clothes, money, guide. I would like to know if the "travel costs'' which you had paid for include entrance tickets to the museums' or any other cultural places, because I would like to some sightseeing in the U.S.A. Furthermore, if there will be cmy tumple dryer or washing maschine to clean our clothes and if there will be a guide who will be responsible for us and the camp.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>A. Adamski.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Generally, most people like shopping, but there are some advantages and disadvantages.</P>
      <P>When discribing the advantages, we should remember that most people like doing shopping. It is very pleasant when you are looking for something special or for special occasions like wedding, birthday, Christmas presents. Next, it can be very good for your wallet to save some money, when you will find a bargain or sales. As well as that, some shop-assistance can give you a lower price, because you always do shopping at their shop. What is more, most people cannot live without shopping. It is their way to spend free time.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, there are some minuses. On top of that, shopping is very tiring and exhausting. Walking from shop to shop carrying heavy bags, takes much of your time. Instead of that you could do more interesting things. such as playing sports or reading a book. Besides that, shopping steal you from money. Very often people go to a shop - usually a big departament store and buy things which they do not need.</P>
      <P>In my opinion shopping is very tiring and I usually try to avoid doing it. When I have to, I do it, but I think we waste too much time on it that we should. On balance some people still like shopping even if it is not always enjoyable and they have to stand in a long queue to buy something. From my point of view it depands on us if shopping will be enjoyable or not.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
