<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR138*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>Referring to the won competition, I would say that I am very happy to be the first. Accordingly I will give you the further information that you wanted.</P>
      <P>First, you asked abut the travel time and the only possible time for me is in July, because my company only gave me holidays in this period.</P>
      <P>Second, I prefer accommodation in tent. I want to feel the real nature and spirit of Camp California.</P>
      <P>Further more, I should choose between two activities and how good I am at each one. I choose singing and surfing, singing because I am a singer in a band and I hope to make my voice more perfect and surfing because I have never surf and I want to learn to.</P>
      <P>Finally, I have some questions. I would know what type of clothes I should bring with me? How much money should I take with me? Is it possible to travel with a friend of mine?</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Marlene Berg</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>How are you? I hope fine. Me, fine, because of helping at the concert 'The Dome'. I can say that this was one of the best experiences of my life. First I have help to cook coffee and make food for popular people like Mariah Carey, Elton John, Backstreet Boys, Echt ect... Before and after the concert the "stars" are very hungry and I have serve them food, drinks and something like this. Kim, check it in your mind, I have had near contact with Mariah Carey! I am so happy about it. Different "stars" gave me signatures and talk really nice and normal with me. At the time the concert was running I cleaned the kitchen and the room where the "stars" ate. The after show dinner party was very nice and I have never thought that popular people like Elton John dances on the table if he likes the music and if he have made a great show on stage. It was just great and after this event I can say that popular people are normal humans like everyone!</P>
      <P>Love,</P>
      <P>Marlene</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
