<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR139*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Manager,</P>
      <P>My name is Manu Roddos and I am writing to complain about somethings that happened in the performance of the show Over the Rainbow, wich took place in your stablishment, The Circle Theater, that made me feel very upset.</P>
      <P>First of all, the show is far away from being the best musical show in London. I was very exited to see it yesterday, but as soon as I arrived at the theater the problems began. I was looking forward on having a discount of some pounds on my ticket, as the leaflet says, however it did not happen. After that, I became even more angry because, as far as I concerne, the show must begin on time, but it started forty five minutes late. Finally, the actors were not Danny Brook and Tina Truelove, but others I have never seeing before, and the restaurant was closed with no advise.</P>
      <P>At last, for all these reasons my evening was horrible, and that is why I would like to ask you for my money back as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerelly,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>In our days, technology has become a very common thing, even among children. It is such an evolution for human race, however we can not forget that it can cause some problems too.</P>
      <P>Firstly, the great boom of massive comunication wich happened in the beginning of our decade, with the devellopment of telephones, radio stations, television and even satelites, and of course, the internet, gave common people the chance to take off on a trip all over the world, and this provided health and education researches to increase as well.</P>
      <P>In the other hand, technology has made the differences between - poor and rich people to grow at a high level, and this is one of the biggest causes of violence in all countries. I addition to that, people will always be affraid of the technological war.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, from my point of view, people must learn that despite technology being such a new area to explore, we have to use it with a great amount of responsability, for us all to survive in the future.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
