<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR141*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Jane Clark,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you to give some opinions of mine abut The International Arts Festival.</P>
      <P>It was a great idea and I had the pleasure of resting and relaxing, plus of getting some important knowledge from it. On the other hand there were some disadvantages: 1. Stars and artists wee only from six countries</P>
      <P>2. Some concert halls were too small. So it was impossible to get tickets there.</P>
      <P>3. I think that there were not enough plays and films.</P>
      <P>To sum up I want to tell you bout my suggestions for next year's festival. It would be wonderful to buy some books or programms with signatures of all the stars and artists taking part in the festival. Also I think that dance shows should include different styles of dancing (e.g. national dancing of all the countries) to impress audience and not to bore with the similar scenes.</P>
      <P>I hope this letter will help you in organying </P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Hello Philip,</P>
      <P>I have just got your letter. It is a pleasure for me to communicate with such a friend as you are. Thank you very much.</P>
      <P>In our school we have the following rules: 1. Every puple has to sit alone (I mean that one desk is given for one man)</P>
      <P>2. One should have such marks as "3", "4", "5" not "2" which is eaqual.</P>
      <P>3. Another strict rule is not to be late for your lessons. Otherwise you are not allowed to come in.</P>
      <P>These rules are strict and certainly we have endless number of just-so-called rules. I don't think you will be interested in them.</P>
      <P>Truely speaking I am not sure about home rules. I think that in our family everything is based on mutual understanding. We don't have old-traditioned rules or something alike.</P>
      <P>I'm afraid I must be going now because I want to send you this letter today.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
