<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR144*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I would like to travel only in July because my boss can not give me a leaving for the other months of Summer.</P>
      <P>Also, I prefer to stay in tents because I think it is a good chance for me to live with the nature and to wake up listening birds which singing. It will be nice!</P>
      <P>Then you ask me which two activities I want to choose. To tell you the truth, I would prefer to do swimming and singing. I'm good in both of these. I have been swimming for eight years! Also I like a lot music and everybody tells me that I have a good voice.</P>
      <P>I would like ask you about the weather. I want to know if I should bring warm clothes or not and how much money.</P>
      <P>Your sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>how are you? Thanks for you letter. It was good to hear from you now. As you know this Summer I really enjoy myself doing things I like a lot.</P>
      <P>Last month, Alice and her friends proposed me to help at a pop concert. The group which was singing was very famous and I was able to meet them and to chat about their plans for the future.</P>
      <P>All I had to do was to prepare something to eat before the concert and to control during it about the sound.</P>
      <P>The concert lasted four hours and in the end they wanted to pay me. I didn't want to take any money because I was so happy that I had seen the concert of "Savage Garden" in live and because that night was the best of my life.</P>
      <P>But the thing I particularly liked about my experience, was the feeling when you are near and when you talk with the people so famousso.</P>
      <P>OK! That's all for now. I'm waiting for your letter.</P>
      <P>See you soon,</P>
      <P>Margaret</P>
      <P>xxx</P>
      <P>P.S. I hope you will find the spare time to visit my country this Summer.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
