<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR147*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>20 Ibiza Road</P>
      <P>San Antonio</P>
      <P>13/06/2000</P>
      <P>Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>Competition Organiser</P>
      <P>Dear Madam:</P>
      <P>I'm writting to you with reference to the letter I have received from you saying I have won your competition.</P>
      <P>First of all I'd like to thank you for the prize, I will enjoy it abosolutly.</P>
      <P>Finally, I'd like to add some further questions: what kind of clothes do I have to bring?, Do I any kind?, and Would it be necessary to bring money?, how much?</P>
      <P>Thank you very much, and I hope the information above would be sufficient. I look forward to hearing from you</P>
      <P>Your faithfully Jose Fernandez</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="5a">
      <P>"Wuthering Heights" by Emile Brönte I think this statement is a very truly afimation in the case of my book because the main character of the story is a very wicked man. Besides that, this character is more interesting than others due to his complex mind and his deep evil manners. It's the richest character at all, his name is Heathcliff, and he's the reason of whatever happens to the others characters. They are always suffering the revenge that Heathcliff swear, cause of which is the miserable situation the other character have put him in. From this point of view I think Heathcliff shouldn't be hated by his bad temper. He's not good not because he was born with this trend to harm but the others character make him become thus. This revenge links the story so without it we would not have such "Wuthering Heights". I sympathize with Heathcliff because I think every bad character is a very important point of every book, film or play and if they were missing we would not love those stories we enjoyed while we were reading them.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
