<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR148*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter of 13 June. I am very happy to have won the first prize in your competition.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel only in July, because I have only one month holliday this year. I would prefer to sleep in a tent, because I think is a great fun and a bit more adventurous. It is not too much confortable, but it is not a problem for me, I like this kind of holliday.</P>
      <P>I am keen on photography so I would love to participated at this activity, I am very good at that and it would be a pleasure for me to help the others. I also will take painting, because I always dream about painting, but I never try to, so I think it is a good occasion.</P>
      <P>I would be grateful if you could tell me what kind of clothes I have to take with and how many money, more or less, do you think I should take.</P>
      <P>Thank you to ask me my taste and to be preoccupated about it.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Audrey Gillett</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>Like you know last month, I had helped at a pop concert and I enjoyed it a lot.</P>
      <P>Firstly I had to make the decor of the scene, so I made in the background a sky with a lot of bright stars. Then I put some blue lights. furthermore I made some stars in paper in argent color. But that was only the begining of my adventure.</P>
      <P>The most exiting part was when I had to make up the pop stars! I never had met pop stars before and I was very impresed, but I was too happy to show my shyness. Do you believe that I spoke with Micheal Jackson, my favourite singer?</P>
      <P>I can't believe it yet! It was a wonderful experience. I will remember that day for the rest of my life. It was like a dream who becomes tru. I wish you had been there with me. I can't explain how supper it was.</P>
      <P>I stayed with him until the concert begun and after the show I had the opportunity to stay in his private room with him and the other dansers. Well, I have to leave you now, but I will tell you more details when we next meet each other.</P>
      <P>See you soon.</P>
      <P>Love,</P>
      <P>Audrey</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
