<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR149*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Brown,</P>
      <P>I went to the Circle Theatre yesterday, to see the play "Over The Rainbow" and I must say that I got rather disappointed.</P>
      <P>First of all, the play was supposed to start at 7:30 P.M. but it actually started only at 8:15 P.M. so I had to wait forty-five minutes. Also, your advertisement sign says that discounts are available. What is quite not true because when I asked for it, the woman who sells the tickets replied with a resounding "no".</P>
      <P>When the play finally started, and the two actors entered the stage, I could see that the male one was not Danny Brook, differently from what the advertisement sign says, what really disappointed me since he was the only reason that I came to this play.</P>
      <P>But my complaints are not over yet. After the disappointing performance the actor who replaced Danny Brook, I went to the theatre restaurant, and, also differing from the advertisement sign, it was closed. There was only a small sign stamped on the door, saying that it was "closed for repairs".</P>
      <P>So, unfortunately, I must say that last night was one of the worst nights I ever had, and given the reasons, I expect to count with your sense of responsability, so, I feel that I must ask for my 20 pounds spent on that terrible night.</P>
      <P>yours faithful,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed your daily life?</P>
      <P>As we all know, technology had a gigantic improvement over the last 20 years, and today, it affects us in many ways.</P>
      <P>First of all, we all became much more sedentary than in the past. Most of the modern jobs involves computers, so there is no physical effort, just mental, but, on the other hand, we improved communications with computers and Internet, a kind of communication where there is no need to meet personally, to see the other person, just the need to talk.</P>
      <P>Also, with today's machines, factories have significantly increased their production, what brings progress to humanity, but also, with the continous replacement of men by machines, the unemployment is increasing too, and today, it worries every single citizen of the world, specially the ones who lives in third world country.</P>
      <P>So, men have invented machines to help him on his tasks, but nowadays, we our becoming slaves of them. The most important thing in the future will be knowing how to deal with machines, so, today's children must be introduced to computers since an early age, so that they could have a chance to compete with the furious emearrence in the future.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
