<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR151*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Swedish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about the musical show "over the rainbow". I recently booked a week's holiday in London to see the musical "over the rainbow" the date was the 9th of June 2000. from your firm.</P>
      <P>It was said that Danny Brook should play the leading part, but there was a different actor instead. This made me really disappointed.</P>
      <P>We arrived at the theatre at 19,00 since the play should start at 19:30 but we had to wait until 20:15 then it started. It was also said that discounts was available but this was wrong, because we couldn't get any discounts.</P>
      <P>The theatre Restaurant that should be open after the show was closed because the chief was ill and there was no food in the fridge.</P>
      <P>This should have been our perfect evening out but it wasn't.</P>
      <P>I am not satisfied with this musical show at all.</P>
      <P>I am therefor writing to ask for a full refund</P>
      <P>I am expecting to receive a cheque for £20.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Anne Svensson</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. How should she manage to keep quiet about this. This was the best thing that ever had happend in years for the Fennall family.</P>
      <P>Pat's sister-in-law was having a baby but she wanted to wait and tell the rest of the family.</P>
      <P>She realised that telling Pat was a very bad idea but now it was done. Pat was so happy the whole day and wanted to tell her mother but Maria told her not to.</P>
      <P>Maria was still a little bit chocked over the naus of having a baby. She and her husband Peter had been trying for so long and now they had succeeded.</P>
      <P>Many weeks went by and Maria and Pat didn't say a word about it.</P>
      <P>The rest of the family understood that something was wrong because Pat started to buy baby clothes. Which was very chooking for her mother.</P>
      <P>One day when they all sat down at the kitchen table for having their lunch Pat said,</P>
      <P>- "Maria and Peter are going to have a baby"!</P>
      <P>The End.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
