<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR152*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>I AM REALLY ENTHUSIASTIC ABOUT THE PRIZE I'VE WON, I'M WRITING TO GIVE YOU THE INFORMATION YOU ASKED ME FOR AND, IF IT'S POSSIBLE, TO HAVE SOME FURTHER DETAILS ABOUT THE CAMP.</P>
      <P>I WOULD PREFER TRAVELLING IN JULY, BECAUSE I HAVE MY EXAMS IN JUNE AND I'VE SIGNED FOR A CONTRACT AS A SHOP ASSISTANT STARTING IN AUGUST.</P>
      <P>SINCE I HAVE THE CHOICE FOR MY ACCOMODATION, I'LL DEFINETELLY GO FOR THE LOG CABINS, BECAUSE I CAN'T BARE THE HEAT INSIDE THE TENT.</P>
      <P>OUT OF THE LIST OF ACTIVITIES GIVEN I'VE CHOSEN GOLF AND PHOTOGRAPHY; GOLF BECAUSE I LOVE THE SPORT ALTHOUGH I DON'T GET TO PLAY IT MUCH (I'M NOT BAD AT IT), AND PHOTOGRAPHY BECAUSE IT'S SOMETHING I'VE ALWAYS LOVED TO LEARN BUT I'VE NEVER HAD THE CHANCE.</P>
      <P>WHAT I WOULD LIKE TO ASK YOU IS ABOUT THE WEATHER CONDITIONS, SO I CAN DECIDE ON WHAT CLOTHES TO TAKE, AND ABOUT COSTS, SO I CAN MAKE A BUDJET FOR THE HOLIDAY.</P>
      <P>YOURS SINCERELY</P>
      <P>Angelo Costa</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>DEAR KIM,</P>
      <P>I'M REALLY GLAD YOU WROTE TO ME TO ASK HOW EVERYTHING HAD GONE AT THE CONCERT; SO I'M GOING TO TELL YOU HOW THINGS WENT.</P>
      <P>MY JOB MAINLY INVOLVED HELPING TO SET THE STAGE AND TO TAKE IT DOWN AFTER THE CONCERT, BUT I ALSO GAVE A HAND BACKSTAGE WHEN NEEDED.</P>
      <P>I WAS PART OF THE STAFF, WE ALL HAD A SPECIAL PASS CARD AND THEY ALSO GAVE US A T-SHIRT AND A CAP (I'VE GOT AN EXTRA ONE FOR YOU); OUR WORK STARTED TWO DAYS BEFORE THE CONCERT, AND I MUST SAY IT WAS REALLY HARD, SPECIALLY BECAUSE WE WORKED UNDER THE SUN, FROM 8.00 A.M TO 8.00P.M. WITH AN HOUR BRAKE FOR LUNCH AND IT WAS THE SAME AFTER THE CONCERT.</P>
      <P>AFTER THE STAGE WAS SET, THE REST OF THE THINGS I HAD TO DO WERE QUITE EASY AND ENJOYABLE; I COULD STAY EITHER BACK OR FRONT STAGE AND GIVE A HAND IF NEEDED, I REALLY ENJOYED IT BECAUSE I LEARNT A LOT OF TECNICAL THINGS I DIDN'T KNOW; AND WHAT I ALSO ENJOYED WAS THE GOOD PAY!</P>
      <P>Lots of love</P>
      <P>Angelo.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
