<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR153*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs. Helen</P>
      <P>I'm writing back to answer the questions that you send me in the past letter, so refering to the question of when I would like to travel, I would like to go anytime during july, because I have to be in august back home, because I need to apply and get everithing sortted out, to go into college next september.</P>
      <P>And according to the question of wich type of accommodation I prefer, I choose a log cabin, because I think that the tent is more messy, so I would appreciate if you give me the cabin. And my answer to the question of wich activities I would like to choose, well I choose swimming cause is my daily excercise and surfing. Anyway I'm not very good doing surfing but with a little bit of help I know I can make it.</P>
      <P>Oh, for last I just would like to ask you how many clothes, and money I have to bring with me. And well Mrs Helen I would really apprecciatte if you send me back a letter with all the answers of my question, anyway.</P>
      <P>Thank you very very much and please keep in contact by e-mail, as normal mail.</P>
      <P>Yours trully</P>
      <P>Alvaro Ramirez</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim:</P>
      <P>I hope you keep in great form, like you were the last time I saw you, how is your family, I hope everyone is ok.</P>
      <P>Well here in Dublin things still the same, but I think somebody told you that I went to the moby concert here at the point wich is the big theatre for events and concerts, I guess it was the best concert I've ever been to, but the coolest thing is that, well do you remember my friend Luke, the one that works as a security guard, well he told me that they needed people to put everything on the stage, so I went to help them and everithing else, and when I get into the point, do you who was there? just imagine, it was moby, so I went to say hello to him, and he told me would you give me a hand with my decks, so I went, and when we finished he gave me a T-shirt and a gold pass to see the concert from the first row, oh my god Kim that the best thing that ever happened to me, well Kim I hope to recieve a letter from you soon, and please tell everybody about the moby concert and everything, thank you.</P>
      <P>See you soon</P>
      <P>love</P>
      <P>Alvaro</P>
      <P>XXXX</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
