<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR154*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I'm writting to you to complain about a theatre play I have seen, called: "Over the rainbow".</P>
      <P>This show was for me very disappointing for many reasons: First of all, I was very surprised by the no presence of the famous actor, Danny Brook, who was one of my reasons to book a sit. Also, I'm unhappy about the bad informations of your advertisement, which clearly says, the play begins at 19.30 instead of 20.15 as my evening' show. At the end of show, unfortunately for me and the others spectators, the worst thing happened: the theatre's restaurant was closed without any reasons and nobody went to us to apologise or advice us for an other restaurant opened late in the night.</P>
      <P>That's why, in return of all those problems, I'm asking you to give back some money. I'm looking forward to have an answer from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully.</P>
      <P>BOUCHER Jean-Pierre.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. That's why all his friends were angry against him and let him alone. It was clear that Pat had to change and show to his friend that they can believe in him thrutly. For those next days, Pat will do his best to be the most sympathic as possible. To beginning, every morning Pat says a pleasant "hello" in adding to that a big smail. His mother always says: "If you are smailing and are nice with the people, the poeple would be nice and would smail to you". As Pat does always what his mother says his friends began to play again with him, but not just his old friends, every body wanted to play with me. The morality of the story is here very clear: be nice with the people and the people will respect you and will appreciate you as a friend.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
