<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR155*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you for the information, that I won the competition. I'll try to answer your questions.</P>
      <P>I would preffer travelling in July, I have only these time, because my summer holidays during these days.</P>
      <P>To your answer about living in tents or cabins, I would like to sleep in a tent. A cabin remember me too much to my home and is too confortable, that isn't what I want to have if I live in a wild area.</P>
      <P>My favourite sports are climbing and surfing, I'm very good at climbing but for surfing I need some practise.</P>
      <P>Yes, I have some questions on clothes, what should I take with me and how much money will I need?</P>
      <P>I hope, I was able to answer your questions and you will perhaps soon give me a reply on my ones.</P>
      <P>Yours, Vadim Titov</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>You can't believe what I did last month. I was given the opportunity to build up the concert and of course I took my chance.</P>
      <P>First I arrived really early in the morning on the place, but the people were just working and I joined them. My duty was to montage the spot lights on the right places, but it wasn't just easy. You had always some problems because like not having enough wire or the lamps were broken by the transport. The experience that I made was, that I had never worked in a such perfect team. I was able to ask anybody, and he answered detailly, althoug he was full of work.</P>
      <P>After the hard work we took cool drinks, sat down on the ground and enjoyed the pop concert. And as the pop stars thanked us for our hard job we all were a little proud to be here.</P>
      <P>Love, Vadim</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
