<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR157*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ryan</P>
      <P>I am writing to reply for your letter about competition.</P>
      <P>First of all I would like to say that I am very happy that I won first prize in your competition.</P>
      <P>Secondly you asked me, when I have time for travel, so I can go only in July, because only in July I have holiday. And I would like to go in the first part of this month, socond part I spend with my familly.</P>
      <P>If you do not mind I would prefer tent, because in tent I will be along.</P>
      <P>While I will be at the Camp I would like sailing, because it is my favorite sport. I am good at it - I am sailing from childhood. The second activities which I would like to do is surfing - I have never do it.</P>
      <P>I would like to know, how much money I must have with me? And what clothes I should take with me.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faitfully</P>
      <P>Aniela Chmielewski</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="5b">
      <P>"The Old Man and the Sea"</P>
      <P>'This is such a marvellous book you will want to read it again'</P>
      <P>In my opininion this book 'The Old Man and the sea' is the best book which Ernest Hemingway had writen.</P>
      <P>Thise book is about men who know that he will die soon, he know that he didn't made his dream coom tru. So he decidet to go for last trip in his life. Hes destenation is get Marlin. He is very old, and he isn't so strong that he should be. He need to rest, but he don't geve up. I the end he make his drems coom tru, he get vast Marlin.</P>
      <P>In thise book Hemingway is trying to tell us, that if we want something, we can get it, it can be deficult and take long time but we can do it. We must believe in our selfs.</P>
      <P>People in our ages should think about this. Sometimes they geve up, befor they get something,</P>
      <P> To sum up I must say that every-one should read this book.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
