<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR158*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>31-40</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Camp California in the U.S.A.</P>
      <P>Competition Organiser</P>
      <P>13th June 2000</P>
      <P>DEAR Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am really happy for receive your congratulations. Was very exciting moment and very nice competition. And now to be the first winner. Is wonderful for me to have the opportunitie to visit the Camp California in the U.S.A.</P>
      <P>In answer at your letter. I would like to travel in July for two reason one's is because I totaly will finish my exam in that date and the other in the first two week I will go to Farnborought is special 10 days the presentation the Air show and will be there the delegation from my country.</P>
      <P>And for the second question. About accommodation during these two weeks at the Camp I would prefer log cabins; because maybe is more interesting to share with other people.</P>
      <P>In other hand you ask me I have the chance for to choose two activities while I am at the camp. but is no easy, because all is very interesting for me. But anyway I like more to have the possibilities for practice climbing and surfing. Meanwhile, these activities are develop. Can you said me if is necessary to bring special clothes, I refer for instance if I practice surfing I need water suit. Is possible to get there? At the same situation for climbing I need special equipment and then there are available in the Camp and what about the guide for these activities? I need extra money?</P>
      <P>I am really appreciate if you can answer me these doubt and saying again. Thanks very much, because is new stimulation for me. this prize.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Isabel Cruz</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>13th June, 2000</P>
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>I think this topic is so exciting in the antropological and psicological point of view, because we can studie the reaction before, during and after to shopping.</P>
      <P>People in general have a compulsory actitud for shopping in my opinion. Because sometimes the article for to buy is not really necessary. We must to accept that media have so important effect in our life in special the T.V.</P>
      <P>For the men and women is important the appearance and they spent a lot of money in buy clothes, cosmetic, accesories, jewels etc. And the other they choose sometimes just for the label. Without give really importance to the calidad in, because people in general they don't spent the time for prepare food and when they shopping they choose pre-prepared food. We know is more easy for these busy life.</P>
      <P>In the other hand the facilities for access to mall center is not good. The area for parking, space for play grown to the children or bus station near the mall is not really appropiate. Otherwise shopping will be more enjoyable.</P>
      <P>I think in the nearly future we need to decide with the goverment. which is special place in the town we lefet just for comerical area, but of course with all the facilities to get there like a big supermarket, and mall centre in different areas of the city.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
