<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR159*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Mr Manager:</P>
      <P>A few days ago I went to London to have a nice holiday. I was expecting to have fun, so I decided to go to the play "Over the Rainbow", thats now presenting in your theatre. I read the advertisement and I thought it was going to be a plesent evening.</P>
      <P>From the beggining it was all a disappointment. When I went to buy the ticket I tried to get a discount with my student card, but that was not posible. I let this pass and I bought it anyway, thinking that was posible that it was only a mistake in your advertisement.</P>
      <P>But the play started fourty-five minutes late, and the star of the show, of whom I'm a great fan an who was the mainly reason of why I decided to see the play, was changed for another actor, how turned out to be really bad.</P>
      <P>You will understand how upseting all this was, and I decided to visit your restaurant, thinking that could save my visit to the theatre, but it was closed and I had to go back to my hotel felling mad an hungry.</P>
      <P>I think you realized why I'm writting this letter to ask you to give my money back. All the thing that were promised in your advertisement were not true, and it was definitly NOT the perfect evening out.</P>
      <P>Specting that you will solve this misunderstanding.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>There's no doubt that modern tecnology has changed our lives, but how?</P>
      <P>I think that some of the changes had been very good, like the impruvement to the medical science, that now can saved millions of persons that one hundred years ago were doomed to die or to live miserable lives.</P>
      <P>It has changed the ways in how people comunicate. First the telegraph and the radio an now TV, the telephone and the Internet allowed people be in contact with others really quickly and distances arent now so difficult of overcome.</P>
      <P>But tecnology had not only changed our lives in a good way, giving us thing that can make our lives more confortable, it had also thing that arent bad, but if they are in the hands of the wrong people they can destroy the world.</P>
      <P>The weapons and the factories are destroing our planet and we need to realized that we have to use tecnology to impruve our lives, but always triying to respect nature.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
