<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR161*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>13.06.2000</P>
      <P>Dear Mrs. Ryan,</P>
      <P>thank you very much for your letter. I am happy that I won the first prize and I am looking forward to travelling to California.</P>
      <P>You have had some questions which I would like to answer now:</P>
      <P>- Time of travelling: According to the vacations and school holidays in Germany I am only able to travel in July. Due to this fact I hope you can arrange it for me.</P>
      <P>- Accomodation: Log cabins would be nice for me to stay in when I am in California. You now that we are not used to living in such high temperatures in Germany as it will be then in California. I suppose I will have more fun if there is a cabin which is air conditioned. If there are only tents available at this time it will not be a problem for me, too.</P>
      <P>- Activities: During my stay I would like to do swimming and surfing. I know it will be hot there and California is famous for its beaches. I am a good swimmer and hope to improve my swimming style, too. On the other side I have no experience in surfing, - I am an absolute beginner with high motivation.</P>
      <P>- Additional question: Could you tell me how much extra money is usually needed for a two week camping?</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to getting further information from you. Greetings from Germany!</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Bruno Aachen</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>"Shopping is not always enjoyable".</P>
      <P>Before we can give our opinions on this statemant we have to make sure that everyone knows what we are discussing about.</P>
      <P>'Shopping' stands for buying goods for your daily requirements, e.g. food, clothes. We do not speak here about luxuary goods.</P>
      <P>In this contest, shopping means a compulsory exercise you have to do regularly and frequently. It is not enjoyable if you look at it as a duty. But if you realize how important it is for your health what you buy you will go shopping with much more consiousness and joy than before. 'Shopping' could be annoying if you look at it as a waste of time because you do it every day. Reorganize your behaviour of shopping and plan to keep food in stock! Try the internet and use e-business and online-shopping to order your pants for example.</P>
      <P>This is even an appropriate way to get around unfriendly service you get to know if you have to buy something in a shop right before closing time. Choose your clothes at home after you have ordered them by e-mail! Another solution to get a friendlier service is of course to go to another shop.</P>
      <P>You have been presented some causes why shopping is not always enjoyable. There are ways of behaviour to make more fun of it. It depends on every individual to change your mind and act as a 'smart' shopper.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
