<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR162*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Madam/Sir,</P>
      <P>I am writing to say I am not satisfied with your musical show.</P>
      <P>Recently I am interested in musical shows, because I have never seen it in my country. When I saw your advertisement for the show, it was so attractive for me. So I went to London to see the show.</P>
      <P>As I arrived there after 5 P.M., I missed the first performance, so I decided to see the 19:30 p.m performance. However it started 20:15! Furthermore there were no student discounts!</P>
      <P>The worst one was that the actor and actress were not the person who had been written in the advertisement, because of that I was extremely disappointed. So, I could not concentrate on the show.</P>
      <P>After the show, when I went to the restaurant it was closed, because it usually opens between afternoon and evening shows.</P>
      <P>It was a really disappointing evening! So I am asking for some money back.</P>
      <P>I look forward to receiving your prompt reply.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Chu Jin-Sun.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed your daily life? It could be difficult to feel how many things has been changed in our daily life. But if you thought 10 years before you can easily notice.</P>
      <P>I would like to see the change in an advantage and a disadvantage view, In an advantage. The modern technology is developing toward convenience for human.</P>
      <P>So, we can be connected other people with a mobile phone no matter where you are and you can correspond to other contry people in real time by using internet. How incredable it is!</P>
      <P>However not only this advantage but also there are lots of disadvantages. Although mobile phone is very useful our life, it might be harmful for our brain because of micro wave it can cause the cancer or traffic accidents. In addition the side effect of artificial farm products also can't be ignored in our daily life.</P>
      <P>So I would like to say the science and techology changed our daily life more convenience it also could be dangerous.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
