<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR164*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Swedish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about your advertisement concerning the Musical show: "Over the rainbow". First of all, according to your advertisement, Danny Brook should be one of the stars, instead there was one for me totally unknown actor. To make matters worse the musical started almost one hour later than it was supposed to start.</P>
      <P>Your advertisement also failed to mention the fact that there was no discounts what so ever and finally, because of a shortage of staf, your restaurant was not available for us.</P>
      <P>This event was not what I call: "a perfect evening out", as your advertisement promised. I feel entitled to compensation for this event. I suggest a refund of the full price and I hope you are willing to take your responsibilities.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Carolina Patharius</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. It didn't take long time until my embarrassing story was out in the open. I asked myself how I could be so stupied, telling her my secret after all I been going through to keep it to myself. But now when the story was out, it was just to start to accept it. Maybe it wasn't so bad after all? All of a sudden I started to believe that this was the best solution of all. Now I didn't need to go around and worring about it anymore. At once I felt more assertive and a big smile appeared in my face. I decieded to thank Pat, and maybe, if possible, teach her a lession.</P>
      <P>That evening I went to her house. I pretended to be totaly miserable. Pat didn't know what to do, she apoligised over and over again and I could really see that she was more than devestated. Finally I smiled. After huging eatch other we promised never to tell others about our secrets. Especially not if it has to do with failing all exams....</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
