<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR165*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Manager</P>
      <P>A few days ago I went to the Circle theatre to see a musical show which it shows in your theatre now. Also it made me very disappoint. There are several reasons that I was not happy about the musical.</P>
      <P>The first one I am going to complaint about is the actor. I could not see Danny Brook during the show. There was an different actor instead of him.</P>
      <P>Secondly, the times, it's available 14.30 and 19.30 so I choose 19.30. However it was deleied it started 20.15. Also I had a student identification card to discount the ticket price but it was unavilable to discount. The theatre restaurant was closed after the show, they said funds are runn out.</P>
      <P>Those are totally unexpectable so I presume that I would like to get paid for my ticket cost. I ask you to transfor money into this account. Barclays bank 1010-10 1234567</P>
      <P>Jon Sun.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed your daily life?</P>
      <P>First of all it's difficult say what exactly modern technology is now but I can say for sure it's keep developing and much better than the past. Think about the conputer, the speed of conputer is much faster than before. I even couldn't imagine our p.c can be that fast.</P>
      <P>Also T.Vs, I guess that I was not able to watch colour T.V if I was born in 1960. T.V colour only consist of white and black.</P>
      <P>Nowdays the technology is keep develop and the better technology gives us easier life.</P>
      <P>Another example, the internet. This is revolution which has changed our daily life.</P>
      <P>You can have a shopping on the internet and it might the fastest way to gather any information you would like to search.</P>
      <P>However it also can make our life very lazy. This is one other important thing to remember.</P>
      <P>People who have their car, they don't attempt to walk on foot even if it is short distance.</P>
      <P>The improvement of technology can makes our life easy and in the other way it also can makes our life lazy.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
