<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR168*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>DEAR SIR,</P>
      <P>I AM WRITING TO COMPLAIN ABOUT A MUSICAL SHOW THAT IS TAKING PART IN THE CIRCLE THEATRE. I WAS WORRIED WHEN I SAW THE ADVERTISEMENT OF THE PLAY IN A NEWSPAPER ON SUNDAY.</P>
      <P>THE FIRST PROBLEM WAS WHEN I READ THE STARRING. IT SAID: 'DANNY BROOK'. BUT, WHEN I WAS WATCHING THE PLAY, I REALISED THAT THERE WAS A DIFFERENT ACTOR AND, REALLY, I WAS DISAPPOINTED. ANOTHER PROBLEM WAS THE TIME THAT I HAD TO WAIT. I THOUGHT IT WILL BE AT 19.30 AND I HAVE BEEN WAITING FOR FORTY FIVE MINUTES!! BESIDES THIS, I COULD NOT VISIT THE RESTAURANT IN THE THEATRE BECAUSE IT WAS CLOSED. IN ADITION TO THIS, I DID NOT HAVE ANY DISCOUNT IN MY TICKET. SO, I HAD TO PAY A LOT OF MONEY TO SEE A PLAY THAT WAS A COMPLETELY DISASTER.</P>
      <P>TO SUM UP, I DID NOT SPEND A PERFECT EVENING. I THINK THAT IT WAS THE WORST I HAVE EVER HAD. ON THE WHOLE, I WOULD LIKE TO HAVE MY MONEY BACK.</P>
      <P>YOURS FAITHFULLY</P>
      <P>MANUELA BELABARA</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>JUST BE YOURSELF</P>
      <P>IN, THE FUTURE, PEOPLE WILL BE WEARING FASHIONABLE CLOTHES LIKE NOW. PEOPLE WILL BE VERY WORRIED ABOUT WHAT THEY WEAR.</P>
      <P>ONE THE ONE HAND, THERE WILL BE PEOPLE WHO WOULD WEAR FASHIONABLE CLOTHES. THIS PEOPLE WILL BE WORRIED ABOUT WHAT THEY LOOK LIKE. ON THE OTHER HAND, THERE WILL BE LESS PEOPLE WHO WOULD WEAR WHATEVER THEY LIKE.</P>
      <P>NOWADAYS, PEOPLE SEEM TO BE ALWAYS WORRIED. ALL THE TIME THEY ARE ASKING, WHAT ARE THEY LOOKING LIKE AND THEY WASTE A LOT OF MONEY IN CLOTHES.</P>
      <P>ON THE WHOLE, CLOTHES WILL HAVE NO CHANGE. IN MY OPINION, PEOPLE WILL GIVE IMPORTANCE TO HOW THEIR PERSONALITY DEVELOP AND THEY WILL GIVE UP WORRYING ABOUT WHAT THEY WEAR. THEY WILL HAVE ENOUGH MONEY TO BUY WHAT THEY NEED AND TO BE HAPPY WITH IT.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
