<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR169*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan:</P>
      <P>I am writing to answer to the questions I have been asked in your previous letter. I have decided I would like to visit Camp California only in July because I have already organized an other trip for the month of august.</P>
      <P>I would rather prefer sleeping in log cabins if its possible because I have back problems and I am not allowed to sleep on the ground.</P>
      <P>I have also chosen as activities the ones of Golf and tennis. I am rather good at these sports because I have practised them since I was a little girl. I am better at tennis that at golf but anyway I have experience in both these sports.</P>
      <P>I have also several simple questions. I would like to know how much money I have to take and what type of clothes I need. Do I have to take with me my tennis raquet and my golf bag? I would be very thankful to recieve answers to my questions. thank you.</P>
      <P>yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim:</P>
      <P>How are you? I'm fine. I finish school next week. I have to tell you all about the pop concert I helped to organize last month. it was really cool. I got the chance to meet Ricky Martin. Boy, He's really really handsom!</P>
      <P>I was in charge of the lights of the stage, you know, all those colourful lights that go all around the stage. It was hard work because I have been practising for several weeks. I had to learn what part of the stage had to be lightened with a blue light or a green one. Even though I ended terribly tired I really enjoyed myself.</P>
      <P>It was a strange experience because its something new for me. I had never even gone to a concert before. I even got the chance to take some photographs of ricky Martin with my sister and I've got one photo of him with me!!</P>
      <P>Well, its an experience I'll never forget as long as I live. Write to me as soon as possible, please!</P>
      <P>yours friend,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
