<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR170*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>31-40</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I am writing to your to complain about the musical show called "Over the rainbow"</P>
      <P>As a matter of fact, I waited for seeing Danny Brook who I appreciate a lot and I was very disappointed that he wasn't here. Besides, the actor who filled him in was unknown and specially boring.</P>
      <P>Secondly, the show had to begin at 19.30 pm, in fact he began at 20.15 pm and that without any explainations!</P>
      <P>Your advertisement mentioned that discounts were available, however when I asked for them to the staff they replied to me that they weren't discounts!</P>
      <P>After the show, I wanted to visit your restaurant and once again, I was disappointed because it was closed. Anybody could explain to me why!</P>
      <P>I can assure you that it wasn't a perfect evening out and I got very annoyed about this evening which could have been wonderful.</P>
      <P>That is the reason I would like you to refund my money. I hope you would take notice of this complaint seriously. I am looking forward to hearing from you as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>My daily life changed in some ways when I got the hand of using new technologies.</P>
      <P>When I started work, I wrote everything I made on sheets and if sometimes I made mistakes, I had to cross out and it wasn't very well-made. I had to work out all my figures two times to make sure that my accounts were accurate.</P>
      <P>Now, I enter datas and I don't need any more to calculate my figures, the work is completely made by the computer and in addition there is no mistake.</P>
      <P>If I have to find out timetables, it is very useful to have the possibility to see on the Internet, besides, it is the quickest way! At the beginning, I wasted a lot of time getting some information I needed because I didn't know exactly where I had to look for. But after a while you gain experience and you get soon used to this kind of research.</P>
      <P>Another thing that has changed my daily life is the mobil phone. As a matter of fact, if I am stuck in my car in the traffic, I can call my boyfriend to tell him that I would be late. Once, I saw an accident and I could call the police. Sometimes the ring is annoying but finally, the mobil phone is a great handy object.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
