<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR171*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about the musical show "Over the Rainbow", that I went to see on the 16th of June.</P>
      <P>Firstly, the actor suppossed to be Danny Brook, but he was not, it was another actor, who I have never seen before, so, as you can imagen, I was very disappointed.</P>
      <P>Another complain is about the time that the musical show started, the advertisement said it started at 19:30, but it did not, we had to wait 45 minutes. It was terrible.</P>
      <P>Now, about the tickets, the were different prices but there were not discounts, and because of this, many people could not see the show, especially students.</P>
      <P>Finally, when the musical show finished, and I have to say, a bit late, I went to the theatre's restaurant to eat something but this place was closed because the chef had already gone.</P>
      <P>At is explain it was not the perfect evening that I expected to have and I would like to have my money back because of the reasons that I mentioned before.</P>
      <P>Looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Pat, Maria's best friend</P>
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets, so Maria was very disappointed when she realised that Manuel knew the truth about the feelings that Maria had for him, in fact, she was so angry she almost kill but, she couldn't because Pat was her best friend.</P>
      <P>Maria talked to Pat about the stupid thing that she did, but Pat refused to apologaising to her, because she felt it wasn't a mistake and she did it for only one reason: help Maria to get the man that she loved. Maria was speechless, it was the first time that she didn't know what to do, so she decided to stop talking to Pat.</P>
      <P>After 3 weeks, Maria got ill so she was not available to go to school. Some friends phoned her everyday, except Pat, the only friend that Maria really loved, despite that, she was not sad. One day, when Maria was seating in her bedroom, someone knock the door, it was Manuel, he was worried for her. Maria was nervous, but for the first time, she could talk to him as she never did before, and at the end of the day, she was the happiest person of the world, she gave her first kiss and she had Pat's friendship back, after all, everything happened because of her.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
