<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR174*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs. Ryan,</P>
      <P>I'm writing you replying to your letter asking for some more information about me, to give you all the information you need.</P>
      <P>First of all you asked when would I be able to travel. You ought to know that is possible to me to go there only in July because I'm going to work the whole August.</P>
      <P>Answering the second question I would prefer my accomodation in log cabins. The reason is that, in my opinion, they are more comfortable, there's more space and in addition they are warmer.</P>
      <P>Providing that you give me the chance to chose two activities I would love to do swimming and singing. I attend to swimming and singing classes twice a week so I'm really good at both.</P>
      <P>Finally I would like to ask you about clothes and money. Where will we be able to wash our clothes during the camp? Are we allowed to carry with all the money we wish to?</P>
      <P>Don't hesitate to contact me for any more question.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Angeles.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Nowadays shopping is considered one of the most usual and enjoyable activities, especially if you are a woman and you are out to buy clothes. At first sight it is, but shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>Basing my opinion on my experience I'm going to talk mostly about clothes shopping. There are some points that give me the reason.</P>
      <P>First of all, who is your companion? If you take mum shopping the right day she has been all day doing housework, that will probably end in discussion.</P>
      <P>In one hand, there's you. You are feeling sick, angry with your boyfriend. How do you pretend to see in a mirror that anything fits well on you?</P>
      <P>In the other, you have always to count on unfriendly shop assistants, no size for you or too high prices.</P>
      <P>Who would talk now about enjoyable shopping journeys? I'm sure there would be plenty of people ready to do it.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
