<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR175*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Sir manager</P>
      <P>Yesterday I went to "The Circle Theatre" to see the musical show "OVER THE RAINBOW". I'm very disappointed of this evening. The first thing was, that it started 45 minutes late. And when it finaly started, there wasn't Danny Brook who plaied. There was a different actor and he was really bad. You should have informed us before that you've changed the actor. On the advertisement you wrote that discounts are available but they weren't. After the show I wanted to drink somthing in your theatre restaurant but when I arrived it was closed because the show started to late! I'm so disappointed! I wanted to have a pleasant evening while I'm here in London for a week's holiday. So I ask you sincearly for my money back becaus it wasn't a perfect evening out.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. I told her that my parents are getting divorsed and that I will move to Chicago with my mother. We are together in High School in California and this is our last year. We wanted to study biology here in Los Angeles with some other friends but now my plans have changed and I have to leave them.</P>
      <P>One day, Pat and I were going home, when she asked me, if I will give a party befor I'll go. I had to tell her that I don't have the time to organise anything becaus we, my mother and I, have to get our stuff ready to move. She wasn't very surprised and soon I've forgotten her question. The year was getting to the end. On Monday in our last week Pat asked me if I want to eat supper at her house. I thought it was a good idea and we went home. But when we get into the hous ther were all my friends! We had a great evening becaus Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
