<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR177*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Helen Ryan:</P>
      <P>I have just received your letter telling me I have won the first prize in your competition, and I am glad for it. I am writting to give the information you asked me and also I would like to required some information about the prize.</P>
      <P>First of all I would let you know I could travel only on July because it is the time that I have holidays from my school. Furthermore I would like to choose for accomodation tents instead of cabins because I think could be more exciting and more contact with the enveiroment.</P>
      <P>Also I would like to response for the activities I had to choose from your list: I would prefer painting and photography because for the others sports I am not healthy at the moment, and I consider I used to do painting and photography very good at the school.</P>
      <P>Finally I would like to ask if I need a special clothes and Do I need money? How much?</P>
      <P>Please if you require extra information do not hesitate to contact me.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim: I am sorry, I haven't written you soon but I still excited for the experience I had helping Will Smith on the freeway the last month. Anyway now I am going to tell you everything about it.</P>
      <P>As you know I have always taken the freeway on Sundays to go to my grandparents' house, but that Sunday I was driving when suddenly I saw in the lay-by one excellent car. It was a Jaguar with Will Smith on it, I stopped and I was going to ask if he needed some help and he said "of course".</P>
      <P>He had a puncture wheel and he didn't know how to repeared then I chanced the wheel and during this time he was asking me for my hobbies, studies, everything. He was really kind and friendly but really what I really most enjoyed of it, was when he invited me this night for a drink in the most luxury pub I have ever been. Could you believe my luck?</P>
      <P>All right that's about all my news, then writte soon and tell me about you.</P>
      <P>Lots of love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
