<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR178*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms Helen</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your letter letting me know that I have won your first prize.</P>
      <P>I am writting to you in order to give you some details you asked me for in your letter.</P>
      <P>First of all, I need to tell you that it is only possible for me to travel in July, because I am going to move to Spain in August.</P>
      <P>About my accommodation prefers, I would really like to be in a tent. Everytime I travel around, I sleep in nice rooms with nice beds; that is why I think it is a good option to sleep in sleep-bags.</P>
      <P>From the activities I can choose to do in these two weeks, I would enjoy playing basketball and climbing. I think it would be funny to play basketball after five years; and since I go out to the mountains once a month, I don't think I would have any problem with climbing.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask you some questions: Could you tell me what kind of clothes would be addecuate for these two weeks? How much money do you think I should bring with me?</P>
      <P>Thank you once again for your attention and interest.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Gloria Ortega</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim</P>
      <P>You are going to be jealous when you hear this.</P>
      <P>As I told you in my last letter, I worked two weeks ago in Edinburgh helping at a pop concert. The pop group were all young people (between 23 - 30 years old), and all of them were really nice.</P>
      <P>Our main tasks during those three days (I worked with 10 other young people), consisted in carrying music instruments and loudspeakers, checking the lights and microphones, cleaning everything,...</P>
      <P>The job was hard, but from my point of view, it was worthful. I have learned lots of things, earned some money for the summer, and the most important thing: I have had fun.</P>
      <P>Every five working hours, we had thirty-minutes break to eat something. We also had time to tell jokes and play with water balloons.</P>
      <P>The most exhiting thing was when we removed all the stuff the day after the concert, and we went to the Highlands to spend the whole day. That was fantactic! If you have never been there, I enormous recemmend you to go. Even I played the drums there!</P>
      <P>I hope your exams are doing well, and you write me back when you finish them.</P>
      <P>Lots of love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
