<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR179*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. (...),</P>
      <P>My name is... Two weeks ago my family and I visited London. During our stay we saw a bright advertisement of your theatre and decided to see this newest and best musical show (as it was said in you advertisement). Actually. I must say that our perfect evening wasn't out!</P>
      <P>In your ad was said that in main roles would be Danny Brook and Tina Truelove. Danny wasn't there! Instead there was a different actor whose play was disappointing.</P>
      <P>The show had to begin at 19.30, but indeed it started at 20.15 and we had to wait for 45 minutes in a great noise.</P>
      <P>Some words about tickets: you ad noticed that discounts were available so we didn't have money with us. When we came the administration of the theatre said that discounts are not available.</P>
      <P>Finally, when we decided to visit your theatre restaurant after the show it was closed (all the staff went home because the show lasted 45 minutes longer).</P>
      <P>For all these reasons I would like you to give me at least half of my money back.</P>
      <P>With hope for a mutual agreement, Mrs. (...).</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. It was May, 15 - our english teacher's birthday. Marion was our favourite school teacher and we decided to make a surprise for her.</P>
      <P>Month ago we began to prepare for this day and we all agreed to keep it in a secret. We have been discussing for a long time what to present her. There were a lot of proposals from the students: one proposed a vase, another - a good pen (he said it would be useful for the teacher). But we decided to buy a picture, because she has always told us about art galleries with a great exitement.</P>
      <P>We have chosen the best one with a beautiful nature in it.</P>
      <P>We also decided to arrange a party on her birthday (and it had to be a surprise too).</P>
      <P>A day before her birthday we had an English lesson, and after the lesson Pat came up to Marion and told her about our surprise. He was bad-tempered and envious and he didn't want everything to be all right, and besides he didn't like Marion. That's why he disappointed Marion and us.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
