<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR180*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear the manager</P>
      <P>My name is Sally Smith. I went to see a musical show last Wednesday. I had a very disappointing evening.</P>
      <P>In the advertisement you said "Danny Brook" is the actor but it wasn't. It was somebody else. I went to see the show because I like Danny Brook. The person that played instead of Denny was not very good.</P>
      <P>The show supposted to start at 19.30 pm but it started at 20.15 pm. It was very late. We had to wait nearly an hour. Staff did not tell us why it started late.</P>
      <P>When I bought tickets, they did not discount at all. I asked them about discounts because I saw in the advertisement.</P>
      <P>They ignored me. We bought tickets without discount. I don't know that they discount for somebody else or not.</P>
      <P>After the show we went to the theatre restaurant but it closed. It closed at 11 pm. It was not our fault that we went in after 11 pm. The show finished late. The restaurant should open until the show finish.</P>
      <P>It was not a perfect evening at all. Could I please have my money back? It was £60 for tickets. I was very disappointed about this. I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sinecerely</P>
      <P>Sally. Smith.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. She is one of my friend at school. She is very nice, clever, polite and friendly. Everybody love her. If you have any problems, she can give you some suggestion. If you want her to keep it secrets, do not tell her. She is not keeping secrets. This is her bad point. She always tells someone else about it.</P>
      <P>Last week, Tim told Pat about his serious problem. He wanted Pat to keep it between them but Pat did not keep his promise. She told us about it. When Tim found out that we knew his problem and tried to help him. He was very angry with Pat. He wasn't talk to Pat at all. Basically, Tim did not know that Pat was not very good at keeping secrets.</P>
      <P>She did not know when she can speak or not speak. We so worry about her in the future. She has not a lot of friend because of this point.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
