<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR182*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>I am shocked that I won first prize in this competition. It will be a great adventure to visit Camp California.</P>
      <P>I am writing to inform you that I would like to travel in July. The reason is that I am a full-time student on Cracow University and I have many exams at the end of semester, which is in June. I hope that it is not a problem.</P>
      <P>I would like you to know that I prefer a tent. I think it is much better than a log cabin. Aspecially in the summer when tempereture and humidity are very high.</P>
      <P>From the list of all activities I have choosen photography and golf. Since secondary school I am very interested in taking pictures and I have a big experience in it. I have choosen golf because I have never played in this game.</P>
      <P>Please, send me any information of what should I take with me. Should I bring my camera, warm clothes or any pocket money? I am waiting for your reply.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Rafael Szymanski</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim</P>
      <P>Thank you for your latest letter. It was really very nice. I know that you're waiting for any information about a concert. Here it comes...</P>
      <P>My friend offered me a job as a member of techical staff on Sting's concert. I love his music and I collect his albums so I was very happy that I helped his crew.</P>
      <P>Our job was to prepare the scene. We've built it using ready metal and wodden parts. It was really big and impressive. Then we had to plug all electric instruments, speakers, lights and microphones. I was working with a specialist who had to connect all lights together to one computer and prepare a colorful show. It was a totally new experience for me and a real pleasure of working with professionalists.</P>
      <P>It was a hard and complicated job but we all had a lot of satisfaction during the concert. Even Mr. Sting came to us to thank for our help.</P>
      <P>I hope that you liked my story. Send me your opinion about that.</P>
      <P>I wish to see your letter soon</P>
      <P>Rafael</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
