<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR184*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear: Jane Clark</P>
      <P>I had been your annual international art festival. Most of the events I went to were good, but I feel that the festival could be even better next year. So, I write some of my opionions and suggestions to you. I hope it's may help for next year's festival.</P>
      <P>The idea of "International Art Festival" was great. But I feel the word of "International" was not really suit; because you just only got six countrie's stars and artists came. I think you should invite more than ten countries. The other problem was choosing space. Like the hall of classical concert was too small and crowded. Next year, you should calulate or examine how many people come before you choose a hall, which I feel very good was plays and films. It can show more for next year's festival. The Dance Shows as well. And the offer of "weedend ticket" was an excellent idea. Because the price was cheaper than buysperateconvience.</P>
      <P>Look forward for next year's festival.</P>
      <P>Yours Sinicerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>One day, a little girls called Sara. She was walking over a bridge. Suddenly, she heart a men voice called her "Sara...Sara.. look down to the river." Then Sara looked down the river. She was very scared. Because she saw a golden fish was smiling at her and talking to her. After a few second, Sara felt that golden fish was lovely. She never seen any fish had that wonderful colour and can talk with her. Because Sara hasn't got any bother and sister, and her Mon and Dad need work everyday, so she was very lonely.</P>
      <P>Therefore, she came river everyday and talk everything to the golden fish. They were very close friend. After half year, golden fish suddenly disappear. Sara was very sad. She sat and cry on the river. Then somebody called her name "Sara... Sara.. look at me.. I'm stand on your left hand side. Sara remembered the was golden fish. She suddenly become a human, a little boy. After a few day they got married. Both together had their wonderful life.</P>
      <P>This story happened a long time ago.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
