<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR185*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Jane Clark,</P>
      <P>I am writing about International Arts Festival which I went to recently. I had a great time there because taking a place the kind of festival in my town is very unusual. I think that International Arts Festival was absolutely fantastic and successful. I was also pleased with the weekend ticket because I tend to go out in the weekend due to my work in the weekday so that I had time to go and did not have to care about the ticket price.</P>
      <P>In spite of having a great time, there were some things I would like to give you my opinion about. Firstly, there was a few stars and artists from only six countries although the advertisement mention that stars and artists would come from around the world. Secondly, some concerts took a place in really small halls. I suggest that concerts should be held in bigger halls than this year's in next year. Therefore, there will be more people coming the concerts. Finally, food shops should be added in this festival in next year because only plays and films were not atrractiveenought.</P>
      <P>I would be grateful if you could consider my opinion above,</P>
      <P>Yours sencirely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Karrie,</P>
      <P>Hello. How are you doing? I've been also considering rules at home with my friends. Isn't it quite interesting to talk about rules? At home I'm not allowed to talk on the phone more than ten minutes, which annoys me very much. I really want to change this. However, I can go out wheneve I want, even in the mid-night. I'm also allowed to come home anytime so that I can chat with my friends for a long time instead of talking on the phone at home.</P>
      <P>There is a lot of rules at my school. Firstly, we're allowed to drive a car to school, which is quite unusual rule in Japanese school because students might crash a car on the way to school or home. I actually love this rule because I don't have to get up early if I have a car. Secoundly, boys are not allowed to have long hire. They have to cut their hair once a month. Girls can't make up on at school at all. I want to at least put lip coluor on. I wish I could change this rule.</P>
      <P>I'll be grade if you let me know about your rules at school and at home. I'm looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Best wishes.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
