<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR189*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Clark,</P>
      <P>I am writing to express my enjoyment that I had at the International Arts Festival the next week.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I want to say that this festival is really good and I hope it will have every year. Furthermore, the attractions were beautiful such as shows, exhibitions and concerts. I liked all the different kind of atmosphere.</P>
      <P>Also, for all these attractions, the price was low and it is important for the big family.</P>
      <P>Secondly, the plays and movies were marvellous. However, I was disappointed by the number of that. It will be great if there were would have more choice the next year. I would like to give you a suggestion about the space in the concert rooms. Considering the crowded, it should have more rooms. Finally, I will be interested in meet artists from everywhere in the world not only Europeen artists.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, I had an unforgetable time. I would like to eat some different kind of foods, if it is possible.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Your sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Monique,</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your letter, I'm very happy to receive some news about you. I'm going to reply at your question.</P>
      <P>In fact, at school we haven't so many rules. So, we aren't allowed to smoke inside - and eat in the classroom. We have to wash the board when it's our turn. Of course, we must respect the teacher and do what he says.</P>
      <P>What about the rules at home? I can't remember, because now I'm 19, then I can do what I want. I know that I had to ask at my Mum or Dad for going by my friend after the lessons. They wanted that I did my homework before to play. Also, I had to come back at home on time, it was very important for my parents. I want to change nothing, I was happy.</P>
      <P>Anyway, it was a great time when I was a child. It's all for now.</P>
      <P>See you soon, bye</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
