<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR780*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madame,</P>
      <P>I was on week's holiday in London and I went there to the theatre to see "Over The Rainbow". I must say that your musical show was very disappointing for me.</P>
      <P>"Over The Rainbow" was looking very interesting on your advertisement but organisation and play was almost terrible.</P>
      <P>First of all I expected to see Danny Brook, but I saw different actor and that was big disappointment for me.</P>
      <P>Secondly the show started at quarter past eight. This is fourty-five minutes delay.</P>
      <P>Moreover there was not any discounts and all of the tickets had the same prizes.</P>
      <P>Out the end your theatre restaurant was closed from unknown reasons, but on an advertisement was clearly sign:</P>
      <P>"Visit our theatre restaurant after the show". That was cruel, because I was very haungry after the show.</P>
      <P>At the end of this letter I would like to ask if you can refund my money. I will be very pleased if so. I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfuly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Twentieth century was a century of inventions. Some of them are big and some of theme are small, but they effect our lives in the same way. Technology maked our life different than life of people for example living in nineteenth century.</P>
      <P>Modern technology makes our lives different, maybe better. Often people do not see how it effects our life style. Useful things like TV sets, radios, computers, Hi-Fi stereos and cars - we are dealing with them every day. They help us with daily life and make it more pleasant. Transport and communication without cars, trains, planes and telephones will not exist. We know our world from TV screens and computer monitors. Without these, and newspapers of course knowing our world could be hard. On the second hand people are suffering from modern diseases like addiction to television or computers. On the end we must mention modern medicine. It saves our lives from ancient and modern diseases.</P>
      <P>To sum up modern technology changed our daily life. Mine too. I think that I could not live normal life without these inventions. They are like air I breath. I am questioning myselfs - am I sick man?</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
