<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR190*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>I would like to know some informations about the advertisement of the show.</P>
      <P>First of all, why the show began at 20:15, not at 19:30 as indicated in the advertisement. I waited quite one hour to see the show, and what happened with the actor? I came to that show only for see him and when the actor appear, it was another one. There is more! Where were the discounts that I should have earned? I was very disappointed with that! After the show my sun wanted to eat some biscuits and when I see the restaurant closed, I gave up, I told to my sun that we'll never come back here again.</P>
      <P>The restaurant was closed because there wasn't electricity you should close the theatre untill the restaurant get appropriate to use. I was totaly unsatisfied with the theatre and I would like to have my money back if it's possible.</P>
      <P>I thank you for read my letter, I hope you write for me back, and don't forget my money!</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>I am writing what I think what kind of clothes will people wear 100 years from now.</P>
      <P>As we see the clothes are changing every hour. People inventing new kinds of clothes and people buying and wearing differents clothes. It is difficult to say how people will be wearing clothes 100 years from now.</P>
      <P>In each country, each people wear differents kinds of clothes, like, people in Brazil wear shorts, T-shirts or only without them, in Saudi Arabian they wear strange clothes, if you analyse the point of view who doesn't live in Saudi Arabia. I'm quite sure that people in all world will be wearing very differents clothes in the future because, especialy women, like to be very elegant and beautiful will create and invent all kinds of clothes to anybody and that's it.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
