<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR192*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms. Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your letter regarding my prize that I won in your competition. It was a very pleasant surprise to win a trip to California and I very much appreciate it.</P>
      <P>I am writing this as a reply for you request to provide you with some information about my preferencies.</P>
      <P>First off all I'll prefer to travel in July, because it is the only month I have free. I'll have to pass several exams in June, in August my family going to visit our relatives in Austria.</P>
      <P>I am not so keen about accomotation but would rather stay in tents than cabins. It is much more fun and you can really enjoy nature and a company of your friends.</P>
      <P>It is great I can do something I really like at the Camp. I am really enjoying swimming. We live near the sea shore and swimming is the sport activitie I am really good in. Far the best swimmer in my school. The other subject is photography. I like taking pictures and want to share my interest with the others. I am not a photographer but my family think that my photos are more then just good.</P>
      <P>Finally I want to ask you some questions. What will be better to take with me, what I'll need at Camp? How much money should I take, will it be any guided tours? And how many will be in Camp in July?</P>
      <P>Hope to hear from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>My best friend is crazy about shopping. She will prefer shopping to everything else. She thinks that it is the most pleasant spending of time, when you going from one shop to another, watching other people, looking at beautiful clothes, getting some fashionable ideas. Somitimes I feel very sorry for her. It seems that going shopping is a sense of living. And it's so many people like her. Lots of families planing a day out to go to a shopping center, and it is a normal routine for them - to spent the all day just shopping. Not so many people thinking about going fishing or playing sport games with their families any more. They forgot how beautiful could be the countryside, and only tourists you can meet in the castles or museums.</P>
      <P>People are normally angry after shopping - because it is so easy to get tied. People are not smiling to each other, not talking to each other at the shops. They look like a robotes who have to do their duties - to buy.</P>
      <P>In my opinion shopping is just to cover our basic needs. Shops are not for spending our lifes. Try to give up shopping one day and try to spend your day with friends going to play something together. It feels much more better. You'll have happy memories and a good mood.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
