<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR193*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms Ryan</P>
      <P>I'm so happy to received your letter, and I want to tell you the information you need. I would like the travel start only july if possible, because this is my Hoilday, at the Camp California I would like my accommodation in tents, because I work in Army and in the camp I usually stay in tent at night, so I will feel more comfortable. In those activities I would like to choose Swimming and climbing for my activities in Camp, this two activities I usually do in the Army Camp, I know how to climb up on Rachiat outside and help other people to climp. Swimming I'm teach people in Army. And I have a question to ask? In the Camp do I need any money to bring with and what kind of clothes I have to wear and take?</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>To make a daily life video in school, we should concentrat on the most things we do in a school, the most thing we do in a school is haveing lesson, it is a very useful parts of this video and is the main subject. The lessons we take in the video, should be the main subject we study. In the video I think we should take part to talk about, what we doing in feel time and study period. This is another important part of our school life, and we should make a section to talk about lunch and where are the people go to eat their lunch or what they do? After we talk about lunch, we should take about activities we are doing and the systems about the activities in school or outside school and makeofSchool. At the end of the video, we should find one or two studen sit together and ask them a few question of how do they feel to study in the School? this is the suggestion to making a daily life video in school.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
