<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR194*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Jane Clark</P>
      <P>I am writing to tell you about the festival in this time and I would like to suggest you three things for next festival.</P>
      <P>First of all, it is great idea to have a this kind of festival. I enjoyed it so much. But, there are three things which I would like to tell you. Firstly. There were stars and artists from only six countries. I supposed to see quite various nationality. Secondly, I actually liked Jazz, rock and classical concerts very much. However, some concert halls were too small for the many people so we couldn't have a enough space. thirdly. I would like to you to consider about having more plays and films next year. It would be nicer.</P>
      <P>Otherwise, the price was really reasonable for all:events the weekend. I was satisfied with that.</P>
      <P>And if there was musical event. It would be greatful. I hope the next one will be better. And I would like to thank you about making this festival.</P>
      <P>I look forward to next festival very much.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Lula</P>
      <P>Hello. How are you doing? I hope you're well. It's nice to hear about your class. It's quite interesting.</P>
      <P>Let me tell you some rules at school in my country. Actually. We have quite strict rules. When I was a student, I wasn't allowed to wear any fashionable clothes. Only It was like a formal clothes. And we couldn't wear any colorful clothes and socks. Also our hair style was the same as everyone. It's really strict.</P>
      <P>At home. There is one thing I'd like to change. I'm not allowed to sleep at my friend's house. I really like chatting all night with my friends. But I can't it. I'm pursuading my mum, perhaps. The school rules in my country are more strict than your country.</P>
      <P>Anyway. If you want to know about something of our country. I'm glad to tell you more.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to getting your letter soon.</P>
      <P>Thank you. Take care of yourself.</P>
      <P>Loves,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
