<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR196*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Clark,</P>
      <P>I am writing in response to your advertisment in Today's newspaper. I recently spent two days at the International arts festival and I found it very entertaining. It was really a good idea to organize a festival containing such different shows.</P>
      <P>The idea that I prefered the most was to suggest a reasonably-priced weekend ticket for all events because a lot of student or unemployed people could not afford to pay too much money.</P>
      <P>I went to see a classical concert and, although the music played was excellent, he concert hall was too small. Furthermore, I had expected stars and artists from around the world, but they came from only six countries.</P>
      <P>A friend of mine went to see the play "Hamlet" and the film "Gladiators". He told me how great it was and I was thinking that it would be a good to have more plays and films next year. In addition to this, I was wondering if you could organize the same festival in sommer.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you in the near future.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerly,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Two sisters, Alex and Daniela were sitting in front of the fireplace thinking of what they could do. That year, the winter in France was very cold. It was near Christmas and the two girls hadn't found any present for their mother. Offering Christmas presents was a tradition not be forgotten and only four days left. Alex suggested that it would be a good idea to go to the city to buy that present. Daniela agreed but she knew that it was snowing and that it was dangerous to walk with this kind of weather. Anyway, Alex was too stubborn to give up and it was like talking to a brick wall: she didn't listen to her sister.</P>
      <P>After forty minutes, the weather became very bad. It was such a pain to walk in the snow. However, Alex was not worried at all despite the fact that her sister was tired and cold. In deep of herself, Alex knew they were lost in the middle of nowhere, but she didn't want to admit it.</P>
      <P>Unfortuneatly, Daniela fainted. She was so cold that she couldn't move her legs. Alex began to cry and to pray and when Daniela was about to die an angle appeared. He asked Alex if it was more important to bring back a present at home or to save her sister. The answer was obvious and the angel saved Daniela.. This story happend a long time ago.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
