<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR198*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Brown,</P>
      <P>My name is Anne Singler and I have already watched the musical "Over the rainbow" in the Circle Theatre. I'm writing to you because I wasn't pleased with the show! In your advert for the musical show you promised the newest and best musical show, but it wasn't. First I was very disappointed about the price of the ticket because I expected to pay a smaller pice than £20 for my six year old daughter. Then the show already started at 20:15 and not at 19:30! I was quite bored, sitting in my chair and waiting for the beginning of the show.</P>
      <P>For me the most disappointing problem was that the starring Danny Brook wasn't there. My husband was also looking forward to seeing Mr. Brook as an actor of your musical because he is one of his greatest fans. The actor which acted instead of Danny Brook wasn't as good as Mr. Brook.</P>
      <P>After the show, which wasn't really the best I have ever seen, my family and I wanted to get some snacks in the theatre restaurant. When we arrived at the restaurant we had to realize that it was closed because the cook was ill. After this last point of troubles we went home with only bad remembers of this evening.</P>
      <P>So I want to ask you for giving me my money back because I think I have better spent my money on anything else.</P>
      <P>I hope you understand my point of view and write back.</P>
      <P>Yours,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>The secret</P>
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets.</P>
      <P>One day her best friend Sally told her that she had betrayed her boyfriend. Pat was really shocked to hear this but she had to promise Sally to keep quiet. Pat really liked chatting about others and so she wasn't able to keep quiet about Sally's secret. She told it to her boyfriend Paul. After that Paul got white in his face, he was pale like a wall and it seemed as he would be very nervous. Pat couldn't understand Paul's reaction and so she didn't care about it.</P>
      <P>Some weeks later when Pat was walking to school she met Sally, which just came out of Paul's house. Now Pat realized what was going on and could undstand why her boyfriend got so nervous about the secret. He was Sally's lover!</P>
      <P>In this moment Pat wished that she never would have been keen on knowing secrets!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
