<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR200*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Jane Clark,</P>
      <P>I am writing with reference to the International Arts Festival I have recently been to and I would like to give you my opinions about it.</P>
      <P>According to the title of the advertisement, which was a great idea, there were stars and artists from around the world; but they were only from six countries.</P>
      <P>In addition to this some concert halls were too small to host all the people who were there fro the occasion and, personally speaking the show could be done at the open air next year, so that music would also create a fantastic atmosphere all around.</P>
      <P>Plays and films had a great success and I would like to ask if there will be more next year because in my opinion people would appreciate it.</P>
      <P>The other events I went to, dance shows, art exhibitions and talk by writers, were well organised and extremely interesting.</P>
      <P>Furthermore the weekend ticket was reasonably-priced and this was excellent decision because it gave the opportunity to a lot of people, adults but also students, to take part to the Festival.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear George,</P>
      <P>I'm writing to answer your question about rules in my life, at school and at home.</P>
      <P>As you may know, I attend a Liceo, which is the most difficult kind of high school in Italy.</P>
      <P>Our teachers are very strick, we have to stand up as they come into class and wait until they say ôDo sit down!,,. We can't talk during lessons and we only have a en minutes break at 10.30 a.m. If we're late, we have to go to the principal and ask for his signature to go to class.</P>
      <P>It's hard to be extremely quite for five hours but I reckon it's a good way of education.</P>
      <P>On the other side, I feel free at home. I help doing cleaning or the washing, but I do it because I want to, not because my parents make me do it.</P>
      <P>I can go out and stay out late, I've got my car and my mobile, so that they can call me whenever they need to hear me; but above all I know they trust me and consider my an adult.</P>
      <P>Therefor I wouldn't change anything in my home life and neither in my school life.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Best wishes.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
