<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR202*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I have just read your letter and it would be grateful if you could give me more information about the two weeks at camp California in the USA.</P>
      <P>I am a nineteen year old gild who is still attending classes at Saint John's School. For the past four years I have been playing tennis and I have also done some courses about painting.</P>
      <P>I would appreciate if I could travel on July because my school gives me two winter holiday's week. As far as accommodation is concern, I prefer staying in a long cabin. I believe it is better than a tent because this one would not shelter enough. As I said before, I have been playing tennis for four years. I consider myself to be good at this sport. As regarding painting, I know a lot since my grandmother taugh me when I was five years old.</P>
      <P>It would be very kind of you to let me know about the clothes you think it would be necessary for me to take and how much money I will need.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear kim,</P>
      <P>I'm sorry I haven't written to you before but I have been very busy helping at Mano''s concert.</P>
      <P>Do you remember when I told you that my dream was helping Mano''s group? Well, my dream come true. All started when I was in Drama Club and my singing teacher told me that Mano''s group were going to have a concert here, in Argentina. She also told me that she have some conections with the people in charge of the lights of the concert. You know that last year I organise the lights in our performance. So, there I was, controling the illumination in Mano's concert!!!!</P>
      <P>I will never forget that wonderful experience. This really help me for our next performance in the Drama Club. It was so exciting to see the Mano' group singer that I felt as if I were in heaven!!</P>
      <P>Please write me as soon as you can.</P>
      <P>Best wishes,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
