<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR205*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P> Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>I'm writing you because I had been asked to make a little suggestion about the programme your have organised to our English class travel.</P>
      <P>First of all, thank you for the programme, we think it is very good, especially the river trip to greenwich, we believe we will enjoy a lot going to greenwich. Moreover, in our opinion, this travel is going to be very interesting for us.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, we have seen an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure show and we would all like to go the show. We think it is a good opportunity because london fashion is the most important over the world, and we all learn a lot about London style going to this show.</P>
      <P>We think we could change shooping for going to the show. The show is free, and it is only on Tuesday 14th of March. It is open from 10.00 until 19.00, and we could go there on the afternoon.</P>
      <P>Thank you for your attention.</P>
      <P>We are looking forward to your answer,</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P> Thinking about the media's treatment of famous people, I've realised of some things.</P>
      <P>On my point of view the media's treatment of famous people is very bad. The media's are looking forward to create great expectations about famous people. They are not trying to give information, they are only looking to get money, and to entertain the public.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, if the media's are acting in that way is because of the society. The society is who increases the audience of the media, if nobody gave attention to the famous people private lifes, this treatment would finish.</P>
      <P>But in my opinion, before you get famous you know which are the consequences. As in another you may know what could happen.</P>
      <P>To sum up, there is no job perfect, and be famous involves a lof money, but also a lot of jouralists following your private life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
