<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR206*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P> Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>I am writing you this letter to complain about you have organized us for our trip to London.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to thank you for your activity programme. I find it really good, specially because of the visit to the Science Museum and the National Art Gallery.</P>
      <P>But I would like you to know that on Tuesday March 14th in London, there is a show, which is free for students, about the latest fashions, leisure and sports wear, make up and hairstyles called The London Fashion and Leisure Show.</P>
      <P>All the clan would enjoy going the show, because it is a great oportunity to see an exhibition as the latest fashions. We know that you have planned a very complete programme. But we would like to suggest you to move our visit to the Science Museum to Wednesday afternoon, so that, we can go to the show on Tuesday, which lasts from 10 am to 7 pm.</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for considering our petition.</P>
      <P>I look forward receiving your reply.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P> Nowadays, in our society, there are some people who, because of their work or because of their success in life, has become popular, and by now is known by everybody. But, how does fame affect to their lifestyle?</P>
      <P>Politicians, musicians or film starts are controlled all the time, since they wake up in the morning until they go to bed in the evening, by journalists and photographers who follow them and observe all that they do.</P>
      <P>It is certain that these people have fame, fortune and success, and that many of them are rich, very rich. They usually appear on TV, go to shows, sports competitions... But I'm sure that all these things can not give them back one of the most needed things: a private life. And believe me, there is no money in the world to pay that.</P>
      <P>But obviously, if these people are all the time in the newspaper, on TV and so on, is because, although we don't want to accept it, we love following their lifes.</P>
      <P>So now, all we should have to ask ourselves is if their damaged lifestyles is in part our fault.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
