<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR207*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms clark:</P>
      <P>I am writing to give suggestion for the international art festival, which I have been to one weeks before. It was really good, but I feel it could be better next year.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I want to say it is a great idea to have this international arts festival, it is very interesting, especially for the young people. I went to this festival with four friends and all of us enjoyed our time very much. It was said that stars and artists from around the world on the advertisement, but in fact they are from only six different countries, so I hope there will be artists from more different countries next year. Although the jazz, rock and classical music was great, some concerts and halls are too small, could you consider making them bigger next year.</P>
      <P>The plays and films were really wonderful, people liked them very much, so could you play more next year</P>
      <P>The last thing is about the ticket. It was excellent about one reasonably-priced weekend ticket for all events, because it is convenient and normally young people do not have a lot of money, so I hope next year the ticket will be also like this.</P>
      <P>I hope that you can consider my suggestions. I really look forward to going to the festival next year.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely:</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Jacob:</P>
      <P>I'm very glad to hear from you. I hope everything is ok. I'm really sorry I didn't write you back immediately, because I was preparing my exam at that moment, so can you forgive me? We should keep in touch with each other, because you know I'm very happy to have a friend like you.</P>
      <P>In your last letter you asked me something about our rules, both at home and at school in my country. I'd like to tell you that. In school, we have lots of rules, especially in the class and some of them are quite strange. For example, we can't go to the toliet during the lessons, we should go there in the brake. And we can't eat food or do any sports in our classroom. If you fail three subjects in your exam, you will be kicked out of school. It's too strickt, I don't like it. If I can, I would like to change this, because I don't think everyone can success at once, we should give them second chance to try.</P>
      <P>Anyway, in my country, generally, children are free at home, but it also depends on their parents. For me, I don't have rules at home, just don't take trouble to my family, that's all.</P>
      <P>OK, just here. I look forward to hearing from you soon. All the best wishes and good luck.</P>
      <P>yours:</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
