<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR208*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Jane Clark,</P>
      <P>The purpose of this letter is to congratulate you on the International Arts Fesival I attended last weekend.</P>
      <P>I believe that the event was good, however I feel that the festival can be improved next year.</P>
      <P>Firstly I would like to tell you that the idea of organizing an International Arts Festival is fantastic, but in your advertisement it was said that I would find stars and artists from arround the world, when, in fact, they were from only six countries. I do understand that it must be difficult to get these people to go to the festival, but it would be nice if next year we could meet other personalities.</P>
      <P>Secondly I belive you should know that a lot of people, including me, were not able to enjoy concerts because some concert halls were too small.</P>
      <P>I would be very thankful if you could tell me if there will be more plays and films next year.</P>
      <P>Last but not least I would like you to know that I think the idea of the weekend ticket for all events was excellent because in the end it was cheaper than paying for each event separatelly.</P>
      <P>I hope you find my opinion useful.</P>
      <P>Once again congratulations on the Festival.</P>
      <P>I hope to hearing from you soon</P>
      <P>yours sincerelly,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>tips to earn money</P>
      <P>When the holidays began everybody is happy because it represents the beginning of a time full of fun and lots of interesting things to do, but in order to do these things we all need money and that is a big problem to most of us.</P>
      <P>there are several ways to earn a bit of money in your spare time. One of the most common examples is baby- sitting taking care of little children is easy and it doesn't require special skills, all you need is a lot of patience.</P>
      <P>If looking after children doesn't fit you, you can try with pets. Lots of people would pay you to take their dog for a walk. So if you like animals this is your chance to earn money and have fun at the same time.</P>
      <P>Another option is to wash your neighbour's car. In this case you need to buy the materials you will work with, but don't worry, soap is not very expensive.</P>
      <P>the most important thing is that you wisely choose the most suitable work for you, according to the things you like to do.</P>
      <P>If you don't find anything good enough for you don't worry, you should always remember: It's not all about the money!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
