<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR210*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Sir Manager,</P>
      <P>My name is Sandre Atos, I am writting to you because this last weekend I went to the theatre, you manage, to see what was called "London's newest and best musical show". However, I must say, it was quite the opposite.</P>
      <P>First of all, Danny Brook, an excellent actor, who (according to the play advertisement) was supposed to perform, was replaced for a disappointing actor. Besides the spectacle was setted up to 19:30, but ended up starting at 20:15. In addition to all this, the promised discounts in the tickets was not offered. Finally, after the play the theatre restaurant was still closed. Sir, I couldn't believe in that, everything that was in the advertisement was a fraud.</P>
      <P>I was told that I would have a perfect evening, though instead of that I had a terrible one. That's why I am writting to ask for some money back, I believe I have this right.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Some people glorify technology as if it was the best thing could ever happened in their lives. However, since I was a child I have noticed that except for the medical facilities and achievements, it has brought to me more disadvantages than advantages. I still remember the day television came to my house, I was only seven, everybody was exciting about the new "toy", however what seemed to be only one more way to get together, turned to rule our lives. Unfortunatly my parents did not realize how TV was creating a role among us. Before TV, we used to spend our nights, playing cards, telling jokes, talking to each other. Nowadays, I barely know my parents, but I do know exactly what is happening in the soap operas. On the other hand, due to science development, I am getting better, recovering from ahsma. In addition to this it is wonderful not have to wait too long to eat, thanks for the microwaves invention. Despite all these advantages, I deeply miss the times I had almost no technological facilities, but a very happy and united family.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
