<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR211*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Jane C</P>
      <P>I have spent two days at the International Arts Festival recently and I am writing in order to give my opinions about it.</P>
      <P>When I knew it was going to be an international festival, I got really excited because I would finally have the opportunity to meet stars and artists from around the world, but I felt rather disappointed when I found out that was not at all true. Besides this, I think that some of the concert halls were too small that I felt very uncomfortable. However, the one-reasonably-priced weekend ticket for all events was marvellous because I was able to attend as many concerts as I wished without spending much money.</P>
      <P>Although that Festival was not well-organized, I would like you to repeat it next year. I wish you could perform more plays and films, and there should be more varied art exhibitions. But I really appreciate it if you would take into consideration the problem with the lack of space in the concert halls.</P>
      <P>I hope you consider these pieces of suggestions.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>It is really nice to hearing from you and I think we will learn so many interesting facts from each other.</P>
      <P>Personally, I can not imagine human life without rules, especially those that have to do with respecting other people. Moreover, I am in favour of rules at school because it is very important for children to learn how to cooperate with others.</P>
      <P>As far as I can remember, I had to respect a lot of rules but the most important concerning wearing the suitable clothes, to arrive in time and get on with every teacher and authority. As a consequence, most mates used to complain about those rules but all of us tried to put up with them.</P>
      <P>At home it is the other way about. Fortunately, rules are made by every member of the family so that no one complains about them. I must admit that I am able to do whatever I want, such as inviting friends, watching TV until midnight and so on. In fact, the only strong rule is to cooperate with house-keeping and meal. That is all!</P>
      <P>Hope you enjoy my experiences</P>
      <P>Best wishes</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
