<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR212*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>17/6/00</P>
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam</P>
      <P>I had a vary dissappointing evining last saturday. I had everythig planned, I and my family where coming to whatch your show and then have a decent meal at your theatre restaurant but it was disasterous. Firstly there was no available discount, as you said on your advertisement so even my 6 year old son was charged adult price. Then everything was going well untill the show didn't start! Supposedly it was to start at 19:30 well it didn't, it started 45 minutes late, at exactly 20:15. And By the way may I ask you how up to date your leaflets are because in spite of the ad vert saying the staring actor was Danny Brook, well it wasn't. It was an other actor I had never heard of. That was a dissapointment for my whole family, infact all the viewers where very dissappointed.</P>
      <P>Anyway the show was nowhere as good as it was mentioned to be and it was definately worse than I had expected it to be, I didn't enjoy it at all so I was relying on the food to fill me up and relieve some of my stress. So as soon as the show was over we walked out and followed all the signs for about 5 minutes desparately searching for your restaurants our stomaches rumbling for food. Finally we found the place. The location is far too far away and, what do you know, the place is closed for restoration, and it has been for two weeks! And your booking staff didn't know this obviously as they took our booking, with no problems whatsoever. they even gave us a table number.</P>
      <P>What kind of an organasation do you call this, sir/madam? You don't understand how dissappointed and angry I was that night. I was expecting a perfect night out but I came face to face with a total nightmare. And I am demanding a refund.</P>
      <P>Thankyou for your time and attention</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely. </P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>The Revealed Secret</P>
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. In fact he was one of the main busybodies of his neighborhood and his school so not alot of people in his school liked him. this was a vary. Another bad thing about this school was that there where different types of students that formed groups. Some where just friend groups but others took it seriously, maby just a bit too seriously, they gave themselves names and acted as gangs rather than just groups of friends, and started picking on younger people, or mempers of other gang, trying to start fights with them. This whent on and on, got more and more serious but it was so secret that teachers didn't notice.</P>
      <P>One day one of those groups decided to have a party and although Pat wasn't in their group they invited him too but told him very strictly to keep it a secret especially from the other groups. But Pat was so exited that he forgot all about the secret and told all of his best mates. and the word spread like wildfire and by the end of the day virtually everyone knew about this party. But luckily for Pat the word did not return to the group having the party. Everyone in the year was anoyed, but not with Pat, oh, no! With the group having the party. No one could do anything about it. exept a few phcyco groups, some of the more serious ones decided to raid this party, just for the fun and meannes of it.</P>
      <P>That night the party commenced. Everyone was enjoying themselves exept Pat who had heard about the raid. So he was thinking up an excuse to go home early. But no excuses where working. Everyone was drunk and they simply would not let him go. Time was ticking away. he new the attack was coming anyminute. now,</P>
      <P>The time had come the who groups had comdined their forces and where ready to strike. They had water bombs and water pistols at the ready. they started charging down the field towards the fire and once in range everyone thew their balloon as far as they could. they all exploded with loud splashes. The group having the party thought this was a serious attack and started throwing back stones and shooting every one wit BB guns. Lots of People wher injured and even more where suspended the next day at school, when the Headmaster found out what had happened.</P>
      <P>Pat recieved no punishment at all and he wasn't blamed for anything by his teachers or friends. But he felt awfull because he new that all this had happened because of him.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
