<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR213*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>To Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>Firstly, I would like to thank you for the programme that you provided. It was very good programme, especially the river trip to Greenwich, which I am sure the whole class would enjoy.</P>
      <P>However, our class has spotted an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show and would all wish to attend. It will be held at the Central Exhibition Hall in London on the 14th March. It will be from 10.00 till 7.00pm. The show will be about all the latest fashion, leisure and sports wear, make up and hairstyles. We would also not have to worry financially as it is free for students.</P>
      <P>This will be a great opportunity for us because we will be able to find out more about the people of London and their fashions and style we might also get a change to meet new people and interest with them. The whole class is also very excited about this fashion show and would really appreciate your giving them a change to go.</P>
      <P>I have a few suggestion on how the programme could be changed to fit the London Fashion and Leisure Show in. We could do as planned for Monday and move going to the Science Museum from Tuesday to Wednesday afternoon. We would have to forgo the shopping as we might not have enough time and the exchange rate might be too high for us to do much shopping. We can however go and look around the shopping mall if we have time after the show.</P>
      <P>Lastly, I would be very grateful if you could give us your permission to go to the show. I hope you would consider this matter. I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Everyday, something changes and we become more modern companies use computers instead of books, dentist use modernized electrical item instead of just a plier, even homes are effected. From letters to emails, from gas stoves to electric stoves and microwaves, but we aren't just going to stop here are we? No, in the future, the present will be the past and these things now new to use will be old, outdated and changed.</P>
      <P>I see a very different home for us in the future. Most things will be computerised. We might even be using voice identification and fingerprints instead of keys. We an on and off lights with touch pads and remote controllers. We might even be able to open the door without getting out from the living room. Cameras will be something usual in every house instead of that little peephole in your door.</P>
      <P>Although all that may change our houses may be still the same. The rooms and size should remain as it was and the living rooms and all may still be decorated in the same style. We might still favour that old carpet and couch. The furniture should not change that much on the outside and the amount of rooms should not change too.</P>
      <P>In the future, every child might have a laptop. And instead of going to school, why not let school come to you? We will be learning at home using computers and disc. Never have to leave the house or wake up so early. Another way our home could be different in the future is probably the utilitles we are using. We might not need maids to do housework anymore as they can easily be replaced with a robot, a machine, or something other with the same purpose.</P>
      <P>Our homes will still be the same in terms of the kitchen, it will still be filled with vegetables and meat. This is because people won't miss the great taste of food although it could be subsituted to a vitamin pill or two.</P>
      <P>Lastly, I think that all this changes won't really be noticed as we change it daily and slowly instead abruptedly. People will be able to adjust and change with the times.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
