<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR214*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Jane Clark,</P>
      <P>I am writing about the International Arts Festival which has just finished.</P>
      <P>I congratulated with you because it has been a great idea since the town needed a cultural event. I especially appreciate the weekend tickets which almost everybody could afford, also students like me.</P>
      <P>However, I think that some concert halls were too small for the musical performances. You probably did not expect such a big audience! Being very fond of films, I would have appreciate seeing more of them. For next year's edition, you could possibly add some foreign films, like the Chinese ones, which I most like.</P>
      <P>Finally, in order to make a really international festival, I think you should invite artists from all over the world, not just from six countries like this year.</P>
      <P>I hope that you will appreciate my opinions and suggestions, which I have shared with my friends.</P>
      <P> Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Simply a good idea and that's enough</P>
      <P>Are you young and full of life but you don't have enough money to enjoy your spare time? Simply let your brain work and you could find out wonderful ideas to earn money enjoying yourself.</P>
      <P>Are you fed up of looking after the screaming baby of your mother's friend? You could move from children to pets and become a dog-sitter, spending your afternoons walking round the park and chatting with a friend.</P>
      <P>Are you keen on music and you love going to disco? With a short training you'll be able to mix songs at parties. You won't dance but the earning is guarantee!</P>
      <P>Do you like do-it-yourself and your house is full of marvellous but unuseful things? You could sell them to a specialised shop and finally tidy up your room!</P>
      <P> So, what are waiting for? Work out your own idea and realise it: money won't be a problem for you anymore!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
