<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR215*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>16.12.00</P>
      <P>Dear Clark,</P>
      <P>I am writing to response to the international Arsts Festival, which took place on 21-22 November. I would like to inform you, that it was a great idea and valuable activitie as a social event.</P>
      <P>However, it was a dissapointment, when I realised that not many countries were attending to the event. I could be fine if I had seen more countries from all around the world, for instance: far east, indonesia etc.</P>
      <P>It wasn't complicated to find the right hall to the shows, I should say it was very well organised.</P>
      <P>But one thing, I have to mention is that some of the concert halls was too small and it wasn't comfortable as well as to fell the great atmosphere.</P>
      <P>On the other side, I enjoyed to being on of the people to see the plays and films, dance shows which was brillantly performed - art exbitions. Listening talks by the famous writers was a opportunity which I couldn't missed.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask, if you could expend the plays and films more for next year? I have to add that the weekend ticket was a ideal idea to sell all the events.</P>
      <P>Finally, I preciate your organisation and look forward to hearing from the next International Arts Festival.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>16.12.00</P>
      <P>Dear Nico,</P>
      <P>Its really nice to hearing from you and thank you very much for the letter with photos. Its a good idea to send them to me, because I have to confess that I have lost my camera and also the films. What a pitty!</P>
      <P>By the way how is your new school? Did you like it more than the previous one?</P>
      <P>I must say that our school rules are quite different than yours. First of all we have to stand up, when we speak to the teacher and have to pay full attention to the lessons. If you missed a lesson, that could be a trouble for yourself. I think it depends on the school. Privat schools have more relaxed atmosphere that the state school. They don't have strike rules and students can take extra lessons.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, in the state schools as I said, we are more respectful to the teacher and bad behaviours are punished. For example, you have to do more homeworks or they are sending you home etc. Of course smoking isn't allowed at any part of the schol.</P>
      <P>I have a relaxed family and we are sharing all the houseworks. My Father does the cooking, my mother does the cleaning and I do tidying up! But in many Families women are doing more than men. I can't accept that, because you have to share all the duties and spend more time together.</P>
      <P>Anyway it think that's it for now.</P>
      <P>I hope to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Lots of Love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
