<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR218*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>41-50</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>London, 20th may, 2000</P>
      <P>Circle Theatre</P>
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am just writing this letter in order to complain about the musical show I have seen last Sunday at the evening.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I become very disappointed because of the actor, who was different from your advertisement, not Danny Brook was starring.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I was ready at 19:30 time, as you have announced, and I had to stay waiting in front of the theatre until 20:15, when finally the show began.</P>
      <P>Besides of all, at the end of the Musical, I went to the your Theatre Restaurant, in order of taking a dinner, because I have leaft home without eating and so I was hungry at that time.</P>
      <P>Thus, you cann't believe what was my disappointment when I noted that it was closed, without no explanation.</P>
      <P>Finally, I would like to say you that I am asking for money back, because I had an evening totally despleased, completely different that you have anouced in your advertisement.</P>
      <P>So, I look forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed your daily life?</P>
      <P>First of all, modern technology have changed my daily life the last five years more quickly than in the anchient time, or even than a ten years ago.</P>
      <P>I became to notice the difference in my work, since when all tasks have changed to the computer and I needed to learn how to use that machine.</P>
      <P>From that time, I decided to buy my own computer and every day I was improving my knowledge. Firstly I become to write letters and articles, next I learned several computers plays. When I learned how to use internet, I didn't stop until now.</P>
      <P>On balance, I can affirm that I couldn't without this modern technology today. My life wouldn't be the same another time without these progress.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
