<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR219*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Rome 16th December 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Jane X,</P>
      <P>I'm an italian boy who went to the International Arts Festival last November and I enjoyed most of the events I went to but given that I think that the Festival could be better next year I write you these lines in order to make you know some observations of mine about the festival.</P>
      <P>The Festival on its own is a great idea because there aren't many of these events dealing with art but I think that instead of inviting stars and artists only from six counties they could be invited really from all the world.</P>
      <P>Furthermore, and for sure it is not your fault, some of the halls for the concerts were too small and that prevented me from enjoying some of the concerts because of the noise but also prevented many people from entering the hall that was often two crowded.</P>
      <P>I hope next year plays and films will be more and that the ticket will be reasonably-priced as this year in way that people not really interested in arts could come and enjoy the festival.</P>
      <P>Friendly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Rome 16th December 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Marie,</P>
      <P>I'm going to write you about rules in my country and I have to tell you that life in school isn't too hard because even if there are many rules to follow nobody does it.</P>
      <P>It's written in the regulament that we can't leave the school during the breaks; we can't smoke near the classrooms; we had to justify our absences or late-enterings and even if you're over eighteen your parents have to justify you with the teacher.</P>
      <P>At my home every rule must be respected.</P>
      <P>Even if my parents don't look after me for all the matters like going out on nights or studying you don't have to think that living in my house is like living in heaven because I can't play the guitar or listen to music at a loud volume or invite my friends for a Saturday night party.</P>
      <P>These are the things that I'd like to chance; I'd like to do what I really want but I don't know if I'm really ready for this!!</P>
      <P>With love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
