<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR220*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs. Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writing as a reply to your letter, congratulating me to the winning of the first prize in your competition and inviting me to the Camp California in the U.S.A. I was delighted to hear from you and am already looking forward to spend two weeks in California.</P>
      <P>I am afraid that the only possible time for me to travel is in July because it is the only month I am able to get time off work. As an accomodation I would prefer sleeping in a tent because I enjoy the closeness to the nature while camping a lot.</P>
      <P>The two activities that I would like to do at the Camp are sailing, which I have never done before and tennis which I already play quite well.</P>
      <P>I need to know how much money you would advise me to bring and what sort of clothes I should take with me.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to your reply at your earliest convenience and to get to know you personally in July.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>Esther Meyer</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>thanks a lot for your long letter! It was great to hear from you again after such a long time. You asked me, how the pop concert was like which I told you I was going to go to in my last letter. Well, let me tell you, it was just awesome!</P>
      <P>My job was it, to help to keep all the little kids out of the backstage area. Therefore I got to stay backstage all the time and to see all the members of the "Backstreet Boys".</P>
      <P>And, you won't believe it, I actually got to talk to Nick Carter!</P>
      <P>Yes, that was the best thing about the concert but I actually just enjoyed the whole experience to be part of the crew. I sort of felt, like I had done my part to make the concert a sucess. Do you know, what I mean? Anyway, I've got to study now, we've got a maths exam tomorrow.</P>
      <P>Hope to hear from you soon</P>
      <P>Lots of love,</P>
      <P>Esther</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
