<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR221*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you first of all to thank you about the good programme that you give us about the trip in London, especially for planning to visit the science museum, which we believe is going to be very interesting.</P>
      <P>However, we have seen an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show and we would like to suggest to including this point in the programme.</P>
      <P>The show is going to be on Tuesday the 14 of March from 10.00 to 19.00 and we fained it very interesting, because we will have the opportunity to see mews, firstly about the latest fashions, secondly concerning leisure and sports wear and finally about make up and hairstyles.</P>
      <P>In addition of this, it is going to be a great opportunity for all of us, because for the students it is completely free.</P>
      <P>We were thinking that meaby we can go early to visit the Science Museum and than go to the Central Exhibition, where the event is going to have place!</P>
      <P>We really look forward to receiving your answer as soon as possible!</P>
      <P>Thank you very mutch!</P>
      <P>Your sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>We have been talking for hours in our class about the treatment of the media regarding famous people.</P>
      <P>Of course I must agree with the opinion of my class - mates: famous people, such as actors, singers or politicians, deserve to have a private life, but of course it is not always like this!</P>
      <P>Almost the time they have journalists following them everywhere and all the time, looking for great news or interesting pictures to put on the first page of the newspaper, and I don't think this is very nice, but is the price that famous people have to pay, just becouse they are popular.</P>
      <P>Anyway, this is not always necessary a problem, but it can be a big thing for the famous person, becouse let people talking about him and increase his popularity.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, I can say that this is not the bigger problem that the world has and -- it is not my problem becouse I am not famous!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
