<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR222*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Robertson,</P>
      <P>My name is Bao-yu Liao. I am representative of our class in your college to write to you.</P>
      <P>We are very grateful for what you have well-organised the programme going to London for us.</P>
      <P>It is a good programme, especially National Art Gallery is one of the most places we would like to visit. This is because we are very interested in art.</P>
      <P>In fact, some of our classmates have seen an advertisement for the 'London Fashion and Leisure Show'. Concidently the show is in London and on Tuesday March 14 which is during the period we are in London for the three-day programme. We think it is a great opportunity because we are very interested in art and fashion. Of course, leisure as well. Therefore, if it is possible, we would like to see the show in the afternoon on 14 March instead of going shopping.</P>
      <P>It would be very much appreciated if you could arrange the programme to be changed. We look forward to hearing a good news from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Famous people, such as politicians and film stars, deserve to have a private life without journalists following them all the time. We know it does not matter they are famous or not, everyone has his own privacy. However, as human beings, almost all of us are curious. We like to know and chat about gossip. This is why gossip magazines are so popular. Due to commercial value, journalists have to follow them all the time to peep their private lives to satisfy us. There, it is impossible for journalists to stop chasing them.</P>
      <P>However, journalists should not only think about commercial value, but morality and priciples are also being concerned. Of course, it everyone pays less attention or interest, the situations should be better. I remember in August 1997 Princess Diana died in the car crash was one of the most disarster examples.</P>
      <P>Although we can not deny it is our nature - curious, we can improve our sence of morality and try to think about the importance of privacy for them. Actually, I am happy to hear that journalists have learned their lesson from the death of Princess Diana and try to let her children and Royal family have more privacy. Lets all leave them more freedom to enjoy their private lives.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
