<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR223*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Basle, 12th Decembre 2000</P>
      <P>(Your English class N3c)</P>
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>We have received the programme. We'd like to thank you for organising good programme, especially the shopping tour on Tuesday.</P>
      <P>Our class is especially interested in latest fashion and trends. London is a good place for discovering it. We've seen an advertisement for 'the London Fashion and Leisure Show' and all of us are very interested in it. It's an exhibition of fashions, sport wears, make up and hairstyles. We think it is a great opportunity because there are some people in our class who like to study fashions after leaving this school. And everyone of us is interested in fashions and clothes! This exhibition is situated in Central Exhibition Hall, London.</P>
      <P>We've noticed that the exhibition will be on Tuesday, 14th of March. Could we change our programme? We'd like to do our shopping tour on next following day (Wednesday afternoon) instead of Tuesday afternoon. What do you think about our suggestion? Please write back as soon as possible. We hope to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="5.3">
      <P>Basle, 12th Decembre 2000</P>
      <P>Dar Oxana,</P>
      <P>Thanks for your letter. It's nice to hear from you again. In your letter, you asked me wheter the book I've read would be a suitable present for your cousin's fifteenth birthday. It's my pleasure to write my suggestion for you now!</P>
      <P>You know I love reading books, it's my passion. I've read all the books of English author Ernest Hemingway. They are great I tell you! But I think your cousin is too young for it. Why? Because he especially concentrates on history, social life and politic situation in the time the story is played. That might be quiet complicated to understand, especially for young people. For me, his books are great. But anyway, do you know the book with the title 'The Best Detective Stories of Agatha Christie'? It's written by Agatha Christie. She's an American and her books concentrate on crime and detective stories. Her books aren't difficult to understand. She especially write books for young people. And I think this book is a very good one for your cousin. You wrote that your cousin is quite intered in magic, detectives and sport, didn't you? I think this is the best choice for him!</P>
      <P>I've send you a copy of the summary from the book and an interesting article about the author and the book. Please read it and write your comments. I hope to hearing from you soon! Have fun with it and say hello to your cousin! See you soon!</P>
      <P>Love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
