<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR224*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>I'd like thank you to take us on a trip to London and have made such a good programme, especially the river trip to Greenwich.</P>
      <P>It also will be "The London fashion and leisure show" on the 14th of March, which consist on an exhibition of the latest fashions, leisure and sports wear, make up and hairstyles. Indeed it will be free for us as we are students.</P>
      <P>As you know we are in England to learn your language and also your lifestyle, and we thought this show would be a good opportunity for us to discorve this way of your country!</P>
      <P>May I suggest an alternative? We could go to science museum on wednesday morning and to the National Art Gallery. We only need wake up earlier and take part of the lunchtime to do both the same morning, but that would leave us go to show on tuesday, because we can use the wednesday's free time to do our shopping. I hope that my idea sweet you and you'll agree.</P>
      <P>Sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="5b">
      <P>Tuesday, 12th December</P>
      <P>Dear Annette,</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter, like usual, it's a pleisure to receive a word from you.</P>
      <P>I understood that you're looking for your cousin's birthday present, and you'd like give to him a book, which, I think, it's a good idea. The last book I read was Wuthering Heights by Emilie Brontë. It's a fantastique book, which I recommend to everybody keen on lovestories. It's a perfect combinaison between passion and life difficulties. I recone that it's quite not an easy reading, but as you described your cousin, I think she really will enjoy it, she's such good in litteracy, that it won't be a problem for her. I really think you should choose this one for her, it does go with her personnality. It'll be a good point for her general culture, Wuthering Heights it's a classic, which everybody knows about it, even if they didn't have read it, they, at liest, know the story.</P>
      <P>Let me know what would be your choice.</P>
      <P>Love from,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
