<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR225*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing you to complain about "Over the Rainbow" musical show which took a place in The Circle Theatre several weeks ago.</P>
      <P>First of all, advertisement for the shows provided absolutely WRONG information about actors. Danny BROOK, who should play according your advertisement was replaced by an another actor and it disappointed me. The show should start at 19.30, however, the audience have been waiting for fourty five minutes. Also, in the advertisement you have mentioned discounts which were not provided. The theatre restaurant was closed that evening and I had not recieved the explanations why. On the whole, the evening was boring and disappointing.</P>
      <P>Based on everything listed above, I would like to recieve £10, which I have paid, back. The ticket for the show is included.</P>
      <P>Look forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has morden technology changed my life.</P>
      <P>New technologies have become the part of our lives. There are a lot of arguments about the weather this influence is negative or positive. Nevertheless, it has affected every person and hopefully in a good way.</P>
      <P>Personally, I consider modern technologies as a positive innovation. Using microwave oven or vacuum cleaner saves me a lot of time.</P>
      <P>Computer is extrrmely convenient in writing reports and essays. And, of course, I can not forget about cars and planes that deliver us to all parts of the Earth.</P>
      <P>However, many people, insist that new technologies affect people in a negative way. I would better prefer seeing my father talking to his family instead of staring at blue screen of TV. But also, I would not be able to imagine my life without the nice way of reciving news with help of it.</P>
      <P>Counting pros and cons, I tend to think that there are more positive points in working out and manufacturing new technologies than negative ones anyway. Modern girl or boy already would not be able to imagine life without them.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
