<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR226*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>12.12.2000</P>
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>I am writing to ask permission to go to the London Fashion and Leisure Show. I would be very greatful if you could let us to go the show.</P>
      <P>I would like to give you some details about the show that I saw its advertisement yesterday. It is in the Central Exhibition Hall in London. It starts at 10.00 am and finishes 19.00 pm. The date of the show is on Tuesday 14th of March. It is really great opportunity to go to the show when we are in London. We would like to go there because it is very popular nowadays. I've heard that Leisure and sports wear, make up and hairstyles are really wonderful. It is also free for students. We all know that you organised everything. However, we can change the programme. Here are some suggestions that I would like to let you know. We have free timer on Wednesday 15th of March in the afternoon so we can go to the Science Museum on Wednesday. We can also do shopping quickly after sightseeing of London.</P>
      <P>I would be very pleased if you let us to go to the show. I also would like to say thank you for organising the good program for us. I look forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>A DAY OF MY LIFE</P>
      <P>It was dangerous, but I knew I had to do it.</P>
      <P>That day, I got up early because I hadn't slept very well. I checked everything again and again. I was afraid of doing it but I had to do it. It was the first time I had robbed a bank. I was her best friend. I promised her to find a money for her operation. She was at the hospital and she was really bad.</P>
      <P>That time, I couldn't imagine how my life would change. After I had had my breakfast I put my clothes on. I didn't want anybody to recognise me. Despite feeling really bad I left home. I got into my car and started it. When I arrived the bank I got out of the car and went into the bank. I told everybody to lie down. They did it. I asked cashier to give me all money. Before I took money one of the cashier had pressed a button to call a police. I quickly left bank.</P>
      <P>However, it didn't take long that they caught me soon. The policeman arrested me and I stayed in a prison for 15 years. The worst thing was my friend died after 10 days I was arrested.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
