<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR227*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>I am writing about our class trip to London. First of all, I appreciate you well-organised programme, especially, "River Trip to Greenwich" which we requested. It would be the most excising activity in this trip.</P>
      <P>However, I saw the advertisement of "THE LONDON FASHION AND LEISURE SHOW" in the newspaper today, and told all classmates about it. We are very interested in going this show. So I would like to suggest you to change the part of programme for visiting this show.</P>
      <P>This show is held in Central Exhibition Hall, London on Tue. 14, March, and open from 10:00 to 19:00. We can see the latest fashions, leisure and sports wear, make up, and hairstyles which we will learn next term. Therefore, I think it is great idea to visit the show for our knowledgement. Furthermore, the addmission is free for students.</P>
      <P>Unfortunately, our programm is fixed but I think we could change the part of the programme. For example, "shopping on 14, March' can be changed to 15, March instead of "Free time". So we will be able to use the time at the afternoon on 14, March for visiting the show.</P>
      <P>I hope that you would give us an opportunity to visit the show. I look forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Some people said that famous people such as politicians, and film stars, needs to have a private life without journalists following them all the time. I strongly agree with this. Firstly, most people might remember the sad story of "Princess Diana" she died in Paris few years ago while she was escaping from lots of journalists called "Paparach". If she was not followed by journalists, she wouldn't die. So, this fact shows obviously that famous people without private life could be the victim.</P>
      <P>But on the other hand, ordinary people, including me, are keen on watching film stars or super models fashion. Moreover, people are interested in their life style. I think that is the reason why journalists are still chasing famous people after "Princess Diana's" accident.</P>
      <P>However, secondly, famous people are not "ailen" so that they might do something, for example, ashame things in public space or argument with partner or family even put on swimming costume like us. So they can be just ordinaly people like us. We have to think about this way.</P>
      <P>Overall, people should think if we were famous people... and then we can find the answer that all people, including famous people, need private life and would like to behave in ordinaly life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
