<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR229*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>Competition Organiser.</P>
      <P>Dear Madame,</P>
      <P>I have received your good news and I'm very happy because I have always wished go to California and now it's real, so, thank you very much about that.</P>
      <P>First at all, I would like to give you some further information from me and secondly, I'll ask you for some doubts that I have.</P>
      <P>About, when I would like to travel I think that my answer will be easy for you, because, I have two months off those are July and August so, my travel should be in between, my accomodation I would like to stay in tent because I remember my holidays in the south of Peru, long time ago, it was wonderful.</P>
      <P>With regard to the activities at the Camp, I would like to choose basketball and photography, because I think that basketball is very complete sport for training your muscles and I used to play in a league in my country, it's hard but at the same time lovely. The other selection has been done because I like to much discover different places and with a camera is possible to do it easily.</P>
      <P>If it possible for you to help me in some doubts I have, I'll be really greatful. One is with regard to how much additional money you believe will be enough to enjoy the holiday? Another thing is if the meals are include or I have to paid for them?</P>
      <P>Once again, thanks.</P>
      <P>Waiting for your reply, best wishes.</P>
      <P>Your faitfull.</P>
      <P>Daniel Ortiz</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I have heard from you recently and I'm really happy, I hope you and your family are well.</P>
      <P>I know that my girlfriend told you that I was helping at a pop concert and enjoyed it very much. Besides, she told me that you are very keen to know how was my experience, so I'll give you some information in this letter that I'm sure you will be glad, even you have not been in the concert.</P>
      <P>First at all, I'll tell you that in the day concert I woke up at 6:30 A.M, very early for me, you know me I'm lazzy, the work began around 8:30, was very hard but when the band come for training, since this moment I was enjoining to work until the concert had finished, the atmosphere was wonderful, the musicians were very kind with every one who was working because they understood that a concert is a job to be done by a team. During the concert I listened the band like everybody, besides I earned money so, was a wonderful experience.</P>
      <P>Looking forward to hear from you.</P>
      <P>You.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
