<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR232*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson:</P>
      <P>Firstly, I'm very glad to hear from you. Thank you for being organised the programme for our class, I think you may think about a long time that how shall we study during three days. We have seen your programme, and like all of those, especially the Science Museum, it will good for us to increase our knowledge, and so on.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I wonder if you know it will have "London fashion and Leisure " be showed on Tuesday in Central Exhibition Hall. In other words, what they will introduce, is most interested in us, I mean it's conflict with your plan, what a pity!</P>
      <P>All of us want to go to the show, the generation who are the same ago with us all like make up, become beautiful, and it's important that it will free for students and just be showed one day. So, we don't want lose this chance.</P>
      <P>Finally, we would like to get your permition to go, maybe if it is possible that you change your programme, we may be going to your college any time after Tuesday. We're sorry to give you trouble.</P>
      <P>We look forward to hearing from you again as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Best Wishes</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>It was dangerous, but I knew I had to do it.</P>
      <P>This story happed two years ago. That was a very hot summer, every people in our city like to swim in the river, perhaps they didn't think it was interesting if they swimed in the pool. Personally, I'd like to say I was good at swimming. Not only I was a member of swimming team in our school, but also I was tought by my father since I was five years old, So I would understood some skills and how to protect yourself from my Dad, if you had a.</P>
      <P>One day, I passed by a river in accident, I saw there were a lot of people playing in the river. Suddenly, I heard of "help, help" in my distance. In a while, lots of passed-by crowed to the river-side. To my surprise, nobody want to save that boy who was shouting, just stood there, like lots of "champ". I started think about it, after all, either had I neve. I just 15 years old. Finally, I jumped into the river, I really knew that was dangerous, but I haven't think about anything except. I also extremely hated those people who stood there all the time.</P>
      <P>Thank goodness, I succeed, save that struggled child. When I went the river-side bank, I saw some red-faced.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
