<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR233*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>First of all I would like to say that organising an International Arts Festival was a great idea. I enjoyed it and found worthy to visit.</P>
      <P>The Annual International Arts Festival, which was held on the 21st and 22nd of November, was colourful with the stars and artist coming from around the world. Although this was true, they were from only six countries. You could have let us get used to more cultures by inviting from some other countries too.</P>
      <P>The concert halls were not big enough to let all the guests in. So I could hardly participated in all of the concerts.</P>
      <P>The organisation was very good I found chances to see dance shows, art exhibitions and to listen to writers, but there could be more plays and films next year.</P>
      <P>It was really a reasonably-priced weekend for me, but you should also recognise new activities like competitions on singing songs, drawing a portrate next year. Then it would be excellent.</P>
      <P>Thanks for everything.</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Ana,</P>
      <P>I have received your letter. It is nice to hear from you again. I'm in a hurry, so I will directly come to the point.</P>
      <P>Everywhere and everytime in our lives we face with the rules. Some find them as a source of protection of their rights and others as a limitation of them. For me they are both.</P>
      <P>At schools we have certain rules like being in the class, sitting in your place before the lecture starts, bringing in your equipment with you, keeping quiet during the lessons and raising your hand when you want to talk. I think these are international rules which help things to go in order.</P>
      <P>Contrary there are other rules which annoy us like the clothing ones. You should wear the same things every time, no changes and alternations are allowed. It makes us like robots and feel bad psychologically, because we want to be different and free in wearing. Also the attendance rules put a strain on us. If we don't come to school for 10 days, then we can't pass the class. They don't care if we have problems, exams to study or if we are ill.</P>
      <P>At homes we have again rules, but more flexible ones. You should be punctual when coming to dining table, respectful, do your home works and watch TV less and not too loud.</P>
      <P>I would like to change the attendance and clothing rules in school, but I don't have the enough power. They are against democracy I think.</P>
      <P>Anyway hope to hear from you soon.</P>
      <P>With all my love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
