<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR236*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>Firstly, I'm writing to thank you the great opportunity you give us, especially in planing all this programme in a sucha acurate way. I think that this programme has a good organisation, as you know, due to we have enough time to visit plenty of local interest points. But, I was wondering, like a student of this college, if we would change part of this programme... we'd like to go to the London Fashion and Leisure Show. It takes place on Tuesday 14th and begins at ten o'clock. In this way, we can go to visit the Science Museum earlier in the morning and the, we can go to the show.</P>
      <P>Front my point of view, we are very interested in the latest fashions like the leisure, sports wear, make up, hairstyles, you know... I strongly believe that we will be at the right time and best city to appreciate it. Please let me know if you are agree with us! Oh I forgot about it! Besides, this show is gree (another positiu point).</P>
      <P>Looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>FANCY GETTING TO KNOW THE FUTURE?</P>
      <P>Do you think you've the future in your hands? Do you think we're living like old times? Would you like living in a modern way? What do you expect about the future? Can you compare it...? Are you afraid?</P>
      <P>Well, you can look at your house... Nowadays, we have all kind of instruments to washing up the dishes, to cook to be more comfortable, for example the TV, the video recorder, etc.</P>
      <P>Maybe, in a few years later we'll have a bigger TV, a more suitable radio but, from my point of view, I think these facts will not change the way of our lifes. We will be able to accelerate the process of the computer's games for example... But not in the strange way you can imagine...I mean I don't think we'll change cars by aereoplanes...</P>
      <P>In this way, you have to be calm because as you know the things are developing in the same way you'r changing, too. In conclusion, I strongly believe that the the house of the future will be the house of a new mindness it will be a very positiu point for opening our lifes. So, we have the future in our hands! Think about it.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
