<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR237*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Principal, First of all, we would like to thank you for good programme which provides us 3 days stay in London. It contains a wide range of activities for example, sightseeing, river trip, visiting science museum and gallery, shopping. It is certain that the programme will give the students considerable enjoyment. However, we have found an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure show, which will be held at Central Exhibition Hall on 14th of March. The advertisement says that the show is full of many interesting programmes, such as the latest fashions, leisure and sports wear, make up and hairstyles etc. Moreover, students are allowed to admit for free.</P>
      <P>All of us would like to attend the show because young people, particularly girls are interested in fashion and make up, so we are expecting the show will be the great opportunity to see what the new trend in fashion will be like. It would be grateful if you give a little change in programme so that we are able to attend the show. It seems to be good to change the programme of 14th into the London Fashion and Leisure show, instead of the science museum and shopping. I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Technical and Warm Home People's way of life has considerably been changed by rapdily developing mordern technology. To begin with, it will be good to look back on how our parents have lived in a house. 50 years ago, Korean mothers should have made a fire by burning woods to warm a room up and make food. Since the eletric fire and microwave oven had been invented, their life have been far easier than before. Today, however, people do not need to spend many times on making food, washing up, or even on turning on an off the light. Machines, such as a dish washer, laundry machine and remote controller help us jut to relax or do a little work necessary. From my point of view, people's home in the future will be controlled by a computer which is devised in every machine, TV, cooker and the light, connecting to the owner. He/she can just press the button or send e-mail to operate what he/she needs, even though the owner is far from the house. On the other hand, people will still be living in a building which is constructed for a "family". In spite of the computer, children will need food their mothers make and love expressed not by a computer, but by parents themselves. Computer might know better than human, but there are many things which it can not replace in our life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
