<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR238*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter. I am very happy to have won your competition. In order to confirm my schedule for travel I have won in your competition, I am writing some information to you below.</P>
      <P>I would like to go to "Camp California" on July because I will have to produce "Mission Impossible III" from August. I will be busy to decide everything about this film and will not have enough time to go there.</P>
      <P>I would prefer in tents as a accommodation because it sounds thrilling and even ecstatic for me and also I have never tried this kind of accommodation before.</P>
      <P>I would like to choose Swimming and Tennis. To produce a film is very hard work. I must keep a good condition to make a masterpiece. Swimming is really nice for my relaxing and I can do exercise for a long time. On the other hand, tennis stimulates my body and soul. It is good for my inspiration.</P>
      <P>I don't have anything I would like to ask you. I look forward to going to go "Camp California".</P>
      <P>Your sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Hi! Kim.</P>
      <P>How have you been? Hope you haven't been working too hard!</P>
      <P>By the way, Do you want to hear my experience about pop concert? OK! Here we go!</P>
      <P>I enjoyed helping at a pop concert last month. There are a lot of people. I conveyed a lot of chairs and looked after the que or people who lost their way. It sounds really bad but I enjoyed this pop concert to my heart's content.</P>
      <P>I like "X". "X" is the musician who sang songs at a pop concert. My aim joining this concert as a stuff was that I could see "X". I know you like "X" as well. Do you envy me? The concert was enthusiastic and even made me ecstatic. His voice is also soulful and sometimes even gave us blissful. Sounds good, doesn't it?</P>
      <P>Hope we join the next pop concert together as a stuff and enjoy our time!</P>
      <P>Bye</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
