<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR21*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Jane Clark,</P>
      <P>I am writing to thank you for providing International Arts Festival. It was absolutely great idea.</P>
      <P>However, I would like to give some suggestions for next year as I have read the advertisement.</P>
      <P>Firstly, could you invite stars and artists from more than only six contries? In my opinion, it might be better to have time with variety nationallites. Secondly, the music concerts were very exciting and had a lot of fun, but some concert halls were too small to enjoy them comfortably.</P>
      <P>Thirdly, I am expecting to watch more films and plays which were impressive.</P>
      <P>Lastly, it could be nice to students who are interested in arts, if you help special events, for instance, song contest, writing competition or dance lessons.</P>
      <P>To sum up, I hope the festival is developed next year with excellent reasonably-priced ticket like this year's.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>PART TIME JOBS: Find in your place</P>
      <P>Do you need money? If you do, make sure why you want to earn money. That is very important to find a way for earning and saving money.</P>
      <P>Probably the best way you can get money is to have a part time job in your spare time. I am recommending you to check your possible time to work - weekdays or weekend? - before you request a job.</P>
      <P>If you just decide to work, you'd better to find a job in your place. Firstly, go to your school or local council. They will be able to help to find safe and suitable jobs for students like you. Secondly, as your family or friends. As they know about your interestings and personality, it is easy to help you. In my case, I could get a telephone researcher part by my friend's reference.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, don't forget that a job is just spent in your "spare" time. That's it!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
