<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR22*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to make a complaint about the show 'Over the Rainbow'.</P>
      <P>During my stay in London I went to your theatre to see this show. As it is said in your advertisement, the show is starring Danny Brook but there was different actor. It is not the only problem.</P>
      <P>The show had to start at 19:30, but it started at 20:15. You promised that there will be discounts, but when I came, I found out, that they were not available.</P>
      <P>I wanted to go to your restaurant. I invited a friend of mine and promised her that we will go there. And what I found out. Your restaurant was closed.</P>
      <P>You promised that if we go to your show we will have a perfect evening. Everything was just vice versa. I am very disappointed, that is why I am asking you for compensation.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat was not very good at keeping secrets.</P>
      <P>It happened at the end of school year. My class was going to a night disco and I wanted to go there too. I asked my parents if I could go, but they did not let me do that. I tried to persuade them, told that nothing will happen to me, promised to do all housework. But all they have done is told me that I am to young for it and I can go there only when I am 20 years old.</P>
      <P>I had such a desire to go to the disco, that I decided to go even without parent's permission. I told my secret to my best friend Pat. But she told it to very kid in school, even the teachers heard it. It occured that one of the teachers told my parents about it. At the end I was punished and stayed at home for two weeks.</P>
      <P>I understood that I must keep my secrets and do not tell anybody, even the best friend.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
