<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR24*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear The Manager of the Circle Theatre,</P>
      <P>While I was staying in London for a holiday, I went to the Circle Theatre to see OVER THE RAINBOW in the evening. That made me feel disappointed.</P>
      <P>First of all, the actor was different from your advertisement. I meant he was not Danny Brook. Secondly, it took times to wait about forty five minutes, because it started at 20:15. It should be on time at 19:30. Then it had no discounts, which the advertisement said so. Due to being a student, I think I should have got the discount from your ticket with ID card. Besides this, the theatre restaurant was early closed. As soon as the show ended, I went to there for having a dessert.</P>
      <P>Lastly, I don't think that it was my perfect evening. I would like to get my money back.</P>
      <P>I look forward to replying from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. Griffin, who is a teacher, wasn't surprised at our preparation. It was so close to be on his birthday, so we made a decision to hold a small party for him.</P>
      <P>She has just learnt with us for three weeks. She is not talkative, kind, and reserved. However, this party she took part in, she was responsible for preparing food. As far as we knew, she's good at cooking.</P>
      <P>While she was choosing vegetables in a market, she came across him. When he asked her 'why do you choose deliberately?', she answered without thinking. That caused the secret disclosed.</P>
      <P>We didn't blame her, because we knew that she didn't intend to do like that. Although he wasn't surprised, he was glad and pleased with our party. Anyway, Happy Birthday to Griffin, again.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
