<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR26*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you as a representative of the class about the 3-day school trip which has been organized for next week.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to thank you for the excellent organization of this trip which seems to be very interesting and useful for the students. Especially I believe that the visit to the National Art Gallery will be a really exciting experience for all of us. All the students are enthusiastic about it.</P>
      <P>However, some of them have read an advertisment about the London Fashion and Leisure Show, which will take place at the Central Exhibition Hall in London on 14th March. The Exhibition will show all the latest fashion in a very wide range from sports wear to make up and even hairstyles. What is more, the show is free for all the students. We feel that taking part to it would be a great opportunity to us since we will be able to have some information about the world of fashion, which is becoming more and more important in our days.</P>
      <P>Under the circumstances, I was asked by the class to inform you about the show and to ask if it could be possible to make some changes in the programme if it could to visit the Exhibition. It will take place on Tuesday from 10.00am to 19.00pm, so we could give up the shopping and go to the show in the afternoon.</P>
      <P>I hope you will consider this possibility and tell us as soon as possible if you intend to accept our proposal.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Being famous and risk is something all of us have dreamt of sometimes. But not always famous people are happy of their condition. Usually if you ask them what they would desire most, the answer is: "I would like to be able to live like ordinary people do"</P>
      <P>There is no surprise to this answer: famous people can not have their own private life. Whenever they go out they are suddenly "hounded" by groups of journalists and photographers who want an interview or a photo. They can not even have a pizza with friend who stops them and asks them for an autograph. But the worst thing of all is that they are often victim of malicious gossips, which most of the times are not even true.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, I believe that it is certainly tight that famous people accept their condition, with all the advantages and disadvantages it brings, on the other hand, however, I think that they deserve to have a private life as all other people have. Also the most famous star can be unhappy and depresed: not always, in fact, money and celebrity being happiness.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
