<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR28*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>Thank you for the programme which you have organised the three days in London. However, some students in our class have seen an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show and we would like to have an opportunity to go to the show.</P>
      <P>The show is opened between ten and seven p.m on Tuesday, March 14 at Central Exhibition Hall in London. Latest fashions, leisure and sports wear, make up and hairstyles are expected to be displayed and studied. We have concerned it as a great opportunity to touch a part of latest cultures, which are concentrated and sharpened in London. In addition, the addmission for students is free.</P>
      <P>Taking the programme and the show into consideration, we suggest that we can have time to go to the show in the afternoon on Tuesday. We suppose that in free time on Wednesday we can find some time for shopping. We hope that you consider our suggestion.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerily,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>The ways of living are always changing. It is no doubt that functions and structures of the home have been changing as well as that of transformation, for example, have been. Thinking about the home of the future, first of all, nuclear families should be expected because of new technologies, which make house-keeping easier and simpler and because of the idea which encourages us to live in cities for convenient life. People may tend to avoid from.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, the bond between parents and children should be unlikly to change. People always need their parents, children and so on. The longer and further they live on their own, the more they may feel that they need a family.</P>
      <P>New materials will surly change the home of the future in any ways. It is just staff's around us improving and turning into new one. Hopefully, the minds of people will stay peaceful and tender in the future.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
