<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR30*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about your entertainment which was advertised in the last edition of "Plays". I am afraid that reality had nothing common with the things I suspected to meet.</P>
      <P>First of all, the prices weren't lower in any cases although you advertised the information like that. Then, I expected the show to start on time, but it turned out that I had to wait 45 minutes. Moreover, when the play started at last, I couldn't look at the actors. Especially I was disappointed by Danny Brook who made me nervous with his lack of talent.</P>
      <P>According to your advertisement, there was a possibility to have dinner in your restaurant, but I was surprised when I found it closed. After that, I should also mention, that this evening was dull, boring and the worst in my life.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you and I insist that you refund my lost money at once.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Come back to paradise</P>
      <P>There is no doubt that fashion affects people and makes them obsessed with this subject, but what can be designed more? Can you imagine the trend which will be as shocking as it has never been?</P>
      <P>The clothes is part of each culture and one of these things which expresses our taste and personality. People spend a lot of money to buy something extraordinary, feel comfortable and stand out. They come up with many ideas but it can't last for a long time. Nowadays it's getting obvious that designers sold only details, but significant changes don't turn up. Styles mix, colours and shapes come back from the past, only the fabrics are different.</P>
      <P>People look for something new but it is not so easy to be creative all the time. Teenagers are bored with casual fashion and their parents laugh at them because of the fact they wear common clothes. That's why I believe in the solution which is the closest to human nature and can help us to omit the boredome I am sure that at last we will take off our clothes and in the future we will be undressed and free there won't be any problem with being up-do-date.</P>
      <P>As it was previously stated I am convinced that the reality will turn out to be a paradise where the most important will be body and purity of our soul.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
