<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR33*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson</P>
      <P>My name is... and I am a student representative. I am writing to you on behalf of my class concerning our trip to London.</P>
      <P>First of all I would like to thank you for organizing the programme. I read it and found it very good, specially, Science Museum and National Art Gallery as I am interested in arts.</P>
      <P>However, I have a great proposition for you. Students in my class have recently seen an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show. I thing it is a great opportunity for us, as it is at the time of our being in London and is free of charge for students. Girls should like to see the latest fashion, new make-up and interesting hairstyles. Boys are interested in seeing leisure and sportswear.</P>
      <P>I would like to suggest a change in the programme by giving up shopping and going to the London Fashion and Leisure Show.</P>
      <P>I hope you will consider this proposition and I am looking forward to hearing form you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>THE HOME OF THE FUTURE</P>
      <P>Home is an important element in everybody's life. It gives you safety. I do not know people who would not want to have a home. We like our houses that is why are always trying to make it more comfortable and useful.</P>
      <P>I think The Home of the Future will be bigger as we will need more room for us, our belongings and interests. The construction will be more simple what will give us a feeling of balance. More houses will have gardens what will make us feel closer to the nature.</P>
      <P>Many people think that we will resign from a kitchen which is a useless place, as we will spend most of the time at work and will eat outside. I do not think so. Because of computers we will have the possibility of working at home, therefore, home will be very important place worth paying attention.</P>
      <P>Take care of your home, do not hesitate in it and you will be very happy.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
