<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR36*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms. Jane Clark,</P>
      <P>I am writing to give my opinion about the International Arts Festival which was held 21st and 22nd November.</P>
      <P>I went to the rock concert by U2 and the Chinese film "Chung King Express". Both of them were not only really enjoyable, but also reasonably-priced. However, I feel that it would be even better if there were some improvement.</P>
      <P>First of all, it would be greater if there were more famous people who have various nationalities. Because most of them were from English speaking country this year. In addition, larger halls should be provided for concerts since a lot of people could not get tickets for those by big stars. Moreover, personally, I hope that the number of plays and films will increase. I think they are the nearest 'arts' in real life.</P>
      <P>I would be glad if you consider my suggestions.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Money - hasn't it always been one of the most important problem for students? Of course, you can't afford a luxualy car and a large apartment unless you've born with a silver spoon. However, there are some good ways for you to earn enough money to enjoy yourself.</P>
      <P>How about working as a waiter or waitress? Not only it's a simple job, but also you can enjoy working with many colleague at your age. It would be great fan to make friends outside your class or club.</P>
      <P>If you say that the wage is far from satisfaction, why don't you teach younger students as a private teacher. It's also really popular job among university students because of the good salaly. If you are interested in teaching and responsible enough, you'll probably become an excellent teacher.</P>
      <P>Stop complaining about lack of money and let's start working to have a new world. You'll find that your life is becoming more and more enjoyable!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
