<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR38*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Robertson</P>
      <P>First of all, I want to thank you in the name of the class for your good organisation and programme, Especially for the fact that you are giving us some free time. We really appreciate this.</P>
      <P>However, we have seen an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show. The show is on Tuesday the 14th of March, from 10 oo to 19 oo o'clock in the Central Exhibition Hall. There will be shown the latest fashions about leisure and sports wear, make up and hairstyles.</P>
      <P>This is a great opportunity for us, because we haven't been ever before in this kind of show. As well as this, the entrance for students is free.</P>
      <P>As you can see this is the best time to go there. We have some suggestions about how to change the programme. Instead of visiting the Science Museum on Tuesday we could go there on Wednesday afternoon and instead of going shopping on Tuesday afternoon we could maybe stop at some places during the sightseeing tour and buy there something.</P>
      <P>To sum up, this is a really great opportunity for us and I don't think that the changes are so big. I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerelly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>The man is a being that need to live close to other human beings and to create a society around him. As well as this he needs his own free space and privacy. This is also important to him as friendship and family</P>
      <P>In our society some people are treated like animals in the zoo by the press. Just because they are famous and well known to a high number of other people. The newspapers print everything about them. The yellow press is searching for every little information they can get. The photographers are chasing these people, just to take a picture of them on how they eat or with who the meat. The photos will be on tomorrow's press and so rumours are born.</P>
      <P>On the other hand the people have choose to walk on this path. Everything in life has a price. The price for fame and money is the lost of privacy. First of all you have to give up something for getting something else.</P>
      <P>However, the press shouldn't create rumours and hunt those people like animals. As well as this, the stars shouldn't complaint at any time about their fans and their lost of privacy. They wanted to be famous and the had known the price before. The fans and the press are those who have made them rich and famous.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
