<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR39*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam!</P>
      <P>I'm writing to you because of the musical show "Over the rainbow", wich I visited on Friday the 16th of June in your theatre. There are several points I have to complain wich made the evening not nice at all.</P>
      <P>At first the show started much later than it was written out. Instead of half past seven the show startet at quarter past eight. I couldn't go to have a refreshment because of two reasons, the first one is that there was no information how much time the start of the show is going to be late. The second reason is that the restaurant of the theatre was closed because of building plans for the next two month.</P>
      <P>After I waited for about 45 minutes the show suddenly started but I had to realize that the main actor Danny Brook, who was the reason why I went into the show had been traded by an other actor, who couldn't sing as half as good then Brook.</P>
      <P>On your ticket information is written out that discounts are available, when I ask at the ticket reception I couldn't get any discount for beeng student.</P>
      <P>To make an result the evening in your theatre and the show was very disappointing and not like promised. For these reasons I want to ask you to get my money of £25 back.</P>
      <P>reasently</P>
      <P>Miss. Winkler</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>What is the prize?</P>
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. He didn't want to say what Sarah just had told him, it just came over his mouth, when he talked to James. "Sarah has won in a quiz show?" James was more than just interested, he wanted to know what she had won. But Pat made a promise not to tell anybody about the quiz show and he already had told enough.</P>
      <P>After one hour the hohle class had heard about Sarah's secret. Everybody was interested in what she had won but knowbody wanted to ask Sarah because it was told in a secret to them. Sarah realized that everybody was nice and friendly to her but something was going on in the class, when she turned around a talking and wispering started. Suddenly, she went to Pat and asked him did you tell anybody about our secret. Pat told her everything. Sarah looked at him for a while, than she stood in front of the class and explaind to the others, that she won a prize for 20 people to travel for 1 week to the sea of southern France and everybody of the 19 pupils was invited, except Pat who wasn't very good at keeping secrets.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
