<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR240*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>25th November 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Mr Clark,</P>
      <P>I have seen your advertisement in "the Sun" newspaper on 10th November, and I went to the festival on last Friday. Most of the events were wonderful and well-organised. I enjoyed it, but I think it could be even better next year, so I would like to give my inmature views of it.</P>
      <P>Firstly, the idea of holding this International Arts Festival is great. I made people enjoyed their weekend, relaxed themselves, also it brought the foreign culture to them, enlarged their kownlegth. In addition to it, one weekend ticket for all events was only £10, this was excellent, it made people only spend pocket-money, and then they could watch all the events at the weeked, for them it is really economical to spent their weekend. So my friends told me that was his cheapest weekend.</P>
      <P>Moreover, the stars and artists were only from six countries, In my opinion, if you can invite more stars and artists from more countries, it will make the festival more exciting, more intesting, and from my point of view, some concert halls were too small, the people in there couldn't even go to the loo! because it was too crowed. Finally, the plays and films were wonderfully welcomed, as far as I'm concerned. If you can show more play and films It will achieve a good effect.</P>
      <P>This are only my inmature views, if it is considerable for you, I will be very pleased, thank you very much.</P>
      <P>I'm look forward to hearing your replies.</P>
      <P>yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>16, Dec. 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Yasmin,</P>
      <P>It was really pleased to receive your letter yesterday, you asked me about rules; both at my home and at my school, I am very happy to tell you about this.</P>
      <P>At my school, we aren't allowed to smoke inside the building, because the building is made of wood, it tend to catch fire easily, and we aren't allowed to use Internet, there are only ten computers in the school, only teachers can use it, if we used, we would be sent to the head office of the school.</P>
      <P>At my home, there are many rules, because I'm careless, so I amn't allowed to smoke at home as well: and I'm not allowed to use telephone, because last year I made £1000 bill for one month, my parents were very angry with it, so they told me I am not to use telephone any more, oh, How poor!</P>
      <P>How is the weather like in England, I hope it isn't too wet, please give my regards to your parents.</P>
      <P>Lots of love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
