<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR241*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to make a complain about your theatre and the musical show "Over the rainbow".</P>
      <P>Firstly, in your advertisement was said that Danny Brook has a part in the show, but there was a different actor in the play. This fact disappointed me a lot. Secondly, there was written in the advertisement, that the show begins at 19.30, however, it started at 20.15.</P>
      <P>According to the advertisement, discounts should be available, but, in fact, I was refused to take the payment for tickets in this way. It was very uncamfortable for me. In addition to this, your theatre restaurant was closed because it was too late (the show did not start on time). Everybody, who came to it's doors, had to go to the other restaurant in bad mood. I could have understood this if the musical show had been marvellous, but it was not even quite interesting.</P>
      <P>Furthermore, I would like you to return my money. You promised me perfect evening out, but it was one of the most terrible in my life.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. She was 25-years-old secretary in one big company. Her boss was rich man, really rich. His name was Timson White. He was one of the most famous person in his city, but he wasn't honest with his clients. Pat had worked for him for two years. Certainly she knew a lot of secrets. One of them was about her boss' private life: he had got illegal son.</P>
      <P>Timson's wife, who was good looking and young, couldn't know about this, but one beautiful day she asked him how his son was and where he was at that moment. Timson was really shocked! He even couldn't say a word. He tried to make up who could give his wife knows. Of course, only one person had known this except his best friends. This was his secretary Pat, however, he couldn't be sure and decided to check it up.</P>
      <P>Next day he understood that he was right. Timson had a row at home and also needed new secretary. It was the worst weekends in a last few years. On the other hand, now everything is o.k. Timson has a good close family, his son lives with them, his company makes a good profit... Only Pat has problems, she should earn her living in other company again!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
