<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR245*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Manager,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about the Musical Show, I have seen last week. There is some disagreement a between your advertisement and show, which I could see at the Circle Theatre.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to indicate that you put wrong starting and finishing hours. The Musical started at 20:15 not at 14:30 - as you have mentioned. It was very surprising for me and I had got a lot of trouble with coming back home at night - when it finished.</P>
      <P>Furthermore, there was no Danny Brook at the stage. She is my famous artist and I was coming there mainly because of him. If this made me really disappointed - he wasn't playing there.</P>
      <P>Another point, I want you to consider, is restaurant. The place you have offered was closed and there was nothing to eat inside the theatre at all. Despite changing the hours, you have closed the restaurant without any reason. Could you possibly explain why you didn't provide us anything to eat?</P>
      <P>Finally, you have advertised, I would have perfect evening out. Unfortunately, I can't say that. I am very disappointed and I would like to ask you for giving my money back. I think, this could be the only, right possibility for me, to forget about my not interesting evening.</P>
      <P>I would appreciate it, if you could consider my complaint. I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>FASHION OF THE FUTURE</P>
      <P>Try to imagine: the wide, colourful street with many fantastic cars and shinny large shops. Try to think about people in weird black and grey clothes on them. It isn't a film, it isn't even a picture from mysterious books. It's a REALITY, its the FASHION OF THE FUTURE...</P>
      <P>People were wearing almost everything, during more than 2000 years of their living on Earth. Everything was changing: style, colour qual. Fashion. Their clothes were always strictly connected with their lifestyle, climate and money. We saw almost all kinds of skirts, trousers, coats, skirts and even hats - which untill nowadays are the main point of many fashion creatures. What can we suspect then? What something new hasn't been invented for now? I say it to you - black and grey. These are two powerful colours, which will be expanding for the nearest 100 years.</P>
      <P>The climate is changing, so we would have only two seasons. And we will need only two colours: grey for hot days and black for cold ones. Women will wear only skirts and dresses but men will be strictly connected with trousers. I hope, there will be times, when women would like to be again thought as delicate and sensible human beings. Showing their figure, they would have possibility to show their sexuality. But, don't forget, any exhibitionism! We have too many taken off people around us, now. And it will be the past. Streets of 21st century will be smart.</P>
      <P>So, are you interested in that style? Do you agree with me? If not, you are very poor. This fashion is coming, so think about it.</P>
      <P>Grey and black - like weather seasons, like people charakters, like all night and dark sourranding us. These are the colours of the FUTURE.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
