<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR246*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Manager,</P>
      <P>Recently, I had a week's holiday in London and during my stay, I went to your theatre to see "Over The Rainbow" and I was really disillusioned.</P>
      <P>In the advertisement, it was told that Danny Brook was starring, but in place of him there was a different actor and he was really dissapointing. I could not see any portion of Danny Brook's performance at him.</P>
      <P>Also, in the schedule, the time of the show was written as 19:30, but it started at 20;15 and, I missed the dinner I was going to have with my best friend in London.</P>
      <P>Since I am a student and not as rich as Bill gates, I was short of money and I was very pleased to hear that there were discounts available for the tickets; but I had to give the exact price of the ticket, which I consider as a fault of your theatre.</P>
      <P>In addition to these, it was mentioned that your restaurant was open after the show, but it was not because there was no food to be served.</P>
      <P>As you can understand, it was a dreadful time and I went my money back as a solace for the dissapointment I had.</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>TECHNOLOGY AND MY DAILY LIFE</P>
      <P>In my daily life, I use the facilities of modern technology very often and it really makes my life easier to live. However, I go far away from my family and other people and have virtual relationships.</P>
      <P>Until 1996, I used to go to school on foot or by public bus; but since 1996; I take the underground to go to school. It is much quicker, and I do not have to wake up very early in order not to be late.</P>
      <P>Also, I use my computer and Internet very much in order to reach some information, do my projects and communicate with my friends. To talk to a friend from another city or country instantly online is really nice and exciting. I do not have to wait for a letter for days and I gain so much time again.</P>
      <P>on the other hand, because of dealing with computers so much, I can not see my family and friends very much, even when we are at the same medium. It is really bad to make your human relations get weaker. But despite this, I am very happy with the facilities of technology in my daily life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
