<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR247*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms Jane Clark,</P>
      <P>Recently I visited an arts festival, organized with your help. I enjoyed it very much and I think the idea of its creation is great. However, I have some proposals about its improving next year.</P>
      <P>At first, I propose to invite stars and artists not from all the world, but from only six countries. This change will give opportunity to create some different performance.</P>
      <P>This year I noticed that there were only few plays and films. From my point of view, there should be more films because this part of the festival is interesting for people.</P>
      <P>And, at last, I should congratulate you with the decision of making one weekend ticket for all events. I support this idea which is convinient both for people and organisators.</P>
      <P>I hope you will consider my proposals.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward for this festival next year.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Ana,</P>
      <P>Thanks for your letter and postcard. It was really nice. The things you wrote about in your letter are quite common for me, because we, actually, have some problems about our rules.</P>
      <P>At first, about school.</P>
      <P>I'm really fed up with our school forne! It is awfull! And the problem is that nobody wants to wear it. That's why our headmaster is really angry. Off course, if we had such pretty forne like yours, we would wear it with pleasure. But it's impossible at the moment.</P>
      <P>What should I say you about home...</P>
      <P>We are quite friendly family, that's why we actually don't have some special rules. However, we promised our perents to make cleaning up every week.</P>
      <P>This is all I wanted to write you about rules.</P>
      <P>I miss you very much.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to see you next summer after my exams.</P>
      <P>Write me what do you think about it.</P>
      <P>Kisses to your family,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
