<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR248*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>During my stay in London I decided to see a musical show called "OVER THE RAINBOW" but, unfortunately I was very disappointed.</P>
      <P>At first, as I have read in your advertisement, Danny Brook should have stared in this show. A different actor has appeared, but I must say that he was very disappointing.</P>
      <P>Secondly, you have written that the musical starts at 19:30. I had to wait for the show for over fourty five minutes, because it started at about 20:15!</P>
      <P>What is more, it has been written that I can get some discounts, but when I wanted to buy a cheaper ticket, it was impossible.</P>
      <P>You have also placed a note about your theatre restaurant opened after the show. I wanted to drink a coffee but, unfortunately it was closed, because the waiter went out!</P>
      <P>To sum up, I must say that this evening out was supposed to be perfect. It was not of course, so I would like to ask you kindly for my money back, because some information placed in your advertisement about the musical was not true.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>In my opinion modern technology has changed my daily life very much.</P>
      <P>At first, there are now a lot of things that most people use at home. For example: a fridge, a cooker or just an electricity. We couldn't imagine our life without them.</P>
      <P>Secondly, thanked to the technology, there are many ways of travelling today. We produce cars, trains and plains which are better and better.</P>
      <P>What is more, there are many new ways to produce medicines and modern hospital equipement. It can really help a lot to cure people. Maybe it will be a remedium against AIDs or cancer soon.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, the modern technology has some disadvantages.</P>
      <P>The main is the ozone hole that affects all the people in the world.</P>
      <P>The second is the nuclear weapon and many wars, in which modern equipement is used.</P>
      <P>To sum up, as far as I am concidered, modern technology has changed my life completely. On the one hand it helps me a lot in daily life, but on the other I'm afraid of the future everyday.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
