<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR252*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen:</P>
      <P>I've recived your letter and I am pleased to have won because I needed some days to relax myself and to leave the city, which is very extressing.</P>
      <P>I only can travel on July because I am working in an office and I must ask my boss for a holiday and it's the mounth he can give me, so I hope it isn't a problem for you.</P>
      <P>To spend the two weeks I would prefer to live in tents, that's in my opinion a way to be nearer the enviroment and the animals, although I don't mind living in log cabins.</P>
      <P>In spite of liking all the sports you wrote in your letter I am only good at climbing and sailing, because I am used to practise them with my father since I was a child.</P>
      <P>I have got a doubt, it is not very important, but I would like to know if I need any money or all is payed , the kind of clothes I should wear, if the weather is good or bad... and all the extra information you can send me.</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for the prize.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully.</P>
      <P>Eliza Vasquez.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Why people like so much go shopping?</P>
      <P>In my opinion the majority of the people that go shopping are women who must buy food and other kind of things for her family, so for them, shopping is a very boring activity that is repeated everyday and that drive them crazy when they have to choose the best product and the cheapest price to save some money.</P>
      <P>Othrewise, there are people who think the opposite; such as: children, teenagers, men; but not always, because they go to buy hardly ever, only when they need clothes or something for their job or school. In that way shopping can be as funny as you want, although if you do it very often, it will be as an obligation in the future.</P>
      <P>To sum up, all you make in small cuantities is good and funny, but don't encrease them if you don't want to feel uncomfortable.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
