<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR256*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writing in reply to your letter asking for further information from me.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to travel in July because this is the beggining of my holidays, and I would not like to miss some of my school classes. Besides, I would preffer to stay in tents, because I got used to being in tents since each summer I spent my holidays with my friends at the hills.</P>
      <P>In adittion, I would rather playing tennis. When I was younger I won the National Tennis Championship. I also like surfing, I think it is a dangerous sport, but I know how to practice it, because of the fact that last year a proffessional surfer tought me.</P>
      <P>However, I would like to know what kind of clothes I should take and if it is possible for you to tell me how much money I will need.</P>
      <P>I would appreciate it if you could send me a reply at your earliest convenience.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>From my point of view, shopping is not always enjoyable, because sometimes when you are looking for a special good you never find it. Besides, I do not like to waste my time just seeing at a wide variety of products, that make you feel confused and you don't know which one fits you, instead of being with my friends or doing something else.</P>
      <P>I think that when you want to buy something you have to be sure of what you really need, if not the shop assistant has the ability to persuade you to buy something you do not want. Moreover in the shops that sales fashionable clothes. Although it is wonderful to buy new things, there are times that it really become tiring.</P>
      <P>To summarize, I could say that if you want to buy something, first make sure what sort of product you need and then, go shopping. If not shopping never be enjoyable, but also tiring and boring.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
