<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR257*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>MR. MANAGER,</P>
      <P>I'M WRITING YOU TO COMPLAIN ABOUT THE MUSICAL SHOW "OVER THE RAINBOW" WICH WAS PRESENTED LAST WEEK. YOUR ADVERTISING LEAFLET WAS COMPLETELY WRONG, IT SAID THAT DANNY BROOK WAS ACTING BUT, WHEN I GOT THERE, THERE WAS ANOTHER GUY ON STAGE. IT WAS DISAPPOINTING, SPECIALLY FOR ME WHO IS A GREAT FAN OF DENNY. THAT'S NOT ALL! IT STARTED FORTY-FIVE MINUTES AFTER THE RIGHT TIME AND WE HAD TO WAIT OUTSIDE THE THEATRE. THE TICKETS WERE SUPPOSED TO HAVE DISCOUNTS BUT THE LADY WHO WAS SELLING TOLD ME THAT I MUST BE WRONG, THEY NEVER GIVE ANY DISCOUNTS TO ANYONE.</P>
      <P>AFTER THE SHOW, I WENT TO VISIT YOUR RESTAURANT AS SUGGESTED ON THE ADVERTISEMENT BUT WHEN I GOT THERE IT WAS CLOSED. ONE OF THE EMPLOYEES OF THE THEATRE TOLD ME THAT IT WAS BECAUSE THEY WERE CLEANING IT TO GET RID OF THE RATS. I'VE NOT IMPRESSED WHEN HE TOLD ME THIS.</P>
      <P>FOR ALL THIS REASONS MY EVENING WAS TERRIBLE AND I WOULD LIKE TO RECEIVE AT LEAST PART OF MY MONEY BACK.</P>
      <P>YOURS SINCEARLY</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>SINCE I WAS BORN, SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY ARE DEVELOPING FASTER AND FASTER, JUST AS EXAMPLE, INTERNET GETS HUNDREDS OF NEW USERS EVERY SINGLE DAY. THIS TECHNOLOGY CHANGED OUR LIFE IN MANY WAYS AND WE ALMOST DON'T NOTICE IT.</P>
      <P>IN MY CASE, I'M COMPLETELY INTEGRATED WITH THEM, ALMOST EVERYTHING I DO I USE THIS TECHNOLOGY. WHEN I WAS YOUNGER I USED TO READ BOOKS, WRITE, LISTEN TO THE RADIO AND, NOWADAYS, YOU CAN DO ALL THIS THINGS USING A COMPUTER. IT'S ONE OF THE MOST USEFUL TOOLS THAT MEN INVENTED IT'S POSSIBLE TO DO LOT'S OF THINGS AND TALK TO OTHER PEOPLE TOO USING A PC. MOST OF MY DAY I SPEND IN FRONT OF ONE OF THOSE MACHINES, STUDYING, RESEARCHING, PLAYING AND TALKING TO FRIENDS ALL AROUND THE WORLD.</P>
      <P>THIS TECHNOLOGY HAS ALSO IT'S BAD ASPECT, IT MAKES YOU MORE FAR FROM PEOPLE, ISOLATED FROM TRUE RELATIONSHIPS BUT YOU CAN HANDLE IT WHEN YOU GOT USED TO THIS.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
