<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR784*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>13 June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Ms. Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am very pleased to be the winer in your competition. I almost could not believe it when I received the letter you had sent. I have never won a prize like this. Thank you indeed!</P>
      <P>I am working as a Mechanical Engineer for a well-known car company and I would like to travel in July because this the only month I can use my annual leave.</P>
      <P>During this exciting holiday I would prefer staying in a log cabin. The reason for this is that I have got a difficulty in sleeping in tents.</P>
      <P>When I was at the Univercity I was very keen on basket ball and I was playing in Univercity's team. In 1998 we were the champion of the First National Leque. Also I am a quite good swimmer. I think that is because of my long legs. So I would love to join Basketball and Swimming activities while I am at the Camp.</P>
      <P>There is something I need to ask you;</P>
      <P>I don know exactly what is California's weather lime. What kind of clothes I need to bring with me? Also, what is the currency in California and how much money I need to take with me?</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to your reply!</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely </P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>Novadays our shopping habits seem to be changed. I can clearly remember my childhood and our only local shop. Yes! There was only one shop in the area where I used to live until we moved to Oxford. I was really astonished by all these shopping centers like ASDA, HOMEBASE, ex.</P>
      <P>One day I decided to go to the shopping center which is only 40 meters from our house. Firstly, I could not find the entrance. I'd walked arround about 15 minutes until I found the door. I realized that I'd walked so many times in front of the entrance but the door had looked like a window. When I entered into the shope I was a bit angry.</P>
      <P>I was holding a peace of paper which my mum gave to me. There were written all things I had to buy. But no way!</P>
      <P>I started looking for the food products written on the paper but I found only the eggs, milk and bread. Nothing else. So what was all that about?! I wasted 2 hours to buy food which you can find in every local shop.</P>
      <P>Later somebody told me that I had to look at the labels on the top.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
