<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR259*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear sir,</P>
      <P>I bought a ticket for the "Over the Rainbow" musical show last Saturday, but I felt very disappointed with it. It was announced that there would be discount tickets available, but there were not. The show should have started at 19.30, but it delayed forty-five minutes. And, the worst of all: Danny Brook was not on stage. He was replaced by a novice actor who made a very disappointing performance. Last, the theatre restaurant was closed because there was a serious leak in a tube and the kitchen was flooded.</P>
      <P>I think there are sufficient reasons for money back. I just wanted to have a pleasant evening out and I could ever imagine that there would be so many troubles.</P>
      <P>I really expect that you consider my arguments and cash me back the value of the ticket, as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Several technological advances in the past five years have changed my daily life. Nowadays, I feel myself entirely linked to these innovations, and I would find it hard to live without them.</P>
      <P>Internet is certainly the most evident of all these innovations. Information is spread quickly and you can access in minutes a wide range of data, that would take a much longer time to be found by traditional means. For a shy person, like me, Internet has another attractive: the possibility of knowing people and making friends worldwide. It's very exciting. Currently, I exchange e-mails with dozens of people all over the country.</P>
      <P>Modern technology granted other facilities: I can pay my bills at any time and do not need to wait on a big queue to be attended by the cashman, I can exchange photos and videos via computer, I can do business and make money at home, and so on.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
