<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR260*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms Ryan</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter. I was so happy to hear that I have won a two weeks holiday in the U.S.A.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel in July. I am going to finish my exams in June, and I am planning to go back to China in early August. So if I could travel in July, and coming back before 6th of August, that would be great.</P>
      <P>I would prefer living in tents to log cabins. I have never had any experience to live in a tent, so I would like to give it a go. I think I will enjoy myself in a tent.</P>
      <P>I love swimming, but I am not any good at swimming. I really wanted to learn how to swim. I was wondering if there is a coach could give us a lesson during the Camp. Also, I would like to join basketball team, I used to play basketball when I was in high school, and our high school basketball team have won many competitions during last ten years in our city. I am glad I had taken a part in a few competitions, and I was so proud of our basketball team.</P>
      <P>Would you tell me that how much money you would give it to me and how is the weather like in U.S.A. Thank you for every thing!</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>It was great to hear from you, haven't seen you since last summer holiday, hope everything is fine in your place.</P>
      <P>You wanted to hear about my experience at the pop concert which I enjoyed helping last month? I must say that was a great fun, I've never had this kind of experience before. Before the concert actually started I had to give out lots of leaflets, they are list of pop band and group which will appear in the concert in order, and some information about their performance and backgrounds. After that, I had to help people who had a ticket but can't find their seat. During the concert, I didn't have a lot to do, so I had chance to see most of the performance, that was excellent. I was excited that I had a closer look at so many famous pop stars. During break time I did give a lots of direction to people who can't find toilet, and information such as where they could have a cup of coffee. That was bit boring, but it was part of my job.</P>
      <P>I got to go. Write to you next time.</P>
      <P>Love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
