<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR264*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson</P>
      <P>I am writing to you about the trip to London. All of the students in my class have read through the programmes that you have set, they are quite interesting, especially the river trip to Greenwich, because some of us may go to the university there next year. So we can walk around and see how it looks like in Greenwich.</P>
      <P>All of us want to go to this trip, but some of my classmates saw an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show, and we all would like to go there. It is from 10 am to 7 p.m., it is about the latest fashion, leisure and sports wear, make up and hairstyles, all of us are really interesting, and it is free for student to get in as well. It is a really good opportunity to go because most of us are studying fashion design, and we can learn loads of things in there. So may you please change the visit of the Science Museum to Wednesday afternoon, and we can cancel our shopping and free time, so we can go to the fashion show on Tuesday.</P>
      <P>Yours Faithfully.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>It was dangerous, but I knew I had to do it.</P>
      <P>It was two years ago, me and my classmates went to a leadership trip in London. This trip was organised by our form tutor, he wanted to test us if we trust each other and worked in a team, and the trip last for 3 days. The first days was going fine, we just had to do some teamwork things.</P>
      <P>In the second day, we had to climb up a twenty metres hill with our hands. It was so difficult for me because I was really scared to stand in a high place since I was young. I did not want to climb up but I did not have any choice. So I started to climb really slow and careful, and I climbed about 15 metres quite success, so I tried to climb quicker because the destination was not far away. But after I climbed two steps more, my right feet slipped over, I was nearly fell down, but luckly my hand caught a rock, it was dangerous, but I didn't had any choice, finally I did it.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
