<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR265*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>17-6-00</P>
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam:</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about the musical show: Over the Rainbow, presented in your theatre on 15th of June.</P>
      <P>I went to the theatre to buy the ticket and expected to have a discount as I was a student. However, the salesman in the box office told me the discount tickets had been sold out. I could not understand why but still bought the ticket because I was crazy about Danny Brook. Then, I went into the theatre on time but became a little bit angry for waiting until 20:15, forty-five minutes after the expected starting time. Furthermore, I was so disappointed to find out that Danny Brook was not on the stage and the leading actor sang so bad that I left the theatre before it finished. At last, I went to the theatre restaurant but it was closed because it needed cleaning.</P>
      <P>I think it was definitely not a perfect evening as garenteed in your advertisement. I look forward to having a full refund in the very near future as I did not enjoy it at all.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. Now everybody in the class knew my mum was a cleaner and teased me for having such kind of mum. I was so sad about it and did not forgive Pat even though she apologise for thousands of times.</P>
      <P>A week later, when I was still in a bad mood, my form teacher, Mrs Brown, talked about jobs in our English lesson. She told us there were numerous types of job in the world. Some offered a high salary while some did. However, they are equal important for our society. 'Who wants to be a doctor?' She asked. Many students raised their hands. 'Who wants to be a lawyer?' Again, many students put up their hand. But when she asked who wanted to be a cleaner, nobody raised his hand and I felt so shameful that I lowered my head. 'Cleaner is a very good job.' Mrs Brown said with a loud voice. 'If there were no cleaner, who would clean the school for us, who would keep the environment nice and tidy.' Suddenly, all the classmates applauded and smiled to me with respect. The teacher also grinned and I was so impressed and repeated the words in my heart: 'All the jobs have the same importance.'</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
