<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR266*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>Being on a holiday trip in London, I dreamed to go to the theatre for a musical show. I saw your advertisement last Monday, and thought "It is that one that I want to try."</P>
      <P>In fact, your musical show was attractive: actors, time, restaurant, discount tickets, and also the title! I started to be OK with the "Your perfect evening out", sure not to be deceived.</P>
      <P>But all was disappointing! First, as I am very found of Danny Brook, I have been surprised he totally changed his voice, face, and so on! It was not Danny on the scene! Second bad point: beeing not narrowminded, I accept other actors.. but if the show begin on time - he began at a quarter past eight P.M.</P>
      <P>There were no discount places because it was not planed like this by the theatre. What was written on the advertisement?</P>
      <P>The summum was reached when I saw the restaurant was closed for "holidays".</P>
      <P>I was terribly ennoyed! I spent the worse evening of my holiday in this show!</P>
      <P>So I need now a "perfect - money back -" for replacement of your "perfect evening out".</P>
      <P>I do hope you will accept and understand this request.</P>
      <P>Yours:</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>"How has modern technology changed your daily life?" First of all, "daily life" concerns (as far as I am concerned) my life everywhere, and more precisely at home, at the university and at work. Up to two years ago, I was working with a written booknote or agenda, and I used to phone with a wired phone system. Nowaday, I organise my activities with an electronic organizer that authorizes me to connect to Internet by infra-red link with my mobile phone to get informations and electronic mails. I am always joinable with my mobile phone, that is also sometimes boring! Being in an apprenticeship, I go both work and university. At the university, I have learned with computer aided systems. I often go on Internet to find informations for studying a precise subject more accutely (university technology sites). At work my personal job uses two standard PC with specifical softwares plus one workstation with the Stanford University Network (SUN) operating system and a particular computer that my firm is developping now. At home, I have got a personal computer for my mails and accounts, and electronic mail plus internet for keeping connected to my friends that are at the other end of France or Germany, Korea and so on. So modern technology has totally changed my daily life!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
