<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR267*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about the musical show which is called OVER THE RAINBOW. I saw the show on 17th of July.</P>
      <P>Firstly, the advertisement claimed discount ticket was available. Although I have a student card for discounts I could not get any discount. So I had to buy a normal ticket.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I bought a second musical show ticket which start at 19:30 but it started at 20:15. As a result, I had to wait over one hour as I arrived there at 19:00.</P>
      <P>Thirdly, your advertisement misled I could see Danny Brook in the show who I adore. When I turned up the show, there was another actor instead of him.</P>
      <P>Fourthly, after the show the theatre restaurant was closed because of it's problems. But I could go evening out.</P>
      <P>To sum up, I believe your advertisement completely misled. So I am fully entitled to ask for refund except for evening out.</P>
      <P>I hope this matter will recieve your prompt attention.</P>
      <P>yours faithfully</P>
      <P>BO-PHAT SUN (MS)</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Nowadays, mordern technology has increasingly been developing. We get many advantages which make improve our lives daily, on the other hands, we get also many disadvantages which could harm us.</P>
      <P>In my opinion, the main advantage is developing of medical technology. For example, if you were hurt seriously like cutting leg, the new medical technology could rebuilit part of your body. Another advantage is sharing information. The more developing the technology is, the quicker and easier international networking is. So at the same time many people can share some information even though they live in different country.</P>
      <P>In contrast, the technology can cause a pollution. By developing of transport, we can get wherever you want to go easily, however it could cause serious air pollution like acid-rain and smog. Also we should be careful as we could be watched by security carmera which has been combined with mordern technology.</P>
      <P>In conculsion, I conciderly said we has been charged by morder technology in two way. One is advantage and the other is disadvantage. And it will change our lives, also in the future.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
