<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR268*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I'm writing this letter to you, because during my stay in London, I went to the theatre to see a musical show, and I had a very disappointing evening.</P>
      <P>Last Saturday I went to see "Over the Rainbow". When I read the advertisement, I noticed that Danny Brook acted in this musical show. I appreciated him a lot. When the show started forty-five minutes later, I realised that the main actor had been changed. That change really disappointed me. Another problem was that I didn't have any discount, and I wasn't alone, we were five persons. Our idea after the show, was to visit the theatre restaurant, but it was closed. Nobody could give me an answer. I really had an awful evening.</P>
      <P>Please send me a letter, with the explanations for all these problems that I told you. Next time, be more careful with what you put in your advertisement.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to receiving your letter.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Secrets</P>
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good a keeping secrets. That night my parents went out, so I had to stay home with Pat. I invited my best friends, and I asked Christian to bring some videos. We left Pat in her room with those videos, and we went to the top of the house, the third floor.</P>
      <P>That room was totally dark. We went upstairs with only a candle, and the idea of planning something crazy.</P>
      <P>Manuel had a farm, no so long from the town, where we could do whatever we wanted. But what was the problem. We were too young to stay a hole weekend alone. I thought of the idea of telling our parents that we had a camping with the school. We were all agree. We were going to spend a weekend alone, with nobody else, playing football, going to bed at the time we wanted, talking about girls. It was perfect.</P>
      <P>We were very calm, discussing the last details of our weekend, when we heard a noise that came out from a room that was near us. Manuel opened the door, and there she was, Pat with Ramiro's sister hearing all our conversation.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
