<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR269*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>41-50</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thanks a lot for your briefly and nice letter. I am very pleased to give you the information required:</P>
      <P>Firstly, the most suitable month would be in July because I am very busy in my work now, and my children are in holiday then.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I prefer to stay in log cabins, because they are more comfortable. I confess you that I have never been in a tent and till now I have never had the intention to do it.</P>
      <P>The activities are really interesting and I would take part on Painting and Climbing. I am not very good painting, but I like it because is a good oportunity to practice it. Personally, Climbing is an interesting activity, where you need concentration and you are working with your whole body. I don't want to dissapoint you, but I am beginner! I choose these activities because I love challenges.</P>
      <P>I would appreciate if you can tell me a couple of ideas about clothes I need there. Thanks in advance.</P>
      <P>Sincerely,</P>
      <P>G. Ramos</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="5a">
      <P>Wuthering Heights - Emily Brontë</P>
      <P>Not only bad characters in a story are more interesting than the good ones, but also this take your attention.</P>
      <P>In this book, Heathcliff as a child hadn't a bad character but the situations lived with the family Earnshaw, where the grown up, made him rude, agresive and noisy.</P>
      <P>Heathcliff used to play with Catherine. They were good friends but Heanly, brother of Catherine, hatted Heathcliff. Heanley couldn't accept the good relationship and love between Catherine and Heathcliff and, for that reason he sent Heathcliff to work in the farm. In the mean time Catherine knew Edgar Linton and at the end she married Edgar because of money and good education.</P>
      <P>Heathcliff promised himself and worked his whole life taking a revenge. Before Heathcliff died he riched what he wanted. The houses and money of the families Earnshaw and Linton, all belonged to him. and he was buried near to Catherine!, his great and only love!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
