<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR270*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Geneva, 13th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan</P>
      <P>Thank you a lot for your kind letter. I was very surprised on the result of the competition. Now I am happy to give you all the information you need.</P>
      <P>I think it would be better for me to travel on July. I will started an Italian course in August, so it will be impossible for me to leave.</P>
      <P>In your letter you ask me to choose beetween tents or log cabins, well I prefer to stay in a log cabin. It is more confortable and I am afraid about wild animals. I saw, you offer a lot of activities, that'is fantastic! It is very difficult to decide which two of these activities I like and I can also do the best. I think I choose singing because I have sung for five years in a church chorus and I do it very well. The other activity I like very muche is swimming. I took part at a lot of competitions.</P>
      <P>Now I would like to ask you if wee need some money and if it is necessary to take with me special clothes. I hope I have give to you all the information you needed and I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>B. Müller</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Geneva, 13th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Kim</P>
      <P>I am happy to tell you about the experience I made at the pop concert last month.</P>
      <P>I had to start very early in the morning, at 7.30. We first had to prapare the stands with food and drinks and buy something which had been forgotten. Then we had to put on the night lights and decorate the whole room.</P>
      <P>In the afternoon the singers cames in and I also could have an interview with Ricky Martin. I was very excited! He is very beatiful! At the end of the interview he invites me to have dinner with him after the concert. I logically accepted. The interview I liked particularly Before the concert started, we had to verify all music instruments. The microphones all had to be controlled. Fortunatly we had no problem. The concert was a success. I was very proude of me and the work I had done. After concert I left with Ricky Martin. We went to a nice restaurant and enjoyed dinner together.</P>
      <P>I am sure my dear Kim, I will never forget that wonderful experience.</P>
      <P>Now I hope you will answer soon and tell me a bit of your adventure or experience you had in last time.</P>
      <P>lot of kisses</P>
      <P>your friend BM</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
