<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR271*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Saturday, June, 17th</P>
      <P>Dear M. White,</P>
      <P>I went to the Circle theatre last week on monday and I would say that I had a very disappointing evening, there.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I've read in the advertisement that the actors who were playing that night were D. Brook and T. Truelove. Now you can guess how disappointed I was when I saw that there were different (and worse) actors!</P>
      <P>Secondly, the musical show started at 20.15 instead of 19.30.. so I had to wait forty-five minutes outside and it was raining cats and dogs!</P>
      <P>And then I discovered that the discounts were not available for the tickets. Moreover, the theatre restaurant was closed after the show and I was really hungry because I hadn't had my dinner that evening in order to be on time for the show.</P>
      <P>To sum up, It wasn't a "perfect evening out". I'd rather say that it was a catastrophe! And I am really sorry, but consequently I would ask you for some money back. Thank you for considering my request.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Modern technology has completly changed my daily life, which became more comfortable, and easier.</P>
      <P>For instance, my discman gives me the possibility to listen to music or to the radio everywhere: in the underground, or when I walk in the city. Moreover, it disturbs nobody, and that's great.</P>
      <P>Another simple example is my mobile telephone; A few years ago, I had to buy a telephone card and then to find a telephone box to call my parents and to tell them that I would be late for dinner, or other stuff like that. Yet my hand phone is in my bag and I bring it everywhere.</P>
      <P>But I think the best technological invention which changed my life is the internet - Thanks to it, I have hundred friends all over the world and I know many different cultures.</P>
      <P>All these examples are very few demonstrations to show how technology could affect our lives nowadays. In my point of view, modern technology is a great thing unless it is used to serve bad intentions.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
