<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR272*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>Thank you for the exellent programme you organised for our class. We especially look for make the River trip to Greenwich.</P>
      <P>However we have send an advertisement for the "London Fashion and Leisure Show", which will take place on the Tuesday 14th March from 10.00 am to 19.00 pm during our trip in London and in which the follow topics will be showed:</P>
      <P>. Latest fashion</P>
      <P>. Leisure and sports wear</P>
      <P>. Make up</P>
      <P>. Hairstyles</P>
      <P>We would like to inform you that we all extremly interested in this show and that it could be a great opportunity for us because the entrance is free for the studends.</P>
      <P>We would like to request if we could go to this show on the 15th March instide off the visit in the Science Museum. We could make this one on the Wednesday 15th March afternoon.</P>
      <P>Thank you in advanced for your comprehention and we look forward to hearing for you.</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely, </P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>The private life of famous people!</P>
      <P>Who have never dreamed to be a famous singer, sportman, actor or a politician? The success of these people is so big that they are known all over the World.</P>
      <P>I think that this kind of people have a poor life because they never can be quiet because all the poeple know them and want to know a lot of things about them. They have always to be careful about what they say and what they do.</P>
      <P>In my opinion I think that if famous people is always followed by journalists it is not the responsability of the media but of the huge quantity of people who are interested in famous people life. Firstly, because it is a lot of "scandale magazine readers". Secondly, because they have admiration for them and lastly because they want dreams and see what a "star life" look like.</P>
      <P>In conclusion I think that people who are to much interested in other people life have not an interesting life and are unhappy! </P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
