<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR273*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Smith,</P>
      <P>I went to London last week for business and loving very much theatre I had promised my friend to offer her, after work, a very good evening with your musical show: "Over the Rainbow".</P>
      <P>I had read about it that was a very enjoyable show! What a surprise!</P>
      <P>Your advertisement was a quite lie and I have to tell you my disappointment. Every point were wrong. (I wondered if it was a fake!)</P>
      <P>At first, from your advert Danny Brook (who is a very good singer I appreciate very much) was not here. An unknown man was singing, not in tone - awful for my ears - (poor Tina Truelove! such a professional singer with a beginner!)</P>
      <P>At second, to go on with the beginning, your show started not at 19.30 but nearly one hour later (20.15 to be more precise!)</P>
      <P>And for the third point, I would hope to offer a good diner to my friend because I knew your restaurant as a famous place but I was still disappointed. It was closed for some improvements!</P>
      <P>I hope you will understand my evening was detestable and you will give me back my money.</P>
      <P>I join this letter my two tickets.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you</P>
      <P>Best wishes</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets!</P>
      <P>Poor of I, I thought it was nice to have a friend and to be able to share lots of things!</P>
      <P>I was very young when this story happened but though it was a child's adventure I remember it yet. I was just thirteen years old!</P>
      <P>I had read a very good book about pirates and I know I got a very creative imagination. To make to profit my ideas my parents lived in a small village near a wonderful country.</P>
      <P>Like my heros I would like to live in a ship and decided to build something in a tree. The highest tree near a river I have ever seen. Peaceful place and wonderful view.</P>
      <P>With my friend Pat (I put him in the confidence) I started to work and my idea became real.</P>
      <P>It was our fortress and every day we could improve it. The tree was our ship and the river the sea. We could play hours and hours without seeing an adult or other children from the village. I prefered it. It was our secret Pat and I. Child's secret.</P>
      <P>But Pat could not keep it too long. He had a fault: he talked a lot and told an other friend our story. What a catestrophee! All children went from the village and wanted to play with us. I accepted them but I was very angry against Pat. Our quietness disappeared and very fast everybody wanted to command my ship. A desaster!</P>
      <P>There was lots of fights between us and we were naughty like child could be with other child.</P>
      <P>The result was my ship was destroyed and never more I could trust in any friend!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
