<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR274*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Miss Ryan,</P>
      <P> I am writing in reply to your letter, informing me that I have won the prize in your competition which is two weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A.</P>
      <P>I am really pleased to hear that the prize includes accommodation. I would like to stay in a tent, because I have been camping nearly every summer since my childhood and I really love it.</P>
      <P>I would be really happy if I could apply Singing and Photography as the activities you have written about. Singing has been my only hobby since I was 5. I could say that I am quite good at it. However, I used to assist my brother, who is a profecional photographer. So that, I consider myself expirienced enough.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask you whether going there in July is possible. I am afraid that July is the only appropriate month, because I am due to start work in August.</P>
      <P>Finally, I would like to ask you for further information about spending allowance and the clothes which I am supposed to take.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I'm sorry I haven't written for so long. But I've been quite busy just recently.</P>
      <P>Last month, I helped at a pop concert which I really enjoyed. The singer, who took place, wasn't one of my favourites, but having the opportunity to experience being stuff there, was just amazing. I was just behind the stage. I was supposed to help my friend with the lights, so that I could see all that screaming like made crowd. I even saw crying girls, who were trying to reach the pop-singer.</P>
      <P>Do you know what Kim, I've never thought before, that enjoying yourself like this, could be weirdly. I think you never realize this, until you're not a part of the crowd. But I'm really happy, that I had even small role in making people enjoying themselves. I mean, all that flashing lights, the changing colours of them, I believe they helped much. Even though I was just telling my friend what the next composition of colours was, I consider myself being very successful.</P>
      <P>And finally, the greatest news. I was introduced to the singer by my friend, who works for him. This was maybe the best part of being there. He was so nice and he even gave me his picture whit his signature on it. I suppose, I will never forget that night.</P>
      <P>That's about all my news, I'm looking forward hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Lots of love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
