<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR275*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>Last week I spent my holiday in London and I've seen your musical "Over the rainbow' in the Circle Theatre and I was really disappointed. When I read the advertisment for the show I was really excited but after the show I was not very happy because of the following problems.</P>
      <P>The advertisment says that Danny Brook and Tina Truelove would play but in this show there were totally different actors and that was really disappointing because I was looking forward to them. The times were also not alright, actually the show starts at 19.30 but in this evening it started at 20.15. The advertisment also says that there are discounts available but this is not true, there were none.</P>
      <P>Usually I go to a restaurant after theatre but this was also not possible because your theatre restaurant was closed because of holiday. Why do you give those information in an advertisment.</P>
      <P>For me it was really not a perfect evening, I was expecting a nice evening but in fact it was terrible.</P>
      <P>Because of these problems I had I would like to ask for a compensation, maybe to get my money back. I hope you understand my complains. I wish you answer me soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Sandra Eichmann</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>In my opinion the modern technology has changed my daily life not really a lot because I am just 20 years old and I used to play computer when I was young or wash my clothes in the washing machine.</P>
      <P>I grew up in a world with full of technology and for me the development in the technology is not very big. Of course, it changes, it became normal to have a mobile phone or to use mainly the computer and the internet. It becomes more and more easier to use the computer for everything. You don't have to go to the shop to buy clothes or to the restaurant to order some food. I can just switch on my computer and order everything. I also don't write letters anymore because I write e-mails to my friends. That goes quicker and it is easier for me.</P>
      <P>But I think in my generation it is not a really big difference. In comparison to my grandparents they have really problems to accept these changes in modern technology. Because the biggest developments were in the last 50 years.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
