<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR276*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Thank you very much for this occasion I'd like to travel only in July, because, in the rest of the year, I'm working in a bank. The second reason is the weather. I love travelling when the weather is warm. About the accommodation, I'd prefer to stay in log cabins, because for me and my family's more comfortable. I have a baby and three dogs, so it should be better in log cabins.</P>
      <P>I'd like spend all of time in a swimming-pool because I love swimming. I like also surfing, because I love the wind in the hair and the fresh on my body.</P>
      <P>Only one question about a baby's accomodation. May I have a babysitter? I'd like to have more free time for myself and my health.</P>
      <P>I've never been there, so it will be a pleasure for me.</P>
      <P>Let me say still thank you.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to meting you</P>
      <P>Best regards</P>
      <P>Irene Venerio</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>How are you? I'm fine. I'm sorry I didn't write you before, but I was so busy with my exams.</P>
      <P>First of all, I want to tell you what happened last month. Do you remember which is my favourite group? So, You don't believe me, but I enjoed helping at a Oasis's pop concert. I was a great and wonderful experience. The group needs to found a good microphone for the concert, because the singer lost his microphone last concert. Me and my friend were there to hear the sound-check, and when I understood was happing on the stage, I decided to help them. Of course you know, I'm a singer, so I came back quigky to my home, I picked my microphone, and I handed it to the singer.</P>
      <P>The concert was absolutely fantastic. I was so glad, because in the ending of show the singer kissed me and dedicated to me a lovely song. Can you immagine? Ok, write me soon, huge hug and kisses</P>
      <P>Yours Irene</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
