<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR277*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>Re: The Musical Show Presented by the Circle Theatre</P>
      <P>With the reference of the advertisement published in the New Strait Times newspaper on the 22nd of MAY 2000, I, as a consumer, who is a musical show avid and a great fans of Danny Brook, who is said to be stared in the show, would like to complain about the presentation.</P>
      <P>1. First of all, I was really furious of watching a show starring by a different actor, instead of Danny Brook. whose name was stated on the advertisement. Besides this, the show started almost 45 minutes later than what it was said to be.</P>
      <P>2. The Price. However, I was completely disappointed when I was told that there were not any discounts for the show.</P>
      <P>3. I also found out that the theatre restaurant was not opened after the show due to the shortage of food sold. I was really hungry after the show and was pissed off.</P>
      <P>With all the above points, I would like to ask for some money return. I would consider to bring this complains to the court if I do not receive any agreeable explaination from the theatre. Thank You.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Fashion is one of the most popular topics people discuss about in the past, now and also in the future.</P>
      <P>However, things re recycling from time to time. So do the objective of wearing clothes. I will imagine that, people in the future, for example 100 years from now, will wear clothes for protection like people did in the past. The people in the past wear clothes to protect themselves from the cold air, hot weather and strong wind. On the other hand, the people in the future will propably wear clothes to protect themselves from the polluted air and water, the harmful ultra-violet rays from the sun and all the dangerous and poisonous gases or chemicals which is result of a developed and full-grown country.</P>
      <P>I think people in the future will likely to wear helmets with oxygen gas well provided. It is because of the increasing number of population and the shortage of the oxygen gas in the atmosphere. They will also wear water-proof, ultra-violet proof and other dangerous liquid-proof clothes to protect themselves These clothes have to be made of something light, suitable to wear and protective. All the above ideas are needed to make them bare when wearing these special designed clothes.</P>
      <P>The future is a hope and a dream for everyone in the earth. Therefore, I will suggest that we all nov to keep the enviroment clean and healthy for the next generation.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
