<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR785*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>14th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Miss Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am really pleased to be the winner of your competition and I cannot help thinking about the two weeks in the USA.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to travel only in June given that my wife will come with me: her holiday are only in June.</P>
      <P>Concerning accommodation at Camp California, would it be possible to live in log cabins? Indeed, my wife is afraid of sleeping in tents.</P>
      <P>Moreover, I practice Basketball in a famous French Club: That is the reason why I would like to choose the Basketball. If I had to chose an other activity, I think I would do Photography. In fact, this activity seems to be very interresting. Unfortunately, I have never practiced but I feel to like discovering that.</P>
      <P>Finally, I would want to ask you whether we had to bring money: Life is so expensive there! Furthermore, what sort of clothes must we have for the different activities?</P>
      <P>I hope my answers will satisfy you. I thank you again.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Tom Turner</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>After having thought about this video and asked different people so as to know what they suggested, I reached the following conclusions: we must film the lessons which are the most important and the activities which take a great part in a day at school; this being in three parts.</P>
      <P>the morning</P>
      <P>That is why I propose to start our film with the beginning of the day, when all students come in class. Then, we should film the English class so as to show who makes the film. Furthermore, as Mathematics are the main lesson in the morning, we ought to film a time where we are in MathClass</P>
      <P>the lunch</P>
      <P>After that could come the lunch which takes two hours per day. The better to do would be to present the cooking personnal for they are very nice.</P>
      <P>the afternoon</P>
      <P>We could begin the afternoon with the sport, showing the different places with surroundings (near the wild): it would give a good impression. I advise to finish with a lesson of Chemistry so that people see the laboratery. Before that, I would have showed the break at 3 o'clock which is important for us.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
