<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR278*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Manager:</P>
      <P>When I first heard about Over the Rainbow I was very exited about the idea of seeing it, plus when I heard about the facilities that the circle theatre was giving, it becomed the best oportunity I ever had to asist to a musical of that category, but instead of being the best evening I ever had, it was a total disaster and that's the reason why I am writting to you.</P>
      <P>Like I have already told you, instead of being the perfect evening, it was the worst I ever had. First, the actors that the Circle theatre publis in their tickets for Over the Rainbow were not, which was very disappointing because, the actors were starring the musical, was one of it mayor attractions. Another point that I want to comply about, is the time that the musical was supposed to start (19:30) but it started at 20:15, so there was a mayor unsatisfaction about it, but the last and worst thing was that your theatre restaurant was closed because the British health institute considered that your food was unhealthy, and not considering many other points like unsatisfactory service, and uncomfortable seats.</P>
      <P>In consequence of the reasons I have already explained, I would like to ask you if I can have my money back, but this is not the most important to me, because I want your theatre to change and become the best.</P>
      <P>Hope to hear from you:</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Science and Technology is a theme very discussed nowdays, most of the comunity of our city, and of the world, were technology has arrived, confirms that it has in some way improved their way of life. And I think it's the same to me, because when advances in technology like computers, internet, etc. were made, it changed my life as a high school student.</P>
      <P>Answering the question: "How has modern technology changed my daily life?, I can confirm, that it has been in many ways, and the most important one that I can remember was the invention of computers and later the internet, because it was easiest to me, and to every one, to make your home works, school works, and in fact, it was easier to me to search for information that in the past I would have to look at in a library. But not all about technology and computers is good, because many people, and me in a control way, had become computer's an thechnologic's slaves, and we can not do anything without a machine, and I am not saying that it's wrong or bad, and I accept that they make easier our daily tasks, but we have to mantain our independence as humans.</P>
      <P>Technology, in fact it has made an improvement on daily tasks, but we have to think and work by ourselves because if not our brain will become atrophied.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
