<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR282*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Miss Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>I was so suprise to hear from you. I couldn't believe that I had won the first prize on the competition. I'm so happy because it is the first time that I win something.</P>
      <P>Here it is all your information. I would like if you could to have my vacation trip on July because is the only time of the year that my job could let me have a vacation. As for the accommodation I would prefer the tent because it is my first time that I'm going to camping and I would like to see how the real life is. I was so thrilled when I saw that I could do some activities also. I would like to choose swimming and the climbing. I'm a very good swimmer but I don't know anything about climbing that's why I choose it because I want to try something knew. At last I would like to ask you about my clothes and how the weather is going to be and what kind of clothes I must to take with me. That is all.</P>
      <P>Thank you for making my dream come true</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Everyone has likes and dislikes. But noone is doing what he likes all the time. There is times that you have to do something even if you don't like it, and times that you are doing what you like but not the time you like it. What I'm trying to say is that I like to shop but I can't do that all the time. First because I'm not so rich and second because I don't enjoy to shop all the time. Nothing in life is always enjoyable even the things we enjoy to do, and that's how life is. You say you enjoy shopping I understand but life goes on you can't do the same things every day. live your life and try to do different things and you will see that to do different things is exciting and more fun. You don't have to be bored with the same old things.</P>
      <P>Because as I said to do what you like is good only if you do it when you like it and how you like it and remember if you have long time to do something the you enjoy it more.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
