<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR283*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dears Ms. Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I was really greatful when I recieved your letter which informed me that I have won first prize in your competition.</P>
      <P>I would like to make this trip the first week or the last week of July. Because my school finishes end of June and I will have a month break after that I have to do a computing course which I have already applied for it. Could you possibly tell me, at Camp California will I stay in tents or log cabins. Personily I prefer to stay in log cabins because they are much more comfortable than tents.</P>
      <P>I really enjoy swimming and playing tennis. Unfortunetley I am not good at both of them. Maybe I will have time to do enough practise as much as I always wanted to do.</P>
      <P>Could you tell me what sort of clothes I would need to bring with me and will I need any extra money for this holiday.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you soon!</P>
      <P>Yours sincerly,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I don't know where to start but I can say it was the greatest time I have ever had.</P>
      <P>As I mentioned you before Friend of mine, she is a stage assistant and she needed a help for that pop concert last month.</P>
      <P>I told her if she need help I would be happy to help her. Next day when I went there I have met lots of people very famous and very friendly. It took us almost a month to prepare for this concert.</P>
      <P>You wouldn't believe how hard it was. the stage was covered with all sort of light and we made it look like a waterfall.</P>
      <P>The waterfall made by real rock so that was the worst bit because they were really heavy and we had to carry them, but the end of moth when the concert started, it was all over.</P>
      <P>I sung and dance all day. I have lots of memory which I could never forget.</P>
      <P>I wish you were there.</P>
      <P>I hope you shared my happiness with me.</P>
      <P>Lots of love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
