<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR284*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Jane Clark</P>
      <P>With attendance to the annual international arts festival which you took place on 21 and 22th November 2000, I spend tremendous two days enjoying some features. Then, I discovered some points and I am writing to express my suggestion and recommendations.</P>
      <P>Firstly, the title 'International Arts Festival' is very suitable for the festival, because there were some variety of features in it. Next, One reasonably-priced weekend ticket for all events is also fantastic idea, because everyone could enjoy everything by the ticket.</P>
      <P>However, according to my notes, there are some doubt in the festival. While you stated that there were stars and artists from around the world, they were from only six countries in fact. The number of plays and films were also very few. In addition to that some concert halls were too small to enjoy the concerts.</P>
      <P>On balance, I feel that this annual festival can be even better next year. Therefore, I strongly recommend that you should collect artists and stars more than six countries and rebuild larger concert halls. I also suggest that more plays and films should be taken. I would be grateful to support you providing that you would like to make the festival more successful.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerelly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Albert</P>
      <P>Thanks for your letter, it was great to hear from you. I know you're fine, but I've been very busy studying because I have to take exam next month. So this is quick note to tell you what you want to know, as you asked about school rules and house ones.</P>
      <P>At school, the most horrible one is school uniform. I really hate it, because we're not allowed to wear casual and fashonable clothes, colourful shoes and colourful socks. We can't also turn our hair colour an have to keep hair length above eye blows. Next, we're not allowed to get driver licences which are for a motorbike and car as long as we've students. We're also not allowed to get part-time jobs. If possible, I want to change all of them.</P>
      <P>However, at home I'm quite free. Just I can't go out after 9 o'clock in the night and I'm not allowed to play computer games over two hours. These are not so strict that I can stand them. I don't think I want to change them.</P>
      <P>Anyway, that's all about my information which you want.</P>
      <P>Write soon, I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
