<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR285*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>13 June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>According to your letter, I am writing to infrom you about the information you need to know for my trip two weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A.</P>
      <P>I am very excited and looking forward to the new experiance I am going to have. First of all I must tell you that I only have freetime in July at any day, any week, because I am still having my lesson at college and it will be finished at the end of June and also in August I have a training course for my studies. I would prefer to stay in tents because I love atmosephere of camping, but I wouldn't mind to stay in log cabins. For the two activities I can choose, I would like to have swimming and Basketball. I have always found these kind of activity make me fell strong and enjoy doing it. I first started playing basketball and swimming when I was aged 9, and I have been doing it up till now. I also used to be in a basketball team in school for 3 years.</P>
      <P>One thing, I would like to know is how many clothes I have to take with me and what kind of cloth they are?</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Vanida Montri</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Report on daily life at school</P>
      <P>Introduction</P>
      <P>The aim of this report is describ and assess lesson and activities should be filmed in a short video. It is base on information made availble by student from each class at school.</P>
      <P>Lessons</P>
      <P>Most student who were interviewed suggested to have a speaking part of the lesson to be on film. It seemed to be the most interesting lesson, because student always make some mistake while they are practising with thier partner, in spite of having told from teacher ten times. It felt to be a good memory to be remember and remind our sleves to speak in a correct way. This lesson will give us to be relaxed and have laugh. We also would like to have a history on.</P>
      <P>Activities</P>
      <P>Going out to visit the history town every weekend seem to be the most enjoyable activity for student. Spending time together out of the class is the nice experiance. Having a sport after class it also fun.</P>
      <P>Conclusion</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
