<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR287*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam</P>
      <P>I am so pleased to know that I have won such amazing prize in your competition. I like to answer the questions you request from me.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I should say that I would like to travel in July because of this is the month wich I could more likely have off at work for going on holiday.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I would prefer to stay at log cabins rather than tents. That is because I do not want to seem fuzy but I like to have some comodities when I am going on holiday and I think slepping over the floor without electricity it may annoy me.</P>
      <P>Finally, I like to choose swimming as activity in the Camp. I love swimming and also I should say that I am very good at this sport because I have been doing that for long time. On the contrary, painting is an activity wich I have never tryied before, so that I have not any skill in drawing but I like start doing that know when I have the chance. So that is my second choice.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, I would like to know some imformation wich could be useful in my holiday like: which type of clothes could be more suitable for me in the Camp? Could I need some extra money? Do I need to bring something else? If is so, please let me know as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>to look forward to getting your Reply</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear friend.</P>
      <P>I am writting to tell you about my experience in the last month pop concert, where I was helping my friend Nick who was the bouncer of the place.</P>
      <P>That was a pop concert with lots of famous singers like Madona, Julio Iglesias, and people like them</P>
      <P>That was a charity concert to save money to poor people of AFRICA.</P>
      <P>My job it was to accomodatetheathre. Of course those places were reserved just for people well-knowed who wanted to help by joined the concert.</P>
      <P>So I had to ask them for their identifications and for their invitations. After that, I have to take them to their respective sit.</P>
      <P>At first, I was a bit scare, I mean I was afraid not be good enough to have a good performance as assistant; but finally every thing went well.</P>
      <P>I should say that it was the easiest and more interesting job that I have ever done. I really enjoyed it and also I did not miss the opportunity to ask the artist to take a photho with me.</P>
      <P>So, I hope to see you earliest to show all my phothos.</P>
      <P>I think, it was very cleaver of me to record that moment wich I will never ever forget, and that was the think that I more liked of that experience.</P>
      <P>Looking forward to getting your reply and to seeing you soon</P>
      <P>lots of love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
