<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR288*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I'm writting to you to make a complaint about your musical show: " Over the Rainbow"... Last week, I, my husband and our two children went to your theatre spend a good time, but we were so disappointed.</P>
      <P>First of all, I think it's not professional to change the principal actor in the last minute, the play should be with Danny Brook, but it wasn't.</P>
      <P>In addition to this, the show started at 20:15 instead 19:30, more 45 minutes in late...</P>
      <P>Moreover, there weren't discounts available like writting in your advertisement.</P>
      <P>There was well a restaurant, even though, it was closed for reparations, also 2 hours 30 without drinking or eating something, was quite difficult for the children.</P>
      <P>It should be a perfect evening out, but it was the opposite. It's why, it would be grateful, if you could give me my money back. I look forward to hearing from you in the very near future.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed your daily life?</P>
      <P>Nowadays, I think it could be impossible for us to live like our grand-parents or great grand-parents lived... we are too lazy, but it's not our mistake, this revolution is called "progress"!</P>
      <P>Every day, like everybody, I watch the TV, see the International news, hear the radio, play games on my computer or get across with American or Asia people without going out to my house. It seem be incredible, but it's commun habits for us.. we don't think that there is less of a hundred years, nothing of that existed.</P>
      <P>I will always said thank you very much to the inventor who has invented the maschines wich make the washing and the washing-up, before this, the women spent a long time had done this tasks.</P>
      <P>In addition to this, thinking also, to the medicine, science or astronomy progress...</P>
      <P>And it's not ending, I hope that for my thirties I'll go to Mars on holidays...</P>
      <P>The scientists are again ten years to find the solution...</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
