<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR291*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen,</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your letter which said I had won first prize in your competition. I was really surprise to hear that.</P>
      <P>I am afraid I can only make it on July, because I am taking exams this month. Moreover, I'll prepare everything for going to University on August. I have no time until Christmas. So, I think the best time is July.</P>
      <P>The accommodation I prefer is tent. I haven't tied it before. I would like to know how interesting it is to live in tents. If I can only choose two activities while I am at the Camp, I would like climbing and Basketball. I started climbing since I was a child. I love it very much. About the Basketball, I have been played it for seven years. I would like to play basketball with local people at the Camp to see how good they are, if I can.</P>
      <P>Finally, may I ask some more informations. What kinds of clothes shall I take? how about the weather there? Would you give me some pocket-money during the trip. Also, may I take a friend with me, how much will she pay?</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>JIA LI LO</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>To: Teacher Cheng</P>
      <P>From: Jia Lo</P>
      <P>Date: 13/06/00</P>
      <P>Subject: a short video about daily life at school</P>
      <P>As I was asked, I spoke to a number of students about their opinions of this short video. I found that most of them had suggested that four lessons should be filmed which as follow:</P>
      <P>1. Grammerbase.</P>
      <P>2. Speaking, it makes you more confident when you talk with other peoper. Let you do more pratices.</P>
      <P>3. Listening, it really helpful for improving your listening and understanding.</P>
      <P>4. Writing, this lesson techer you how to organise what you want to write.</P>
      <P>Also, there are two activities should be filmed.</P>
      <P>1. Students are talking to each other when they are having break. It is important to pratise your English after lessons.</P>
      <P>2. Teacher are helping students with their problems. If you have problem on studing, asking teachers is the best way.</P>
      <P>In Conclusion, the short video is only 60 minutes. It must show the daily lifes of the English students at the school. It should include all those points lists above.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
