<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR294*0101*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Brown,</P>
      <P>It would be a pleasure to us and to your husband to come at the party. All the students wanted to organise a surprise party for Mr Brown. Next Tuesday is his birthday. We would like you to come and if you can to help us in an important decision.</P>
      <P>Firstly, we should tell you that it is a surprise party. He must not learn about it subsequently you must not tell him.</P>
      <P>Secondly, the party will take place on Tuesday 16th of June at College Canteen. We think the suitable time will be 3-6 p.m. You can come earlier, if you want. We would have junky food, some juices and drinks. Moreover, will come some teacher, of course all the students and the Principal.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, we do not know what to give him as a present. Can you help us? We want something that it would like him or would be necessary.</P>
      <P>Please try to come and help us to this problem. We ar looking forward to your reply.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>John said he had some good news to tell me. I am waiting him to come. Suddenly the bell rings. I thought that would be John and was he. We had finished the exams two weeks ago and we were waiting for the results.</P>
      <P>The first good new was that we both had passed the exams. It was a wonderful new. Then we thought about going for swimming to discuss about some things.</P>
      <P>The second new was that he had found a job for the summer. He would go to work in a café. He would earn a lot of money, in addition they wanted an another person. As a result I had a work too. We had the greatest day.</P>
      <P>Then we had an idea! We would have much money from the work. At the end of the summer we are planning to visit a cousin who lives in Australia. We imagine that would be the best holidays in our life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
