<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR295*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>13/6/2000-11-07</P>
      <P>Dear Madam Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>First of all, we happy to won the first prize on your competition. Thank you for choosen our ticket at the final.</P>
      <P>We like to go on July, because my wife Catrin just have holidays next month. We prefer the last two weeks on July. Would that be fine for you too?</P>
      <P>Is there a possibility to stay in a log cabin. I have sometimes troubles with backache when I coud't sleep on a flat ground.</P>
      <P>It would be great if we can choosen swimming and Golf. My wife Catrin is a local master on swimming race. Im not so good as her, but I'm going every week once to her training. In Golf, we are both total beginners. We have no experience but we like to learn this game.</P>
      <P>We are both a little afraid, what kind of clothes and shoes we have to take off with us? Which temperature will be on the summer season in this area? Are there some possibility to rent the golfshoes?</P>
      <P>Finally, we like to know, when you will send us the airline-tickets and the tripbrochure. Moreover, what do think how much pocketmoney we will spent on this trip.</P>
      <P>We looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Leon Hofmann</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>13/6/2000</P>
      <P>Dear Kim</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your last lovely letter. I'm fine. How are you?</P>
      <P>You are interessted on my last job! I really like to tell you all my experience.</P>
      <P>However, I'm happy that we finished this hard work. I worked in a team by seven people. We were mainly on work for all the lights at this great concert. Its sounds easy, just for the light.</P>
      <P>In addition, it was a nine days hard work to mount all the different spot and houndreds of Coblights on the right place.</P>
      <P>Finally, we had worked the hohl night befor the concert. We had to adjust the laser extremly on the correct position. We spent hours till it was good enough for the Technical-manger. Moreover, the band was exhausted about this great laser show at the end.</P>
      <P>For me was this aventure one of the Best. It shows, when all member of a group work hard together, you can reach a lot.</P>
      <P>I think I can't forgotten this experience on my mind</P>
      <P>Lots of Love</P>
      <P>Leon</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
