<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR297*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Smith</P>
      <P>My name is Manuel Olmez and last week I went to see the musical show 'Over the rainbow' to the Circle theatre.</P>
      <P>Firstly I want to tell you how disappointing was that night.</P>
      <P>Everything in the advertisement for the show was wrong. The actors I saw in the show were not Danny Brook and Tina Truelove.</P>
      <P>I went at 19.30 and the show didn't begin until 20:15 so I had to wait a lot and I arrived late to a meeting I had after the show. There were not discounts available for the tickets and the theatre's restaurant was closed after the show because it was too late.</P>
      <P>So I want you to send me some money back for that unpleasent night.</P>
      <P>I hope you can understand me.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets.</P>
      <P>So in very few days all the College knew that me and my friends were who had crashed headmaster's car.</P>
      <P>The headmaster wanted to tell the police what we had done so we decided to close him in a little house, we had twenty kilometers far from the village until we could change his opinion. Marc, one of my friends, hit Mr. Heyman with a bottle and he lost his conscience. We put him in my car and we left him inside a closed room.</P>
      <P>When he woke up he started shouting and we had to make him calm.</P>
      <P>We took some photos of him naked and told him not to tell this anybody because if he does we will hang the photos all arround the village.</P>
      <P>He accepted and we left him free.</P>
      <P>Everything began because he is a nasty person and he forced us to clean the college every day, for not paying a cleaning assistant.</P>
      <P>We need to do something like that to make him change.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
