<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR298*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>Thank you very much. I am very glad I have won first prize in the competition - two weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel only in July, because in June I have to study at school which hasn't finished until the end of June. In August, I have already made another appointment with my friends. We are going to visit the places of interest of China, as usual, our new term begins in September. I only can travel in July</P>
      <P>Accommodation I would prefer in tents to in log cabins. Tents are very easy to take and go everywhere. What's more, in my opinion it is very romantic.</P>
      <P>I am good at singing and photography. I can sing most kinds of songs, such as pop music, folk. I like taking photograph, in my only room. There are all kinds of photos, for example, beach, sea trees and so on.</P>
      <P>In the end, I wonder what kind of clothes I should take and how much money I should bring with me.</P>
      <P>I look forward to seeing you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>To: Mrs Flame</P>
      <P>From: Kate</P>
      <P>Subject: which lessons and other activities should be filmed</P>
      <P>Instruction:</P>
      <P>The aim of this report is to suggest which lessons and lessons be filmed into a short video. In order to write the report I interviewed about one hundred students who are studying in our English class.</P>
      <P>Results:</P>
      <P>The majority of them said it's a good idea to make something about Maths and English study skills. Sixty percent recommended that the activity which called make the brain up in the morning class should be filmed. Ten of them said should make the computing. Two thirds said we should film a part of playing football.</P>
      <P>Reasons:</P>
      <P>Although Maths is very boring, it is very important in nowadays. English is the most popular language in the world, what's more, more and more people start to learn English. The activity of making brain up can help us remember new words. Playing football is good for health.</P>
      <P>Conclusion:</P>
      <P>It is recommended that should be filmed about Maths, English study skills,make brain up and a part of playing football.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
