<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR304*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you to explain how was my experience in the theatre last Friday. I did not expect to find all the problems that I had.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I would like to say that the actor who played was not the same one that I read in the advertisement.</P>
      <P>Secontly, the musical show began fourty-five minutes later and nobody explained me what was happened.</P>
      <P>Thirdly, I did not receive any kind of discounts when I payed although in the advertisement it was written.</P>
      <P>After the musical show, I went to the theatre restaurant but I could not have had dinner because it was closed. I think that if the musical show will begin later the restaurant should close later, too!</P>
      <P>Finally, from my point of view, I would like to receive the money that I payed because it was not the same as you offered in the advertisement.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. I think when you explain a secret you must be sure that you have chose the best person to keep it. In your life you will meet a lot of people and you should choose your friends.</P>
      <P>When I was a child my friends were my companions of class and, especially my neighbours. In the summers I always were playing with them on the street. When I was fourteen years old some things changed. I prefered going by motorbike with the people who studyied with me in the Institute. But, until you are twenty years old you choose your best friends. When you go to the university you are a person who can begin to make a good friends. You have an experience to know people and now you have an opportunaty to select good friends. You must select well if you want to have very good friends.</P>
      <P>For theses reasons, I think that you should know well the person who wants to explain a secret and keep it.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
