<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR305*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Swedish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Manager,</P>
      <P>I have recently seen "Over the rainbow" and I must tell you that I'm really disappointed! I found the advertisement about this show in a newspaper and thought it would be fun.</P>
      <P>I like Danny Brook as an actor and when I read that he would be starring, I booked the ticket imagetly. But, instead there was a different actor, who I never heard about before!</P>
      <P>The show should start at 19.30, but it didn't start until 20.15! So, because of that, I missed my last bus home!</P>
      <P>While we were waiting for the show to start, we were thinking of going to the restaurant. In fact, it was closed the whole evening, because of some work.</P>
      <P>As I'm a student, I usually get discounts on different things, so I was so disappointed when I couldn't get it here!</P>
      <P>I'm really upset and disappointed after all this and at least I want my money back!</P>
      <P>It could have been a perfect evening out, but it wasn't!</P>
      <P>yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Karol Johannes</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed my daily life?</P>
      <P>I belong to this generation who had grown up with a lot of different technolgy. For example TV, telephone, micrown etc. But the last few years, it has change and so many new important things had been discovered. What I'm talking about are the computer, which now can be found in almost every home and of course, the mobile phone!</P>
      <P>I tought I would never need a mobile phone, but my mum and dad gave me one for Christmas last year and now I can't live without it!</P>
      <P>But the discovery that I'm most thankful to is the computor and the Internet! Thanks to it, I can easy communicate with my family and friends at home when I'm here in England. It's so quick and not too expensive either. To use the mobile phone by the way, is very expensive. I usually use it for sending SMS Messages to my friends.</P>
      <P>So, I start every day, swiching on my mobile phone, to see if there are any more SMS messages before I go to the library to check my e-mail and that's just the begining of the day...</P>
      <P>Karol Johannes</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
