<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR308*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Swedish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Manager of the Circle Theatre.</P>
      <P>I am writing regarding to our visit to the Circle Theatre the 17th June.</P>
      <P>When we saw your advertisment for the musical show, over the rainbow, we immediatly decided that this must be a perfect evening out. There was in our opinion two reasons for that, our favourite actor Danny Brook and the opportunity to visit your theatre restaurant afterwords.</P>
      <P>However the evening become very disappointing. Firstly, Danny Brook was not acting, there was another unknown actor and he was not good. Secondly, the show was supposed to start 19.30, but did not start until 20.15.</P>
      <P>Thirdly, in your advertisment it says that discounts should be available, but it was not.</P>
      <P>Above these the restaurant was closed because of water leakage.</P>
      <P>I am therefore asking for a compensation for our disappointing evening and hope we can reach a sollution as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerelly</P>
      <P>Adra Johansson</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. It didn't take more than one day before everyone knew about my decision. I had thought about it for many years but never been able to fulfill my dreams. This year I had the opportunity to make my dreams come through.</P>
      <P>However I wasn't sure if my decision was right and therefore I decided to discuss it with Pat.</P>
      <P>Pat is my best friend, since we first met in primary school. It is now twenty years ago.</P>
      <P>I really like Pat, she's funny, has a good sence of humor and like me she loves to discuss everything.</P>
      <P>So therefore, my choise to ask her about my decision was the best I could do.</P>
      <P>She really listen to me and told me that I did the right thing and persuaded me to send in my application for an language course in England.</P>
      <P>I wanted to keep this as a secret until I received the answer from the School. But it is ok, I still like Pat, even though she can't keep a secret.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
