<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR310*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>I am writing in reply to your letter, which I have received last week, and in fact I am very surprised and please for the prize.</P>
      <P>First of all I would like to travel in July because is my free month since I am student and I am very busy during all year.</P>
      <P>Secondly, according to accommodation, I would prefer to stay in a long cabin, due to I used to use the tent on holiday and I haven't got very good experiences.</P>
      <P>Thirdly I chose photography and swimming because I have previous experience in these activities and of course I have some diplomas which I will send you.</P>
      <P>In addition, I work every summer as a Monitor in the leisure centre in my town.</P>
      <P>Apart from this photography is one of my favorite hobbies and I usually spent nearly all my spare time practising it and of course I have some diplomas as well.</P>
      <P>Lastly I would like to ask you for some questions.</P>
      <P>On the one hand I would like to have further information about which kind of clothes I need for that area. I don't know if I have to bring only light clothes or both.</P>
      <P>On the other hand I would like to request all details of accommodation and if you could specifie what this trip includes, since I need to know how much money I have to take.</P>
      <P>I look forward to receiving a prompt reply.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Hello it's been ages since we were in touch, I'm sorry I haven't written to you for such a long time but I have been very busy last month, with this job.</P>
      <P>I have to tell you that this experience was wonderful and in fact I enjoyed a lot and of course I knew a lot of people there.</P>
      <P>I found this opportunity through the Radio in an advertisement.</P>
      <P>On the one hand at first I was a little insure about if I was able to do this job, because they needed people with some skills and experience. But later I decided to call them and ask them for further information about this job.</P>
      <P>After a interview I was chosen for it, I couldn't believe it. I feel that this was a good oportunity for me, not only for my professional but also for my personal life.</P>
      <P>Moreover I practised a lot of aspect of my speciality, for me was the most important real experience.</P>
      <P>According to my job, I had to help the teams with the outlights and of course it had been my first proffesional experience: at the end I felt a member of them, because they were so kind to me, and I could colaborated a lot of and I learnt a lot with this project.</P>
      <P>Furthermore, I found it very short time and they offered me new project for the summer.</P>
      <P>I hope to hear from you soon.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
