<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR311*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear manager</P>
      <P>My name is Lisa and I'm 21 years old. I went to the theatre last Friday to see Over the Rainbow and I felt disappointed about the musical. I expected more from it. First of all the actor was the same since last semester. I would really like to see a new one such as Markin Davis, he is a great actor and he would fit well this musical. Then I was sitted with my friend just waiting for the start that lasted forever and was supposed to start at 19:30. After the show I felt really hungry, so I meant to go to the restaurant which occasionally was closed. By the time I thought: "I want my money back." That was supposed to be a perfect evening turned out to be the most hateful musical I've ever seen.</P>
      <P>Attencionally</P>
      <P>Straussburg 17th June 2000</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. Despite the fact that she was my best friend I could never count on her or she would tell everybody in high school all my secrets.</P>
      <P>Once, when we first met I was about 15 and she was the same age, we started talking and by the time we found out a very good friendship on our conversation.</P>
      <P>One day she came over to my house and we spoke all night about our lives. Then I told her about my first kiss (it was terrible, the guy didn't know how to do it) and things like that.</P>
      <P>The next morning when I got to the high school I heard what I wasn't expecting, Pat had told everybody about my first experience in kissing. People would be starring at me and laughing.</P>
      <P>I got really mad at her, but nowadays we are friends, not as close as we used to. I don't tell her my secrets anymore.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
