<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR313*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am replying to your letter for the first prize of the competition, that I won and there are a number of thinks I would like to make clear.</P>
      <P>You asked me in your last letter when I would like to travel. I think the best time is the first two weeks of July, because I will be free then. I cannot travel earlier because I take an examination and I have to study for it. In addition, I would prefer to have a log cabin, because I am not used to sleeping in a tent, so it would be very difficult for me. at the beginning You state in your last letter that I will have the chance to do two activities. I would prefer basketball and swimming. When I was younger I attend I local basketball team and we became local champions, so I am good at basketball and have a lot of experience. I am also good at swimming. Last year I entered a swimming championship and won the silver medal.</P>
      <P>Finally, there is one think I would like to ask. Could you tell me what sort of clothes and how much money I should have with me?</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>Many thanks for your last letter. It was great to hear from you again.</P>
      <P>As you know, I helped at a pop concert last month. and I must say it was fantastic. Let's start from the beginning.</P>
      <P>First of all, I had to prepare the clothes of the pop stars. I had to iron them, put them in order, so that the pop stars, who will sing at the concert, look impressive. and handsome. The most exciting things happened later. I saw all the pop stars, talked with them and realized that they are very nice and always helpful.</P>
      <P>I had a lot of things to do during the concert. I had to look after the tone that nothing goes wrong. That was very responsible but fortunately I had help from other person.</P>
      <P>I must say that being in a concert is very nice. But helping in a concert is much nicer. At the end I realized that all your need is co-operation and don't think selfishly. Hope to hear from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours</P>
      <P>Pantelis</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
