<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR314*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>14.06.2000</P>
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter. I was very glad I won the competition. This trip will, undoubtedly be a wonderful experience.</P>
      <P>As far as the dates of travelling are concerned, the only period available would be in July as I am fully booked for the remaining summer. I really didn't expect to win the trip. I would therefore be very thankful if you could book the tickets for then.</P>
      <P>Concerning the accommodation choice you have proposed me, please make sure I am sleeping in a tent, as I have never experienced open air camping before. I think it would be nice to try it at least once.</P>
      <P>Concerning the proposed activities please, accept me for Singing and Painting. The only problem would be that my drawing is pretty bad. Concerning Singing activities, I think I'm quite good as I have been in my school's choir for 3 years.</P>
      <P>Could you please include in your next letter some information about the amount of money and clothes we have to carry?</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>17 October 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>As you asked me, I write you about my experience at the Pop Concert.</P>
      <P>Well, on the whole, it was pretty cool. There was no big stress about it. The only thing I was asked to do was to help carry the lunches of the singers and to help with light and sound management, when the guy there had to do something else. Oh yes, I also had to check the tickets for five minutes. The woman had to deliver something. The problem about this job is that you have to deal with huge amounts of people. There were 963 persons in the "Armaggedon" that night!</P>
      <P>But, as I said, the whole thing was fun. You must show a great sence of responsibility. But, Kim, can you see an other way to meet the "New Bentley" for free, talk to them and even get paid? That was my best day ever, the one I shared a meal with Paul McPartney. I'm sure you are jalous now. Don't worry they still organise these "youth work" programs.</P>
      <P>With love</P>
      <P>John</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
