<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR316*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>31-40</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs. Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your letter. I am very happy to be the winner of the competition and I am looking forward to come to Camp California.</P>
      <P>I hope there will be no problem if I travel in July, as this is the only free period I have. From August, in fact, I will start with a new job and I will not be able to live Rome for a long period.</P>
      <P>As far as accommodation is concerned, I would prefer to stay in a log cabin, because tents are too hot for me.</P>
      <P>I am also pleased to have the chance to do some activities and I would like to choose something I am not able to do so. So, I have decided to chose photography and surfing because I am an absolute beginner at both of them.</P>
      <P>Please let me know how is the climate like at the Camp, so that I can take with me the right kind of clothes. It would be also useful for me to know if there will be some extra expenses, in order to take enough money for two weeks.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Vittoria Santini</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Being a woman, I naturally love shopping. It is a really great pleasure going in and out from different shops, try on a variety of clothes and shoes, and finally go back home with dozens of bags in your hands.</P>
      <P>However, there are a few moments in which you cannot enjoy shopping. The first one is the Christmas period. Shops are incredibly crowded. You cannot try on a dress and decide to buy it or not in peace, because outside there is a queue of people waiting for their turn. In many cases, you do not even find the things you want, because shops run out of products very quickly. Moreover, during this period, prices are usually much higher than in the other month's.</P>
      <P>Another situation in which shopping is not enjoyable, is when you go shopping with a man. For the majority of men, in fact, shopping is the most boring activity in the world. A man will try to prevent you from trying more than one dress and will refuse to stay in the same shop for more than five minutes.</P>
      <P>Anyway, apart from these two cases, shopping is always very amusing.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
