<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR317*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you to complain about the musical show "Over the Rainbow".</P>
      <P>I have recently been in London for spending a week's holiday. As I am an enthusiasmic of musicals I went to see this musical show.</P>
      <P>I am very disappointed because the things that were writen on the advertisment were not really true.</P>
      <P>It was writen that the stars would be Danny Brook and Tina Truelove. Danny Brook is one of my favorite actors and there was playing another one. I felt abosolutly disapointed.</P>
      <P>The musical should have begun at 19:30, but it started at 20:15; it is inacceptable!</P>
      <P>It was writen too that there were discounts available and I asked for them and they said me that they weren't allow to do any discount. After the show me and my friends wanted to have a drink and the theatre restaurant was closed because there weren't enough drinks.</P>
      <P>As you say in your advertisment it was not my perfect evening out and therefore I would like to have my money back.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>Ms MARIA AROZ</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed our daily life?</P>
      <P>Modern technology has changed a lot our daily life.</P>
      <P>On one hand nowadays if we have to travel to Paris and return in the same day you can take a plane without any problem. In the past it was impossible to go to Paris from Barcelona and come back in one day.</P>
      <P>Another advantage is that if you go on an excursion and you take your mobile phone, if you get lost somebody could find you.</P>
      <P>I think that the most important modern technology in these days is internet. With internet you can do whatever you want without going out home (shoping, speaking with a friend, working, putting your money aside....)</P>
      <P>On the other hand the main disadvantage is that using modern machines it can be very difficult for ederly people; it would be very pratitable if the modern industries train people about using modern technologies.</P>
      <P>To sum up modern technology has change a lot our daily life and this is going to increase.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
