<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR318*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>I'm writing back to tell you that I am happy to accept this prize and to give you some further information that you need from me.</P>
      <P>If it's possible I would like to travel on July because of my job. I can't leave it until this month and I'm not able to travel at any other time of the year.</P>
      <P>As I see I have the chance to choose what accommodation I prefer. I would like to stay in a tent because I'm used to go camping at weekends but if there's any problem I could be very confortable in a log cabin too.</P>
      <P>It's incredible the large list of interesting activities that you offer. It's difficult just to try two but if I have the chance I would like to practice sailing and photography. I have never done noon of them before and as a result I can't be good but I've always wanted to sail because I love the sea and now I have the opportunitie. I also think that it would be great to learn photography because it will give me the chance to go sightseeing and find wonderful places to take pictures.</P>
      <P>If you don't mind I would like to know what kind of clothes are apropriate for the camp and for the weather of California. And also may I have to bring money? because I know that all the costs are paid but it could be necessary for other things.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hear from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Luna Juarez.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>I completely agree with the following statement:</P>
      <P>"shopping is not always enjoyable"</P>
      <P>From my point of view a lot of people believe that it's very fun to go shopping and it's a great way to spend Saturday afternoons and that's true but in my opinion go shopping can be stressing and disgusting.</P>
      <P>First of all we usually go to the shops at the same time than the rest of the world and that's a little bit complicated because the shops are fulled and it's impossible to try acurately.</P>
      <P>Secondly you have to thank before you come in a shop if you're going to have luck. I mean that you have to wait until the seller came to know if he or she is going to drive you crazy. Thirdly you have to pray to find the right size and once you've got it you have to think Does it fits me?</P>
      <P>And after all of this it's important when you're going shopping to have a big amount of money or you will end stressed, disgusted, and depressed.</P>
      <P>At last but not at least let me give you some advice try not to go with that friend of yours that is crazy about clothes and shoes because she wants you to be like her and that will be awful.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
