<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR319*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>31-40</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>18 June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Ms Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your letter. I have just received it yesterday. I am very exciting.</P>
      <P>I would like to go to California in the U.S.A. in July. It is the only month that I can have my holiday in a year and it would be nice in the summer time.</P>
      <P>About the accommodation at Camp California, I prefer a log cabin. It would be nice and safe for me than the tents. The activities I would like to choose the swimming and sailing. It could be fun for me because I like swimming and sailing could be exciting too.</P>
      <P>Lastly, I would like to know about the money and clothes. How about the weather in California in July? Is it hot or raining? Then I can prepare my clothes, or can we buy some clothes there? Are they accept the credit card or only cash. I don't want to take money with me.</P>
      <P>I would be greatful if you could send me the full details. Many thanks.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>In the following paragraps I will discuss the advantages and disadvantages about shopping.</P>
      <P>Everyone needs to shopping everyday. It is very important thing for our life. We need food, clothes, book etc. There are many kinds of thing for shopping and they are different for example the price, the quality</P>
      <P>In suppermarket, shop, department store have many things. We could buy mostly all we need in one store. It is very convenien.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, shopping is not always easy. Sometime, it's so many people and they are not friendly at all or you are hurry while you are in the long queu.</P>
      <P>We have seen then, shopping is very important for our life. Most people enjoy shopping because it more convenien for today but if you found the busy place for shopping or it is not as good as you expect. It would not enjoyable for you.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
