<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR321*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ryan,</P>
      <P>I'm just finish reading the letter from you about won first prize in your competition two weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A. You had ask me some further information.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel on the July only Because I'll be free for the whole month. So any date on the July. I'd like to accommodation at Camp California in tents. Because i like to sleep in tent when i go camping. Also I would like to choose the two activities that you had gave me on the list. I would like to choose Swimming and Photography. I'm good in swimming. I used to swim for the school team. But I never do photography before. I love to take a photo but never have chance to do so. But I have chance to choose.</P>
      <P>Also I would like to ask you some questions. Do I have to bring a lots of money? I mean do I have to pay for the tent? What about the clothes do I have to bring a lot? That is all i want to know. Thank you</P>
      <P>Your sincerely</P>
      <P>LINDSAY WATTANA</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>10/05/2000</P>
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>Hi, how are you? I'm fine. I just got your letter yesterday. You had ask me a question about my experience helping at a pop concert. You wanted me to tell you about it right?</P>
      <P>Well, it quite fun while i helping them to do the stuff before the concert gonna start. I have to get everythings that they need up to the stair. It's so tried. Then after that I have to help them carry all the clothes for the singer to wear from the bus down in to the stuff room. I saw Westlife too you know they are so cute. Then I can take rest about 30 mins. After that i have to go in to the stuff room again because they wanted me to go and buy some drink for the singer. After i came back i have to help them clean all the make up stuff. The concert begin... that mean i can take rest until the concert finish. After the concert had finish i have to help them again to clean all the stuff. the carry everythings that I can carry back to the bus. We were so tried but it's good fun. I think this experience was quite interesting. If somebody ask me to go and help again I would like to go for sure.</P>
      <P>That's all i did in the pop concert for my experience. What about your experience? Don't forget to tell me about yours okay... Better go to sleep now. Bye</P>
      <P>Antonia.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
