<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR322*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson!</P>
      <P>I'm writting to you to thank you for good programme of our English class in London, especially for river trip to Greenwich, it will be a great experience for us. But the students in our class have seen an adverstisement for the "London Fashion and Leisure Show" which'll take place in Central Exhibition Hall, London, on Tuesday March 14 from 10.00 to 19.00 and at the same time we have to go to the Science Museum but we would all like to go to the show. It will be very interesting for us to see the latest fashions, make up, hairstyles and we can speak to English people and make new friends. There is one more advantage: it is free for students. So we would like to suggest you how the programme could be changed.</P>
      <P>First of all on Tuesday we all will go to the show and spend there all our day, but on Wednesday in the afternoon when we have free time we can go to the Science Museum if you don't mind, of course.</P>
      <P>Please let us know, as soon as you make your decission. With best wishes, your student.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="5b">
      <P>Best Detective Stories of Agatha Christie</P>
      <P>Dear Lucas!</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your letter, I was glad to get it and know a lot of news about you.</P>
      <P>First of all I want to congratulate your cousin with fifteenth birthday and with all the best. I hope that it will be good holiday for her, her family and friends.</P>
      <P>Now about your questions, it is very difficult for me to give any advice you about it, I don't know your cousin very well so I don't know what she prefers reading. But when I was fifteen my favourite book " Best Detective Stories of Agatha Christie". So I can recommended you to present this book, because it is very interesting, amuse, sometimes dramatic and mystery book. This book help us to impove our logic, mind, memory and it teaches the reader not to lie, be more honest with other people and pay attention for the smallest details in our life because sometimes it can help us very very much.</P>
      <P>So I hope I could help you.</P>
      <P>Write me as soon as you can.</P>
      <P>With best wishes, your</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
