<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR324*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about your musical show "Over the Rainbow". Last week I was on holiday at London and I was very dissappointed when I visited your theatre.</P>
      <P>First of all the show was supposed to start at 19.30, but it was delayed untill 20.15, and when the show finally began we were supriced to see that Danny Brook who was the star of the show, was not playing and someone else had replace him and he was really disappointing.</P>
      <P>Moreover, the advertisement says that discounts will be available with the price of the ticket, but when I asked for one they told me that there was not any.</P>
      <P>Last but not least, the advertisement says to visit your restaurant after the show, but when we went to the restaurant we realised that it was closed because the cook was ill.</P>
      <P>The advertisement says that it is going to be your perfect evening out, but it was not. it was a complete waste of time and money. That is why I would like to request full refund of my money.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully, </P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets, but she was her best friend and she had to trust her. Anna told her again: "Pat don't tell it to anyone please, especially to my brother everything will be ruin then". and Pat answered: "Don't wory I won't tell anyone".</P>
      <P>The big secret was that Anna was prearing a suprice party for her brother, John and she didn't want anyone to know about it. She had told it to Pat though and that was extremely dangerous! Anna couldn't do anything though because she needed her help to give the invitations. The party was set up to be in two days.</P>
      <P>The two days passed really fast and Anna was happy because Pat hadn't told anything to her brother, or so she thought!</P>
      <P>Pat went to Anna's and she seemed really unhappy.</P>
      <P>- "Anna I have a confession to make" Pat told her and she started crying</P>
      <P>- "What is it Pat?" Anna asked and she started to worry.</P>
      <P>- "I've told your brother about the party. I couldn't help it!, I'm so sorry!"</P>
      <P>- "What?" Anna couldn't believe it, she was devastated, she started crying and told Pat "Get out of my house, now!!!" Pat left. Everything were destroyed the party and their friendship.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
