<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR326*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing in order to express my extreme dissatisfaction with the musical show 'Over the Rainbow' that recently took place in The Circle Theatre.</P>
      <P>During my prior holiday in London I came across an encourageing advertisment for the show and decided to see it.</P>
      <P>Unfortunately, I was very dissappointed to find out that there were no discounts available! Therefore, it cost me more money then usual.</P>
      <P>In addition, I was very annoyed by the fact that the event had started at 20:15 - not 19:30 as mentioned in the advertisment.</P>
      <P>My dissatisfaction became even bigger when I had realize that there had been a different actor than Danny Brook performing!</P>
      <P>Moreover, I was unable to use the theatre restaurant as it had been closed due to redecoration!</P>
      <P>Having noticed that this was not 'a perfect evening out' I would like to ask for my money back. I feel as if I had been lied to and thus I demand my money to be returned.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to receiving a response in the near future.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. Everyone had already heard of me getting the secret access code for the 'Secret Society' organisation.</P>
      <P>This was the kind of association everybody knew of but nobody talked about. Everyone was aware that telling aloud about 'Secret Society' could get you in trouble, serious trouble. There had been cases when somebody entered the club but never came back afterwards.</P>
      <P>I guess it was that thrill that actually made me anxious to know what really was going on inside the dodgy-looking old house guarded by a man with an unfriendly hound.</P>
      <P>I've always enjoyed the hazard and this time getting the password was, indeed, a tough coockie. But knowing what these people are capable of makes me doubt wether to use it or not. Especially now, when 'big-mouth' Pat spread the news to litterally everyone. I wouldn't be surprised if suddenly something bad happened to me.</P>
      <P>Therefore, I have to escape. What I've learned from this situation is to never trust people again. You should remember about this in the future.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
