<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR328*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>Competitor Organiser</P>
      <P>Dear Helen,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you in replay to the letter I have recently recived, to inform you about some details that I am concerned about. First of all I want you to know that I would prefer to travel in July due to the exam I will be taking in June and, afterwards, I will start my university studies in September which means lots of things to be sorted out.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I prefer staying in log cabins because it is easyer for me to keep my personal belongings clean and tidy apart from the fact that I am terribly afraid of insects such as spiders and ants.</P>
      <P>In your letter you settled the possibility to choose two activities and I would like to let you know that I would be pleased if I could join to basketball and climbing, as I am very good at both of them due to I've played in my secondary scholl as leader of my team and due to my long training periods in lifting weights.</P>
      <P>Lastly, do I need to take with me any special staff of clothes? Do I need some money? and if it is so, how much?</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable</P>
      <P>Suppose you go shopping with your girlfriend, that means that you will have to spend hours walking behind her from one shop to another and during the time that she is trying the items on, you have to bear with the odds faces of the other women looking at you as if you were an alien into their territory.</P>
      <P>There is as well the struggle you have to endure when you find yourself into the crowds crambled in the small shops during the unique day-off you have to buy somthing you like. All this can easily leads to a nerve-collapse, particularly when you realise that your money has been stolen either during your difficult way across the crowds or while you were qeuing to pay. If this wasn't enough you strength and mental health can be completely destroyed when despite having been stolen, having spent hours walking around and being tired and hungry you finally buy something you really liked with your credit card and after having walked a few blocks you see the same item at half price in another shop.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
