<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR329*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen RYAN,</P>
      <P>I'm the winner of the first prize in your competion and I'm writing to you to give some information which was required for you.</P>
      <P>Your first question was about when I'd like to travel. Well, it's only possible in July because of the University's holiday (during the rest of the year I'm attending to the classes).</P>
      <P>If I can choose accommodation I prefer log cabins, because when I've been in Camps, it always has been in tents, then I'd like to change and try this other kind of accommodation.</P>
      <P>It's really difficult choose two activities from that list. Everyone are very interesting. Anyway, I think Basketball could be the right because it's the sport that I'm practising from I was a child and photography because it's my hobby on my free time, I'm really enjoy it and I can say I'm so good in it.</P>
      <P>I was wondering which kind of clothes we need and what about money and meals, Are they provided? or can we find some places to buy it?</P>
      <P>I suppose it's everything that you need from me. Any other question don't hesitate to ask me. I'm looking forward to hearing from you, again.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>SHOPPING IS NOT ALWAYS ENJOYABLE.</P>
      <P>I think shopping is a subject really up to date. I can say that nowadays is growing up very quickly in our society like a kind of sport or hobby to waste or spend the free time. And it's creating a lot of adict people, call "shopalcoholics".</P>
      <P>Otherwise shopping is not always enjoyable. You can spend hours and hours going shopping and not find what you were looking for, perhaps because it is not your size or the colour that you like, or just nothing is suitable to you. Another common problem could be the long queue in the fitting rooms waiting stand up for your turn. After that, the unfriendly and sometime's unpolite shop assistance who breaks your nerves down. But never mind! the worst arrive when you get at home in the evening and find a chair to sit because your feet are killing you and realize you have spent all the money without buying the stuff that you need to cook tonight.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
