<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR330*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>17th June, 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam:</P>
      <P>Or to whom it main concern:</P>
      <P>I am writting to you because I had a very disappointing evening at the Circle Theatre.</P>
      <P>Well I seems to me that you should know what had happened there.</P>
      <P>First of all, I read your advertisement where it was written that the musical show started at 19.30, but do you know at what hour it started? It started at 20:15! Don't you think it is a lack of respect? Really it was.</P>
      <P>I forgot to tell you that there were no available discounts. And tickets were too expensive! Most people couldn't afford them.</P>
      <P>As a matter of fact, when the musical show was over, I was really hungry. But as I had read your advertisement I knew there was a restaurant. So I went there in order to have something to eat. But can you believed it, it was closed. Absolutely closed. So I asked someone who seemed to be in charge, and he told me that it was too late to have a meal. This really disappoint me. I was both hungry and angry.</P>
      <P>Well I think that is all, but I will ask you to give my money back.</P>
      <P>Looking forward hearing from you.</P>
      <P>yours Faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Secrets</P>
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. Maybe this is how my story begins.</P>
      <P>Well first of all Pat was a very friend of mine. He was really a good friend, until something had happened.</P>
      <P>I was attending college, as I normally do. With nothing to lose, at all, but on the contrary, with a lot to learn from.</P>
      <P>I was very keen on English lessons, maybe because I was sitting near the Boy I loves. Yes, I think this was the only reason. His name was Cody. He was a very handsome and good looking boy. But far from that, he was a very kind person.</P>
      <P>Pat told me that he was also in love with me. He told me that it was nessary to do something about. But I didn't know what to do.</P>
      <P>Pat suggested me to talk to him. But I really didn't managed to do so.</P>
      <P>As Pat was lossing his patience, he decided to talk to him. I can say that I was very nervious or anxious about what was going to happen. He didn't kept my secret.</P>
      <P>Pat told him that I was in love with him. This was my secret and now it was not. But so, I think it was for the best, he was also in love with me.</P>
      <P>But on the other hand I will never trust in Pat.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
