<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR331*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Madame,</P>
      <P>I am writting this letter to informe you about the decisions I have made according to your questions.</P>
      <P>First of all I would like to travel on July because I will I have finished my exams by the end of June. I will not be able to travel on August because I have found a job for that month.</P>
      <P>Secondly I would prefer to be accommodate in log cabins. When I was a child I was affraid of all these little insects that they live in the ground and this fear still remain till now. I also think that the log cabin will be much more confortable than the tent.</P>
      <P>asketball and swimming are the two activities I have chosen. I play basketball since I was twelve years old and I am member of the basketball school team for four years. In swimming I had won the first price of a local competition.</P>
      <P>Finaly I would like to ask you for some further informations about the clothes and the money we will need.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>As you already know, last month I was helping at a pop concert. It was a very excited experience and I really enjoyed very much.</P>
      <P>I didn't have to do something very difficult. I was only responsable for the property of the back stages. But if anyone was been asking for some help I was always there.</P>
      <P>The most exciting about this experience was to meet all these well-known people. I was shocked and terrified the firt time I saw them, but the truth is that they are men like us. They have a very simple life and behavior when they weren't on the scene</P>
      <P>If I have the opportunity next month I really want to go back. I will definitely apply for a place.</P>
      <P>Love</P>
      <P>Kelly.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
