<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR788*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear manager,</P>
      <P>My name is Joseph and I am writing this letter to complain about the mass that the adimnistration of the Circle theatre presented to me.</P>
      <P>Last week my son and I went to see Over the rainbow at the Circle theatre. We paid to see Danny Brook, my son's favorite actor, but we seems quite disappointing, my son was very happy because he would see for the first time his favorite actor. However it's just the begining of the problems we had. Expecting the britan pontuality we went to the theatre at 19:00 to wath the 19:30 section but it only starts at 20:15, it finished later than it was suposed to and then we missed the train. I haven't seen any discounts available, I though my son would payed less than I. As we had alredy missed the first we went at the theatre restaurant that is famous for the good food, however it was closed.</P>
      <P>In spite of this, less you can do for us is to give my money back and work hard so that this theater that is famouis about its beauty and pontuality don't become famous about it desorganized shows.</P>
      <P>Thanks,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>People have seen in the last 10 years how diferent our clothes had become to. Clothes that used to be made of coton, but nowadays we can see shirts, pants socks....made of almost everything. It is a revolution in the fashion that is starting now. Nowadays we have drifit a kind of clothes that keep the temperature of our body, clothes that don't get wet or even dirty. Computers that make some little things for us nowadays, but at the speed at tecnology goes in the next century those clothes will tell our doctors our healt at any moment, any time, any where, people will be able to locate us arround the world. In the future we won't by clothes by size or even color, our clothes will adapt to our body, the weather, our fit so, our necessities. It already started and don't have limites to go.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
