<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR336*0101*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Brown,</P>
      <P>I am writing to give you information about Mr Brown's surprise party.</P>
      <P>First of all, the reason that we decided to do this party was because Mr Brown helped to the organisation of our trip to France. And we preciate to not tell him about our party.</P>
      <P>Secondly, the party it is on Tuesday 16th pm at the College Canteen. As concerned the food, our mothers they will help about that. Also, the drinks we will take them from our canteen and there will be a group of mucisians for our entertainment.</P>
      <P>Moreover, at the party they will be come of course all the class, our teachers and the Principal at our school. Finally, I would like to ask you about our present. We should buy a book or a Cd player.</P>
      <P>I hope that to have been of some help you about the party. I look forward to seeing you there.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>It was Friday morning when I saw John and said me he had some good news to tell me. And it was real good news. It was about a job which I wanted very much. He also tell that I must be the next day at 7:00 p.m. in the company.</P>
      <P>All the night I did not sleeping at all. I was draw 6:30 p.m in the company. The executive calls me on the office, and he has show me my office.</P>
      <P>From, that day, every day I was gone to the office 30 minutes before. When I complete a month to this job my executive he tell to John to go to the office. I was surpised because I did not know what he wanted. When I went his wants to tell me that from the next month I will be his personal secratary and my salary it will be the double how the previous. I cannot believe it.</P>
      <P>Now, my life it is in the best way it would be thought about. And every day when I wake up I think that I live in the dream which I never want to finish.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
