<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR339*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam.</P>
      <P>I am writting to inform some problems we had. I want to the theatre to see "over the rainbow" at 17th June.</P>
      <P>First of all, we went to ticket office to get the tickets. I thought we can buy discounts tickets according to the advertisement. However, we couldn't buy them the price. eventually, we got the tickets, Because we would like to see the musical and Danny Brook. After we arrive at the theatre, We were very disappointed. Because the different actor played the musical that day. In addition, It started 20:15. We had to wait over 40 minitues. and we couldn't enjoy dinner at theatre restaurant after the show.</P>
      <P>I think if the musical start late time, you should open the restaurant until late time.</P>
      <P>To tell the truth, we couldn't enjoy our evening. Would it be possible for me to back money for tickets.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets.</P>
      <P>We had a secret. After we finish school, we usually gathered the place. Where do you think?</P>
      <P>It was ship!! There was beach our town. One day, Freddie found it there. it was old and little broken. But it was most important place in the world. We always played there and it was adventure for us.</P>
      <P>One day, Suddenly, heavy storm came our town. I went to the sea to see our ship. My friends had come there, too. We worried about it and we tryed to pull it. It seemed to sank into the sea, but fourtunately, storm went soon. Our ship left on the beach. And our parents and teachers, too. Because Pat called them. Of course we couldn't play there after that.</P>
      <P>But now, I am thinking about new secret our place. Where do you think?</P>
      <P>It is a secret!!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
