<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR341*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>lausanne, the 17th of June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>Last weekend, I have been in London with my friend and I saw your musical show "over the Rainbow".</P>
      <P>I write this letter to you for explain my very bad evening I have passed in theatre. On the paper it was writting the principal actor is "Danny Brook" but it wasn't him, it was a different actor that we have never seen, and heard. I think it's really not correct.</P>
      <P>They haven't respect the timetable, the show had to begun at 19:30 and he started at 20:15 how can you explain this fault?!</P>
      <P>But it's not finish you wrote on the paper "Discounts available" but it wasn't true, it was a very badly organisation. After this bad show we had want to go to the Restaurant for drunk and ate something and it was closed and nobody had explained us why the Restaurant wasn't open.</P>
      <P>So, I'm very angry when I think about this evening, and I want to have my money back. I think it's the minimum you have to do for me.</P>
      <P>Thank you in advance.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>SCHOOLS ENGLISH LANGUAGE MAGAZINE</P>
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets, this sentance is very popular in our school. Pat is not an angry girl. She is very friendly but she can't keep a secret. Last year, on a Saturday evening my boyfriend phone me at 20 h o'clock and said me, "Would you like to go to the cinema with me" I asked my parents but the said me "No you can't go to the cinema, tomorrow you have school. Then I phone to Pat for explain my big problem. Pat said to me "You said to your parents that you sleep by me and you don't go to the cinema. I asked my parents and they said alright you can go to Pat for sleeping. I was very happy, I phone to my boyfriend and I explained him my secret he said allright so at nine o'clock in front of the cinema". I passed a really beautiful evening with Pat and my boyfriend in the cinema, but on Sunday my mother phone Pat's mother and Pat's mother explain all the story to my mother. If Pat haden't say the secret to her mother I would be have no problem. Since this Saturday evening I had never speaking with Pat.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
