<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR344*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan</P>
      <P>I would like to thank you for your letter you recently sent me concerning the competiton of two weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A.</P>
      <P>This august I will start a new job so the only possible month for me to join in the Camp is July. I hope this will cause no problems.</P>
      <P>I am glad that you offer for accommodation not only tents but also log cabins. Because I am a light sleeper and have problems with my back I prefer to sleep in a log cabin with a comfortable bed.</P>
      <P>Although it was not easy to choose two activities from your list I decided to do Singing and Surfing. It is difficult to say how good I can sing but I really like it and I think I am not too bad. I never did Surfing in my life but I am a very good Snowboarder and this could be an advantage.</P>
      <P>I hope I gave you all informations you need. There is something I like to know from you.</P>
      <P>Should I bring some special clothes (surfing) with me? How much money do you think I have to change and is there a possible to get more (bank)?</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Rosalinde Schulz</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim</P>
      <P>Last saturday evening I spent a wonderful time. The motor bike club of our town organized a pop concert. A girlfriend of a member of the club asked me if I would like to help at the information desk. I did not hesitate one moment.</P>
      <P>The only thing I had to do was solving the different problems of the guests and just being there if they have any questions. Some people came from Germany some from Austria and some came from England or the U.S.A.</P>
      <P>Talking English with the people from England or the U.S.A. was wonderful. They were all very kind and with some of them I spent the rest of the evening and also the following day.</P>
      <P>That I reached a lot of money for doing something I like very much was very nice but the most important thing for me was meeting people, having fun and using the English language. I will never forget this evening.</P>
      <P>Love,</P>
      <P>Rosalinde Schulz</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
