<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR345*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sirs!</P>
      <P>First I want to thank you for all the congratulations, and I'll try to answer all your questions about for instance travel and accomodation. I have to tell you that for me it is only possible to go on holiday in July because my father is very ill and it is only possible for my sister to take care of him in July (because her small children are in summer school at this time. Another question was about the accommodation. I have to tell you that I'd prefer tents. For me tents are a kind of back to basic living and I like this very much. In my opinion people should become more familiar with the rules of nature.</P>
      <P>I was very glad to read that it is possible to do activities at Camp California. I've chosen singing and swimming. Singing is one of my favourite activities and I know that I do it very well. I'm also used to sing in front of a large number of people 'couse I did it several times. I'm also good at swimming but I do not do it professional.</P>
      <P>There are two further questions which I have to ask you. First How much money do I have to take with me? and what clothes should I choose? I'd be very happy if you could give me a call and answer this questions.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim!</P>
      <P>Today I have to tell you something really exciting and also very hard to believe. Last month I received a letter which told me that I've entered a competition. I was so happy and suprised that I first could not really believe it. But it was true. My price was the chance to meet a pop group and to help at the concert. The pop group which was going to act is called "Metallica" and I like their music very much ('cause in my opinion the music is a bit different from all the songs you usually listen to.) But now to the concert itself. It took place on the 10th of June in Salzburg. I started at 8 pm but I had to be there at 11 am. First I had to help with the catering which lasted until 2 pm. After this I met the band members and got to know them while we were having a good meal. The front man felt a bit sick and so he skipped the meal. I was so excited that I also was not able to eat anything. At 5 pm the band members disappeared again and I was responsible for some kind of guiding tour for the journalists. I had to show them the way to the interviewing room. It was a bit boring but more or less okay. At 7 p.m. the first group started. They were unknown and not very good but when I met them afterwards I recognised that they are very nice. At 8 pm Metallica started and I have to tell you, they did a great performance. When I met them after the concert they asked me questions like Did you like the performance! or How do you think about the first group? Questions like you and I usually ask each other. You know what I mean, they were not conceited or something like this. They were like any other person and I have to admit that I like them very much. This was one of the best and most exciting days in my life.</P>
      <P>Hope you answer this letter as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Lots of hugs and kisses</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
