<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR347*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen,</P>
      <P>I am very glad to hear from you that I have won the first prize in your competition. I would like to reply and ask you some questions.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I would be available for travelling only in July because my university will finish at the end of June and will start again in August. Secondly, for the accomodation, I would say I prefer living in tent rather than in log cabin because I used to sleep in tent while I was joining a local scout camp in my country. Thirdly, I have choosen Sailing and Photography from the list you gave me because both of them are my favorite hobbies and I have been enjoying Sailing and Photography for several years so I am quite good at both of them. Finally, I would ask you whether I have to prepare any speacial clothes for camping or the camp will provide them for me.</P>
      <P>I look forward to receiving the details of travelling soon and joining your camp in July.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>In my opinion, I do agree with this expression. One of the most unforgettable habit of city life is going out for shopping. I used to hang around famous cloth shops looking at the new arrival clothes section. It is not only a good fun to see the new fashions and things but also decrease the money in my pocket.</P>
      <P>Sometime shopping doesn't give anything to you but always waste all your free time. A group of girls can spend their time in a shopping center forever. It seems to me that more people in my hometown tend to go shopping in their free time because the shopping complexs nowadays are more attractive and combine every facilities inside. From my point of view, someone goes shopping just because he/she wants to show off that he/she is wealthy.</P>
      <P>Keeping balance between daily life and shopping life may give more enjoyable rather than always walking in an air-conditioned shopping complex.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
