<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR349*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mz. Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter and I am very pleased that I won the first prize in your compition. However, I am writing to you to ask for more details.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I would like to go to California in June if his is possible because I will have finished my course in Merton college at the end of June.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I would prefer to staying in a tent rather than staying in a log cabin in order to have experience, which I haven't had before.</P>
      <P>I am very knee on swimming and playing tennis so that I have had a part-time job in a sports centre in the evenings. I also have qualifications to teach them.</P>
      <P>In addition to all this, I would appriciate it if you could let me have more details about clothes and how much I shall be paid for the travel.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>To: Mrs. Sexington</P>
      <P>From: An Soo Kim</P>
      <P>Subject: Speaking classes and school trips</P>
      <P>Introduction.</P>
      <P>The aim of this report is to describe our English classes in Merton College and suggest that what we should film for making a short video.</P>
      <P>Speaking class should be filmed.</P>
      <P>It is suggested that speaking classes should be filmed the reason why is that the more students tend to attend.</P>
      <P>Another reason is that it will be more useful for forigen students who want to speak English. A number of forigen students have recently been increasing.</P>
      <P>School trips</P>
      <P>It is also thought that school trips are to be filmed because it is a wide range of interesting places available. It is believed that one of the most popular activities in Merton College.</P>
      <P>Conclusion</P>
      <P>To sum up, it is recommened that speaking classes and school trips should be filmed.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
