<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR352*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sirs</P>
      <P>We are writting to you to complain about the musical show "Over the Rainbow", we saw last week in your Theatre.</P>
      <P>We have spent a week's holiday in London and wanted to see a musical show. We read an advertisement about your musical show, starred by the well-known Danny Brook and Tina Truelove in a local newspaper</P>
      <P>We were very disappointed to hear that the actor was replaced by other at the last minute. The advertisement said that it starts at 19.30, but it started actually at 20:15 due to the probleme of the sound. We were also surprised to discover that the student discounts wasn't available for us, because they didn't accept our student indentity card from Switzerland.</P>
      <P>We were very frustrated to read on the door of the theatre restaurant "Close due to holidays" specially when we were very starving.</P>
      <P>This evening was a waste of time. So we asked you for our money back.</P>
      <P>I looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed your daily life?</P>
      <P>Could you figure out how your life will be without all the modern technology? What is the effect of it in your environement? Were the people happier in a past than to day? If you are interested in the question, you will be interested by this article.</P>
      <P>Nowadays, the technology takes a large place in your daily life and improves the speed of the achievement. For example at work, we look on the computer screen all day, sending e-mail at the other side of the world, doing some searches etc. We gain a lot of time with computer, but if your computer brooks down, you couldn't do anything because everything is on it.</P>
      <P>The technology moves very fast specially in the domaine of transportation. The cars are able to reach 300 km per hours speed and are more reliable than in the past.</P>
      <P>The major probleme for the industry cities is to deal with the bad effect of polution in the environement. A lot of money are involved in research to stop the increasing of polution.</P>
      <P>To sum up, all the improvements have a price to pay; The condition of the environement. We are too reliable at technology today. But we can ask us "What will be happen in 50 years? Our children will be able to travel in the moon as we travel to Japan?</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
