<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR353*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir</P>
      <P>Owing to the bad organisation of the last play that was played in your theatre those last weeks I want to explain you some incorrect information that I found in your advertisement and as a result of it, all the problems that I had.</P>
      <P>First of all, I think if you go to a play and you are watching to see your favourite actor playing a good play and then appears a silly one, who doesn't know what to do, it is disappoint at all.</P>
      <P>Secondly, all the spectators were waiting the begining of the play at 19.30 and it started at 20.15 then I would like to know why do you say one time in the advertisement why do you do what you want.</P>
      <P>Another thing that I want to know is why you didn't do any discount if it was showed in the advertisement.</P>
      <P>Maybe, I could be a good way to get spectators but I'm going to comunicate that to my travel office.</P>
      <P>When the play was finished I was looking for your theatre restaurant but it was closed because like on the paper that was on the door was writen, it was too late.</P>
      <P>I think, that it wasn't my perfect evening out so I wait to be payed back.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets so she lost all her school friends.</P>
      <P>All started when she was fifteen, when started a new course on the institute and met some girls that passed the time they would became her friends.</P>
      <P>Three years passed and like is normal between friends, she knew a lot of things about them like her friends knew a lot about her</P>
      <P>When it was time to do the final exam, she became ill and she couldn't do it so teachers decided to allow her to pass the course because she had a lot of good marks but on the other hand the principal desagreeded with it and didn't give the permision to pass her.</P>
      <P>She had to repeat that course and all her friends passed and like is usuall girls from the last course became popular.</P>
      <P>Pat, to win her new classemates' friendship tell all what she knew about her friends and owing to what Pat said, her friends broke they friendship with Pat because their popularity was damaged.</P>
      <P>Pat's classmates made the same and Pat finished alone.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
