<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR355*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir of Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about the musical show which was presented by The Circle Theatre last week. I saw the performance and it was not like it was mentioned in the advertisent I read in the local newspaper.</P>
      <P>First of all, the main actor was not Dany Brook as it was expected so. That was very disappointing. Secondly it must have started at 14.30 and ended by 19.30. However, it started at 20.15. I had to wait almost an hour. Then, I was planning to buy three £20 tickets because it was mention in the advertisement that there were dicounts available but that was not true, so I just could buy two tickets and my son could not see the show. Finally, I was thinking to have dinner in the threatre restaurant after the show but it was closed due to some problems with the employees.</P>
      <P>What was suposed to be a perfect and enjoyable evening, resulted in a very disappointing time. So I would be greatful if you payed for a full refund of the money I spent in the tickets.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Computers, radio, CD's, sattelite television and a lot of other things have changed my daily life. Modern technology affects the way things are done and many aspects in my life, and it has some advantages as some disadvantages.</P>
      <P>On the one hand, technology is a great help for me at school. What I mean is that computers are very useful to do my homework (like some monographies or researching). And I can't even think about how it would be not having a computer. Another advatage is that, for example sattelite television, which is an example of modern technology, makes me be informed about what is happening on the whole world.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, I have to admit that technology makes things so easy that when I have to do them without it I find it very difficult. The best example is the homework I have to do for school, I can't manage to do it when I don't have my computer to help. In addition to that, technology doesn't sometimes let me develop my imagination and creative skills. My mother says that I'm always playing with my computer or watching T.V. instead of reading or doing some more interesting activities.</P>
      <P>To sump up, I can't think about how my life would be without technology.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
