<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR356*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>June, the 13th 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>You can guess how an enjoyable surprise receiving your letter was for me. I am glad to send you the items required.</P>
      <P>First of all, I must precise that I can only leave during the month of July owing to the job I obtained for August. After considering your accomodation offers, I'd rather stay in a log cabin if possible. I hope you have no doubt about my taste for camping, however I admit I will appreciate a bit of comfort two weeks long.</P>
      <P>Moreover, I must recognize that the activities offered are really attractive so it's hard to make up my mind. On the one hand, I own a camera that I often use during leisure times. Even if the photograph made are modest work, I am really interested in this activity. Then, as low my level of basketball is, I have enjoyed playing this sport for fun for a long time. So it will be pleasant for me to practice this activity.</P>
      <P>Your letter indicates that the pride includes that some costs are paid. Nevertheless I would like you to precise what I eventually need for this travel.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>What obviously appears about our daily life at school is that it is hard to sum up all the different aspects it includes. Therefore, the film will manage to be a success if it doesn't forget the main times that make our life.</P>
      <P>To my mind, the class attending a lesson must be shown at first. It evoques the reason of our presence here and it is a cliché; that can not. A philosophy lesson seems quite appropriate in that the pupils take part in it.</P>
      <P>Next, students during the pause in the yard should be filmed. It would not only emphasize the sharp contrast with the classroom atmosphear but also show how they are as young people. Students chatting, laughing, eating and even smoking must remain in the video.</P>
      <P>Furthermore two moments could have a role. First of all, the arrive of every students, namely the picture of the school without anybody at first, and then with the crowd of students increasing gradually is typical of its life. Then, the opposite situation, that is to say the scene of this crowd disappearing at the end of the day can make a parallel.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
