<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR357*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I have recently had a week's holiday in London and, during my stay, I went to see the musical show 'Over the rainbow', which was shown at your theatre.</P>
      <P>At first, the advertisement said that there were discounts availables, but when I went to buy the tickets there were not any discounts.</P>
      <P>As if this was not enough, the show, instead of starting at half past seven as the advertisement said, started at a quarter past eight and one of the main actors, who was supposed to be Danny Brook, was someone else.</P>
      <P>On top of everyting, the restaurant which was announced in the advertisement was closed because it was being arranged.</P>
      <P>You can imagine how dissappointed I felt after that evening, and I am writing to ask you for a further return of part of the money.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>I think modern technology hasn't changed my life a lot, but it has in some things: I work with music and with graphic design too, and computers help me a lot in this things.</P>
      <P>In music, before having a computer I could only write my compositions and 'listen' to them into my mind, because, of course, I haven't got an orchestra to play them, but now I just can record one part, and then another part, and then another one.. and I can get the sound of every instrument controlling it with a keyboard, or even create new sounds.</P>
      <P>In graphic design, before having a computer I just could draw, but now I can create pictures pixel by pixel, develop ideas more easily, or take photographs into my computer and transform them or mix them.</P>
      <P>But, in other things, I think modern technology hasn't changed my way of living too much: I do more or less the same as I did some years ago: I get up in the morning, go to school, have lunch, study and go out with my friends without being afected by microchips or nuclear energy.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
