<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR358*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I have happily received your reply letter and I want to thank you for this marvelous prize you have given me. Now to answer your questions, I can only travel in July because that's the only period of the year I can get out of working for more than two weeks. I would like a log cabin because I think you should give me a good accommodation and not just a tent to sleep in, with no electricity and entertainment. I would like to play basketball and tennis for you. I am a regular basketball player. Most of the time I play as a slammer and I do feel that I'm reasonably good in it. At tennis I'm the best player of my whole school and once, I got to the top 10 of my country in tennis.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask you what type of clothes should I bring? Money, how much should I bring. Would $200 be enough? Well that's all for now and I hope to hear from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Basilio Romero</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>How are you? I have just received your letter and let me tell you what you missed over here. You should have been here, it was amazing. The concert began at 8:00 p.m but my friends and I had to be there by 2:00 pm to help set up the stage. We started by putting up the lights. We had to climb up to 15m to put up those lights and afterwards the band didn't even use them. Well, we also had to carry all the instruments up to the stage and believe me, that was the hardest bit of all. They were extremely heavy and there were a lot of them on the bus. After helping to do that and many other things, my friends and I watched the concert and before Green day (the group) left, they came up to us an thanked us for all the hard work we did, and shoke our hands. I'll never wash my hands again. Well that's all the time I've got for you now. Hope to hear from you soon.</P>
      <P>Basilio Romero</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
