<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR360*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs. Ryan,</P>
      <P>I'm writing you in response to your letter, I was delighted to know that I won the first price.</P>
      <P>With reference to the date, I only can go on July, as I'm going off on holiday on August, and I start university on September. The place I'd prefer to stay in is a log cabin, where I'm sure I'd feel more confortable than in a tent.</P>
      <P>It's very nice of you to let me choose my favourite activities. The ones I'm most keen on are Tennis, in which I think I'm pretty good since I took some classes last year, and Painting, which is one of my favourite hobbies, and helps me to relax myself and forget about problems. I think I'm not bad at painting either, at least everyone in my family likes my work, includying myself.</P>
      <P>Anyway, there are some questions I'd like to ask you: What kind of clothes would be the most suitable for California weather in summer, and how much money do you think I'll need?</P>
      <P>I'm waiting forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Manela B.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I'm so sorry I haven't written until now, but you know I'm always very busy.</P>
      <P>As I told you in my last letter, last month I worked for a pop band, and helped them at a concert in Barcelona. It was such a great experience!</P>
      <P>Basically my work was carrying the instruments, the speakers and the lights from the vans to the stage, which is not an easy work because, as you can imagine, it's not exactly light stuff.</P>
      <P>But the most exciting part was meeting the band, mainly the singer and the drummer who are very nice and also good-looking.</P>
      <P>Anyway, I had lot of fun working for them. I hope they call me soon, I'd be the happiest girl in the world if I could see them again...</P>
      <P>I'd better leave now. I hope you write again soon.</P>
      <P>Manela B.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
