<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR361*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Madam</P>
      <P>I am very happy to win this prize and I am going to give you some information from me that you need to make me have a good time at Camp California.</P>
      <P>I would like to know only in July because I have set my holidays this month since last January.</P>
      <P>I want if it is possible a log cabins like accommodation because I have been suffering from my back since my childhood, therefore I need a confortable accommodation.</P>
      <P>I will be pleased to swim and paint when I am at the camp. I selected swimming because it is a cure against my backace and I have not practiced since I started my new job five years ago. I also choosed painting because I have never done before, I would like to learn and moreover I want to do a calm activity.</P>
      <P>Otherwise, could you tell me approximately how much money I have to take for the food, please?</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely.</P>
      <P>Xavier Fournier</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>How many times have we heard people complaining about shopping? Sometimes, they are happy to do shopping. but why? Therefore, shopping can be enjoyable but it is not always the case.</P>
      <P>Shopping is enjoyable when you want to offer some thing to someone. In fact you try to get a present to make receive happy.</P>
      <P>Shopping is also good, when you know what you want. For example if you want a new track suit you know that you have to go to a sport shop but if you don't know what you want you are going to waste your time in the shops.</P>
      <P>In the opposite, shopping can be disenjoyable.</P>
      <P>Shopping is boring if you go with people too fussy. That is to say, they are never happy with what they get and see. They always find a problem.</P>
      <P>Shopping is not enjoyable with people who just look around the shops. It is stupid, they do not have any goal. They waste their time.</P>
      <P>To conclude, I agree with shopping is not always enjoyable. Even if I like to do shopping with some people and kind of shops I will kill myself because I waste my time.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
