<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR362*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>I am writing you in relation to our next programme in London from 13th March to 14th March. First at all, it is a pleasure to say that the programme which you so kindly have prepared is very interesting, especially the visit to the National Art Gallery on Wednesday.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, our class has recently read an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show which takes place during our visit to London, on Tuesday 14th. This show is a good opportunity to know the latest fashions in several topics like make up, Hairstyles and leisure and sports wear. We think that it could be a great chance in order to know British fashion and probably it would give us good information for improving our studies.</P>
      <P>We would like to know if it could be possible to introduce a little change in our programme. Our question is: instead of going to the shopping on Tuesday, in the afternoon, could we go to the London Fashion and Leisure Show?</P>
      <P>I hope you will consider our suggestion. I look forward to hearing your reply.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Classroom 5</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>How will be our future homes?</P>
      <P>Believe it or not, our lives are changing and becoming more complicated every day. The reason of all of this things is the impressionable introduction of the "new technologies", such as Computers, Internet or WAP technologies.</P>
      <P>Of course, this new facilities will be introduced at home. Now, it is already possible to send our shopping list by the computer, and this opption, in the next years, will become the most common once.</P>
      <P>The new technologies probably will produce a considerably revolution in some essencial parts of the house. For example, we will have got computerizated ovens, microwaves and freezers, or we will probably have got central heating controled through Internet from our office.</P>
      <P>Despite all of this facilities, there are some home activities that will remain the same, fortunately. Who don't like to prepare a cup of tee with traditional kettles, waiting for the boiling watter? And to read the newspaper at breakfast instead of watching TV?</P>
      <P>Some pleasures must be untouchable! We are human beings at least, not "new technological" machines!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
