<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR363*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I was very pleased to receive your letter which informed me of my winning the first prize in your competition, namely two weeks at Camp California in the USA.</P>
      <P>To begin with, I would like to travel in July. This is the only possible time for me, as the school holiday starts on the 29th of June. And from August on I planed to do some part-time job in order to earn some pocket money.</P>
      <P>Referring to the possibilities of accommodation, I'd prefer log cabins to tents. Firstly, log cabins are more comportable than tents. Secondly, I do not like tents. Last not least, I always have backache after sleeping in a tent for a couple of days.</P>
      <P>As I had been asked to choose two activities I would like to during my stay at the camp, I chose Golf and singing. I have never played Golf actually, but I would love to try something new. As for singing, I am very keen on singing as I get lessons in it. I just love singing.</P>
      <P>I would like to know whether there is some facilities for washing the Clothes. Especially in summer, clothes get dirty very easily.</P>
      <P>Lastly, does the prize include pocket money? If not, I will have to bring some with me. Is there a possibility of exchanging different currancies to US dollar? I ask you to enclose the answer in your reply.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you at your earliest convenience.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Mee-Yon Areum.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>When you think of shopping, it reminds you of going out (mostly) with friends, looking for new things like clothes, accesoires etc. and buying them. It sounds nice and shopping is great fun - or it should be.</P>
      <P>Nowadays shopping can be very stressful. It all starts with the search of an appropriate parking-space which can last annoyingly long, especially at weekends.</P>
      <P>Nevertheless, the nightmare starts when you enter the shopping mall or the passage, which is terribly crowded. You cannot make a step without "touching" the others. It gets enormously unbearable in hot summer days, when the temperature increases. In such a situation your friends or the people you are shopping with get lost very easily and looking for them can be very tiring. But the worst moment comes, if you cannot find the thing you were looking for, because it is no longer trendy or because it is sold out.</P>
      <P>Of course, shopping is not always so unpleasant, but sometimes it is simply better to stay at home.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
