<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR364*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Smith,</P>
      <P>Last week I and my family had a holiday in London. At the end of a holiday we decided to go to the theatre. I insisted on going to your theatre, to the Circle Theatre, because I have heard that it is one of the best theatres in London. That days you presented "The over the Rainbow". how you have written at the advertisement: it is the London's newest and best musical show. But I and my family had a very disappointing evening. Because, at first, at the advertisement was written that in this music show would play Danny Brook and Tina Truelove, but it wasn't so. Danny Brook didn't play at the performance, there was another unknown actor. And he played awful, I couldn't hear him. Then at the adverstisement stood that performance begin at 19.30. I and my family came to that time and had to wait till 20:15, because the show started only at that time. I was very nervious. What is more you wrote that discounts available, but it was also lie. After the show I was very disappointed, because I spent a lot of money for nothing and my husband decided to make me a pleasure. He suggested to have a supper in your theatre restaurant. But when we came to it, we saw that the restaurant was closed, because it was reconstructed. But why do you mention about the restaurant at the advertisement, if it is closed? So this evening was terriable. It broke all my impression about London. And now I requere my money back. Because of nothing what was mentioned at the advertisement I didn't get.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>There are a lot of new modern technologies around the world, which appear not long ago. Among them a mobile telephone, computers, telefaxes, different mashiens for kitchen, mashiens which helps housekeeper to do any work about the house. All of them play a very great role in people's daily life. The first change is that they very simplify the life of people. For example, now women don't spend a lot of time at the kitchen, preparing the meal or washing up dishes. They can only push on their dish mashiens and go to do something what they think more pleasant. So with the appearance of new morden technology people have got much more free time. The computer also plays a very important role in daily life of people. Some years ago people especially students had to run to lubraries in order to find a book about something. But now they can use Internet, where you can find any information you need. Very often I use Internet, and I must say it is very convienient. The another modern technology that I use is a mobile telephone.</P>
      <P>If I need to say something important to my parents or my friends, of if something terriable has happened with me, I may not run somewhere to find a telephone box. I just use my mobile phone. Finally, I can say that modern technologies very help people at their works. With them people do their work more quikly and successfully.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
