<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR366*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen,</P>
      <P>I've just seen your letter and I'm really delighted to have won the first prize in your competition.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel in July because it's the only month I have two weeks holiday during the summer. I would prefer to be in log cabins because I feel insecure staying in tent. While I'll be at the Camp, I would like to play tennis and swimming. I've done it for many years and I want to do both once a day. I'm very good at swimming and my level is medium at tennis. If possible, could you let me know what I'll need for example which clothes I must take and how much I can expect to spend.</P>
      <P>I'm excited to go on holliday there and thanks to you, I will realize a dream that I always wanted to do.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim, I want to tell you about my good experience I had last month. I'd enjoyed helping at a pop concert and it has been fabulous. At first, I'd helped them to carry the material and we had fixed everything in the good order. They were so many pieces that we had spent a whole day to prepare the scene. At the end, we have had a beer and we talked together. I was astonished to see so friendly and funny they were and we got good friends. During the show, I was behind them and I could see the spectators shouting and jumping with their and up. It was unbelievable to realize that I'd worked with stars and that they were my friends. It is difficult to explain what I'd particularly liked about my experience because the most memories are in my heart and I'd never thought that I could get on so well with a group of people which I'd known only for few days.</P>
      <P>If possible, I would like introduce you to them, they are very nice guys.</P>
      <P>Best wishes</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
