<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR367*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Manager of the Circle Theatre</P>
      <P>During my last holiday week in London I went to the Circle Theatre after reading the advertisement of the "Over the rainbow" show. I wanted to spend my leisure time well by taking in that cultural event. How stupid of me! I felt really disappointed. First of all in the advertisement was written, as I had read that before, that Danny Brook would be starring in the show. Unfortunately, the different actor stood in for in it. The time of the beginning of the show was written at half past two p.m. and at half past seven that evening, again. Lack of my time made me to go at the evening show. And unfortunately again, from some reasons it was postponed to quarter past eight. Another problem - in the advertisement was exactly written some of the discounts of the tickets. No, alas in reality it appeared a mistake. According to the advertisement, after the show anyone could go to the theatre restaurant for a drink. That appeared impossible, because the theatre restaurant was closed. The reason was unknown. That wasn't enough yet. At the end of the advertisement as I noticed it was said something of perfect evening out. It wasn't truth. That's why I write my letter to you and I ask for my money back. I was expecting something really better. Mr manager, I warn you, if I don't get my money back, we'll meet at the court.</P>
      <P>Yours faitully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>I believe, living in a modern country, that science and technology affected any aspect of my daily life. Looking back in the past, I can see, how big difference is between life of my grandparents and mine. People living in the past couldn't travel so far as we could now and couldn't express the news around the world as we do it now, at present days. They could not communicate with someone living in other country, often located far away from his own. Using mobile phones, e-mails or internet, we have a better access to a lot of different news.</P>
      <P>So, we are in better situation now. But there are some drawbacks, which appeared last years. For example a lot of pollution has raised. We now breathe worse air in our lungs, then our grand-parents breathed. I think, we are more addicted to do some things, which are not concerned with human nature. For example, people are addicted today to watch TV or often using the mobile phones. I don't really mind them. But I think and strongly believe, that we are the part of wildlife. And the modern technology that we use in our everyday life might not only help us, but determinly might destroy us.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
