<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR368*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Robertson</P>
      <P>I am a student from your class and I would like to thank you first of all. It's a good programme, especially the visit to the National Art Gallery.</P>
      <P>A few students and me have heard about a fashion and leisure show. That show takes place on 14th March from 10.00 - 19.00. They show the latest fashion, leisure and sportswear ands something for the women: make up and hairstyle trends. That show is free for students, so it's also a big advantage. We have it already discussed and we think it would be a great opportunity because a lot of students a very keen ongoing.</P>
      <P>I know that it is a change. But I have thought about it. On Monday we could first go to the Sience Museum and in the afternoon to Greenwich. Then we could go sightseeing by bus on Wednesday after lunchtime. I think there is no need to go shopping because we can do our shopping in Cambridge, as well.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Your sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Who would like to be famous?</P>
      <P>Are you dreaming of being a Star? It must be wonderful when you have a lot of money and everybody seems to know you. Really?</P>
      <P>I think the main problem is that you would lose your private life. That's the price you have to pay nowadays. But you need all the journalists to become famous so the only way is to accept that there are journalists and that they are just doing their job.</P>
      <P>No one told you to be famous. If you are famous it was your choice and therefore is a price to pay. Of course you have fame and poverty. But then everyone will recognise you when you are walking on the street.</P>
      <P>To sum up I think, if you well-known you have to deal with that. There's no other way. Everone knows you because of the journalists so can't just ignore them, can you?</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
