<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR370*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you because of the unpleasent evening I have spent recently.</P>
      <P>I have always thought that plays of the Circle Theatre are worth of seeing, but two days before I was very disappointed after visiting yours theatre. Ealyer I had seen an advertisement for the show but the informationes on it caused fals.</P>
      <P>First of all I have not seen my favourite actor Danny Brook. The second think is that the play did not start at 19:30 but at 20:15! I could not get a discount. The last think is that it was unpossible to get the theatre restaurant because it was closed. I was told that it had been painted but nobody had written it on an advertisement.</P>
      <P>At the end I would like to say that my evening out two days before was not perfect and I wold be glad if you could pay my some money back.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Modern technology is changing world every day. I would like to write how it has influented my daily life.</P>
      <P>I am a student of a technical univercity. Some time before I did not know the internet. When I neaded some informationes I had to go to liblary to find it in books or newspapers. Now the only think I have to do is to go to computer room and turn on the computer. The computer is helpfull when I want to contact somebody very fast. I just send an e-mail and that is all!</P>
      <P>The second think is that when I neaded a phone card to call somebody I had to stay in a long queue. Now I just only put some money into a machine and I can take the card from there!</P>
      <P>The last example is that I have in my house a lot of modern equipment like TV set, fridge or microwaves which help me for my living.</P>
      <P>It is obvious that modern technology has changed my daily life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
