<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR372*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear miss Ryan,</P>
      <P>With reference to your letter of 13th of June I would like to thank you for the prize your organisation is offering me.</P>
      <P>I am pleased to provide you with the following information.</P>
      <P>Since I am a student I have to follow the vacation programm of my school, which means that I would only be able to travel during the month of July.</P>
      <P>I would be grateful if you could book a tent for me at Camp California because I am a nature lover and the idea of outdoor-sleeping really makes me happy. Concerning the activities, as a matter of fact tennis is my favorit sport and I am very keen on it, for the second activity I would like to enroll surfing, because my husband, who is already a proficient, keeps telling me about the excitement of this sport, and I think it is worthwile trying, therefore I'd love to be in the beginners group.</P>
      <P>I would like to know if you would be kind enough to send me some information on weather conditions for that period of time, the kind of currency I should take with as well as the vaccination requirements.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you and thank you in advance for your help.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Abril Botella</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Benoni's school is a recognised school for tourism located in the heart of Brussels, Belgium. It offers a wide choice of courses from cooking, computer, make up, languages, geographie to culture and civilization. Students start their day at the Gym, where they learn the importance of being fit, that is way I suggest to film this activity. Once students have taken a shower after a hard physical training they come to real life, depending on their levels they have to study for instance languages wich I personally find very important for a person working in the tourism field because these enables stuff to communicate with clients in a proper way, students have to manage to speak at least three languages. Another important lesson to film is "culture and civilization, therefore people will know that the hostessess prepered at this school are not only, as French say, "pot-au-fleurs", beautiful faces to show off but also well read persons. Last but not less important is the class called "know-how" wich shows students how to cope with unspected problems even if they are in stress. I would also take an outdoor lesson "training". The school works together with known companies of the branch as Mariot hotel, Air France Princess cruise among others in order to provide students with high qualified training.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
