<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR374*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>Thank you for informing me that I have won first prize in your competition two weeks at Camp California in the USA. I will be pleased to send more further information which you need.</P>
      <P>In addition, I would like to travel on july because my school will have finished that month so I will be able to go on holiday. And if it is possible, I would rather be accommadated in log cabins because I would not like to share the bathroom facilities someone who I do not know well. Thank you for asking me to choose the list of the activities. Either I am in the school swimming team and I am intered in photography professionally. Therefore I would like to improve my skills and knowledge about the subjects during my holiday. Could I please know which kind of clothes I should bring with me and the company offers us some expensise money to spend?</P>
      <P>Once again, thank you for sending me information. I feel, it will be the best holiday, I have ever had. I look forward to hearing from you at your earliest convenience.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable</P>
      <P>Who does not like shopping? Perhaps just men or anybody who has lack of time or if you are looking for something to buy particular and shop has not range of variety.</P>
      <P>Frankly, if I had a lot of money I would have spend my entire life to do shopping. Although I am the one who loves shopping, I can not stand on the Easters, the Christmas and Sundays, because those days are suitable for anyone to consume the food, buy some presents etc. However, everyone prefers to do the same thing and the same time. it causes over crowded shops, high-pitch noise, lack of parking place and if you have to go shopping with a child, the whole matters just enough to drive you crazy. Despite knowing the difficulty we do not resist to do shopping in those days. On the other hand, some companies offer special service such as sending your order with the post or on telephone. It could be the solution, avoid busy hours or days, do not bring your child with you, choose the right shop which has park.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
