<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR376*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Robertson Thank you for your good programme for English class, especially it is well-organised and has many different places we can go and we can see. All of us in English class look forward to visiting these places. However, we'd like to ask about London Fashion and Leisure Show that we've seen an advertisement on this week college newspaper. We would appreciate it if you could give us a chance to go there while we are visiting in London. It should be a great opportunity for us because we can see the latest fashions, leisure and sports wear, make up and Hairstyles, As you know, this year is our final year and most of us would like to get a job straight away after this course. We've been worried about our future career and we believe that we need some preparation for it such as dress and hairstyle for an interview. And mostly, it should a great opportunity for the Art students who are attending English class. Most of students in our class are studying Fashion as full-time. Especially, it does not cost at all for students. But the only problem for the show is the date which is on Tuesday 14 March from 10.00 to 19.00. As we're considering your programme we're supposed to go Science Museum and shopping. We're thinking that we can go to these place the next following day. But Mr. Robertson, these our suggestions are depended on your programme, we're just suggesting. Again we're so sorry that we give you an inconvience for your plan and thank you for considering us. We are look forward to hearing from you Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>The Home of the Future.</P>
      <P>Have you ever thought about our future home?</P>
      <P>Living in a high building! But we could have everying we want to. Home might be a mixture with moden styles and natural view as well.</P>
      <P>These days a lot of contries have been worried about lands that can't have enough place to build houses. The prises for lands are getting increasing it's because of this reason.</P>
      <P>So I think that the future home could be considered this points. I mean most of home are going to be in a building like a flat. Maybe it is right say that in a flat instead of a building. I believe there are a lot of high buildings now in Japan. Most of them are flats which have at lest 20 Floors. It means Japanese are planning for the future home.</P>
      <P>But what my imagination is that these flats'll have many functions such as offices, leisure centre, shopping centre even school. Because we are living in computerlised life, so we'll able to do most things at home or these flats'll have these places as well.</P>
      <P>But one more thing, I believe these flats'll have a park for people who'll be living in there. And because it'll be a big building we'll able to see a whole view through the window.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, our future home will have a natural view like these days home and give people a new technological home life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
