<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR378*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear manager,</P>
      <P>Last week I went to the Circle theatre, of which you are responsable, to se the musical show "Over the Rainbow". The advertisement outside the theatre explained a lot of interesting things to enjoy. I am writing this letter because I have had a very disappointing evening. Everything in the advertisement has been done in the Wrong Way. Firstly there was a different actor in the starring; you have written DANNY BROOK and he was absent. I had joined the show because I like DANNY BROOK a lot, but you have changed the program. Moreover the advertisement said that the show time was 19.30; on the contrary it started with 45 minutes of late. Another thing that was wrong is about discounts: you had written they were available, but they were not and so I had to pay the whole ticket's price. But the worst thing was that after the show the restaurant of the theatre was closed and so I had to go to another place to have dinner.</P>
      <P>So it was not "my perfect evening out" and because of my disappointment I am here to ask you some money back.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>I think modern technology has changed human's life a lot, expecially starting with the last century. The changements brought by modern technology are so important that today no one can live without this technology or with a part of it. In my situation for example cars and motorcycles are a necessity to get out: I live on a little mountain at 160 metres of altitud so I cannot go to the city using a bycicle. Because of my "isolation" telephone is very important and I need a good personal computer with a modem and internet so study or do researches, because there are not book shops to buy or borrow books in my little town. Moreover without a cellular phone my mother does not let me go out with my friends to the city because it is too far and she is worried. Another thing that I appreciate a lot is the electric guitar; I like very much play guitar, and in my free time I prefer play electric, than acoustic or classic guitar using distortion and gain and the highest volume possible.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
