<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR381*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I have received your letter about the prize I have won in your competition. I would like to thank you and give some information you asked about me.</P>
      <P>Re time: I am a student and have examinations until the end of June. The only convinient time to travel is in July. I hope you can arrange this.</P>
      <P>Re accommodation: I would like to stay in a log cabin. I have had sleeping and breathing problems in tents which were serious. I hope to avoid these this time.</P>
      <P>Re activities: During the two weeks I would like to do tennis and swimming. I regularly play tennis since I was nine years old and I entered several competitions. Swimming is another sport I learned when I was six.</P>
      <P>I have a few questions about the camp. Are the meals free or do I have to pay for it? Do you have a choice of food? I'm vegetarian and can't eat any milk products. What kind of clothes will I need? Are there any special clothes you suggest?</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to your reply</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter. I'm glad to hear that you have found a job. I want to apologize for writing so late, but I had a lot of work to do.</P>
      <P>Do you remember the concert I helped at. It was absolutely amazing. My job was checking the entry tickets and the bags of the fans. We started at 7 am. to let them in the concert area. I had to tear off a part of every single ticket. This part had to be saved for later because the concert orginazer wanted to know the exactly number of visitors. After two hours of tearing tickets I changed my place and went to help at the security section. Here, I had to check the bags and couts of the girls. Fans weren't allowed to take any sharp things with them, like knifes or scissors. So I looked into every bag and found some forbidden things in some of the bags. I really felt like a security guard.</P>
      <P>It was a great experience. I had a serious duty and also a lot of fun. I met new people which I still see. I would like to introduce them to you.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
