<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR382*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Hello,</P>
      <P>I'm so glad I won this prize, but I have some questions for you, and of course, the answers you asked me.</P>
      <P>Well, at first, I would like to travel only in July, because it's my holidays here in Portugal. And if it's possible I would like to go after day 10th, because I've got some things to do.</P>
      <P>And for me, I think tents would be better, I don't know why but, I feel more comfortable. I think it's because the last time I travelled (with my friends), we stayed at log cabins, and when I was sleeping felt some thing moving in my skin, then I work up frightened and when I openned my eyes, I saw lots of big ants! After that day, I've never stayed at a log cabin. Yeah, I think that's why!</P>
      <P>About activities, I enjoy most painting, because I am a plastic artist since I was nine and I've won lots of prizes with my art. And the other activity is singing. Everybody says I have an excellent voice, I like to sing when I painting too, it's so relaxing. Is that enough?</P>
      <P>I would like to ask what kind of clothe I probably will use there? And how much clothe? A lot, or few? And what about money? Will I spend much? If you could tell me about this, I'll be glad!</P>
      <P>Greatefully</P>
      <P>Teresa J. Pereira</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Tina,</P>
      <P>You won't believe what I'm going to tell you! Remember when I told you I helped someone important? Well, listen to this.</P>
      <P>I was walking down the main street looking for a gift shop. (I had to buy something for a friend, it was his birthday) when I found a beautiful store, I stopped in front of it and start looking at the window (outside), then I thought interesting and came in. Suddenly, I saw a man with a cap covering his face. I tried to look again to see him better, because he seemed to be very handsome. And then he said "if you promise me you won't get out of this store shouting and screaming and telling everyone that I'm here, I take this cap off of my face". I didn't know what to do, I was sure he was a Robber, or even a murther! Then I said "OK, I promise!" (frightened, of course). Carefully, he took off the cap. Tina, guess WHO was he? Ricky Martin!! Can you believe it! And there's more! He asked me if I could help at his concert here in São Rafael. Because the store manager told him that I was the best hairdresser in the city! And his hairdresser was sick, so he and his producers were looking for one. Isn't that amazing? I met all the staff, and Ricky took lots of fotographs with me and gave me an autographied Record. Tina, I'm the luckiest girl in the world, don't you think? I'll send you some photos.</P>
      <P>Love,</P>
      <P>Teresa.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
