<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR384*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms Clark,</P>
      <P>I spent two days at the last annual international arts festival and I would like to congratulate on the organization. I am also writting to make a suggestion and to give my opinion for next's year festival.</P>
      <P>An internation arts festival is a great idea, but at the last die there were starts and artists from only six countries, and it could be more interesting to have the possibility to meet artists and stars from more than six cultures.</P>
      <P>In my opinion some concert halls were too small. I could not listen to one of my favorite classic concert, "La Moldava" by Smetana. Most of the plays and films were brilliant but I think that if there is money enough, it will be better to have the possibility to watch more movies.</P>
      <P>I am glad to tell you that one reasonably-priced weekend ticket for all events is an excellent idea because also people who do not have a lot of money can enjoy the festival.</P>
      <P>I would like to give a suggestion. I think that meeting writers, dancers, musicians and artists could be very interesting for anybody.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear George,</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your recent letter. I'm very happy that you are well. When I read your letter I was surprised because I didn't know that you have so many rules both at school and at home.</P>
      <P>In Italy there aren't a lot of rules at school and they aren't very stricht. Nobody has to be late in the morning because it is important to respect class mades and teachers' effort of getting up early. Nobody is allowed to speak to a friend during the lesson. I can't have my mobile on and drinking and eating in the classroom is a bad beheviour. There isn't a kind of punishment for people who do these things.</P>
      <P>My parents are very good. The most important thing for my parents is that I don't tell them lays. It's important for them that I tell them where I'm going if I go out and what time I think of coming back home. I can do what I like doing but I have to study. This is the only condition to do what I prefer.</P>
      <P>There isn't anything that I'd like to change.</P>
      <P>Write soon</P>
      <P>Love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
