<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR385*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen,</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your letter telling me about the first prize. It seems so exciting. I really look forward to taking part at Camp California.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel in July because my examination will be finished on June 15th. And I have a plan to go to visit my parents in Bangkok, Thailand, in the middle of August. So, I think July is the best time to go for the Camp. In addition, the weather may be nice at that period of time. For accommodation, I would prefer tents because I get used to it. Because I'm not good at sporting, so I will choose singing and photography as my activities. When I was studying in the university I joined the Photo Club where I got the knowledge aknowhow taking photo. As I love singing and always spend my free time in Karaoke to practise, I think my singing is not too bad.</P>
      <P>I also have a couple of things to ask you. What type of clothes and how much money do I need to prepare? I would be delightful if you could recommend me.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>"Shopping is not always enjoyable". I strongly agree with this sentence. I used to do shopping a lot when I was in the university. I was 19 years old but I spend over 200 pounds in some weeks just to make myself up-to-date all the time. I bought lots of new fashion clothes, bags and shoes. Four years in the university I never had saving money.</P>
      <P>Now, I hate shopping because I spent a lot when I was young as mentioned so it came to the conclusion that shopping is a way to waste the time and money. I found that it's not worth when I went to the southern part of Thailand 3 years ago where I met an old man and his little grandson. They are very poor. The money that I spent on shopping can help them a lot if I would not do it before. Little grandson tried to help his grandfather who was 70 years old by hiring himself out as a gardener after school, though he was only 10 years old. This thing tell me shopping is not enjoyable any more.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
