<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR386*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>41-50</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Smith,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you in order to describing my last visit in your theater. Unfortunatly I am a very disappointed about organisation in your company.</P>
      <P>Firsty the musical show started not at 7.30 p.m. but 45 minutes later. I paid for this performance the full price £20 because discounts were not available although on your advertisement there were. And the biggest disappointment for me was that the grateful Danny Brook, the best singer in London, wasn't present and it was singing a mother unknown person. And last but not least I recognised after the show that your theatre restaurant was closed because waiters didn't come...</P>
      <P>I don't know it is a typical situation in the Circle Theatrer that is promised much more then the people can get for their money, or it was on June 7 (my visit) only, but I am not agree with such situation and would ask you for my money back - my bank account number is enclosed. I am looking forward for you answering.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>In my opinion modern technology changed our daily life tremendously.</P>
      <P>First of all it changed our life-style. For example ten years ago it was very common that almost all people visited cinemas and today they prefer watching films at home because they have relatively good video-recorders and TV. Because the people have fast and comfortable cars, they are much more mobil and can spend their free-time more aktiv - they can often visit their friends and travel much more. People today are more open for the world.</P>
      <P>Secondely we can do our jobs today more efficient. We have modern equipment for communication - phones, faxes, E-mail. We can communicate with our partner faster and better and offer them better service. The ordered goods can be deliver in shorter time by train, trucks and modern ships. If we are more efficient we can earn more money and spend it more for our daily life - for better clothes, furniture, spare time.</P>
      <P>I am a fan for modern technology.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
