<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR389*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>31-40</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sirs,</P>
      <P>The Circle Theatre was so far the best theatre in my opinion, but now, I must change my opinion.</P>
      <P>I visited your Theatre yesterday. I would like to see the best musical show with the best artists.</P>
      <P>Unfortunately instead of Danny Brook we have seen unknown actor. We have disappointed. Moreover this show did not start at 19.30, but 45 minutes later.</P>
      <P>Another problem - the tickets for students according to your advertisement should be available with discounts - unfortunately I could not buy such ticket.</P>
      <P>During the interval I would drink coffee in theatre restaurant - it was closed. I don't know, why? I no thought, that so serious theatre makes such mistakes.</P>
      <P>In accordance with, I would like to ask you to return me my money.</P>
      <P>I hope that your answer will be positive, and in the future in your theatre all will be O.K.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>What will clothes be like 100 years from now?</P>
      <P>"Fashion of the Future" - it is good question. Fashion are changing every year. During the next fashion shows we observe new clothes.</P>
      <P>In my opinion in the future people will wear clothes made of a natural fabrics; silk, cotton, leather, wool. All syntetic material will be uncomfortable for these people.</P>
      <P>Women will prefere the long skirts and short blouses and jackets. Of course, it will be smart clothes.</P>
      <P>Young people will wear jeans and T-shirt. Such clothes is comfortable and easy in using. Teenagers have not free time to go to a washing-cleaner.</P>
      <P>Men will wear as usualy - a suit.</P>
      <P>Fashion colours - it will be earth colours: grey, blue, yellow, brown.</P>
      <P>For special ocassions, for example - the party, the concert, people will wear very smart. I think that it will be: dresses, suits swewed by the well-known tailors.</P>
      <P> All materials should be thin, delicate and soft, because of the warmly climate.</P>
      <P>I think that, we will observe a little and slow changes in fashion, but I hope that new clothes will be always pleasent for people.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
