<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR391*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Robertson,</P>
      <P>As we have seen the advertisment of the programmed the school set for us as a farewell activities, we are very appreciate and would like to thank for your kindness, as all of them are very interesting and give us a chance to meet and join the other class which we hardly done it before.</P>
      <P>However, on the March 14, there is the "London Fashion and Leisure Show", which is also interesting for us. As you know all of us in this class are preparing to go in for the art and design school in the next semester. So this is a great oppotunity for us to get used to the real world of fashion design, because in this show there will have a fashion show, a demonstation from make up artists, and a contest for hair stylist. Furthermore, most of the famouse brand of sport were will join in this exhibition with their new product for the coming season.</P>
      <P>We would like to know if all of us can join in this event. We all agree that we are going to join the school trip to Science Museum, which is the most interesting trip for us. Anyway, intstead of go shopping in the afternoon session, we will attend the show. This is the solution that we all think it will be the less effected to the other students, as the school do not need to re-arrange all the trip just because of our special interesting.</P>
      <P>We hope much that you understand, and would like to thank in advance for your cooperation.</P>
      <P>We looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>I had never wanted to be a hero</P>
      <P>It was dangerous, but I know I had to do it. Even though all of my friends who were with me in that day all said "Just let it go, it's just only a puppy. Why do you have to take a risk?" It seemed that all of them didn't have any sympathy to that lovely blue eyes puppy that somebody who have no mercy just left it there, in a highway.</P>
      <P>If you imagine how dangerous you were while you had to stop your car and got off the car on the highway where there were only car at least 120 km/hr running along your side. It was true that small dog were in danger, but your life was in that situation as well once you decide to do that brave thing. All my body was shaking, and I would almost have turned back to my car if I didn't here that small creature cry as if he wanted me to be his owner.</P>
      <P>So I just crossed the road, and jumped, picked him up. I feel like I was a hero at that moment, even though I'd never though of it before.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
