<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR791*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>We would like to thank you for all the time you have spend for us in order to organize the programme that we should follow during three days that we are going to spending London.</P>
      <P>We all believe that is a great programme which concludes both education and free time.</P>
      <P>We would like to inform you that we notice an advertisement for the London fashion and Leisure Show. This show is going to take place in the Central Exhibition Hall of London on Tuesday, March 14 between the hours 10.00-19.00, and we would like to ask you if it is possible to go to that show.</P>
      <P>We think that is a great opportunity and we are all very interesting to go because we can see there the latest fashions, leisure and sports wear, lot kinds of make up and some of the famous hairstylers. The show is absolutly free for students.</P>
      <P>As a class we suggest to go to this show on Tuesday, March 14 morning and to visit the Science Museum on Wednesday afternoon during our free time. If that of course is possible.</P>
      <P>We all like to thank you again.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>In the year 2000 media is one of the most powerful things on the planet. The media is everywhere, televisions, radio stations, newspapers, magazines all have one goal, to inform the citizens.</P>
      <P>Some of them, however are not doing their job probably. They don't inform people about news, education or documentaries. They just published gossips about famous people, such as politicians, musicians and film stars.</P>
      <P>I believe all the people famous or not, deserve to have private life without journalists to following them all the time. They are humans like all of us with their problems, their good and bad times and of course they don't want to be publish them in front of millions of people because a journalist thought that this is right. And good for his pocket.</P>
      <P>I think the only way of change that is, the people, If the people shows no interest the journalist would have no goal of publish any gossips because is not going to be watch or read by anyone. So the power is to the people.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
