<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR392*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Robertson.</P>
      <P>I and all of my college have read your programme, which you organised for us, for our three days trip to London.</P>
      <P>We all think the programme is organised well, especially we're so keen on the idea to go to the National Art Gallery, to see work of the bigest painters on the world.</P>
      <P>I'm writing to you, because we saw a great advetisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show and we really would like to go to see that show.</P>
      <P>The show will be in Central Exhibition Hall on Tuesday, 14th of March between 10.00 pm to 19.00 pm.</P>
      <P>I think it's a great opportunity because, we will have a chance to se the latest fashion, leisure and sport wear, and as well the way to do the perfect make uphairstyl. In my opinion, we can have a great time there, and entrence is free of charge for students, what is very important as well.</P>
      <P>I'm wondering if there is any possibility to go on that show on Tuesday afternoon, and move our shopping to next day.</P>
      <P>I hope you'll think about our proposition and consider to change the programme.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>'My perfect holiday'</P>
      <P>'It was dangerous, but I knew I had to do it'</P>
      <P>My story began on my holiday. It was nice, hot summer so I and two friends of mine have decided to go for holiday this year to the see side.</P>
      <P>We thought with that beutiful weather the seeside is just perfect for relax, sunbathing and joy.</P>
      <P>However the truth was a little bit diffrent.</P>
      <P>The things started happening from the first day we arrived.</P>
      <P>The weather had changed suttendly, and there was no more sun, but strong wind and rain.</P>
      <P>Despide of that we were still thinking optimisticly.</P>
      <P>We were thinking is so many other activitesourself.</P>
      <P>We went to few Exhibitions, night clubs, restaurants around area and we really had a fun.</P>
      <P>In the end, the weather got better, so we decided to go to the beach.</P>
      <P>Everything was showing, today was going to be a good, sunny day.</P>
      <P>We went for swimming.</P>
      <P>Then again in a few minutes the weather changed and strong storm begun.</P>
      <P>The sky went completly black, so at first it was difficult to see, where everybody is.</P>
      <P>I look around and I relised one friend of mine is still in the see, and fighting with storm, trying to get to the side.</P>
      <P>I didn't think just went to save my friend.</P>
      <P>Everything was looking so dangerous but fortunetly ended good.</P>
      <P>That was the end of our holiday, and next year for sure we won't be going to the see side.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
