<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR394*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>Firstly, I am being the representative of my class to thanks for organising a good programme in London, especially the visiting of Science Museum and National Art Gallery. We know that it is a good chance for us to learn more different things and can widen our knowledge in the Science Museum. In addition, we can appreciate and enjoy the art in National Art Gallery. Unfortunately, I know that most of the students have already visited this two places before. So we decide to choose the other programme which have seen as an entertainment. It is the LONDON FASHION AND LEISURE SHOW. The show is hold at Central Exhibition Hall, London. The date is on Tuesday March 14, from 10.00-19.00. It shows the latest fashions including leisure and sports wear. In spite of these, there is also make up and hairstyles which attract girls most.</P>
      <P>Secondly, the show is a great opportunity because it holds only 1 day which is Tuesday March 14. And, it is free for students. So I think it is worth visiting.</P>
      <P>Personally, here is my some suggestions about how the programme could be changed. We can join the programme that you planned as usual and we go to that fashion show on Tuesday.</P>
      <P>Finally, the above information is my opinion and I hope you can accept it.</P>
      <P>Thanks for your kind attention.</P>
      <P>Your sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>How is the home of the future will be? Remain the same, as usual or have a great difference?</P>
      <P>For me, I think people's home may not be built on the ground. The home will be built on the sky - so as to save more land to build the other buildings. As the home is built on the sky. It will save a lot of electricity as solar energy is used.</P>
      <P>For electrical goods, there will be no any kind of electrical products except computer. People will do anything on the computer, including watching TV, listen to music, chat with people. As the computer is being as a multi-functional products.</P>
      <P>on the other hand, there're some ways that remain the same. The toilet should remain the same as people need to use daily and nothing can replace it. Second, there should be friends and family members in the home to provide joyful and fun. Since friends and family members won't change and replace, by anything.</P>
      <P>These are my imagination. I really wonder how the home of the future will be.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
