<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR395*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir!</P>
      <P>I am writing with reference to your theatre. I would like to apologise you for my controversary opinnion but I feel really disappointed. Firstly I would like to explain you where the problem is. I came to London for a short journey to meet new poeple and to have a meeting with an English culture. I've seen your advertisment which had recommended the play 'Over the rainbow' and I enjoyed it very much. I decided to go to the Circle Theatre with hope that your show will provide me all these emotions that I have been looking for in Great Britain. Please forgive me but you didn't do your best. I heard about Danny Brook in Poland and I wanted to see him on the scene but it wasn't hardly possible. There was a change of the leader-actor what annoyed me indeed. Further more the show was to begin at about 19.30 but it didin't. You were 45 minutes late. Waiting was horrible. On the advertisment was written 'DISCOUNTS AVAILABLE' shall I ask you one question? - Why they weren't available? Everybody were schocked and I was trying to keep the faith. I didin't expect more surprises at your Theatre. Nevertheless after the show I was very hungry so I went to the theatre restarrant and what I've seen? A poster: "Closed because of the illness of the chef." There were some more disappointing situations about which I don't want to write. Eventually - you offered a wonderflul evening but I must say that if I had known that it is going to be like that I wouldn't have wasted my time. I feel honoured to write this letter and I feel the oportunity. I would like to recieve back my money. I am looking forward to hearing you from you.</P>
      <P>Your faithfuly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed your daily life? The entrance in to the new millennium brought us a lot of changes. Many things have been replaced by the others which are more helpful and useful. The most important thing for me is using a computer. The main adventage is that, it provides you all the informations that you need. For example you have to write an Essay about 2-nd world war. You get into the internet and you're looking for those facts and informations which will help you to do your homework. Searching in the computer's memory takes about 1 minute so it is very fast. Further more you can play with the computer, and unfortunetly this advantage has especially changed my life.</P>
      <P>Playing the games takes me a lot of time and it became a bad habit. I have no time for learning and for domestic works. On the other hand playing games and using a computer wide my brain so as you can see this modern staft has got many advantages and disadvantages.</P>
      <P>The next thing that has changed my life is a mobile telephone. This little thing brings a lot of satisfaction. It is very useful either. I have got a steady contact with my parents and friends. I have no problems with changing the time of meeting because I can always phone. But actually it is boring when you're almost always under observation. The modern technologies brought to my life a lot of changes. It is even seen in the domestic works. For example I've got at home a very modern and special machine which irons hardly itself. My mother is happy and I am happier because I don't need to put an effort to iron the clothes. I only press the button and everything is going alright.</P>
      <P>These are the main reasons why I admit that technology has changed my life and other people's life.</P>
      <P>I admire people who made those machines and I would like to give them the tribute. They made my life better.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
