<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR402*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson</P>
      <P>Our class is looking forward to going to London next week. The programme which you've organised we find very interesting especially the river trip to Greenwich. Thank you very much for it.</P>
      <P>There is only one thing that we'd like to change, if you wouldn't mind. We've read an advertisement about London Fashion and Leisure Show which will take place on Tuesday, March 14 from 10 oo to 19 oo. The latest fashions will be shown there and many useful tips about make-up and hairstyles will be given.</P>
      <P>According over programme we have a free time on Wednesday, March 15. So we'd like to go to a disco and this fashion show would be a great opportunity for us to learn something about styling. As we are from the small town we don't have any possibility to learn about this.</P>
      <P>We suggest to visit the Science Museum on Monday after the sightseeing tour by bus. We think we'll find one free hour befor the River trip. It would be a good solution. We hope you are agree with us.</P>
      <P>Your class</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>In every country there are the famous people who are in the middle of the public attention. They are always expected to be beautiful, intelligent, good-looking. This is very stressful.</P>
      <P>That's why it's very important for these people to have a private life without journalists where they can relax and where they don't need to be superstars.</P>
      <P>To have a private life is the natural desire of everyone and the famous film stars or politicians have a right for it. Otherwise they can get soul problems, fall in deep depressions.</P>
      <P>I think that it must be awful to know that you are observed by journalists or other people, your fans for example all 24 hours in a day, and the all things you do in your life are published and the whole world knows who is your friend, where you go shopping, who you love in and who you sleep with. On my opinion this is the worst thing that can ever happen.</P>
      <P>I think we should have a little bit respect for the famous people and let them some time for their private life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
