<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR403*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>It had been a real joy to receive your and I still can't believe it. In answer to your letter, you will find below the informations you need.</P>
      <P>I start my first job on August 1st, that's why I must travel on July. I can't change anymore the date of umployment because I signed the contract a month ago: I hope it will not make problems to you.</P>
      <P>For accomodation, I would prefer to have a log cabin, it would be better to let money or anything without thinking of theft. I've always dreamed about climbing but I never have the opportunity to discover this sport. When I saw you propose this sport, I was really excited. So I choose climbing as a beginner. For the second activity, I will choose sailing. I've done sailing for more than ten years and I really enjoy it. Moreover I was sailing teacher on summers the past few years.</P>
      <P>Does Camp California provide all clothes for sailing? Do I need to bring money from Home? Or can I retire some at Camp California?</P>
      <P>Thank you very much.</P>
      <P>G Morin</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Life at school is made of several things. first, lessons are the most important part of what school wants to provide us. But there are also a lots of clubs and activities that take part in the daily life of pupils. That's why they both have to be taken in account in the video we will make.</P>
      <P>The most interesting lessons for pupils are lessons in which we can do something real, concrete. for example, the lessons of mechanics or physics are very interesting. And especially the practical work. It would be great if we show it in our film, it might be also very interesting to watch it.</P>
      <P>For other activities, we could probably show a training one of our sport team. For example the team basketball which has won the student regional tittle (we can also say it) or the team of football. After all, it is not important the one we will show. but I think we must give a good picture of the school with sport.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
