<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR404*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>I am writing with reference to the trip to London on the 13th, 14th and 15th March.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I would like to thank you very much for the good programme you have organised for my class. We are especially looking forward to join the river trip to Greenwich and the sightseeing by bus.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I have seen an advertisement in the times about the London Fashion and Leisure Show. It will be attended in the Central Exhibition Hall in London on Tuesday 14. My class and I are all interested in it and we would like to go there to have a visit.</P>
      <P>It will be great opportunity for all of us because they will show the latest fashion, the leisure and sports wear, the make up and the different hairstyles. Furthermore, the admission for students is free.</P>
      <P>I have alredy thought about a changing of the programme. On Wednesday we could enjoy our free time doing shopping, so on Tuesday afternoon we moved have time to go to visit the London Fashion and Leisure Show.</P>
      <P>I hope you will take my proposal in favoreable consideration. I am looking forward to hearing from you soon. Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>It was dangerous but I knew I had to do it. What was so dangerous and why I had to do it? Now I will tell you in brief what exactly happened to me.</P>
      <P>It was a fantastic sunny day of August and my friends and I took a day off from work. There were just four of us. We all decided to go to have a day by the seaside not far away from Portsmouth. When we got there we were wearing our costumes. We lied on the sand under the sun, we had funny beach volley matches, interesting chats, but after two hours there, my friends decided to go swimming. For me, it was a big problem because I had never had swimming lessons before and my friends didn't know about that. I didn't want to tell them because I was sure they would have started laughing of me. So I took the decision to go and join them also if I knew that it would have been dangerous for my life. I walked very slowly through the water and I was very scared but I had to do it because if I didn't go my friends could understand that something was wrong with me. In the end fortunately everything went well as I didn't sink in the sea. After that day, I decided taking up swimming, so that I would have had no embarrass in the future trips to the seaside any more.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
