<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR405*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>To the manager of The Circle Theatre!</P>
      <P>I have been recently in London and I've seen the art "Over The Rainbow" at The Circle Theatre. I have to say that it was a very disappointing evening for me. It should start at 19.30 and it had at 20:15! There were no discounts available and the theatre's restaurant was closed. But the worst thing in "London's newest and best musical show", as you called it, was the abscentness of Danny Brook. The actor wich was "dancing" was horrible. He had been mistakeing all the time. At the advertisement, there was written "your perfect evening out". Well, it wasn't perfect! I want you to give me back my money, I hope that in future you will corect all this mistakes.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. I told him my worst love story. One day, I was going to school by bus and I don't know why I went to the end of it. I looked up and I saw her, standing next to me with her friend. Every time when I looked up at her my legs were shaking so I couldn't come up and talk to her! But with help from my friend who convinced me to do this, I've met her. Her name was Sue and she was so beautiful that I still can't find words which could be good to describe her. I was constantly seeing her but my shyness made my mouth close so I couldn't say anything! I was in Love but that wasn't nice. Few days later someone told me that Sue was actually a boy! That was supposed to be a joke from my "coleagues"! From that moment I feel like I have been in front of a video camera and the operator of it is me! I couldn't speak to anyone. The worst thing in this story is, that Pat told this to everyone at school. From that moment I live alone. Thanks to Pat.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
