<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR406*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Miss Clark,</P>
      <P>I have recently taken part in your International Arts Festival. I enjoyied it and here are some feelings and advice for next year.</P>
      <P>First of all, it was a great idea to put together different countries to organise this Festival. However, there were only artists from six countries, not as written in your add.</P>
      <P>Then I had pleasure listening to your variety of concerts. Each one was fantastic and fill in with euration, but I'd appreciate more place, because unfortunately some concert halls were too small!</P>
      <P>You certainly saw that plays and films had a lot of success. So, I wanted to know if there will be more films next year. It could be an advantage!</P>
      <P>An other excellent thing was your choice for the entry. That was a great idea to have just one ticket for all events. That was simpler than an other way of selling tickets (practical and attractive).</P>
      <P>Finally, I want you to make a suggestion for next year. It would be better if people have had the possibility to let their cars very near to the Festival during the week-end!</P>
      <P>I am sure you'll pay attention to my suggestions and advice and I am looking forward to seeing you next year.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Mark and his family decided to go for a walk in the Alps. So, her father prepared the car and her mother took some food for the journey.</P>
      <P>That was a Sunday and, as always, Mark was very excited. He was very keen on going in the mountains.</P>
      <P>Suddenly, the father stopped and said: "Here we are!" They were near a little house, built in wood and began walking. The sun was shining and Mark was really happy to be outside with his family.</P>
      <P>They ate with the owner of the little house, whose name was John. It was very quiet because they were in nature; they could just hear cows and John's two dogs.</P>
      <P>Mark was very interested in building small things with John. He was able to make different objects in wood.</P>
      <P>After that, marks father who had fluent traditional Swiss language spent time with an old woman he had just met near the house.</P>
      <P>After eating old cheese and Swiss chocolate, that was high time Mark's family went back home.</P>
      <P>Mark was such happy but very exhausted to recognize this story nevertheless this story happened a long time ago.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
