<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR410*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I am writing to explain to you what the problems were at the musical show "Over the rainbow" at your theatre.</P>
      <P>On your announcement foil I read that the actor was Danny Brook, but in the show there was a different actor: this is the first disappointing thing.</P>
      <P>The second problem was that the show should have started at 19:30; but it did not; it started at 20:15!</P>
      <P>On the announcement foil I read that we could have had some discounts, but it was not true.</P>
      <P>This is a very disappointing thing!</P>
      <P>Then your theatre restaurant after the show was closed because the staff were not there; so we could not visit it.</P>
      <P>I expected you to prepare "our perfect evening out" for us; but you did not for unknown reasons.</P>
      <P>So, now I ask you to send my money back, because I really did not enjoy that night.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets.</P>
      <P>Kim, her friend, used to go camping at Sunset Village every year, and that year Kim, asked Pat to come with her. She accepted.</P>
      <P>In the evening Pat and Kim used to walk along the beach and they used to stop and turn at the Main Rock, a very big rock.</P>
      <P>But one night, with the moon light, they felt encouraged to continue their walk. Pat was a little bit afraid, but Kim convinced her to follow her saying that she knew the street. But, when they heard a scream, they stopped and, when they saw a shadow coming forward them, they started running, hearing a voice saying: "Our secret!"</P>
      <P>When they returned to Caan, their town, they promised to keep silence about that. But Pat, coming back hom, told her mother everything. That night Kim heard another scream and the day after she ran to Pat to tell her what she heard. But Kim, and no one else found Pat.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
