<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR411*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>31-40</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>To the manager of the</P>
      <P>Circle Theatre in London</P>
      <P>I'm a tourist and I had a week's holiday in London a few time ago. I had enjoied to see the musical show that the Circle Theatre presented some night ago; and the actor's Danny Brook performance. I went to the theatre at 19.30 o'clock but, with my surprise, the show started at 20:15 and so I couldn't remain here until the end because I left London, with my group before the end of the show. The star, the actor Danny Brook, there wasn't in the musical show but there was an other actor, with my great disappoint.</P>
      <P>Then, in the program I could read a discount available for the tickets, for the groups, but I couldn't have that. I couldn't have all the things I expected.</P>
      <P>That evening was terrible for me and for my friends, so I'm not satisfied about your informations and I ask some money back.</P>
      <P>I hope in your answer and in your explanation about this.</P>
      <P>Your Sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets.</P>
      <P>Some days ago, when the school was ending, Pat and her friends decided to make a party for their friend, Frances, because the end of the school and the Francis's birthday were the same day. That might be a secret for Francis - and they decided the program and the present, a new gold watch.</P>
      <P>Peter and Sue asked to Francis some help for their exam's subjets and Francis, for to help them, was very busy all the week. The last day all the friends went to Pat's home with food, musical instruments, tape recorder. Pat was very excited about this. In the afternoon she had phoned at a Francis's mother and she explained her the secret, then she phoned at her best friend and she speak about that too; she phoned at many people all the day. Now many people knew the secret but Pat said everyone: "I tell you a small secret, but you don't speak, please!"</P>
      <P>In the night Francis was invited to the party, at Pat's home. When he was out he needed to buy some cigarettes so he went to the shop where the owner, a his friend, ask him if he was very happy about his present, the new gold watch, he was very lucky to have best friends like Pat and her friends. The Francis's secret was discovered!</P>
      <P>Now all the Pat's friend don't tell her about their secrets because Pat isn't very good at keeping secrets. </P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
