<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR414*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>I am writing to tell you that the students of my class have seen an advertisment about The London Fashion And Leisure Show.</P>
      <P>First of all I would like to thank you for making such a good plan, for us, so we could have a good time. Then I would like to explain to you about The London Fashion and Leisure Show. Finally how the programme could be changed.</P>
      <P>The London Fashion And Leisure Show is taking place in Central Exhibition Hall in London and happens on Tuesday March 14. From ten o'clock in the morning till seven o'clock in the afternoon. The reason that I suggest that we go is that it is a great opportunity because we can see the latest fashions, leisure and sports wear as well as make up and different hairstyles. In addition to these we will not have to pay anything since it is free for students.</P>
      <P>I suggest that we should transfer our visit to the Science Museum on Wednesday afternoon in our free time that we have. I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>It was dangerous, but I had to do it. I did not have any choice since my brother was in trouble. I had to become a burgler again and steal jewelry from the jewelry shop near by.</P>
      <P>As I knew the teknics to break in a place without being noticed, I should not be afraid but tonight I had to steal the most precious diamond in the country which was very well secured.</P>
      <P>When I got close to the shop, I checked if anyone was around and luckily was not. Then I approached slowly the door, broke the lock and opened the door. However, my adventure was not over yet. There were laisers all over the place, with which I had to be careful with.</P>
      <P>Suddenly something went wrong, the alarm was making noise. I ran towards the diamond grabed it got out quickly, ran out of the back door. By surprise I saw a car waiting for me outside. I got into the car gave the jewelry in exchange of my brother, took him and left the place.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
