<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR415*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>We would like to thank you for the programme which you have prepared for us. We really like the variety of our trip to London. The programme contains enjoyment and education, what is very esencial for young people.</P>
      <P>However, we would like to say, that recently the advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show has been seen by one of your English class student. The show will be about latest fashions, leisure and sports wear, make up and hairstyles.</P>
      <P>In our opinion, we should go to the show. Firstly, because we are keen on fashion. Secondaly, because we do not have to pay for the tickets.</P>
      <P>We have already orgonised our visit new programme. The show is on tuesday and we could go to see the show in the afternoon, instead of shopping. We think, that we may shopping next day, on wednesday, in our free time.</P>
      <P>We are looking foraward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P> Students.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>The Home of the Future</P>
      <P>The future is unexpectable and human beings are afriad of dangers, such as tornado or earthquake. Thinking about home like a place to live, is not already worth. We must think about home from other point of view. We need to make our home a place where we want to come back after the work or school. It has to be pleasure to be there for us. What we really need in the next millenium is love, that is what will keep all family together and forever. Do we care about a new carpet or a fashionable furniture? No; I do not think so. Live is too short to think about the poscesives.</P>
      <P>The houses will change because of new technologe, what may make our live more comfortable. Everything will be faster. We will used to that. What depends on us, is how atmospher we will have in our houses. The home of the Future, for me, is a place of hapinest.</P>
      <P>We cannot future technologe, but we might still have some feelings to eachothers.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
