<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR416*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>It was grateful for your message. I can gladly give you some information which you need.</P>
      <P>I would be able to travel only in July because I have a job at the moment, but it will be my vacation in July. I would prefer to be in tents, so that I could enjoy a nature life more than being log cabins. Moreover, it would be more exciting for me.</P>
      <P>It could be nice for doing two activities while I am at the Camp. I am interested in sports. Especially, I am wonderful at swimming. I have swimmed since I was in primary school. I would like to learn playing golf at the Camp. I have never played golf in my life. Is it possible to learn playing golf, although I am not good at golf?</P>
      <P>Would you mind giving some answer whether I need some clothes and money at the Camp?</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I'm sorry that I haven't written to you for a long time. It was nice you wanted to hear about my experience, and I know you're looking for a job which I did.</P>
      <P>It was a wonderful chance for me. As you know, I love music. Before the concert started, I cleaned the stage for singers and I gave some drinks to singers. Finally, I cleaned the stage again. My works were for singers, so I could meet singers and talk together.</P>
      <P>Do you know "Radio Head"? It is my favourite group. I was able to have some signatures of them. It's brilliant, isn't it?</P>
      <P>Especially, I liked cleaning the stage, because I could stand a famouse singer's stage and I could feel his enthusiasm, even though I had to clean it.</P>
      <P>I want to hear about your school life, and your part-time job.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Best wishes,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
