<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR7*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Cambridge 13.06.00</P>
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>Competition Organiser</P>
      <P>I am glad to know about the news that I have received. It is a dream becames true and was really unexpected for me!</P>
      <P>I would like to travel on July because of it is more suitable for me. I think I will really enjoy if I could stay in tents it is going to be a new experience and looks exciting.</P>
      <P>About the activities while at the Camp I would like to enjoy swimming, not because I am good in it, just because I keen on and the other one is Photography.</P>
      <P>As I never did this in whole my life could you tell me if we have to do our own meals or I can find everything ready to eat there? If no, what do you sugest? The same question for clothes and money. How much I have to get in my pocket?</P>
      <P>I hope has had your questions out of your mind.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Cambridge 13.06.00</P>
      <P>Dear friend</P>
      <P>Kim</P>
      <P>Last month, I enjoyed to help at a pop concert in Portugal. Everything were new for me. I had to tidy up the place where they have to wait until their turn. The group asked me make sure that in the fridge they always could find a big variety of drinks including honey and lemon for throat.</P>
      <P>Other thing I had to do is keep an eye in the towels, I mean, dried towels because as you know that country is too hot, especially for my liking, as they have to change the clothes and looks fresh; don't ask me why.</P>
      <P>The pop concert happened in a big stadium called "Mararcanã".</P>
      <P>I just did not enjoyed when they were making the instruments work for the big day. But what I particularly liked was see and ask autographs from the rest of the others groups. Don't be jealous, I will make a copy for you, OK?</P>
      <P>Love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
