<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR10*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>17/06/00</P>
      <P>mr. MANAGER</P>
      <P>MY NAME JAMES CAMIREZ AND I'AM WRITING THIS LETTER TO YOU BECAUSE I HAVE SOME COMPLEINTS FOR THE DISAPPOINTING EVENING I HAD LAST NIGHT.</P>
      <P>FIRST OF ALL ON THE ADVERTISEMENT FOR THE SHOW IT SAYS THAT THE ACTOR WAS GOING TO BE DANNY BROOK AND INSTEAD OF HIM WAS A TOTALLY UNKNOWN CLOWN THAT HAD NO IDEA OF HOW TO ACT, IT WAS HORRIBLY DISAPPOINTING!</P>
      <P>SECOND I GOT TO THE THEATRE AT 19.20 BECAUSE IN THE ADVERTISEMENT IT CLEARLY APPEARS THAT THE SHOW STARTS AT 19.30, AND I GOT HEAVILY MAD WHEN I LOOK MY WATCH AND NOTICE THAT I HAD BEEN WAITING FOR 40 (FORTY) MINUTES AND THE SHOW DIDN'T START YET...I MEAN I WAS AMAIZING!</P>
      <P>THEN I READ ON THE ADVERTISEMENT, DISCOUNTS AVAILABLE, AND I DIDN'T GOT ANY DISCOUNTS WHEN I ASKED FOR THEM.</P>
      <P>AFTER THE SHOW I GOT OUT THE SHOW ROOM DEEPLY DISAPPOINTED AND WENT TO THE RESTAURANT TO DRINK SOMETHING TO RELAX, AND DO YOU KNOW WHAT?.. IT WAS CLOSED! I COULDN'T BELIVE IT HOW THIS CLASS OF THEATRE CAN BE SO.. OH I'M GETING MAD AGAIN SO I'AM GOING TO TELL YOU THE LAST THING, IT WAS THE HORRIBLE NIGHT I HAD EVER GOT SO I DEMEND FOR MY MONEY BACK!</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>I THINK THAT MODERN TECHNOLOGY HAS AFFECTED ALL THE HUMAN BEINGS. MODERN TECHNOLOGY HAS AFFECT ME IN SEVERAL WAYS, I MEAN THE MORE THE TECHNOLOGY MODERNIZES; MORE CONFORTNESS WE GET. NOW WITH MODERN MACHINES I CAN MAKE A BETTER USE OF MY TIME, IF I'AM LATE TO GO TO TRAINING AND I HADN'T IT YET I JUST TAKE MY FOOD AND PUT IT IN THE MICROWAVEOVEN. ANOTHER EXAMPLE IS THE COMPUTERS, I THINK THEY ARE ONE OF THE MOST ADVANCED MACHINE IN THE WORLD, YOU CAN LIVE YOUR ENTIRE LIFE IN A HOUSE WITHOUT GOING OUT, BY JUST USING THE INTERNET, IT HAS ALSO HELPED ME IN MY SCHOOL HOMEWORK, I MEAN IT'S INCREDIBLE THE TIME YOU WAIST BY MAKING THING WITHOUT A COMPUTER. BUT I THINK ALSO THAT WITH MODERN TECHNOLOGY WE GET MORE COMFORTABLE SO THAT MAKES ME A PACIVE PERSON AND NOT SO ACTIVE, THIS CAN BE BAD TO BECAUSE IF I GET USED TO BE CONFORTABLE WHEN I NEED TO DO HARD WORKS I WON'T BE ABLE TO DO THEM.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
