<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR18*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing with reference to the musical show I saw last week in your theatre. I hoped that it would be the most excited evening during my week's holiday in London. Unfortunately it wasn't.</P>
      <P>I wouldn't like to be unkind but I must say that the advertisement for the show included a lot of false information. First of all, when I had bought the ticets it appeared that there is no discount available. Secondly, I must complain that the musical show started almost an hour later and in addition to this anyone didn't excuse. Moreover I would like to ask why Danny Brook, which is my favourite actor, didn't play in the show. Furthermore I would like to enquire why the theatre restaurant was closed.</P>
      <P>Finally, I must say that I had a very disappointing evening and I would like to get my money back.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. I wish I had know it two days ago... Exacly on 15th June we were at the birthday party. Dora wanted me to come with Pat because she was in love with him. I really like Dora and Pat and I just wanted to help them to be together, but it wasn't such a good idea.</P>
      <P>I thought that if I said something specific about her he would look at her in a different way. Well, I forgot that it's just a boy! I shouldn't have told him that she was a virgin. It was awful when he started to laugh and everybody was stearing at us. Yesterday I discovered that he told everything to Marl and Tony. I really regret that I was so foolish.</P>
      <P>The most horrible is the fact that my friendship with Dora seems to be on the rocks and I don't know what I have to do to overcome the difficulties.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
