<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR419*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about The Circle Theatre which is very different from what it have shown. I will let you know about what I have in mind.</P>
      <P>I went to your theatre last saturday, about 7. p.m. I asked for discounts. But a clerk said that time for discounts had been finished. I did not care about money and I rushed into and then took a seat with some food. I was waiting for the show that was supposed to start at 7.30 p.m. But it started at 8.15. I felt nervous. When I saw an actor, he was a different actor. I was very upset and disappointed.</P>
      <P>After the show ended, I was on the way to the theatre restaurant. What was more, it closed because of refurishing.</P>
      <P>If you were me, how would you feel? So, I could not help to writing to you and would like to take money back.</P>
      <P>I enclosed the receipt of theatre.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>Bying Kak</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>- How has modern technology changed your daily life?</P>
      <P>I was born in 1973. At this time, our nation was under a developing country. Almost all the people had a Television which provided events around our county very quickly. As I growed up, T.V was one of the mysteriest things like a telephone and a bus.</P>
      <P>When it comes to modern technology, I grately appreciate it.</P>
      <P>First thing is a computer. When I was a university student, I had to find out some imformation about my homework. I could not get them. but a computer made me get them from internet.</P>
      <P>Second thing is an airplane. I have been imagining where another contries are like England. Now I am in England. I know a ship but an airplane made an arrival to here be quick.</P>
      <P>Third thing is a telephone. It saves time. Whenever I do not know about something, I phone and ask it.</P>
      <P>All in all, I have been having many benefits from modern technology which is very useful. But it might be a problem, making me lazy.</P>
      <P>Now, the world is one end and I have to take advantage of modern technology for my future.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
