<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR424*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson.</P>
      <P>It is a pleasure to write to you and we want to thanks for organising a school trip to London. We have seen the programme list and we all think it will be enjoyable. Especially to the science museum because we all doing science in school.</P>
      <P>Recently, some students have seen an advertisment about a fashion and leisure show in London. it will be on the 14th and we all want to go. So, it would be greatful if you can give us this opportunity to watch the show.</P>
      <P>This is a great opportunity to learn something else because most of us have not been to this kind of show And it is free for students. it will be incredible if we have a chance to watch the show. So could you give us permission to go?</P>
      <P>We also can suggest how the originally programme can be changed. We will have free time on Wednesday afternoon. So we can do shopping instead. Then, we can go to the show during that period</P>
      <P>We are all looking forward for you answer.</P>
      <P>faithful</P>
      <P>12-12-00</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>It was dangerous, but I knew I had to do it. Because there was a man had a serious car accident and I was walking pass him. Nobody had noticed him because it happened at night and the car had actually crashed into the bushes.</P>
      <P>I was thinking 'what should I do?' I haven't got my mobile phone with me And I was half way between my school and home. At that time he was unconcious, I kept asking myself 'should I wake him up or try to use my unsure first aid skill to deal with him. I was struggling because I knew if I didn't help him, he would die in a short time.</P>
      <P>I decided to do something to this man, my first move was to check was there any solid or liquid which could blocked his breathe. And checking his body condition. After that I turned on the car light in order to tell the passing cars.</P>
      <P>I ran back home for help. I phoned to police And told the whole story. The strange thing happened to me, when I got back to that man. The car and the man were not there anymore. Where could they be? I was wondering.</P>
      <P>Oh, sorry they were not in this road, they were in the next road.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
