<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR425*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>DEAR HELEN,</P>
      <P>I AM WRITIN TO YOU IN ORDER TO GIVE A REPLY TO THE KIND LETTER I RECEIVED FROM YOU. I CANNOT EXPRESS HOW THANFUL I AM FOR THIS BEAUTIFUL PRIZE.</P>
      <P>FIRS OF ALL, I WOULD LIKE TO TELL YOU THAT THE ONLY TIME I WILL BE ABLE TO TRAVEL IS IN JULY, BECAUSE BEFORE THAT I HAVE TO TAKE SOME EXAMS AT THE UNIVERSITY.</P>
      <P>IN YOUR LETTER YOU ASKED ME WHETHER I WOULD PREFER, IF A TENT OR A LONG CABIN. WELL, THE ANSWER IS A LONG CABIN, BECAUSE I HAVE A PROBLEM WITH MY BACK. THAT IS WHY I CANNOT SLEEP ON THE GROUND OR IN A SLEEPING BAG.</P>
      <P>BY THE WAY, YOU ALSO MENTION THAT I WILL HAVE THE CHANCE TO DO TWO ACTIVITIES. WELL, THE TWO ACTIVITIES THAT I WOULD TO CHOOSE ARE BASKETBALL AND SINGING. I HAVE CHOOSEN THOSE BECAUSE I AM QUITE GOOD PLAYING BASKETBALL AND I SING EVERY WEEKEND IN THE CHOIR OF THE LOCAL CHURCH AS WELL.</P>
      <P>FINALLY, I WOULD APPRECIATE IF YOU LET ME KNOW IF I WILL HAVE TO TAKE SOME CLOTHE OR MONEY. I WOULD LIKE TO KNOW IF I WILL HAVE TO PAY FOR ANY OTHER EXTRA ACTIVITY.</P>
      <P>I HOPE YOU WILL ABLE TO ANSWER ALL MY QUARIES. I LOOK FORWARD TO HEARING FROM YOU.</P>
      <P>YOURS SINCERELY,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>DEAR KIM,</P>
      <P>THANKS FOR THE KIND LETTER YOU SEND ME LAS WEEK. THE PHOTOGRAPHS ARE VERY NICE AND FUNNY. BY THE WAY YOU ARE A BIT TALLER, AREN'T YOU?</P>
      <P>WELL, THE FIRST THING I WANT TO TELL YOU IS ABOUT THE POP CONCERT WE HAD, LAST FRIDAY, HERE IN OUR CITY. BUT TO MAKE THE THING BETTER I WAS CHOOSEN TO HELP THE BAND AND THE ORGANISERS OF THE CONCERT. GREAT!</P>
      <P>AS YOU KNOW, I AM A SOUND TECHNICH, SO I HELP THEM TO PUT THE SOUND EQUIPMENTS AND THE INSTRUMENTS PROPERLY. THEN SOME HOURS BEFORE THE CONCERT, I MET THE BAND AND THEY LET ME STAYED IN THE SOUND TEST. I WAS ALREADY SPECIAL TIME FOR ME! THE MEMBERS OF THE BAND WERE VERY NICE AND FRIENDLY WITH ME.</P>
      <P>THEN, WHEN THE CONCERT STARTED; THE ORGANISERS GAVE ME AN IDENTITY CARD, ONLY FOR MEMBERS OF THE STAFF. THAT CARD WAS THE BEST THING THAT SOMEONE HAD EVER GAVE TO ME, BECAUSE I WAS UNABLE TO BE IN THE SCENARY WITH THE WHOLE BAND! IT WAS THE BEST TIME IN MY LIFE. I FELT REALLY LUCKY.</P>
      <P>SORRY IF MY EXPERIENCE WAS BORING BUT I KNOW YOU WILL ENJOY IT AS MUCH AS I DID.</P>
      <P>I LOOK FORWARD TO HEARING FROM YOU. I SEND YOU SOME PHOTOGRAPHS OF ME WITH THE BAND.</P>
      <P>LOT OF LOVE,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
