<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR426*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Saturday, 17th June, 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I am writting you in order to obtain you my money back, concerning the musical show: OVER THE RAINBOW. I live in France and I recently spent a week's holiday in London. I decided to go to theatre to have a nice evening. I saw your advertisement in a newspaper. It seemed to be very attractive. But in fact it is not!</P>
      <P>I had a very disappointing evening. First of all: actors were mentionned are not the same. I supposed to see the famous Danny Brook, and what a surprise it was not him. I was very disappointed.</P>
      <P>Secondly the show had go on 19.30 pm. In fact it started at 20.15 pm without any explanations.</P>
      <P>Thirdly it said that "discounts available". This is not the truth.</P>
      <P>After that it suggested to visit your theatre restaurant, but the restaurant was closed! It is a shame.</P>
      <P>And you write, I quote "your perfect evening out", excuse me but I do not agree with you. It was awful, the worst evening out of my life.</P>
      <P>So please, it would be fair, that you give my money back.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you in a near future.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>"What will clothes be like 100 years from now?"</P>
      <P>In my opinion, clothes will not change so much, because fashion is an eternal cycle. You will find always basic clothes, but I think that it will be the materials which will change.</P>
      <P>We will find the same kind of clothes with gadgets included. For example: a short very classical inside of it could be included a mobile phone, or we could find too some buttons, to have.. fresh air, why not? Or special flying shoes, and maybe on your watch you would have a screen to watch your favorite soap operas.</P>
      <P>Everything is possible, but it would be fun to see this type of gadgets with old clothes, like a dress of the middle-Age.</P>
      <P>Do not worry about this, it will not happen! Fashion is always the same!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
