<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR431*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Miss Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am very glad to hear that I have won the prize and thank you very much about that. Here is the information you want, I hope they are useful.</P>
      <P>First of all, July is the only month I can travel, because I have got exams at school and I won't finish them until the last day of June. And in August, I have to go back to school to do some classes work and I have got a camp to organise. So I would like to travel on July. Secondly, I would prefer the accommodation in tents. Since I haven't been camping in tents so I would like to take this chance to feel and experience what will it be.</P>
      <P>About the activities, I chose swimming and climbing. I am in swimming term a school and I won a prize last month. Although I'm not good at climbing, I want to experienced myself.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask what is the weather in USA like and what kind of clothes should I wear? And I was wondering how much money do I have to take? Also, if I can join climbing, what do I have to bring? At last thank you very much for answering my questions.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>It was lovely to hear that you want to hear about my experience. I helped the concert which was my favour singer's concert.</P>
      <P>I helped with the piano part in that concert. At the concert, I had to play 4 songs and I had never played in a concert before, so I felt very nervous before the concert.</P>
      <P>But it was a good experience for me because I learnt how to claim down and play well in front of the audience the concert. And also I have never played the piano with the singers before, and after that it makes me more confident and improved my skills a lot. When the concert finished my favour singer talked to me and they invited me to play the piano in their next concert and they said that because I performed will in that concert. They taught me a lot about playing piano as well.</P>
      <P>At last thank you for sharing my experience. I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Best wishes</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
