<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR434*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam</P>
      <P>I am writting to complain about I am really disappointed your musical show which is "over the rainbow". on last week. I could compare between the advertising of musical and actual musical show last week.</P>
      <P>First of all, the advertising shown us starring, which is Danny Brook and Tina Truelove, however, when I had seem it, starring of musical completely diffarent actors, I really disappointed about it.</P>
      <P>Secondary, the advertising shows as the musical start 14.30 and 19:30, but the musical started 20:15, it's 45 minuts late, and also, I'd asked discount ticket in the ticket counter, but there are not available any discount tickets.</P>
      <P>Finally, your theatre restaurant was closed after show, it is because I saw it was opened at break time for musical, but afterwards, the people of staff for restaurant were closing.</P>
      <P>Now then, how was this advertising, it was completely diffarent, I am really disappointed your musical, I am ask you for money back, because I wasn't enjoyed your musical.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Your Faithfully,</P>
      <P>from</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>I am writting composition about "How has modern technology changed your daily life", this is our question. All at the technology developed about every day, not all of them, but still a lot of modern technology changed our daily life.</P>
      <P>First of all, I thought more than half population of British has "mobile phone", it is small and compact, much lighter than home telephone, and one of the biggest advantage is you can carry it, so that easy to contact your friend or someone who other, even they can easy to contact you as well, so you can phone anytime you wants, whenever you wants.</P>
      <P>Secondary, Personal Computer (PC), these "Desk Top" and "Lap Top" computers developed each year, however, most important thing is "Internet", Mobile phone could easy to contact anyone in your country, "Internet" easy to contact world wide, you can send E-mail anytime, anywhere you wants, it is most popular thing all of the world.</P>
      <P>Thesetechonologygetthesediffarent.</P>
      <P>from. </P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
