<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR437*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am a foreign woman who had a week's holiday in London and decided to go to the theatre to see a musical show. That show wasn't as it supposed to be and it is for that reason that I am writting to you.</P>
      <P>One of the problems is that a couple of actors, Danny Brook and Tina Truelove, were the ones supposed to act and a different actor took Danny's place, it was disappointing!</P>
      <P>The second show was supposed to start at 19:30, but to make the matters worse, it started at 20.15, so after the show I couldn't got to the cinema.</P>
      <P>Apart from that I couldn't visit the theatre restaurant after the show because it was closed for holidays.</P>
      <P>On top of everything the tickets didn't offer any discounts, so the last day I couldn't buy the present for my neighbour.</P>
      <P>I am writting to ask a refund of the £55 which I spent on the ticket for the miserable show.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully.</P>
      <P>Jane Smythe</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>I am going to write about how has modern technology changed our daily life.</P>
      <P>First of all I think that technology has been one of the most important inventions of human and that without it we couldn't be where we are wright now.</P>
      <P>One of the best examples is the car: in a lot of cities around the world, cars can be seen in the streets all day long. During the last decade the number of people who has a particular car has increased very fast. On the other hand people who hasn't any cars, can also be helped by technology: they can use the public transport like the train or the bus, which is also a comfortable form of travelling. But if you want a fastest transport, the plane is the perfect one!</P>
      <P>But technology can also help you at home if you use modern machines for cleaning your house, clothes or dishes.</P>
      <P>Apart from that, technology also helps in hospitals. Every time more machines help doctors and nurses with their difficult tascs.</P>
      <P>In contrast, technology is very bad for the nature: if we use cars we contaminate, and many cars are being used every day!</P>
      <P>On balance I think that evidently technology has got more advantages than disadvantages.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
