<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR442*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you for the letter you wrote to me to inform me about the prize I won. I was so happy! I couldn't believe it.</P>
      <P>If it is possible I would like to travel in July because school is finishing on the 28th June and I have already excepted a job in August.</P>
      <P>I think it would be fun to stay in a tent those two weeks, I have never done that before, by my friends told me that I would enjoy it.</P>
      <P>As you offer many activities it was hard to choose which ones I want to do, but I dicided to take swimming and photography, because I am very good at swimming and because currently I am attending a photography course in Vienna. I am not very experienced but I think that I will find a lot of beautiful motives in the USA.</P>
      <P>I would be very kind if you could inform me about how much money I have to take with me and which clothes I will need.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>Thank you for the card you wrote to me, I hope you enjoyed your holidays.</P>
      <P>I spent some great days in Vienna where I had the chance to help at the concert of "pearl jam".</P>
      <P>The first thing I didwas to controll the tickets of the fans who visited the concert together with a friend of mine.</P>
      <P>There always was a lot of security stuff around us to make sure every thing is ok, because there really were thousends of persons.</P>
      <P>Then we had time to listen to the music.</P>
      <P>The other thing I had to do was to make some sandwiches and drinks just before they returned behind the stage to rest a little bit before they continued playing. It was amazing to be in the same room they were. Edi Vedder even talked to me about their programms!</P>
      <P>I think that I will never see them again personally, but I will never forget those two days - being so close to them, unbelievable!</P>
      <P>Hope to see you soon!</P>
      <P>Yours</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
