<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR445*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear, Sir/Madam</P>
      <P>I am Writing this letter to say my dissatisfaction of your entertament.</P>
      <P>Last week I was on holiday and I went to The Circle Theatre to see over the rainbow musical. I was really looking forward to seeing it, because I like musical and also I like Danny Brook. However, the reading actor was not him! Of course, I was so disappointed. The actor was not famous for his acting.</P>
      <P>Also the musical did not start on time, it was late thirty minuts. We just sat on the seat and nothing to do.</P>
      <P>I was going to a restaurant with my friends after the musical, but the musical finished at ten thirty. It was too late and we could not have a dinner. If the musical had started on time, we could have eaten in the restaurant.</P>
      <P>Fathermore, discounts was unavailable. Even though we had a student card. In the advertisement they said that tickets discounts available. I think it a bombastic. Anyway I was so unpleasement. It was not marvellous evening. Could you back my money please? You have responsoiblity for the audiences.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed your daily life?</P>
      <P>My life have been changed by technological improving. Nowadays. We have so many technological things. For instance, TV, computers, telephone, air-conditionings. These things are very convinience on the other hand, there lots of disadvantage point.</P>
      <P>I have my own TV in my room and I enjoy watching TV everyday. However, I need balance. If I watch TV too much I might not speak to my family often. It will lack of communication. In addition, it is difficult turn it off. I think I should cut down watching TV. Sometimes it waste of time.</P>
      <P>What about computers? It is very useful too. I am living in London, but my father lives in Taiwan and my mother lives in Tokyo.</P>
      <P>I sometimes want to hear their voice on the telephone. Unfourtunately it is not so cheap. If I use e-mail much easier and cheaper. And I can send e-mail anytime.</P>
      <P>If I addicted on internet, it will be problem. I do not want to spend much time with computers.</P>
      <P>In conclusion. people include me need balance. We must be good at using computers.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
