<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR448*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Swedish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about the musical show, OVER THE RAINBOW, and also about the servic.</P>
      <P>When I went to London, during my holiday, I decided to go to the theatre to see a musical show, OVER THE RAINBOW.</P>
      <P>During and also after the show lots of disappointing thing turned up.</P>
      <P>Firstly, it was not Danny Brook and Tina Truelove who acted, it was someone else.</P>
      <P>Sacondly, in your advertisement I read "Times 14.30 and 19.30". In fact the show started 20:15</P>
      <P>Thirdly, I also read "Visit our theatre restaurant after the show", but the restaurant was closed because of painting.</P>
      <P>Last but not least, it also says "discounts available", but there was not any staff there who could do it.</P>
      <P>So I am sure that you will understand why I feel so frustrated and disappointed about the whole thing.</P>
      <P>I look farward to hearing from you in the very near future, to offer me the money back.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Maris Svensson</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>"Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets." I was reading when I suddenly hard a big bang. I looked out through the window and saw a big strange "thing". It looked like a floating potato, a brown potato. After that a being climed out from the potato. It looked at me and said.</P>
      <P>"I am hear to help you. I only need to touch your teacher and you never need to do any homework again."</P>
      <P>I could not belive my ears. It was the happiest moment of my life.</P>
      <P>I went back to my chair and when I looked up I saw my main-teacher walking through the door with the being after him. The being moved its hand farward and.....</P>
      <P>Then I felt a big pain in my head and heard "You can't sleep in the lesson". I looked up and saw my friend with the coursebook in her hand. Immediantely after I heard "And don't forget your homework". I looked at the book and read:</P>
      <P>"Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets"</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
