<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR456*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am very happy to answer your letter, which I received this morning. I am very exiting with the wonderful news.</P>
      <P>Well, I start to make a plan for my travel, and the only time I have is on July because I will be finish my course of language at St Jame's School.</P>
      <P>About accomodation I would prefer cabins, because I suffer alergic, and I think tend, would be not very suitable for my health.</P>
      <P>I am very happy to have the opportunity to do some sports. I'm very good in swimming and surfing. Swiming I won last summer competition in the school, although I'm not very good at surfing I like, and I always practis in my holidays every year.</P>
      <P>I would like to know if is necesary for me to bring some money, or if we will have time to visit the City, about the clothes I have to bring some winter clothes?</P>
      <P>Im very greatful to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Your sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I was very happy to receive your letter.</P>
      <P>It's wonderful that you are going to listen a pop concert. I'm sure you will be enjoy. You asked me to tell you about my experience to help in the concencert last week.</P>
      <P>Well, let me tell you, first of all I was very nervous you know was my first time in such event. I was asked to put in order all the chair for the singer, this was only in the begining, after that I need to control all the microfons. However I was not very sure in this I enjoy. After that all the singer arrived and I was in charche to greeting them and give them something to drink. You immagine how existing I was specially because I always wanted some photograph with them and this was special moment and I realice I didn't bring my camera I was very sad.</P>
      <P>Well Kim, remember if they asked you to help go you will see how wonderful experience.</P>
      <P>Write to me and tell me about your concert.</P>
      <P>Give my regards to your boyfriend.</P>
      <P>With Love.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
