<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR81*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms Ryan</P>
      <P>I'm very much surprised to receive your letter announcing the first prize in your competition and I'm looking forward to spend the two weeks at Camp California.</P>
      <P>Just because I'm studying at the moment and I won't have my holidays till July. This is the month that best suits me. The second week of July would be perfect to start my trip.</P>
      <P>I would rather sleep in a log cabin. I find it will be much more comfortable than a tent.</P>
      <P>The leisure activities sound fantastic especially climbing and photography. I'm very keen on climbing. I've joined a climbing group in my town 2 years and reached the top of several middle-high mountains. The other activity I would like to try is photography. I have no previous experience on it but I wish I'd learn a lot.</P>
      <P>However, there are some questions that I want to ask you about. Do I need passport to travel? What kind of clothes would be appropriate, winter or summer? Are there any food service at the camp?</P>
      <P>I hope to hear from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>This is a report to plan and suggest ideas for the daily life video at school. The activities suggested are write below.</P>
      <P>The opening time recording the students while they meet outside the school and come in could be a good begining. It would reflect the atmosphere when they meet early in the morning.</P>
      <P>Filming lessons such as grammar lessons and speaking either theory lessons or practice would give a general idea about a day at school and how students work on their lessons.</P>
      <P>Why don't include some sports, for example, voleyball? The team has been training very hard during last weeks. And they'll certainly feel very proud of being at the video.</P>
      <P>The musical lessons and the singing club in the afternoon are very popular among the students of all courses. Practically the whole school would appear on the video.</P>
      <P>I think that if we mix lessons with sport activities the combination will give us complete success.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
