<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR475*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Hello!</P>
      <P>My name is Alois Blau and I'm very happy that I've won this competition. Unfortunately I can only travel in July, because I have to attend school until June the 30th and in August I have to work in an office for experience. I hope, that's possible.</P>
      <P>I would prefer living in a tent during the two weeks because I think a tent is more natural. A log cabin doesn't sound like a camp holiday. It sounds like a summer-holiday at the beach of Italy.</P>
      <P>From the activities I want to take Golf and Surfing. Both activities I've never done in my life, so I am a complete beginner in playing Golf and in Surfing. But the reason I want to try these two activities are their image. Golf play the wealthy people, the upper class of a town, and surfing sounds like freedom.</P>
      <P>There is only one more question I want to ask: Can I take my girl-friend with me, of course with paying?</P>
      <P>I hope all my wishes are realizeable.</P>
      <P>Yours</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>In my opinion shopping is not always enjoyable. Very often, for example on Friday afternoon or Saturday, there are so many people in a shopping centre, that you can't move yourself forwards or backwards. Many people say that this is real shopping, when you queue for hours to pay only a pair of socks or a bottle of mineral water at the supermarket. I think, you can't really enjoy shopping when there are hundreds of people and everyone wants to buy something.</P>
      <P>I like going shopping during the week, when I can look at each good a store sells. But for me it is better, when I go at the weekend because then I don't spend so much money because I think, before I have to queue for half an hour I buy nothing!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
