<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR488*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms. Ryan</P>
      <P>I refer to your letter regarding the prize I have won in your competition.</P>
      <P>I was really pleased to find out that I have an opportunity to spend two weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A.</P>
      <P>As requested in your letter please find below some additional information about me and my plans.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel in June as I have already arranged for a part time job later this summer.</P>
      <P>I prefer to stay in a tent as I go campping every summer and am used to slipping in tents.</P>
      <P>From the list of activities, which was provided by you, I'd like to choose photography and swimming. I'm very good at swimming as I have been a member of different swimming clubs since I was 6 and I chose photograthy because I have a new camera and want somebody to teach me how to use it.</P>
      <P>At the end I would like to ask you to let me know how much money and what kind of clothes I have to take with me.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Report</P>
      <P>Subject: Video about daily life at our school.</P>
      <P>Introduction: To support an idea to make a short video about daily life at our school I have spend some time discussing it with other students, observing and analaising an avrege day in our scholl and came up with some suggestions.</P>
      <P>Places to video: We should try to video not only class rooms but also our playground, cafe, sport hall, art club and library. Most students spend a lot of their time in such places and they are very important part of our school life.</P>
      <P>Activities to video: We should show students during their formal studies as well as after lessons. I think it is a good idea to include a record of one of our big events such as anual sport turnament or wellcoming evening for new students.</P>
      <P>Conclugen: To sum up the above I'd like to suggest not to film anything longer than 1 or 2 minuts and have a nice mixture of places, faces and events.</P>
      <P>If you have any further comments or questions regarding this case please let me know.</P>
      <P>King Regards</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
