<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR504*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>To the Manager of the theatre</P>
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam</P>
      <P>I am writing in order to tell your some things that happened to me at the theatre, at that moment I felt astonish thinking about: "How an important theatre have problems like this." But, Yes.</P>
      <P>First the starring was going to be Danny Brook, but then another man took his place, I couldn't believe it, you couldn't change Danny Brook, a very important artist, and put a begginer one. It was very disappointing.</P>
      <P>Secondly, It was supposed to start at 19:30 and it started at 20:15. Yes, 45 minutes, I want to see you in that case. What would you do? I felt like a dumb, and all the people felt like me.</P>
      <P>And well, don't talk about the discounts, because they didn't exist. More than that, the restaurant was closed because it was on repairing.</P>
      <P>At end, I could see that the advertisement said "Your perfect evening out", it wasn't the perfect evening, now I'm looking for a layer, because I want my money back, if don't well you know the end of this story.</P>
      <P>Faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets, because one day when Maria, her sister, was walking to the school, a car stopped at her and a man said "I know who is your love, it's Peter".</P>
      <P>Maria passed all the day thinking about who told them that, there were two posibilities: one her best friend Becca or his sister Pat.</P>
      <P>But the problem began to increase because all her friends knew her secret. It was like a "chain reaction", until Maria didn't want to go to school any more, her mother talked to her, but there was no case, she was very angry and hurt.</P>
      <P>One day, at his house, she listened Pat talking with a friend and Maria realised that Pat said everything, because they were talking about a secret of another friend. But there was a problem, how to said it to Pat, in a good or in a bad way, she decided for the good one.</P>
      <P>Obviously, Pat first refused, but then she accepted that she was wrong, and apologyse Maria, after then Pat never again talked about someone within his or her permission.</P>
      <P>The End.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
