<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR506*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>13.06.00</P>
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P> I would like to thank you for first prize. I am really surprised that I have won. I have not expect it.</P>
      <P>I would like to send you some futher information which you need. I can only come in July because I am working in the office and I cannot take two weeks off in other month.</P>
      <P>I am greatful that I have the chance to choose an accomodation. I would rather stay in a tent if its not problem for you. I would like to experience a reall camp again. I used to be a scout.</P>
      <P>I need relax after year in the office thats why I choose photography and painting which are not very active. I am very shy person and I would prefer to stay in a small group of people, if its possible.</P>
      <P>I have to questions. I would like to ask you which kind of clothes I should take and I would like to know your opinion how much money I should take.</P>
      <P>I would like to thank you onc again for this great opportiunity.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Apolonia Gorski</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>We would like to belive that shopping is the most wonderful part of our life. After working all week, finally on Saturday we can do shopping. We love spending money, but spending money is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>Problems start when we cannot find any space to park our car. When we finally do this, we cannot go confortable because of crowd. Why its always the same! The answer is that we choose the same street (usually the most popular) and the same time as six hundrets other people. We become customers who want to do their shopping with pleasure. I think we can achieve pleasure at home with our new goods.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
