<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR508*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>16.12.2000y</P>
      <P>Dear Ms Clark,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you in connection with the advertisement in newspaper. I would like to express a couple of thoughts that I have after the festival that I have recently seen.</P>
      <P>I believe that it was a great idea to organise such a festivel, connected with art and culture. Especially the date was very suitable for me, as I have a lot of free time.</P>
      <P>What is more there was a wide vareiety of music Although the artists were supposed to be from all counties, there were only six nationalities.</P>
      <P>I hope that next year there will be much more possibilities to enjoy films or plays and that the halls will be bigger, as they were overcrowded. However I was really suprised that the entrence fee was so low. I have also one suggestion, if I may. Maybe next year the festival could be ended with fireworks show.</P>
      <P>Thank you for your kind attention and I hope that my advices would occur useful.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Tom,</P>
      <P>Just I got your letter and sat straight away to write you a few sentences that will illustrate my opinion.</P>
      <P>To begin with, I'd like to show you how are my obligations at school. Although we have to change our boots, we don't need to wear special uniforms. Our clothes should be in a good taste. We are also allowed to have jewellery and a make-up, what's especially crucial for girls.</P>
      <P>When it goes to my home, I think I have usual duties I have to clean my room, wash the dishes or vacuum the carpets, but they're not exhausting things, as I share them with my sister and brother. However my parents aren't demanding, I have to be home at least at 11 o'clock and tell them where I go out.</P>
      <P>In my opinion there's nothing special that I'd like to change, maybe only this, that I wouldn't have to change my boots.</P>
      <P>I hope that it'll claryfy your questions and doubts. So, that will be everything as for now. I'm looking foreward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
