<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR509*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>DEAR MR ROBERTSON</P>
      <P>I AM WRITING YOU WITH REFERENCE IN THE LONDON TRIP WE ARE HAVING PRERY SOON.</P>
      <P>I AM WRITING IN REPRECENTATION OF MY GROUP, AND ALL OF US WANT TO SAY THANK YOU FOR TAKE US ABROAD.</P>
      <P>WE SAW THE ACTIVITIES PROGRAM ALREADY AND WE THINK IS EXCITING, ESPECIALLY THE VISIT TO THE SCIENCE MUSEUM. AT THE SAME TIME WE WOULD LIKE TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.</P>
      <P>THERE IS GOING TO BE THE LONDON FASHION AND LEISURE SHOW ON THE 14TH OF MARCH, FROM 10.00 TO 19.00. WE ARE REALY INTERESTING IN THIS SHOW. EVENTHOUGH YOUR PROGRAM IS PERFECT WE WILL PREFER TO GO THERE.</P>
      <P>COULD YOU PLEASE BE SO KIND AND CHANGE SOME OF THE ACTIVITIES THAT WE WILL HAVE?</P>
      <P>WE THINK IS A GRATE OPORTUNITY, BECAUSE AS YOU KNOW, WE DON'T HAVE ACCES TO THAT KIND OF SHOWS IN THIS CITY.</P>
      <P>IN CASE YOU DECIDE TO CHANGE THE PROGRAM, WE SUGGEST ON TUSDAY GO TO THE SHOW AND ON WENSDAY INSTED FREE TIME, VISIT THE SCIENCE MUSEUM. THOUGH WE DONT HAVE SHOPPING AND FREE TIME.</P>
      <P>WE ARE LOOKING FORWARD FOR YOUR ANSWER.</P>
      <P>YOUR SINCERLY;</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>"THE RIGHT PERSON"</P>
      <P>MAY 29, 1997. IT WAS MY FIRST TIME IN LONDON. THAT NIGHT I WENT TO A PUB IN BAYSWATER. WHEN THEY CLOSED I TOOK THE 7 BUS.</P>
      <P>I WAS LIVING QUITE CLOUSE TO PORTOBELLO ROAD BUT I DIDN'T KNOW VERY WELL THE AREA BECAUSE ALL TIME I JUST HAD TO GET OFF IN THE COURNER OF MY HOUSE. BUT THAT DAY, LIKE I WAS KIND OF DRUNK, I DIDN'T REALISE THAT THE BUS TOOK A DIFFERENT WAY; SO WHEN I NOTICED IT THE DRIVER WAS ALREADY ASKING ME TO GET OFF, BECAUSE WE WHERE IN THE GARAGE IN PORTOBELLO. I TOLD HIM, I DIDN'T KNOW WHERE I WAS BUT HE JUST SEID SORRY.</P>
      <P>I WAS REALY SCARE. THERE WERE SOME PEOPLE AROUN BUT I WAS AFRAID TO ASK THEM THE WAY I SHOULD TAKE.</P>
      <P>AT LEAST I ASKED A BOY AND HE SAID "I'LL TELL YOU WHERE IS THE PLACE YOU ARE LOOKING FOR, JUST FOLLOW ME".</P>
      <P>IT WAS DANGEROUS, BUT I KNEW I HAD TO DO IT. 10 MINUTES AFTER I WAS FOLLOWING HIM, I START KNOWING THE PLACE, AND I WAS FELLING MORE CONFORTABLE.</P>
      <P>HE TOOK ME RIGHT IN FRONT OF MY HOUSE. I THANK HIM SO MUCH, AND I WAS SO HAPPY THAT I ASKED TO THE RIGHT PERSON AND NOTHING WRON HAPPEN TO ME.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
