<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR513*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam</P>
      <P>I went to see 'over the rainbow' presented by the circle theater. I was really disappointed therefore I am writing a complain.</P>
      <P>Firstly I bought the ticket because I like Danny Brook's acting but in the show someone was acting his part. Also the person was not really good at acting.</P>
      <P>Secondly the time on the leaflet is totaly wrong. It said it will start at 19:30. Infact it started t 20:15. I was waiting for 45 minuts.</P>
      <P>Thirdly the ticket was no discount and after the show I visited theater restaurant but it was close because the show started too late.</P>
      <P>Finaly last nigh was not perfect evening. (Therefore) I want to have money back and I hope you will think about these problems.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>I am writing an article about fashion of the future to the international student magazine.</P>
      <P>Fashion are always changing therefore it is really difficult to say what sort of clothes people wear in future. But when I heard the word of future, I have image of metalic colour so that my imagination they are wearing metalic or bright colour cloth. May be they have more different types of colour than now.</P>
      <P>However I think the style of fashion will not have big differences because I believe that fashion is in a circle. The mean of this is all our fashion styles come from history. For example our fashion style at the moment is comes from 70's fashion. We always repeat the fashion with adding some new fashion at that time.</P>
      <P> I think the people will wear clothes which are metalic or bright colourful colour with mixture of history and future fashion style. in future.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
