<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR515*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>31-40</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Miss and Mister</P>
      <P>Thank you for the letter that conformed first prize.</P>
      <P>I am happy to receive it. Of course I will able to go to Camp California in the U.S.A. However, I only will able to go to there on July 2001 because I have a job which is extreme busy work. Our department, which is sales department, have to make good sales result befor end of June because of financial month. So, if I can choose days, I would like to go to the U.S.A on July 2001. About accomodation, I prefer stay log cabins because I don't like to stay in tents which are unconfortable for me. I am not also keen on preparing it.</P>
      <P>This prize, I can choose two activities, can't you. So, I am going to choose Golf and Tennis. In Japan, I often play Golf but as you know Japanese weather condition is not enough enjoying play Golf but California has good weather which are every day sunshuin, hopefuly. I used to play tennis when I was university student. I am interst playing tennis very much.</P>
      <P>Finaly, I have some question. When I join this camp, what kind of clothes should I carry? Moreover, how much money do I have to need? Please reply for me as soon as possible</P>
      <P>Best riger.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim.</P>
      <P>Hello Kim. How are you? I am well. I have a big news. I could enjoy helping at a pop concert in last week which is "The Max". As you know, I am big fun with "The Max". Can you believe it?</P>
      <P>I have got good experience and fantastic memory. At the same time I have got a small money but it was not important for me. I was so happy.</P>
      <P>So, my templary job was sound engineer but I was not main engineer. I've just helped for staff. When I was university student, I studied sound effect but I haen't used effect equepument whole my life because our school dosen't have it. I used this equepument during concert but I was so compricate. At first I couldn't understand this system but our staff was very kind people. They teached me paticulaly. After that I was able to understand this system, time after time. Now, I able to use sound effect system.</P>
      <P>Of course, I could enjoy this concert, as well</P>
      <P>If I got a chance, I would like to work for creative companies, I hope.</P>
      <P>Any way,</P>
      <P>Take care of youself. I am waiting your letter</P>
      <P>Your</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
