<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR525*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Miss Helen Ryan:</P>
      <P>Last week I recived your letter in wich you told me that I won first prize. I am writting in response of it.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to travel in July, because I can arrange 2 weeks in July with my school holidays, in order not to lose classes.</P>
      <P>I think I would prefer to be in tents, because I think it is funnier and you can be in more contact with nature, but if I don't like the tents can I change my mind?</P>
      <P>You told me to choose 2 activities and I chose surfing and singing. In both of them I am very good. I did a surf course last summer and I have gone to singing lessons almost all my life.</P>
      <P>I have a few questions. How much money should I take to spend in those two weeks? and also what kind of clothes I should take?</P>
      <P>Please, when you recive this letter give me a call so we can arrange everything.</P>
      <P>Looking forward to hearing from you</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>We are going to do a video about daily life at school, the following classes are the ones I recomend to film.</P>
      <P>ENGLISH: the classroom is beautifull, and in the same day we do a lot of diferents activities, so it won't be boring watching it because we can have a great time there.</P>
      <P>CHEMISTRY: We do a lot of experiments and the materials we use are very good. I think that if we film that class the people that watches it will be impress with the equipment we have got.</P>
      <P>SPANISH: We are doing a play now. We could film it and produce it, instead of uniform we could wear costumes, the ones that are animals could pain their faces. I think that if we do it properly we could have a great spanish play.</P>
      <P>Those three classes are my choises, I hope we could do them and make a very good video about our school.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
