<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR527*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Dutch</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you to give you some further information about the competition I won. I am very pleased that I won your competition.</P>
      <P>First of all I would like to travel in July because I already made an arrangement with my boss about my free days.</P>
      <P>I would prefer to sleep in an log cabin. I am not just to sleeping in an tent and I think it mabey ruen my holiday. I hope it's possible to sleep in a log cabin but if it's not, you can also put me in an tent.</P>
      <P>The two activities I would like to choose are: Photography and Surfing. Photography I never realy took pratice in, yes I have made some holiday pictures but I would like to learn more about this. So I am not very good in Photography.</P>
      <P>Surfing is my passion. I live nearby a beach and whenever I have the time I grape my bord and go surfing. I would like to have a surfing contest with other surfing nerds, if it's possible. I would like to know if I have to bring my own wetsuit for surfing and how much money do you think I need?</P>
      <P>I am realy looking forward to this holiday. I hope I have informed you enough.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>How are you? I'm doing great esspecially after my experience with helping at pop concert. It was fantastic. You also would have liked very much.</P>
      <P>I had to help back stages. I had to take care of that every artist went in the right dressing room and not in someone elses.</P>
      <P>Every artist could scream at me whenever they wanted. The realy thing was that I had to look after them because without me they would have been lost. That was a good feeling for me. I had to tell them when they had to go on stages. What kind of clothes they shoot wear. I also had to give them drinks and food and help them to relax whenever they were nervous.</P>
      <P>The thing I realy liked, was helping the artists and talking to them. Oke, they screamed at me all the time because they were nervous and excited about their concert.</P>
      <P>Afterwards they talk to me and thanking me for helping them in those exciting moments. I realy got to know them after the concert. They also took me to a after hour party and they asked me if would like to do this again. And of course I immediately said Yes!!</P>
      <P>Mabey next time you can come with me that would be a lot of fun.</P>
      <P>The will call me next week, so I write when I talk to them.</P>
      <P>Talk to you soon.</P>
      <P>love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
