<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR528*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>Last week I had the chance to spend time in London and this is why I decided to go to the Circle Theatre to see the musical show.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I would like to tell you I had unfortunately a very bad evening. Indeed, I was very surprise to ear when I asked for a discount that it was not possible to have one.</P>
      <P>In spite of that, I finally decided to take one ticket.</P>
      <P>The other bad point was the time when the show started, it was already 20:15 when the first star entred on the scene, but your advertisement sayed 19.30!</P>
      <P>The worst was when the actors were presented to us and the starring names were completely different than I expected.</P>
      <P>Finaly, I didn't understand why you pushed people to visit your restaurant if you don't open it after the show!</P>
      <P>This is why for all of those good reasons I am asking for some money back.</P>
      <P>I am sure you will understand my request regarding my complaint, your credibility is depending of.</P>
      <P>I look forward to earing from you.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Our century is a century of changes, of evolution. Since the end of the 40's which is the period where the technology started, nobody can say that nothing has changed.</P>
      <P>Every day, from the morning to the evening we are completely dependent of the technology.</P>
      <P>In fact our life style is based on the technology, now, if we want to stay at home without having contact with other people, we can do it, we just need a computer and a modem and that's it.</P>
      <P>If I want to discuss with friends or order a Pizza, I can do it easely as I want, when it want. In spite of that, I think the technology is improving my quality of life.</P>
      <P>A good example is the celular phone, I can contact my family without problem, I can inform my company if I had an accident with my car.</P>
      <P>If I compare my life now with the life of my grand parents, I think both are comparable, I say that because without knowing the technology, it's difficult to imagine a best life, in fact, you leave with your time. Even if the technology is important for my quality of life, I am not able to say if it will continue to be the case in 10 years.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
