<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR532*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing in order to explain to you the problems regarding the musical show I saw at your theatre.</P>
      <P>First of all, there was written in the advertisement for the show, that there would be Danny Brook as main actor, but a different actor played in the show.</P>
      <P>The show started forty-five minutes later and this really disappointed me. Besides, when I bought the ticket, I found out there was not discounts for ticket, while you wrote the contrary. Moreover, I could not go to the theatre restaurant because, by the time the show had finished, it had already closed.</P>
      <P>Definetely, it was a very disappointing evening and I would appreciate your if it was possible to have my money back.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you in the near future.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. She was a very pretty and kind girl, but she had this bad habit. This was her only fault. She had a lot of friends but nobody trusted her. That was why she decide to change her behaviour. She was given a chance: if she had been able not to tell everybody a secret for a short time, her friends would have started trusting her. The secret was about a surprise-party for her bestfriend's birthday. As soon as the arrangement for the party started, she began to feel nervous and anxious because she wanted to tell everything to her bestfriend. But, as the days went by, she was surprised because she realized she was getting used not to tell secrets any more. The day of the party arrived and Pat succeeded in keeping the secret. All her friends were amazed at her change and started trusting her at once.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
