<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR537*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>2 Desember 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Mrs Clark:</P>
      <P>I am writing to suggest a few things that could be changed or added in next year's International Arts Festival, wich in my opinion has been a great idea to create.</P>
      <P>Although I have read that Starts and Artists came frome around the world, I have realised that they only came from only six countries.</P>
      <P>I spent a good time in the jazz, rock and classical concerts in spite of the fact that some concert halls were too small. I think that if you want to enjoy music you must be comfortable. All my family liked the films and the plays that there were very much, but I personaly think that It would be better to add more because there were only five plays and seven films.</P>
      <P>The rest of the activities were very interesting for us, we learnt a lot of things and we met a lot of interesting people, and all of this without being expensive, I think that ticket was exellent for us because of its price.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing you as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerelly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>2 Desember 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Andy:</P>
      <P>I'm sorry I haven't written for so long, but I have been very busy with my exams. It's good to hear that you have passed all of them.</P>
      <P>In your letter you told me something about rules. I imagine that you want my opinion for your homework?Don't you?</P>
      <P>You know that I'm studing in a hard school, and as you can imagine you have to work hard and you have to do homework everyday. The other day I arrived five minutes late and the teacher ordered me to go home.?Do you understand this? She might be crazy</P>
      <P>I have friends that are studing in other schools and they are very happy with their freedom. At home it's very different, as you know I have a very good parents that let me do a lot of things. they let me go out with my friends every day, but they make me do homework and I hate this!!</P>
      <P>I hope that it is what you wanted from me. I'm looking forward to seeing you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
