<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR560*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your nice letter which informed me to have won first prize in my competition.</P>
      <P>I'am really surprising and happy about it.</P>
      <P>In your letter you needed some informations about me. Unfortunately, I have only the possibility to travel in July because in August I will start a new job for six months. I won't be free, however all July I am at home.</P>
      <P>For accommodations at this camp, I would prefer being in a tent to being in a log cabin. It is more amusing and friendly. It will allow me to make friends more quickly.</P>
      <P>Two of my best activities are swimming and photography. The first one is a needless for me. I go every day swimming one Mile. The last summer I won a prize in competition of swimming. The second one is more a hobby. I like go in nature and make photography. I started it two months ago. I don't have any material.</P>
      <P>Could you tell me if you would lend me some material for photography?</P>
      <P>What sort of clothes will I need for these two weeks?</P>
      <P>How much money will I take with me?</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Henri Devereux</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I'm so happy with the experience I lived last month.</P>
      <P>I told you that I have helped at a pop concert last month. I was really great.</P>
      <P>Firstly I was designed to sell the tickets. I was already happy to help in such a big concert than the Mylene Farmer's concert.</P>
      <P>I was starting to sell the tickets when a person who organised told me to go into the lodge. They needed one person for putting the clothes into a wardrobe. It was the lodge of Mylene Farmer. Are you thinking? I was so exciting! Unfortunately, I didn't see her but it allowed me to talk with her manager John and her musicians. All were very kindly and pleasant. It was a big moment for me. Finally these people are like us, they have just a special job with special times. The next year, if it will be possible, I would like go back with you. They will organise a same concert pop but with an other singer. I look forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Love,</P>
      <P>Henri</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
