<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR562*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms. Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>I am very happy to here from you that I have won first prize in your competition - twe weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A. and I am writing for my information to tell you.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I will be able to travel only in July because I go to univercity and I normaly spend the most of time for work. to do. and I have holiday only in July.</P>
      <P>Secondly, It is accommodation. I prefer in tents. When I go to camp, I stay in a log cabins all the time so I would like to try different way to stay, this time.</P>
      <P>And I choose phtograghy and tennis from the activities list. I am taking photograghy courses at univercity and I started tennis, when I was 10 so I am good at bouth of them.</P>
      <P>Endly, I have questions about clothes and money.</P>
      <P>How much money should I take and should I take only casual clothes and trainers?</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Your sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim.</P>
      <P>Thank you for your lovely letter and I hope you are well.</P>
      <P>The other day, I worked at a pop concert to help. It was really interesting than I expected. My job at behind the stage was helping make-up, hare and clothes staylist. It was very hard. The singers often changed them clothes and them make-up was easy to be off because of the sweat. It was different from I did at college. There was no time to rest. But I met a lot of famous singer and spoke to them. In front of the stage was so many people and they couldn't see them very well, but I was at very near from the stage and I could see them just there.</P>
      <P>You like pop music, don't you? So, don't go to a concert! Work at a concert! That's much more exciting.</P>
      <P>Anyway, shall we meet sometime? We haven't met each other so long time and I'll tell you more story of this.</P>
      <P>Write soon,</P>
      <P>Bye Bye.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
