<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR565*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about your advertisement which inform me wrong information. While I had a holiday in London I went to your theatre to see "Over The Rainbow", but I had a very disappointing evening.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I am a fan of Danny Brook so your advert attracted me but when I went there a different actor was in the musical show instead of him. I was so disappointed.</P>
      <P>Secondly, your timetable was wrong. It said the show started at 14.30 but, actually, it started at 20.15 so we had to wait for about six hours.</P>
      <P>Thirdly, I saw "Discount Available" on your advert but your staffs said it was just for Mondays. Your advert made me misunderstood.</P>
      <P>Finally, we visited your theatre restaurant after the show. However, it closed because it was being decorated.</P>
      <P>Your advert promised me "Perfect evening out", but it was terrible evening to me. So I want you to give me a refund.</P>
      <P>Looking forward to hearing from you soon</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>Ko Hyu Tung</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has mordern technology changed my daily life?</P>
      <P>When I was young, I used to play sports such as football, basketball and tennis with my friends but, these days, I am getting used to sitting in front of the computer and watching TV.</P>
      <P>When I bought my computer, I wasn't interested in it but when I started studying about internet and playing games, I found it interesting. Sometimes, I think I am a computer addict because whenever I come back home, my hand go to computer swich, automaticaly, even though I don't want to use the computer. I usually spend my time on playing computer about three hours a day.</P>
      <P>After that, I go to the sofa for watch TV. Although there aren't programmes which are interesting, I just watch TV, so my mother calls me "Couch Potato".</P>
      <P>As a result, my health is getting worse. I know I need to excercise but it is difficult for me to start.</P>
      <P>Modern technology has changed my daily life from physical activity to mental activity (??)</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
