<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR567*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing this letter to let you know my decision about your letter, which I have received recently. I would like to thank you for competition which was organised by your agency and I must say that I was very surprised when I received the result of the competition.</P>
      <P>I think, I could have an holiday just in July because I will have been working in my previous company for one year by the end of the June and I will have a one month holiday period from my company. I would rather prefer to stay in the tent than to stay in the log cabin because the tent is more enjoyable.</P>
      <P>I might say that I am really good at swimming and sailling because I have been joining these kinds of activities for five year and I had really good training about sea-sports.</P>
      <P>Should I take my clothes with me or are they arranged in the camp placement? Also, how much does it cost.</P>
      <P>I am looking to hear from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim</P>
      <P>I hope you and all your family are well and everything is ok. I'd like to tell you about what exciting experience I had last month during a pop concert. I wish you were there and saw the concert, it was really brilliant.</P>
      <P>As you know I'd never been to any activities like to be a valunteer before. The concert tickets were very expensive and I'd seen an adversitement on the tv. It said, "be a valunteer for our concert and get a free ticket". After that I applied and they accepted my application.</P>
      <P>You should have seen, there was really terrible rush before concert and everybody was runing around to do something. I helped to carry huge speakers to the concert venue. Than I was told to stay in front of the entrance door and check the tickets. Some people tried to enter without any ticket but they weren't allowed by police.</P>
      <P>Finally, I helped them, in return I had good experience as well as enjoyed listening music.</P>
      <P>Love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
