<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR568*0101*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Brown,</P>
      <P>I am writing in connection with a surprise birthday party for your husband, Mr. Brown. We are writing to invite you and to give you some information about the party.</P>
      <P>All our class love Mr Brown very much, so we decided to organise a surprise party for him. The party in on Tuesday 16 of June. You should come on 3 pm in college Canteen. We have bought some snaks to eat and three students will sing for him, also.</P>
      <P>Besides this, we have invited all other teachers and the Principal of our school. Of course all the class will take party to this party. Furthermore, we don't know what present buying for him. So we would appreciate if you help us with this matter. We have thought to buy a cd or a book. He loves to read books. What do you believe? If he needs something else, we are happy to buy this.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you soon especially as I am concerned about this matter.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Nowadays people's life has many problems which need some solutions. Especially younger's life has been very difficult the last years.</P>
      <P>The only appropriate to solve people's problems is the family. Teenagers usually think about a matter which is drugs. Their family could explain them how they avoid things. They know the way to do this. And the way is love.</P>
      <P>Apart from this, parents could be very helpful to their children with difficulties of school. They help their children with lessons and give them some useful advice with their relationships. Because sometimes they are upset when they lose a friend.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, friends are not suitable to do this. Definately, they don't give real solutions and advice. There is a chance not to be so good friends and imitate that they are.</P>
      <P>The way which family comes in contact with the members so easily is love. So we should trust only our family when we need help or solutions of our problems.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
