<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR569*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam.</P>
      <P>I've just recived your leter, and I must say that I am so surprised, I wasn't expecting to win it.</P>
      <P>I still studing at the moment I will finish at the end of June so I will be able to leave at the begining of July.</P>
      <P>About the acomodation, I would prefer a log cabin instead of a tent so as to get a better rest. I've got some problem to sleep and a log cabin will be more peaceful than a ten.</P>
      <P>You are asking me to choose just 2 activities. It's quite dificult for me because there are 4 of them I like a lot wich are climbing, tennis, surfing and photography, but if I have to make a choise, I choose climbing and surfing. I'm rather trained in climbing, I have done it once a mounth since I was 17. But in the other hand, I have never done surfing, I am a completely Beginer but I am dieing to do it.</P>
      <P>I've got just one question to do, I know it is all include, but is there anything I will have to pay for? If there is, please let me know.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you very soon, and please let me know if you need any further information.</P>
      <P>Yours Faithfully:</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>First of all, I think we should have a protagonist for it. A good idea to start will be a clock alarm ringing close to his bed, because that's the way everyone get up in the morning, (unless the people who don't do anythink)</P>
      <P>After that, we should have a morning view of one of the most busiest London tube station in order to show stressed people going in and out, Including our protagonist going out peacefully with a couple of books on his hand - then the school's door, and him going in.</P>
      <P>After all this introduction, will be the time to show some of the acitivities every one can join in the school, such as lesonscofecoleaguescofe..</P>
      <P>And finally a view of all the students leaving the school would be a nice end.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
