<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR573*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I have just returned from my holiday in London. During my stay I went to see a musical show in the Circle Theatre and I have very disappointing evening.</P>
      <P>Firstly I expected Danny Brook and Tina Truelove but I felt very angry when I saw diffrent actors. What is more you advertize there were discounts available but it were not.</P>
      <P>You said that the musicial show started at 19.30 but recently it began at 20.15. I was very bored because I did not have anything to do when I was waiting for your show.</P>
      <P>Additionally I felt very hungry and uncomfortable because your theatre restaurant was closed and you did not give us any reason why.</P>
      <P>You promised us a big show and perfect evening but it was only an average show with unknown actors.</P>
      <P>In my opinion you are not very respectful and responsible. I will never trust you again. I would like you give me my money back as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>I am looking foward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. As I remember I have known her for ever. She had always been my best friend and I had said her everything. We lived in the same street and the weekends we spent together.</P>
      <P>When I had 16 years old I fell in love with the most hundsom boy in our school. Paul was older than me and he was playing basketball. Only Pat knew about my lover.</P>
      <P>One day he invited us for his party. I was very happy and nervous. Everything was great. But when Pat drank some beer she told him everything about me. Everybody started to laught at me. I was angry and I run away to the forest.</P>
      <P>'She was my best friend, how can she do it to me' - - I was crying. When I was walking through the forest I saw a very tall man who was staying in front of me. 'My name is Jon' - he whispered - 'Don't be afraid'. We started to talk. This alien was so intelligent and funny that I forgot about my troubles. We talked for all night and I fall in love with him. We met again and again and now Jon is my husband. Maybe it was good that Pat was so talkative.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
