<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR575*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>17th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Sir!</P>
      <P>I am writing this letter to you, because the show "Over The Rainbow" which is the London's newest and best musical show, was not... for me. Pleas apologise me, but there were many mistakes and problems on the note you have made, which disappointed me very.</P>
      <P>I thought that Dany Brook who is my favorite actor play in that show. And I was really disappointed when I saw Jeremy Brook on the stage. Please, if you would be so kind and mind correct this mistake. I would be gratefull if you could correct too that show start. Other thing was that there was no discounts available, and that the restaurant which I wanted to visit after the show was closed because of the main cookersikness.</P>
      <P>I would be very grateful if I could get my money back. That evening which should be my perfect evening out, was in fact very tireing and boring.</P>
      <P>Apologise me for disturb.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward for answer!</P>
      <P>Best regardes!</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets, I knew that he's very talkative person, but it was nessesery because I wanted him to be the main director of that birthday party for tenes. It started a week before that day. Pat found the great place for the party called "Blue Box". I made a beautifull invite cards for every Agatha friends with a sign "Do not tell Agatha about that, this is a suprise party for her, please keep the secret!" Pat arranged great DJ and drinks. My friend and I made a perfect decoration with ballons and other party stuff. Everyone told us it was breath taking. Everything was set... the day and hour came. Everyone gathered in disco at 21.00. We were only waiting for Agatha who should come at 22 o'clock with her boyfriend. It was so exaiting!!! We put off the lights and then the door opened and I just heard "What the hell is going on?!!" She entered the room, and everyone shouted HAPPY BIRTHDAY DEAR! She was so touched that we started to cry. Enyway the disco was great, music also. We had fun to 5 o'clock! Agatha said that it was the greatest present she could ever get!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
