<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR577*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan.</P>
      <P>I am writing to reply your letter about my first prize in your competition and give you all information for my two weeks at Camp California.</P>
      <P>First of all, I prefer travelling in July, because it will be my school vacation and I'm not allowed to travel during school times. It'd be great if I could be accommodated in tents, because I've never slept in tents before, and I think it is an interesting experience.</P>
      <P>Secondly, the two activities wich I'd like to pratice during the campsite are sailing and surfing. I have already surfed when I was travelling in Brazil, but since them I have hadn't a chance to do it again. Although I know how surfing, I have no idea about sailing, I just only read about it and I am very interested to practice. Is there any problem?</P>
      <P>I'd like to ask you some questions: Is necessary bring money to the Camp? How much? And about clothes? What is more appropiated?</P>
      <P>Finally, I want to thank you for the great opportunity I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely.</P>
      <P>Camila Beatriz de J. Branco</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>A programme not often good.</P>
      <P>Shopping is said that an enjoyable programme in all situations. However sometimes it isn't so wonderful as it seems to be.</P>
      <P>When you go to a sale shop it is dificult to find what you look for without a help of the shop assistant. The problem is find a shop assistant who hear your problems and can help you. After that you have to wait a long time in the qeue to pay and many times isn't possible pay with your credit card and you don't have a money in cash. So you had lost hours to buy nothing. You can't talk to manager even to give him suggestions to improve his business, because he is always absent. And don't try to complain to someone else because they won't hear you.</P>
      <P>To conclude, although you can have good moments while shopping all of us know that it is not always enjoyable, isn't it?</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
