<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR578*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr/Mrs,</P>
      <P>I've seen your festival and I would like to give you my suggestions to it. I must say that International Arts Festival is really great idea. And your last festival was very intresting too.</P>
      <P>But also there are some notes that you should improve in the next year's festival to make it absolutelly wonderful. First of all, you must invite artists and stars from more countries around the world, because there are people only from six countries. I think it can make your festival more popular.</P>
      <P>Jazz, rock and classical concerts are amazing, but I think that some concert halls are too small, so not everybody can come.</P>
      <P>Your dance shows are very beautiful, art exhibitions is something original and exciting. And also it is very interesting to talk with writers.</P>
      <P>I think that one reasonably-priced weekend for all events is exellent idea because it isn't so Expensive as buying ticket to each event, and with this ticket you can visit everything you want. I hope you will continue to making your festivals.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Tom,</P>
      <P>How are you? Thank you for your last letter. It was very interesting. The question you asked me in it is very original too.</P>
      <P>I must say that rules aren't same in schools of our country. Every school has it's own rules. I think that my school is very democratic and so there are very good relations between teachers and students. We are all very friendly in our class and we help to each other when we have a problem. So the main rule in our school is regarding theachers.</P>
      <P>I'm allowed to do many things at home. My parents are very kind, and they know that their son will do everything right. And the main reason Why our family is so friendly, it's because we haven't go many rules. So, I think there isn't something I'd like to change.</P>
      <P>I hope everything is good in your family and your school.</P>
      <P>Take care,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
