<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR580*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>13th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to thank you and your organisation for giving me this opportunity. I've just received your letter this morning. I am very happy an exciting about it.</P>
      <P>I can only travel during July because I have many A-levels examinations to take during June. I would prefer staying in a tent because I haven't done it before and I would like to give it a go. I also would like to chose basketball and surfing as two activities to do while I am at the Camp. I am very keen on basketball. I am a captain of school's basketball team and we have won many competitions. However, my surfing skill is very average as I have only been surfing for three months. There are two questions I would like to ask. First question is how many and what type of clothes do I have to take with me? Another question is how much money do I have to take with me (roughly)?</P>
      <P>I am really looking forward to take part at Camp California.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Duangkamol (Denis) Saowaluk</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>13th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>How are you? I am fine. Remember I have told you that I have been selected to help at a pop concert of a local band? Well, it turned out really well and everybody had a great time.</P>
      <P>It was last month that I was selected. I had to help the director writing a script of the concert and design the background of the stage. I have also been told that they were going to make a music video from that concert, so I tried as well as I could. I didn't get involved that much in writing a script because it was very hard and the director wrote most of it but the main idea of the background of the stage was my, and I am very proud of it. Everything has been finally planed two days before the concert.</P>
      <P>On Saturday night, the concert began. Everything went really well, the music was great and the fans were loving it. When they've finished singing the last song I was surprice when they called me up on the stage and said thank you to me in front of hundreds of people. I am sure that I'll never forget that moment.</P>
      <P>Love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
