<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR586*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>13th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan</P>
      <P>Regarding your letter dated on the 6th of June I'm so happy to receive the first price. Thanks very much.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel in July to California. The reason is that we have long holidays at school on this time. Although, the accommodation isn't so important for me. I would prefer the log cabin because of the comfort and the better bed.</P>
      <P>I have choosen the activities surfing and photography. I'm a beginner on both activities.</P>
      <P>I have some questions as follow:</P>
      <P>1. What kind of clothes are needed?</P>
      <P>2. What I have to pay by myself?</P>
      <P>3. Should I take some money with me?</P>
      <P>4. How is the wheather in California?</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerelly,</P>
      <P>A. Becker</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable</P>
      <P>Most of the time is shopping fun and enjoyable.</P>
      <P>There are a lot of reasons that could be awful to go shopping. Even if you run out of money or you have to buy a particular thing which is difficult to find. I had once this problem. I was looking for a special fruit.</P>
      <P>The sales assistants in the stores aren't so nice and helpful. Sometimes they give me a bad feeling as.</P>
      <P>Last week I was shopping with my younger brother. Awful. He wanted everything what his eyes saw. All the stuff for children are in the same level as they have their eyes. Afterwards, I felt tired and unsatisfy the store.</P>
      <P>The shops have bad opening times.</P>
      <P>When I feel me comfortable for shopping everything will be closed or you haven't enough time to look around.</P>
      <P>My conclusion on these points are not so bad. I like shopping at all with my best friend.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
