<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR592*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs. Ryan:</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your letter. I am so glad to know I won the first prize.</P>
      <P>Regarding your questions, the following are my answers.</P>
      <P>The only time available for me to travel is July, any time during the month suits me. I need to insist in it, because I am not able to take holidays during the rest of the year.</P>
      <P>I will love to be in a log cabin. They are more comfortable and really match with the enveiroment.</P>
      <P>It is not easy to chose from the list of activities, all of them look interesting. Although this is a new experience, I would prefer climbing and Photographe. The first one sounds like a great adventure, while the second will allow me to capture all the unforgettable views.</P>
      <P>In addition, I would appreciate if you let me know what is the kind of clothing required for the Camp; if I need some money there and for what; and finally if the prize is just for me or if I can go with somebody else.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim:</P>
      <P>Finally I'm writing to let you know about the most exciting experience in my life. Can you believe that I was helping in the last Britney Spears's Concert?</P>
      <P>During the day I helped preparing her room, then she arrived, and I was there to continue helping.</P>
      <P>She was so kind with all of us, of course I asked her for an autograph. I hope to see you soon, I can't wait to show it.</P>
      <P>The concert was a big success, lot of excitment. Everybody sang and danced, and I was there to see everything from the best position.</P>
      <P>Each time, when she comes back to the room, she asked for something to drink, just a diet coke, because she's always looking after her weight. Then she eat something small and she looks full of energy all night long.</P>
      <P>At the end, she took the time to say good by to all of the people helping her. I really think she's the best.</P>
      <P>But now, tell me about you. Don't be lazy and write more often.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
