<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR596*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>51+</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Madame Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>Competition Organiser</P>
      <P>I've just received your letter and I thank you very much indeed for that. I didn't expect to win the first prize in your competition, I am very happy. It was always my dream to spend two weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A. Now it's become a reality.</P>
      <P>If I can choose the period, I would like to travel only in July because in other months I have a lot of thing to do.</P>
      <P>As accommnodation at Camp California, I would prefer to stay in log cabins because I think it is safier than in a tent.</P>
      <P>I've red that I will have a chance to do two extra activities while I will be at Camp.</P>
      <P>I think it would be a good idea to practise my photography, because I'm not so good a photographer and I would like to learn swimming as I can't do it. Taking part in these two activities would be very useful for me.</P>
      <P>There is another thing I would know, what kind of clothes have I bring with me? And how much money can I take with me?</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to hearing from you. Your sincerely -</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable. This is true.</P>
      <P>Some days ago my class had a big discussion about shopping.</P>
      <P>In that occasion I hadn't the opportunity for giving my opinion about this task.</P>
      <P>Now, my English teacher has asked me to explane all what I think.</P>
      <P>In my opinion, nowdays, shopping is very easy and in the same time very hard.</P>
      <P>It is very easy because there are a lot of things to buy, shops are plenty of every kinds of things. You can chose the price more suitable for you. Choosing from a lot of things and choosing the prices too are very enjoyable for me.</P>
      <P>Shopping is not enjoyable when you have not enough money to buy what you want, or when you are not sure about what you would like to buy.</P>
      <P>I remember very well two people who thought very different about shopping.</P>
      <P>My grandmother thought that shopping was a terrible thing, she hadn't enough money to buy even the bread.</P>
      <P>My mother, whereas was very keen on shopping everything.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
