<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR611*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writing to provide you with the information you require.</P>
      <P>First of all, I want to inform you that I would like to travel only in July, because in California at that time of the year is very hot and I prefer going on summer to going on winter or during other season, because I can do lots of activities that in winter would be impossible to do.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I would rather be accomodationed in log cabins than go in tens. In my opinion staying in log cabins is funnier and much cleaner.</P>
      <P>Thirsthly, I would prefer to swimming and playing tennis, because I have been practising them since I was I child, and I think I very good in each other.</P>
      <P>Finally, I would like to ask you if I have to take some money, or everything is provided for the organisers. Furthermore, I would be grateful if you could tell me what type of clothes I have to take.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>Sorry for not writing you before, but I have been so busy, because last weak I went to a pop concert to help the singers.</P>
      <P>First, when I arrived they told me to go to a big room, where the singers try on their clothes and they are made-up. There, in the room I had to helped them, I mean the singers, to put on theirs clothes, and I had to make-up them. A few minutes later the show started and the grup appeared on the stage. While they were singing a man told me to clean the room, where the singers get dressed. Later, when the show had finished, I stayed with the grup in their room for a few minutes. Then, they went to the airport, and my dream finished.</P>
      <P>What I really liked doing was to helped them with their clothes and to make-up them, because I learnt how to make-up a person and I spend a few minutes with the most popular grup of the world.</P>
      <P>Write me soon.</P>
      <P>Love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
