<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR615*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I'm really happy to know that I won in your competition. And first of all, before to ask for informations about the travel, I want to tell you thanks a lot.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel in July because is the best period to take a break from my work.</P>
      <P>For the accomodation, if is possible I would like to stay in camping because I think is a relaxing place where to stay. Further because I like to live in contact with the nature. Also is possible to meet a lot of people, and chatting during the night, might around the fire, playing a clutone and singing I think is a nice way to have fun.</P>
      <P>I'm really happy to know that is possible to play sports. I would like to play Tennis, and swimming. I choose tennis because is a sport that you can play with others people, also because I like the competition in the sport. The other sport that I would like to do is swimming. Swimming is my favourite sport because you can relax your body and your mind.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask you for further informations about this travel.</P>
      <P>First of all which kind of clothes I have to bring with me? How much money I need to do this travel?</P>
      <P>Also, if is possible I want to know if there is the possibility to organise a trip around the most important cities near the camp? And if during the nights there are entrotenements?</P>
      <P>Thanks for all these informations, I'm looking forward to hearing you again.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>After the discussion that we had in the english class, I understood that a lot of people sometimes don't enjoy during the shopping.</P>
      <P>I can't understand these people because this situation never happen to me. By the way usually the people that don't like shopping are men or children. I think is difficult to find a woman that doesn't like shopping. But I have to admit that sometimes I don't really like shopping above all when I'm tired or when I'm not in the right mood. In fact if I'm not in the right mood I become nervous because I can't find anything.</P>
      <P>For me, the best moments for the shopping are two opposite situations.</P>
      <P>For the first situation happen to me, when I'm hungry with somebody really close to me like my boyfriend or a component of my family, so for relaxing my mind I go to shopping and usually I enjoy a lot.</P>
      <P>The opposite situation is when I pass my exams and I really need to buy something for me as a preseant for myself.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
