<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR616*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>Last week, I had visited your theatre and I was very disappointed because I did not have a perfect evening out like what advertisement said.</P>
      <P>I would like to complain four things about your theatre. Fist thing, the actor is very horrible so I recommend you to change the actor because he will make an audience who visit you theatre disappoint.</P>
      <P>Second thing, you should open the show on time because if the audience have to wait, they will not feel happy but I think you know that.</P>
      <P>According to the advertisement, it said tickets £ 10, £ 15 and £ 20 discounts available but when I bought the ticket, the discounts did not available</P>
      <P>After the show I was very hungry so I went to the restaurant in the theatre but it was closed for decorating that make me very angry and disappoint.</P>
      <P>To conclude, your theatre is not good like what advertisement said so I would like to ask for some money back. I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>(Chan Suntavee)</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Nowadays, science and technology are very important to our life. The technology make my daily life change a lots compare to the past.</P>
      <P>For example, when I was young, I used to walk to school everyday but now my father has a car so I don't have to walk anymore, because my father gives me a lift everyday.</P>
      <P>At home, I have a video game so I play it all the time and I'm very enjoy that make my daily life happy so it's excellent but on the other hand I didn't do any homework or study at all.</P>
      <P>Another example is computer, I don't have to watch television or read a newspaper because I can know the news by using internet in the computer.</P>
      <P>To sum up, the modern technology has changed my daily life in bad ways and good ways. Therefore my daily life will change to bad ways or goods ways, it depends on how I use the technology.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
