<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR618*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Madam:</P>
      <P>How delighted I was when I receved your letter!</P>
      <P>About the information required, I would like to go in July because is my half term at University and summer time would be ideal.</P>
      <P>For accommodation I would rather go in a tent, I want to enjoy wild life and admire the landscape.</P>
      <P>In relation with leisure activities, my favourites are Basketball, which I have been playing for two years because I have been selected for my University team and I think a time practising with players from different countries will help me develop my skills at international level.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I would like to practise tennis, which is my hobby and I think it helps my mind to keep working.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask you how much money do I need, how is the weather in order to pack the necessary clothe and wheter I need something else.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim:</P>
      <P>What a fantastic experience I had helping my favourite group!</P>
      <P>You wouldn't believe it! I was working helping to mantle and dismantle the stage, sometimes I had to check the sound by saying something on the microphone, that was my chance and I always pretended to be a singer and that I sand in duo with the vocalist of the group, it was such a great fun!</P>
      <P>But the most exciting part of my job, and the one that I was looking forward to, was the last night of concert, because all the staff were promised to have a party with all the members of the band. That night was the best of my entire life.</P>
      <P>I send you some pictures, the best ones because there were some quite embarrasing.</P>
      <P>I hope you like them and I am already waiting for your next letter.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
