<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR627*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan!</P>
      <P>I'm very happy that I won first prize in your competion. Two weeks at California in the USA is the thing about I dreamed a lot. You asked me few questions in your letter. I would like to answer.</P>
      <P>The only one term for me to visit you is July. I can come to USA on July becouse on August I will be working with my father. We are building a new house for our family. What about accommodation, I prefer tents to log cabins. Nights in hol. on July are hot. Tent will be more cooler to sleep then the cabin.</P>
      <P>You offer a great veriety of activities. My best sports disciplines are swimming and basketball. I am a life guard and I could work in your camp as a rescuer next summer. Basketball is the game which I love. I always watch the NBA matches on T.V. It will be great for me to train basketball in USA. I have qustions to. How much money should I take with me and what sort of clothes are requested</P>
      <P>Thank You.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely K.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shoping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>Ten or fifteen years ago we had in Poland empty shelves in shops. We could only buy things from Russia. People alwas queued for stuff from west. If you had wanted something special for example for a gift you had to stay in a line all night. It was the worst side of shopping in Poland couple years ago. Nowadays we have capitalism, free market lots of privete shops, markets and super-markets. We can buy everything what about we imagine. Polish super market are not Polish origin shops. They are imported from enother Western Europe country.</P>
      <P>I apprieciate this shops for lots of products, cheep prices end big spaces. But the problem is when I want to buy only one thing, for example bread. On Friedy evening and at on the weekdays each supermarkets are crowded. They are filled by people who went buy everything.</P>
      <P>I do not like crowded places. This is the reason why I do not like shopping.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
