<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR637*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam</P>
      <P>I have visited your theater and I was very dissapointed because of the number of reasons.</P>
      <P>I've read your advertisment and in reality to what was written there was different.</P>
      <P>There was no Danny Brook but instead of him was a different actor and I'm very dissapointed about it because I'm his fan. The show started much later, on 45 minutes later than it should be so I was late for the bus. There were no discounts availible so I overspended the money. The theater restaurant was closed for no reason availble to me.</P>
      <P>It was a realy bad evening and because of it could you possibly give my money back? Because it was just a waste of money to go to your show.</P>
      <P>Yours Faithfully</P>
      <P>Vaisili Solatov</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. But when I came to this school a few months ago I didn't know this. We are in the same maths set so I met him rather soon. He was one of the first people who I get know. After a few days he was already my best friend. Everything was going perfectly befor last month when I met a girl from the other school. Her name was Marine. I saw her as a perfect girl with who I fallen in love with. So one day she offered to me to come to her house at night and to do so I had to run away from our boarding house and that was illigal. I had decided to go. So I woke up at 2 o'clock in the morning and climed out of the window. Unfortunately for me Pat at the time went to toilet and saw me. So I asked him to keep it in secret. I came back at 6 o'clock in the morning and went to sleep again. Next day my best friend went to headmaster and told him about me so he gave me a sespend.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
