<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR643*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir, Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complan about your service. Last Sunday I went to the Circle Theatre. I watched a musical show which called 'Over the Rainbow'. I was very disappointed it. Because there were other actors which played too badly. I don't understand why you changed them. I hoped to see Danny Brook and Tina Truelove as was presented in an advertisement.</P>
      <P>You had to start the show at 19.30 p.m. but you started too late at 20.15 p.m withour any ecxpenetion to people.</P>
      <P>Why did you put into the advertisement 'Discounts Available'? It wasen't!!! Any kinds of tickets were original prase.</P>
      <P>After the show many people wanted go to your theatre restaurant, but it was closed because there someone has fixed somethinghas fixed.</P>
      <P>I had the very disappointing evening so I would like to ask for return my money. I got the ticket for £20.</P>
      <P>I am hearing to looking fermards from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>Ilya V.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. I knew that but I needed someone who could understent and support me at that moment. I told to her about my pregnency because she has friend who works in a hospital as a doctor. I asked her for hepl and she promised me do everythings what she can and keep my secret. Pat gave same advise for me and I disayded to have an operetion.</P>
      <P>In a week time my classmates and teachers started to toking from me. I understand who told my secret to everyone. I got the big dipress but my parents supported me. We had a big conversation. They stopped me to do the operetion.</P>
      <P>Then I was 15 years old. Now I am 16 and I have got nice baby boy. My family very love him and support us. I still go to school and I have plan go to a college on next year.</P>
      <P>I would like to tell to everyone, don't be naive when you share with sameone your big secret or promlem. First tell to your parents. I am sure it is the best way. Ofcoure secrets can be different...</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
