<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR652*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir.</P>
      <P>I'm sorry to say it but your musical show was very disappointing to me. I was very disappointed. Lot of things that you have written at the advertisement are not true.</P>
      <P>You writer that the actor was going to be Danny Brook but he wasn't there. A different actor was played and this was very disappointing to everyone.</P>
      <P>Also the show did not start at half past seven o'clock as it was said but at eight and fifteen o'clock. Everyone get bored until the show start.</P>
      <P>About the discount that we are going to have. Why it does not make to us?</P>
      <P>I am also wondering why you told us to visit your theatre restaurant after the show. as it was closed. Everyone after the show run to take a good seat at the restaurant but everyone disappointed when they see the sight which said "Close for today".</P>
      <P>That evening wasn't my perfect and I have to say that I want my money back because the show was a disaster. I'm really sorry I am saying this but is the true.</P>
      <P>I am hoping that you will not make such mistakes again.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. Pat is a friend of mine and we are friends for almost a year. She is a very good girl and she can deal with every promblem she has.</P>
      <P>It was Saturday when I called her and told her to go for a walk at the park, which was not very far away from our houses. I had never told her a secret before but this time, I was going to tell her. The secret was about our friend Maria who was very kind with everyone I told her that I have heard that Maria had concern. Pat told me that she would not told that to anyone but the other day I learnt that all the school had known about Maria.</P>
      <P>I was sure that was Pat who told it to everyone. After that I had an argument with Pat and then she told me that she said it only to one person. I was very sad with what Pat do and I didn't speak to her for a long time.</P>
      <P>But now we are friends again but I will never say to her a secret in my whole life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
