<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR91*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I write you this letter to complain about your musical show. First of all, the show began three quarters of an hour late: it started at quarter past eight instead of half past seven, what of course was very bothering.</P>
      <P>I went to your show to see Mr. Danny Brook, who was supposed to play the main character, but he didn't appeared. He had been replaced by a really bad actor, whom I don't even know the name. I was very disappoint of that change, because Mr. Brook is one of my favourite actor.</P>
      <P>There were supposed to be discounts for the tickets, what appeared to be wrong to. I had to pay the full prize for them, which was quite expencive.</P>
      <P>My wife and I had decided to eat at the theatre restaurant after the play. It turned to be impossible: the restaurant was closed and we didn't even received an explaination therefor.</P>
      <P>I had a really bad evening and would like to ask you for my money back.</P>
      <P>Waiting for your reply</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Pierre Gaussier</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>In my opinion modern technology has changed my life a lot. First off all, if computers haden't been invented, I wouldn't spend half of the day in front of it! I use my computer for many things, such as homeworks, games, digital video or Internet.</P>
      <P>The developpement of portable communication systems, such as mobile phones has greatly changed our way of life. It is now possible to talk to a friend almost everywhere and everywhen, even if we are two thousand kilometers away from each other.</P>
      <P>Precision industry has changed my life a lot too. I practicate Scuba Diving during the week-ends and hollydays. That wouldn't have been possible a century ago, because all our material, such as dive computers, tanks or regulators didn't existed at that time.</P>
      <P>I think that we live easier now (thanks to modern medicine) and that our lives will get easier with the time.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
