<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR656*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Manager,</P>
      <P>I'm writing this letter to you because I had a very disappointing evening to your theatre. and I would like to explain what the problems were.</P>
      <P>Firstly, as I read at the advertisment, the actor would be Danny Brook and this is one of the reasons why I came to the theatre. But at big suprise I saw that the actor was different and I was very disappointed.</P>
      <P>Secondly, on the article the times were 14:30 and 19:30. I prefered to come at 19:30 because it is better at night and it wouldn't finish late, but the theatre started at 20:15 and we got bored waiting to start.</P>
      <P>Another reason why I was disappointed was that you said there would be discount available but there wasn't.</P>
      <P>At last I was waiting to visit your theatre restaurant after the show but it was closed because a machine was broken. This was very disappointing.</P>
      <P>As you can see there were many problems with the theatre and I would like to ask for some money back as an alternative</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully, </P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. The next morning at school everybody was looking at me with a strange way. Nobody was talking to me except the ten persons who I invited to my party.</P>
      <P>At first I didn't know why but after a few seconds I realised that telling Pat about my party wasn't a good idea. I was very ungry with her, I didn't know what to do I was afraid that I would have lost all my friends.</P>
      <P>After a few seconds of thoughts I went straigh to Pat. "Why, why did you do that?" I said she looked as if she didn't want to talk to me. I ignored her I couldn't do anything now. Everybody knew about my party and I had invited only ten persons. I was confused. I wondered why I made the mistake to invite Pat. I guess I didn't know that she would have said it.</P>
      <P>After a big confusion I decided not to make a party for my birthday so I could had all my friends back. And that's what I had exactly done even if I stayed alone at my birthday. It was much more important to me to get all my friends back.</P>
      <P>With this story I learnt that there are a few friends who are real friends and who you can trust.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
