<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR659*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear manager,</P>
      <P>During my stay in London, I visited all the most famous place and I enjoyed a lot during this days.</P>
      <P>I love London's musical shows and I read the advertisement for the show called "over the rainbow".</P>
      <P>I've gone to many musical shows where the main actor was Danny Brook and I can say that he is really good.</P>
      <P>It was my last night in London and I decided to go to this musical show. When I asked for the price I was surprised becaused the seller told there wasn't any discount available. I showed the advertisement to him and he said it was wrong and I paid the normal price.</P>
      <P>I bought the ticket for the second session and I went to the theatre at seven o'clock. I had been waiting half an hour outside the theatre and finally it started at a quarter past eight.</P>
      <P>I was angry about all of this problems but I was disappointed when I realised the advertisement was wrong with the actor's name.</P>
      <P>When the musical show finished I went to the theatre's restaurant and it was closed because it was too late, so I couldn't have dinner there, as it was announced.</P>
      <P>I wasn't a good evening and I would like to have my money back.</P>
      <P>Waiting for your answer.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Modern technology has changed my daily life and I'll try to explain it.</P>
      <P>We have been using personal computers for nine years and it's one of the most important changes.</P>
      <P>Last year I spent ten hours looking for information for my homework. The subject was "What's happening in Irak?" I started my research in the town's library and all the information I collected was from a local newspaper. After two hours I thought that all of this information was writted from a foreign point of view and it wasn't the native opinion.</P>
      <P>I used my computer for collecting reports from internet and I can promise I found so much information that I couldn't analize it in two weeks.</P>
      <P>Internet has changed our daily life: you can find whatever you want. Do you want to have a different lunch? Do you want to organize a different holiday in a strange place? You can find there all you need and more!</P>
      <P>I can't imagine my parents playing in the street without watching the TV. I couldn't life without modern music. I'm not interested in films without special effects..</P>
      <P>And what about mobile telephones? Changes won't stop it's caming the WAP technology (you'll buy a cake in a corner's machine without any coin, only one call), digital TV, virtual reality and more...</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
