<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR663*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>51+</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writing in reply to your letter in which you communicate I have won first prize in your competion. I am glad. Thank you very much. Now I am answering your questions and then I would like to know further information about travel and accomodation.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel in July because in June I am going to take some exams at University and at the moment I do not know the exact date. I can tell you I am only free in July.</P>
      <P>I would prefer an accomodation in log cabins because I am not keen on tents and I think that a log cabin is more comfortable than a tent.</P>
      <P>As regard as the chance to do two activities while I am at the Camp I would like to practise painting and photography. I am a painter in oils from life and my subjects are landscapes, people, animals. I like also taking photographs, for example during my journeys or trips. So when I go back home I can use my best pictures to reproduce them as a painting.</P>
      <P>Would you give me some information about clothes to wear there? I would like also to know how much money I can bring. Looking forward to hearing from you</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Billy Esposito</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>There is somebody who says that 'Shopping is not always enjoyable' and who is happy only when can go shopping.</P>
      <P>In the first I do not think that shopping is enjoyable when you must do so in a hurry or for duty. If you have to run from one shop to another and always looking at the watch, doing shopping is a terrible activity.</P>
      <P>On the other hand if you can walk without anytime problem with a good friend I think that shopping is very enjoyable. For istance, it is funny enter a clothes shop and try on a skirt or a t-shirt although you do not buy anything.</P>
      <P>To sum up I enjoy wasting money and buying useful things or not. I often like getting gifts for my relatives and friends. In my opinion, shopping is relaxing above all on Saturdays when you have finished a work week and you are expecting a wonderful Sunday.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
