<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR665*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>I have just received your letter informing me that I won a two week holiday at Camp California, so I am writing to you to indicate my preferences for the travel and the accomodation.</P>
      <P>I have no particular needs but one: it will be necessary for me to travel in July because my work will keep me very busy in all other months.</P>
      <P>About the accomodation, I have no problems, but I would prefer staying in tent, so that the holiday may be more adventurous.</P>
      <P>During the holiday, I would like playing tennis and golf. I can play tennis quite well, but I have never played golf, so, if it is possible, I would like taking lessons with a teacher.</P>
      <P>I would like to know also what I will have to pay with my money and how the climate is at Camp California, because I have to decide which clothes to bring. I look forward to your answer.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Clara Mancini</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>People often have very different opinions about shopping. Most women and girls like it, especially when they want to buy clothes and shoes. A man usually is less interested in shopping, maybe because he frequently has to pay what his wife has bought.</P>
      <P>In my opinion, shopping can be interesting in big stores, where you can find everything, or in shops which sell something special or strange. On the contrary, I don't like going to shops where you see only common things, and I hate it when there is a lot of crowd. In this case, you have to stay in long queues, you can't walk without being pulled or pushed, and you often have to spend a hour to buy some soap or a packet of biscuits. Even if you are with a friend, you can't talk, because of the noise and the confusion, and you may find it difficult also to walk close to each other.</P>
      <P>The better thing to do to skip queues and crowd is not to go shopping on Saturdays, but it is not always possible.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
