<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR672*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writting this letter to inform you I had a very disappointing evening during your musical show "Over the rainbow" at the Circle Theatre where you are the director.</P>
      <P>First of all, the actor was expected to be Danny Brook. He is my favourite actor and the most important reason I went to your theatre. But finally, without telling us anything, there was a different actor. This was very disappointing.</P>
      <P>Secondly, your famous restaurant was closed. That was very displeasured because I had planned a romantic dinner with my wife. If you had told me your restaurant was going to be closed, I would have made a reservation anywhere else, but you didn't.</P>
      <P>And finally the play started with a delay of forty-five minutes and there were not discounts available. Both things do not agree with what I read on your advertising sign.</P>
      <P>Due to all of these reasons, I hope you could give my money back.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>MANUEL ALMODAR</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. But I didn't know that when I told her I was thinking in going away from home.</P>
      <P>This was a very difficult decission but I had to take it because of my personal situation, all the time shouting and fighting will all my family.</P>
      <P>Therefore my girlfriend lived alone so I could have stayed with her or just have gone on travelling around the world. I was thinking a lot about this problem and how to solve it so I needed someone to talk to and Pat had always been my best friend.</P>
      <P>But it was a big mistake because she told it to her mother and I don't know how but now my mother know it, and she is very worried about me and my future. And my father thinks a year travelling and living by myself will be very good for me.</P>
      <P>Finally, my parents are all the time argueing about differents solutions to my problem, and this all thanks to Pat.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
