<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR675*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen,</P>
      <P>Thanks you very much for your recent letter. I can not believe that I won the first prize (It's great!) and of course, I am very happy.</P>
      <P>As your questions, I am free to travel only on July because I will having my holiday after finished the exams. And, I have to returned to my university by August.</P>
      <P>I prefer to stay in log cabin rather than in tent because I am not used to with narrow space and feel more comfortable with a place like bedroom.</P>
      <P>Furthermore, I prefer to do painting and photography as my hobbies and my fasinative in art and enjoyed to take a photograph of wildlife.</P>
      <P>Finally, please could you give me an idea what sort of clothes to bring? and how much would be spend there. Also, please advice for any necessary things to prepare and bring.</P>
      <P>I looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>Sorry for I haven't written to you for such a long time, but I've got a good excute!</P>
      <P>Last month, I was partly in the concert teams. It was a big one that I never thougth and I couldn't imagine how amazing was it.</P>
      <P>I didn't know what is my responsible until they called me to trained. What a surprised! and unbelieveable, I was responsible for looking after the pop stars. You might understand how excited I was. But, I've got though it. I have to taken care of them during a break, served a drink, clothes, even brought them some cigaratte and anything they wants. I think they are so hospitality and warm with people around them. You know! because of these are change all my opinions about self-important behavior of superstar.</P>
      <P>The most appreciated was they've given me their latate CD with signature. Marvellous thing! and of couse as you have seen it I've given one to you.</P>
      <P>I hope you're well and enjoyed with CD and don't forget to write back all about your news during my summer holiday job.</P>
      <P>Love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
