<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR679*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I'm writing to you with regard to the letter I've just received as I wish to give you some further information about myself.</P>
      <P>I would rather travel on July because I'm not as busy as on June or August and because in my opinion during July there's excellent weather.</P>
      <P>Regarding the accommodation I would prefer a log cabin because in my opinion tents are very uncomfortable to sleep and they aren't very cozy.</P>
      <P>Regarding the activities I've chosen swimming as I'm very keen on it and I'm fairly good at it, but I expect the water to be as crystal clear. I've also chosen singing. I'm an awful singer, but I would like to learn.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask you for vegetarian food for me as I am a very extrict vegan, and to suggest me what kind of clothes to bring.</P>
      <P>I'm really looking forward to my stay at Camp California and to your response in this regard.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Nuria</P>
      <P>Valverde.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Have you ever asked yourself which lessons or activities should be filmed in the school video? Well, I've just polled some students and here are their responses.</P>
      <P>70% of students think we should film the Speech and Drama lesson because is one of the lessons they enjoy the most.</P>
      <P>The vast majority say Maths and History should be filmed too, because they love these subjects and think they are very interesting and are also great fun.</P>
      <P>60% of students say breaks should be filmed too, because they want to show in the video they can also have fun at school.</P>
      <P>Most of them said Science, English and Literature shouldn't be filmed because they are not very interesting and are also very boring.</P>
      <P>In my opinion I think basketball should be filmed too because is one of the activities the students are very keen on doing and they usually enjoy it.</P>
      <P>But I don't think we should film breaks, because in my opinion everyone knows how breaks are and what students do during them.</P>
      <P>In a nutchel I think Maths, basketball, Speech and Drama, and History should be filmed.</P>
      <P>Nuria Valverde.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
