<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR687*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>17th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>Having seen with two of my friends your musical show last week-end at The Circle Theatre which called "OVER THE RAINBOW", I am writing to complain about our disappointing evening.</P>
      <P>First of all, in your advertisement you refer to discounts that are available, but when we bought our tickets, one of the employees refused to give us 'tickets student price'. Despite being forced to buy adult tickets, we still were excited and took our seat, and waited for the beginning of the show. Usually, the show starts at 19:30, but this time we had to wait until 20:15! In addition to this, it was not the famous actors that you have mentionned in the advertisement, so we were disappointed.</P>
      <P>Concerning the restaurant, it was closed due to transformations. In the result, I am sure you will understand our annoyed and frustrated, so it was not a perfect evening out that your advertisement stated was.</P>
      <P>Finally, I am writing to request a full-refund for my friends and I, because I felt your advertisement was misleading.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>H. Boulard</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>What do you think about what will clothes be like in the future? I'm sure that anyone has already thought about it, because fashionable clothes have always been really important for almost all of us.</P>
      <P>Let's have a look at different points. From the past until now, we have wearing several different fashionable clothes, but why? From my point of view, almost all humans would like to be more and more attractive, so we always think about it. As a result, clothes are the easiest way to be more attractive. In addition to this, anyone will agree with me that clothes are the best invention ever. Furthermore, it's one of the best way to make money.</P>
      <P>Anyway, don't you think that nowadays, fashionable clothes is quite similar than 20 years ago? It's evident that whatever we wear look like clothes, and I think we should stop being so stupid. We can't wearing peculiar clothes like in science fiction films. I bet you that in 100 years, humans will wearing exactly the same clothes as today, because we love the actually fashion of clothes which is wonderful. The last survey about fashion shown that people feel really comfortable with those now!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
