<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR690*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I'm writing in order to make you know how angry I am for having gone to one of your shows.</P>
      <P>I went to London for a week's holiday with some friends and every evening we decided something to do in order to enjoy our staying in that beautiful city.</P>
      <P>I wish we had never chosen your show. In fact, only after having going into the theatre, I realized that the advertisement I had read was probably about another show.</P>
      <P>First of all, when I paid my ticket I noticed that nobody could obtain the discount you'd written about. But that would be nothing if I thought to dinner I had to cancelled because your show started at 20.15, although it should have been at 19.30!</P>
      <P>Besides, when we decided to spend the evening in the theatre restaurant, we were informed that it was closed because the chef was ill.</P>
      <P>At that point, even if there had been Danny Brook as the advertisement announced, it wouldn't have been a less disappointing evening.</P>
      <P>According to all these things, I ask my money back.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets, but I realized it only when it was too late.</P>
      <P>What have moved me to this discover were the facts that happened last month. I had just quarreled with Jon, who is my fiance. In that period we weren't getting on with. So, when Peter, who has been a friend of mine since we were children invited me for a pizza, I accepted without thinking at the consequences.</P>
      <P>And there would have been no problems if I hadn't talked to Pat about that evening. It was only a dinner with a friend and in fact we'd spent all the time remembering our childhood, but probably Pat can have thought that Peter and I weren't only friends. So she ran to Jon in order to make him know the terrible mistake I had made that evening. He became very angry no matter how hard I tried telling him the truth.</P>
      <P>By the way, I've understood I had better trust in nobody.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
