<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR691*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr</P>
      <P>I'm writing to complain about what it happened me two days ago, during you musical show "OVER THE RAINBOW". A friend of mine went to see it the last May. He told me to go because the actor's performance was good.</P>
      <P>So I decided buying a ticket, but no discounts were available. Then with my disappointing I noticed that there was different actor instead of Danny Brook. Nobody informed me about it.</P>
      <P>And why did the show start at 20:15 instead of 19:30?</P>
      <P>After the show, my friends and me decided to go to your restaurant, but we were amazed to find it close.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, I ask for my money back because it wasn't a perfect evening like your advice showed.</P>
      <P>I hope that you understand me.</P>
      <P>Awaiting your reply,</P>
      <P>Your faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>It's true that modern technology has changed our daily life. In the pass, for example, we used to write letters to comunicate, but now we surely send an e-mail, a fax or make a phone.</P>
      <P>Certainly it will be easier and faster than write, but it was nice when you were waiting for a letter. Nowadays, you have all things immediatly and soon, but will it be good? I think no.</P>
      <P>Everyone have to use modern technology carefully, because too much technology could be dangerous. It couldn't allow us to think and to do freely.</P>
      <P>Today there are children that don't know nothing about nature and its things.</P>
      <P>Probably, because their parents haven't enough time to go out the city and show them nature. So they prefer leave their sons wecting TV.</P>
      <P>Modern technology? Yes, but we mustn't loose the values and our free time to stay with our family.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
