<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR692*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you for the amazing inform about the competition. I am really glad to be able to win the first prize and travel to the U.S.A. which I used to dream.</P>
      <P>Now, I would like to reply some questions you need, willingly. At first, I would like to travel only in July because I study at University at the moment. However, they will give me such a long holiday enough to travel for two weeks in June.</P>
      <P>I would prefer staying tents to log cabins, as I'd like to observe nature and stay in outdoor as much time as I can.</P>
      <P>I'm very happy with the activities you organised. I am good at playing basketball, swimming, tennis, surfing as they are my hobbies for donkey's years. I would rather play golf and go sailing, than the others so as to find new hobbies in my life.</P>
      <P>Finally, what I would like to ask is what sort of cloths are suitable for the travelling, and also, how much money I should prepare for the travelling, approximately.</P>
      <P>I would be grateful if you could reply my letter with some further information soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Takashi Oshima.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>How are you going these days?</P>
      <P>I'm fine as usual.</P>
      <P>Anyway, I joined the team which helps anything at a pop concert last month as you know.</P>
      <P>In my view, it was extremely interesting and satisfing for me all the concert long.</P>
      <P>Talking of my work, I had to mostly make the concert stage with some fellows. If you choose the post, you would be exhausted throughlly in the end of the concert. However, there was a particular thing I really liked during the concert. As I could take a rest beside the concert stage while someone was singing a song, I saw a number of famous musicians nearby.</P>
      <P>Although I can not explain any more about the thing I felt during the concert in this letter, I'd like to recomend you to help at a pop concert or the other. It must be a good experience and a special memory for you.</P>
      <P>See you and write me soon.</P>
      <P>Best Wishes</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
