<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR693*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>13th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am satisfied to have received your letter that informed me that I have won the first prize in your competition.</P>
      <P>I am very happy to spend two weeks at Camp California, because I have never gone to U.S.A. I would prefer to travel only in July, because I have not to work and because I would prefer to have accomodation in tent and so I think that july is the best period to spend two weeks in tent. I have just been in tent and I think it is always a beautiful and interested adventure.</P>
      <P>During the journey I would do surfing and photography. I like very much to be alone with nature and when I was a girl, I had gone to a surfing-course for five years and I won a lot of prizes. I like also doing photography because they can be memories IN my future.</P>
      <P>I would receive further information about which kind of clothes I should put off during my holiday and I would know if I should bring with me a lot of money.</P>
      <P>Looking forward to spending my holiday in the USA I wait your letter.</P>
      <P>Your sincerelly</P>
      <P>Guillelmina Farina.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I am afraid that I couldn't write you immediatly, but last month I enjoyed helping at a pop concert and so I am very busy.</P>
      <P>Even if the job was so hard, it was an amused experience. I woke up at six a.m. and I worked until nine p.m. but it isn't a problem for me, because I like spending my time with other people.</P>
      <P>I particularly liked to know people of different countries and some pop-stars, which were friendly with us. I was surprised of the co-operation that there was during the job, because it was as a big family, where each member helped others.</P>
      <P>There was a lot of work to do but we were happy to do it with glad people and at the end we had the possibility to take part in the pop concert. It was wonderful!</P>
      <P>Looking forward to meeting you as soon as possible. I greet you.</P>
      <P>Best wishes</P>
      <P>Guillelmina</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
