<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR695*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ryan,</P>
      <P>I have received your letter and I so happy because I have won the holiday in California. It will be a pleasure for me give you the information that you need.</P>
      <P>First of all I would like to travel in July because I am going to Ibiza with my parents in June and in August I start to work part-time, so I am afraid but I can go only in July.</P>
      <P>With reference to the accommodation I would prefer log cabins to tents. I think the log cabins are more comfortable and I have never slept in a tents.</P>
      <P>I am very good at playing basketball. When I was a child I used to play daily with my classmates and now I am playing at least at the weekend. I have taken a Photography course and I enjoy taking photos to animals.</P>
      <P>I would like to know, how much I need and what type of clothes I should take? Could you tell me about the weather, please?</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I hope you are very well. I am writing about my exciting experience at a pop concert.</P>
      <P>First of all I was too busy but it does not matter because I enjoyed a lot of this experience. I was doing different activities from designering flier to selling tickets.</P>
      <P>I had to search in the internet pictures that could be used for the flier. We booked the accommodation for the group. I was responsible for checking the light and sound. In addition I checked the e-mail dialy and answered the phone. As you know I sold tickets in some schools and pubs, too.</P>
      <P>Anyway, it has been one of the most wonderful experience in my life, but the concert day was really amazing. I think this was the best of all. I feel really happy that I participated in this event.</P>
      <P>If you have the opportunity of involving in something like this you do not hesitate.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
