<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR696*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>17th December 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Sirs,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about my awful evening at the Circle Theatre. I am very disappointed.</P>
      <P>Last week I went to see a musical show called 'OVER THE RAINBOW' at the Circle Theatre.</P>
      <P>I was first, very excited to see the show, because on the advertisement it said that it is the best musical in London. Also it said that I can have a perfect evening at there, but it turned out to be a very disappointing evening.</P>
      <P>I went to see my favourite actor Danny Brook acting in the show, but he was not there. I was shocked. There was another man acting. The show started late then I expected. It should be from 7,30 p.m, but it was from 8.15 p.m.!</P>
      <P>I want to complain about the ticket. On the advertisement it said that discounts are availble, but when I asked a staff in the theatre about the discount he didn't offer me one. After the show I went the 'THEATRE RESTAURANT' to have dinner, but the restaurant was closed. It was because they closed early than usual. I think they should keep the times correctly.</P>
      <P>I am very disappointed with everything what happened last week.</P>
      <P>I would like a refund.</P>
      <P>I excpect this will be possible.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Fashion of the Future by XXX 17/6/00</P>
      <P>My article is about fashion in. future</P>
      <P>Right now in 2000 many people are wearing modern clothes. Like wearing T-shirts, trousers, skirts, coats, long-sleeved shirts, jumpers, etc. They also wear little items on them to go with their clothes. Like earings, necklaces, bracelets, rings, glasses, hairbands, hand bags, shoes, watches, etc. They like designers clothes and everyone wear different modern clothes in size, in colour and in shapes.</P>
      <P>The fashion gradually changed from the old days and it is still changing to the future. Maybe in 100 years from now, fashion will be totally different. Everyone may think that in future people will wear silver clothes like in space movies.</P>
      <P>I think everyone will wear balloons for clothes in future. Every one will wear very colourful balloons on them. With balloon clothes they will be able to fly up in the sky.</P>
      <P>Everyone will not walk on roads. They will bounced on roads with there balloon clothes.</P>
      <P>In future they will wear balloon clothes, because to make people fly. They will use a special gas inside balloons to make them fly.</P>
      <P>For the special gas they will mix carbon dioxide and some chemicals. This special gas will be not dangerous. If we use up carbon dioxide with balloon clothes there will be less carbon dioxide on Earth, so there is no worry about Ozone breaking. This is one more reason to wear balloon clothes in future. It is to save our Earth.</P>
      <P>Would you like to wear balloon clothes and bounce around the world?</P>
      <P>If yes, wait until 2100s!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
