<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR697*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>17.06.2000</P>
      <P>Hello Sir,</P>
      <P>"Um very unpleased that I have to write you this letter. I have to do this because things happened which I can't ignore and which disappointed me very much.</P>
      <P>On the 12th of June this year I went to London to visit a friend of mine. We had a great time together until we decided to visit the musical "Over the Rainbow" in the "Circle Theater". We went there at 19.00 o'clock to get some tickets, but when we arrived, a long line of people were standing there, waiting to get tickets. After we waited for half an hour to get two spare seat tickets, we had to wait 45 minutes until it started. One of the points because, I wanted to see the musical was my favourite actor Danny Brook, but he didn't play! So when the miserable musical came to his end, we were happy to leave the theater room, but we both wanted to have dinner in the theatre restaurant, because no restaurantes were opened anymore, because it started too late. So we went upstairs to find the restaurant, but we just a big empty hall, with nothing in it, with a short sign on a door: "Sorry, we are closed because of renovations"! We thought it would be a joke, but it wasn't. Because you are the manager, I think you are the only person who can change something. I would prefer getting my money back, instead of taking a lawyer. I will never visit your theatre again!</P>
      <P>Sincerely</P>
      <P>Hedwiga Heinkel</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. And we knew that from the day on, that he knows anything about our secret we will live in danger being caught. We, that were Tim, Gudrun, Paul and me Hedwiga had founded our own mafia, we were the kings in our small town, and we had a lot of people paying us money, so that we won't attack them. We had this idea first, when we watched a movie about the Italian mafia in an English lesson in school. It was love of first slight and we were fascinated by the thought, building a kind of the same organisation in our town. Pat was my big brother, who had heaed of some people paying, "safty-money", but never know the reason, until he found a big amout of money in my room. His thoughts combined and ready to go to the police he went out of our house, where me and my homies were just hanging aroud. He saw me and tolled me into my face you are a thief and a burglar and I will go now to the police, I didn't know what to do,but then I had an idea.... Yeah fokes, that was the point I got interupted by my parents in this beautiful dream, but when you will hear the end of my story than buy the "Rossall-School-magazin", net time again, and you will hear the end of this unbelievable story.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
