<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR699*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>June. 13. 2000</P>
      <P>Competition Organization.</P>
      <P>Dear Sir or Madamme,</P>
      <P>I'd appriciate the first prize in the competition. It's my pleasure to give you some information and I'd like to ask you about the Camp California.</P>
      <P>First of all, I'd like to travel only in July because I'm supposed to be a volunteer in the Music festival, held in August.</P>
      <P>Additionally, I'd rather stay in tents as I've never slept in tents before. Therefore it'll be a great experience for me.</P>
      <P>I'd like to choose swimming and photography as activities. I go swimming three times a week so I have no problem with swimming. I'm also the member of photography club at my university and really keen on taking a picture of nature.</P>
      <P>By the way, I'm wondering what kinds of clothes I should prepare and how much much I should bring with myself. I'll look forward to hearing answers from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>YEUN-Ja. HONG</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>The suggestion about making a short video.</P>
      <P>Introduction</P>
      <P>The aim of this report is to summerize the result of the survey, which is about making a short video.</P>
      <P>The survey was done to 300 students, who are between 18-28, at our school.</P>
      <P>Prefered lessons.</P>
      <P>The 70% of students said that the acting lesson should be filmed as the students, attending this lesson, are not only excited but also very active. Additionally, 15% of students answered they want the presentation lesson to be filmed. The reason why they choose this lesson is that every student in their turn of presentation does his or her best.</P>
      <P>Prefered activities.</P>
      <P>The soccer game, played every Monday, was ranked in the most favorite activity by 45% students. They said the soccer game enable them to get together and have fun. However, the girls'd rather play table tennis or badminton. Hicking activity was chosen by 20% students, followed by the soccer.</P>
      <P>Conclusion.</P>
      <P>To sum up, according to the survey, it's obvious that more than half of students want acting lesson to be filmed. Moreover, it seems that the students prefer the soccer play to be filmed.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
