<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR59*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs. Helen Ryan.</P>
      <P>It was so great to hear that I had won first prize. It would be meaningful in my life to take part in your camp. I am writing to reply about your questions.</P>
      <P>I am wondering that I will be only able to travel in July, because I have to finish my first year at the university. It finishes 29th of June. In addition to this, I have already resistered another course which starts from 2nd of August.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I would prefer living in tents, I always admire outdoors life. Finally, I would like to surging and golf. In case of surfing, I have never had an experience, I am absolutely beginner. On the other hand, I used to play golf with my father. When I was 14, I won the competition.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask about Camp California. Let me know if I have to take which kind of clothes and how much money I need. It would be very helpful.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Your sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Hi. How are you? I am fine. Thanks for your letter. I want to let you know about my experience as you wanted.</P>
      <P>Well, last month, I worked at a pop concert. It was fantastic because I could see Madonna. My main job was to tide up her dressing room. Can you imagine? You are working with your idea woman, I can't still belive that I spoke with her.</P>
      <P>Anyway, the most important thing was that I had good experience. If we had worked together we would have had a good time. It's pity, isn't it? Now, I know how difficult to sing in front of the audience and behind the start there are a lot of the people who help the performance.</P>
      <P>Next time, I hope that we'll work together. Let's find some information to get a job. Shall we?</P>
      <P>I have to go now. I am fed up with studying, but I have to. I hope that you'll be alright.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>With lots of love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
