<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR60*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>I'm so happy that I've won 2 weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A. At first I couldn't belive that I was a winer</P>
      <P>I would like to travel at the Camp in July, if is possible. This is just one months which I've fee.</P>
      <P> I'm a student. My school starsts in September and it finishes in June. July is months when I'm having a rest and I'm doing nothing. In August I'm working in the shop which is my sister. If I could go in July would be greate.</P>
      <P>I can sleep in tent, it would remain me a good time which I'd spent with my friends a few years ago. I'm not scared of darkness, rain, cold or hot whether. I'm sure would be good fun; sleep next to each other telling scared story. Is good for make friends, you can know them better doing everything together.</P>
      <P>Also I know that I have the chance to do two activities while I'm at the Camp. I would like to choose basketball. This is sport which I "love". I play basketball since I was 12. Some of my friends say that I'm very good player, but I don't think so.</P>
      <P>Another sport which I'd like to do is swimming. In swimming I'm not as good as in basketball, but I'd like to practise more and maybe learn something new about it.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask you, what sort of clothes shall I take with me? I don't want take too much; jeans, jumper, swimming costium, T-shirt, sports shoes I think should b O.K.</P>
      <P>Know, I can just wait for July</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Hi Kim!</P>
      <P>How are you? I'm fine. I'm so exited. Last month I was helping at a pop concert with a few friends of mine. It was Tina Turner concert! To this moment when I'm thinking of it I want shout.</P>
      <P>At first I was helping to seill the tickets - wasn't difficult. Anyway, four hours, before concert had started, I was helping with lights. We had to check evey plug, switch, lights. I couldn't belive how big the lamp can be. That's why singers are hot. When concert had started and Tina cam out I forget about lights, just I was looking at her. fortunetly nothing had happend. Every-thing was O.K</P>
      <P>After concert we were invited in backstage. then I could see her very, very clear.</P>
      <P>Just people who was helping and organizating this concert could meet her. Some of them were speaking with her, I wasn't this lucky person, but still I'm happy, that I could be thear.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
