<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR61*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Madam</P>
      <P>I am writing to answer the informations that you need from me.</P>
      <P>First I would like to thank you for doing this competition and I would also like to thank you for the prize.</P>
      <P>Answering your questions, I would like to travel only en July because this is the month of my vacations. In July I will be free to travel anywhere I please.</P>
      <P>According to your letter I have two options of accommodation, or in tents or log cabins. I would prefer in tents because I think that is something more exciting and new for me. I never stayed in tents in the middle of nowhere, in my life so I would prefer something more realistic and new. Log cabins may be more confortable, on the other hand I think that I will be able to "survive" in tents. Looking to your letter, I can see many options of activities and I realized that I like most of them. I think I would prefer Climbing and Painting. The reason of choosing this two activities is that they contrast itselves, I want one more exciting and that asks for more agility and another more calm and relaxing, that asks only for my ability to paint. Climbing is something new for me and I am not so good on that, however I wish that I can learn about it on the Camp. Painting is something that I love and I am very good doing it.</P>
      <P>I have some doubts about my prize and travel. Is there a possibility that you send me a list of material and clothes that I have to take?</P>
      <P>Is all the travel already paid including food and meals, or I have to bring some money?</P>
      <P>Do I have to bring something especial for the tents and camping?</P>
      <P>Please answer my letter as soon as is possible.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully,</P>
      <P>GUSTAV SOARES.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>How are you? Is everything good in USA?</P>
      <P>I'm writing to you because I had a wonderful experience last month.</P>
      <P>There was a concert of a famous band here in my city. I vish you were here with me. So, I went with my friend to the concert with a lot of fans. We bought tickets to the show and also to the fan's bus. Yes, there is a bus that take you to the concert and bring you back.</P>
      <P>The concert was going to start at 22:00 and the bus arrived at my house at 18:00. When we entered inside of it, we saw a lot of fans using T-shirts, caps and shouting, "Almendegos, Almendegos..." (that is the name of the band).</P>
      <P>AT 20:00, we stopped in a coffee house to eat. The shouted: "20:30 you all have to be back because the bus will leave."</P>
      <P>We sat and started to eat and talk. Suddenly a man came and started to tell us his adventures. They were very interesting and we liked him so much. After a few minutes (I fought were few) I realized that the coffee house was empty. I looked to my watch: 20:45. The bus had left about fifteen minutes. The man offered a ride. We accept. You can not imagine how dissapointed I were with my ownself.</P>
      <P>When we arrived the concert had already began. When we were running to enter a man called us. He was helping to put the materials of the concerts (microphone...) on the stage. He asked if we could help. We answered: "Yes!"</P>
      <P>We started to put everthing on the stage and after this we realized that the band was entering into the stage near us.</P>
      <P>By my side the vocal of the Almendegos was and he touched my arm. I will never wash my arm again. After all of this we saw the show in the best place, near of the stage and after, the thing that I most liked, we were convidated to see the group and had their signatures.</P>
      <P>That was the best night of my life.</P>
      <P>I wish that you liked my experience.</P>
      <P>Kisses,</P>
      <P>GUSTAV.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
