<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR62*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Ryan,</P>
      <P>I received your letter and I am very glad I have won a two weeks travel to Camp California. I will give you some information which helps you to know me better.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel to camp in July because this is the best time for me and I hope for you. I will be very busy in June so let me tell you some details about my travel. About accommodation, I think tents would be great.</P>
      <P>Basketball and swimming I think are the best for the children. Basketball will help children to build team character and leadership. And swimming is very good for health. I swim really good and I am a proffesional basketball player. I count on my experience.</P>
      <P>And there are few questions I would like to ask. First, what clothes should I take with me, secondly. how much money and by cash or by travel cards. Thanks!</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to our meeting.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Vasiliy Alekseyev.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>Last month I enjoyed helping at concert of "Modern Talking'' and now I want to share with you about my experience.</P>
      <P>It all started when one of the organizers asked me to help him at a concert of my favorite band. And what do you think I answered? Of course, yes!</P>
      <P>I have got very responsible work I had to bring food for Peter Bolen and Tomas Anders. Can you imagine? I came into their room and give hot Cheeseburgers, Coca-Cola and ice-cream to Peter. It was the happiest moment of my life. He asked me was the cheeseburger hot and I answered that it was. I was very nervous talking with him. He told me about concert programme and gave me his photo with a sign.</P>
      <P>I will never forget that summer day. It was my day, I am sure about it.</P>
      <P>Well, I think that is all. See you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>Vasiliy.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
