<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR66*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I have come to watch the musical show called 'Over The Rainbow' in the Circle Theatre. I was really disappointed because a lot of things were not done. I will explain these now and want to ask to get some of the money I have given you back.</P>
      <P>It was written that Danny Brook and Tina Truelove were starring in the show. Danny Brook was not there, a different actor was in his place. That was very disappointing for me.</P>
      <P>The musical show was going to start at 19.30, but it started t 20:15. We have waited for 45 minutes getting bored for it to start!</P>
      <P>When I went to buy tickets, they didn't accept the discounts. But I had read that the discounts were available.</P>
      <P>Like it was written again, we went to visit the theatre restaurant after the show, but it was closed. They said that the time was late and they wanted to go home. There was nothing for us to do, the show started 45 minutes later.</P>
      <P>Now, I think that you have seen it was not a perfect evening at all, a lot of things written were not done So I am asking to get some of my money back.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>DAILY LIFE - MODERN TECHNOLOGY</P>
      <P>MY daily life. I get up early in the morning, go to school, then come home and do what I would like to do. I go shopping, watch TV, walk around the city, use my computer and get lost in Internet. etc.</P>
      <P>Modern technology is everywhere in my life. I don't see it in a normal day, but when I sit and think, its everywhere!</P>
      <P>For example, I get up whenever I want using my watch or clock. It's not a good example for modern technology, but it's a piece of technology at last!</P>
      <P>TV was black and white at first and there were only two or three channels. Now it's colourful and there are many channels on TV. You watch whichever you want. I can't think that I watch the same channels every day.</P>
      <P>A wonderful example for modern technology: Computer! It is not a living thing but it has a brain. It knows more than most of the people.</P>
      <P>And Internet. You can look for everything you want. You can talk to every people living all around the world. You don't understand the time passing when you are in that world. You can have information about all the things, go everywhere. Everything is near you. You can reach them whenever you want!</P>
      <P>You see, our daily life consists of modern technology. It would be hard to live without it.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
