<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR68*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>London, June 17th</P>
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I'm writing to you to make complaints for the very disappointing evening I had at the Circle Theatre.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I found that there were no discounts as it was announced in the advertisement.</P>
      <P>Then, I not only had to wait 45 minutes more than it was expected for the beginning of the show but I realised that the main actor had been replaced by another one (very bad) as well. Of course I must tell you that the strongest reason for my going to see the show was Danny Brook's presence.</P>
      <P>Finally, after the show, I went to the theatre restaurant just to find that it was closed and the friend I had asked to meet me there was not waiting for me. As if that was not enough he thought I had been kidding, inviting him to a closed restaurant where I didn't appear.</P>
      <P>Those were the reasons for my asking a refund of the £20 I paid.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Every day we find out new devices that promise us to satisfy our needs. I usually don't buy a lot of them but I must recognise that some of them are useful.</P>
      <P>I can't remember waking up with the alarm-clock, making a hand-made orange juice or heating water for the coffee. Therefore, I have more spare time to enjoy the one I consider as the most important influence technology had in my life: the computer and Internet.</P>
      <P>The improvement of electronics and global communications has made it possible to know places, look for information or even keep close contact with friends all over the world.</P>
      <P>Now, I will never say again that I don't know where can I find some information about this or that and when on holidays or every time I make a new friend, I just ask for the email and that's enough to know we will know about each other soon.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
