<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR70*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson</P>
      <P>I am writing in the name of the whole class. First of al, I want to thank you for the interesting programme, which you already have organised. It is very good, especially the Sightseeing tour by bus.</P>
      <P>This is a great opportunity because as you know most people of our class are going to work in this sector so it will be very interesting for everybody and also a kind of education.</P>
      <P>Instead of going to the Science Museum on Tuesday morning we thought we could postpone it to Wednesday afternoon. The shopping could be done after the river trip to Greenwich but only if we have enough time.</P>
      <P>I hope you will agree with our suggestion and if you have any further questions do not hesistate to contact me.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Will the home of the future really look different? It's quite difficult to say, but of course there will be a change.</P>
      <P>For example if you look back into the forties and compare the home with nowadays you can see that it has become more modern, especially the facilities in the kitchen and in the livingroom.</P>
      <P>in the future it could be that you don't have to prepare your breakfast by your own, perhaps you just have to press a button when your alarm clock has gone. In addition to this you may have some roboters bringing the newspaper at the table, tidying up the house, doing the shopping and maybe they are also your living patners.</P>
      <P>The place to spend the night will still be the bed. The livingroom won't get any big changes although the televisions, stereos and videos will become more modern and perhaps more difficult.</P>
      <P>In general we can say the huge change we already had, but who knows exactly what the future will bring to us?</P>
      <P>Let's have a surprise?</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
