<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR71*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs. Ryan</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter which I have just received this morning. I am really appreciated to hear that I have won first prize in the competition - two weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A. I am writing this letter to inform you more information about myself.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel only in July because I will have a summer holiday for 2 months at that time. I would prefer the accommodation at Camp California in tents because it would be nice to spend the time living in tents with a nice environment and fresh air. Also I would like to do two activities while I am at the Camp which are swimming and photography. Photography is quite interesting for me to take a photograph in the place where I have never been to. Swimming is quite nice activity to relax and work out. It is really enjoyable to keep my body fit and healthy by swimming.</P>
      <P>Anyway, I would like to know that how many people are joining at this Camp. Could you please tell me about the clothes I should take?</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Boonsri Thanasukolwit.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim</P>
      <P>Thanks for your last letter. I'm really sorry, it's taken me so long to reply. How are you doing? I hope that you can get on well with your roommate.</P>
      <P>Anyway, I enjoyed helping at a pop concert last month. I and my friend - Emma, we helped to paint the scence of the background on the stage. As you known, I like drawing and painting when I have a free time so that why I chose to paint the scence of the background. I really enjoyed painting it and it looked very nice. And I particularly liked the experience that I helped to screen and paint a picture of "Bon Jovi" on every T-shirts which are given to the audiences. I felt that it was a great time in my life.</P>
      <P>However, I told my teacher that I am willing to give a hand next time. Are you willing to give a hand next time? If you are, I'll tell you in advance. I must stop writing now as I have a lot of homework to do.</P>
      <P>Best wishes</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
