<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR72*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>Ref: Over the rainbow musical show.</P>
      <P>I am writing to you to mention some problems about the musical show shown in your theatre.</P>
      <P>First of all, it was supposed to be starring Danny Brook and Tina Truelove but in a real show, it wasn't. Because I'm big fan of them, if was pretty much boring without them and not to mention that it was disappointing.</P>
      <P>It didn't start at 19:30 and there was a delay for 45 minutes which was quite a long time and everyone got frustrated.</P>
      <P>The tickets also caused a problem. Discounts weren't available at all. Moreover the testament was till under the construction so that we couldn't use it when we were extlemely hungry.</P>
      <P>Finally, I wonder why you didn't ask for the money back if you have guaranteed the perfect evening.</P>
      <P>I am therefore writing to you to ask for the money back as I didn't get any advantages or services from you.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>L. P. Lou</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Technology has been developed extremely fast these days and as it is still going on, it can't help affecting our lives.</P>
      <P>One of the biggist thing has changed is a change in a method of communications. People have invented such things like TV, radio, telephones and so on which made us enable to hear the news quickly and stay in touch with people easily.</P>
      <P>There are also changes in biological areas. Nearly almostdisease except only a few like AIDS. It helped us to live longer and make us stronger against them.</P>
      <P>I have mentioned few changes above but there's still a biggist one left which is about computer areas. It helped us to be able to work much more quicker and accurately than before with the help of Internet.</P>
      <P>Basically modern technology has changed our life more comfortably but there are some disadvantages such as lack of friendship, togetherness because of people staying in their house being on the Internet for whole day. But we still have to admit that we can't live without them even they give us some disadvantages.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
