<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR73*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter. I was pleasantly surprised that I have won the first prize in your competition.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I would like to answer your questions. As I am doing my A-levels exams at the moment and they continue until the 30th of June and my further studies start in August, I can only travel in July. I would prefer to stay in a tent. It will give me an adventure feeling and I have always prefered tents to log cabins. I enjoy basketball very much and I am quite good at it. I would like to play this game at your camp. I have never tried out climbing, but I have always wished to do it one day. Would it be possible to do this activity at your camp as a beginner?</P>
      <P>Secondly, I would like to ask you for some information. Would you be kind enough to tell me which kind of clothes I should bring with me? Could you possibly tell me how much money I might spend at California Camp? Would you recommend me to bring some equipment, like a rope, sticks, with me?</P>
      <P>Thank you in advance for your help. I look forward to receiving your prompt reply.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>Hi, how are you? I'm actually fine at the moment, but have to study a lot because of my exams in English.</P>
      <P>You asked me to wite about my experience which I made by helping at the pop-concert. And I can say it was terrific! My job was actually to listen to Tim and do whatever he said. This included to clean up the rooms which were used by the singers and put some equipment on the stage. Tim was in charge of organising this concert. I had never been behind the stage before and you know the rooms, in which singers dress and make-up, are actually small. Can you imagine, I could stay at this concert without paying anything! And I managed to speak to Ricky Martin out of stage. O.K., I actually asked him only: 'How are you?' and he gave me his signature. He was fantastic, you know that he is my favourite singer. I think this was my best job as a student in Cambridge. Probably it wasn't so nice to do jobs which you were told to do, but you see many stars out of stage. And you might manage to speak to some pop-stars. Beside this, I earned some money, not a lot but enough for me.</P>
      <P>Well I'll have to close now. Give my regards to your parents. Looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>With love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
