<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR75*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>16/12/2000</P>
      <P>Dear Jane Clark,</P>
      <P>First of all, I'd like you to know that the whole organization was nearly excellent. I spent two nice days at the festival full of art.</P>
      <P>The idea of making the festival "international" was very good. I could find the opportunity to watch the artists from different countries, but there could have been stars from more than 6 countries. The jazz, classical and rock concerts were great despite some of the concert halls were too small. Plays and films I watched were also excellent, but more could be on the stage next year. I joined the art exhibitions and saw interesting pictures. The dance shows made sight for our sour eyes, they were really fascinating. I learned so many things about the writers and their ideas, their life styles by talking to them. Beyond all these, the application of joining all activities by one nice-pricednice ticket was excellent; because it saved you from buying one ticket for each activity. Next year, I think you should increase the number of shows, concerts and others, also the time spent at the festival (for example: at least 5 days), then everything would be perfect.</P>
      <P>Thank you for making a great festival which made all the art activities come together.</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Jennifer,</P>
      <P>I'm glad that everything's going on well there. It's the same here. I've got too many exams nowadays, but that's all. By the way, it would be better If you wrote quite often to me.</P>
      <P>The things you wrote about the rules made me think for a long time and I understood that some really don't make any sense! The more you obey the rules, the better person you are! Our school is really very diciplined, especially about our clothes and behaviours. I understand the second part, but I can't get the reason of wearing in white an dark blue only. Do we become the "perfect one" then? Then again, we have to obey all these rules. It can be said that I'm much more free at home. I'm allowed to do whatever I want at my room. I can't go out at nights easily, but that is not something that I mind about. There are three main things that are very important for my family: respect, honesty and trust. I think I show these three to them.</P>
      <P>Don't ever forget to write to me, okay?</P>
      <P>Love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
