<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR76*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>I have just received your letter and I am writing in response of your questions.</P>
      <P>I can travel only in july because is the only month of this year that I will be available because I finish school in june so I will be very busy and in August I start to study at the University, so july is the best month for me to travel.</P>
      <P>Accommodation for me is not problem. I am very easy going and I will be satisfied wherever. But if I have to choose, I prefer sleep in tents, because when I travel I usually sleep in that kind of accommodation so, for me they seem very comfortable.</P>
      <P>I would like to do the following activities:</P>
      <P>- Tennis because is my favourite sport and I enjoy playing it.</P>
      <P>I play tennis since I was a child and I have won some competitions in my town so I think I play very well.</P>
      <P>- Climbing because I have never climbed in my life and it is a dream for me to do that.</P>
      <P>I am a terrible climber but with a little bit of help I think I can enjoy the activity and have a good time unforgettable.</P>
      <P>I wonder to know what kind of clothes I have to wear because I don't know how the weather is in U.S.A. Also I would like to know how much money I have to bring to the trip.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hear from you as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Hello Kim:</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter it was great to hear from you.</P>
      <P>Sorry but I haven't written you because I've been very busy.</P>
      <P>Last month I helped at a pop concert, it was marvellous. I have a friend and she knows that I speak English so she offered to me work with an English singer so I said "yes, of course". But you can't imagine who was the singer, it was Sting, can you imagine? You know, he is my favourite singer.</P>
      <P>My job was very easy I had to help Sting in everything, for example if he wanted water, I had to give to him water, it was marvellous. He was very kind to me, we talked many things and after the concert he invited all the team to have a dinner, yes I know what you're thinking, "Dinner and Sting" yes my friend it was the best thing in my life. I understood everything he said and Sting said to me that I spoken very well English. The best thing was I spoke in English because I was forgetting it and I met my favourite singer.</P>
      <P>I hope my friend call me again to work because I had a wonderful time and it was a great and unforgettable experience.</P>
      <P>I hope you are O.K. and write soon.</P>
      <P>Lots of Love</P>
      <P>P.D. I send you an autograph that Sting wrote for you.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
