<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR77*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I have read your advertisement for the show and I went to the theatre to see it but I had a very disappointing evening.</P>
      <P>In your advertisement, said that one of the actor was Danny Brook but it was a different actor. This was very disappointing and I believe that all the people there, were angry.</P>
      <P>The musical show must have been started at half past seven but it started at quarter past eight.</P>
      <P>About the tickets, I the advertisement said that discounts would be available but it would not.</P>
      <P>Also the theatre restaurant was closed and I do not know why. When I read the advertisement, it said that the restaurand would be opened.</P>
      <P>Lastly, I want to tell you that I had not a perfect evening and I would be grateful if you could send me my money back.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to your answer.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat was not very good at keeping secrets. Pat was my best friend. She lived next to my house and we went to the same school. I told her all my problems and I could rely on her.</P>
      <P>One day I heard my mother to tell my father that she want to divorce because she can't live with him any more.</P>
      <P>When I heard it, I went to my room and I was crying. I called Pat to come to my house because I was not very good and to tell her what had happened.</P>
      <P>Few minutes later Pat came to my house and I told her that my parents are going to divorce. Pat did not believe me and she started to ask why. I told her that I did not know.</P>
      <P>She helped me to forget it for a few minutes, she made me to laugh and the she left. But before she left I begged her not to tell anybody.</P>
      <P>The other morning I went to school and all the students came next to me and told me not to be mad because of my parents.</P>
      <P>Then I realised that Pat told my secret and I felt very angry, that's why I said at the beginning that Pat was not very good at keeping secrets.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
