<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR94*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Robertson,</P>
      <P>I have been asked by my classmates to write to you to suggest a new activity which you could include in the London programme if you liked it.</P>
      <P>We are very grateful to you for these three days that we are going to spend in the English capital, especially because you planned very interesting and different kinds of things to do for all us.</P>
      <P>However, all we agree that we would like to introduce a visit to the London Fashion and Leisure Show in the Central Exhibition Hall of London in the trip organisation. I am sure that, if you allow us to go, we are going to enjoy it a lot, to learn new topics about the English culture and have an opportunity to communicate ourselves with all those professional.</P>
      <P>It is a very good chance to join this exhibition to see all the new fashion tendences, the latest hairstyles and make up as all we came from many different countries and have not the same customs either.</P>
      <P>And another important thing to consider is that for the students the tickets are free.</P>
      <P>As the show is held on Tuesday from 10:00 to 19:00 we could go there instead of doing shopping in the afternoon. By this way, we would visit the museum as you had planned and n Wednesday afternoon we could use the free time to do some shopping if we wished it.</P>
      <P>Well, that is all I wanted to tell you. We do hope you like our suggestion and we can have an agreement to join the fashion exhibition.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerelly,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Do famous people, such as politicians and film stars, deserve to have a private life without journalists following them all the time?</P>
      <P>Some people think that they should. They are human beings actually and they need to keep a little bit of pirvacity and freedom in their lifes to continue like normal people, to feel that they are unknown and anonymus and they do not have to wear sunglasses, hats or caps every time they want to go out home not to be recognised..</P>
      <P>This is supposed to make them happier...</P>
      <P>Nevertheless, if the famous are known everywhere in the world it is because of the people, if they appear often on TV or in films it is because of their popularity, a popularity which has given to them by all us.</P>
      <P>So they need to become famous to be what they want and if the people don't know them, they are forgotten, they die...</P>
      <P>To sum up I would like to say that for me is very difficult which group has the reason but, by the moment, we should try to respect each other and go in the other's soul to feel like them in those moments we cannot understand them.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
