<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR700*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I'm writing to you to complain about my deceiveful experience at your theatre last Saturday night.</P>
      <P>What I thought it was going to be a wonderful night became into the worst night at the theatre I've ever had.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I must admit that when we realised the main character had been changed we felt really disappointed. This is because I had been waiting to enjoy Danny Brook's performance since I saw him the first time on television.</P>
      <P>Secondly, despite of your advertisement of the possibility of discounts, when I showed my student identity card to one of your employes she angrily told me that I had to pay the whole prize.</P>
      <P>Moreover, not only had the actor been changed but also the musical show started forty five minutes late.</P>
      <P>In my opinion you ought to be more serious because of the commitent you have with the people who comes to your theatre.</P>
      <P>Finally, at the end of the night we felt a bit hungry but we couldn't eat until arriving home due to your restaurant new cooker illness.</P>
      <P>The truth is the night wasn't my perfect night out as you have announced so I would appreciate if you could give my money back.</P>
      <P>I wait to receiving a prompt answer from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets.</P>
      <P>I had always thought that I could rely on her whatever my problem was. Yet, one extremly hot day while I was pacefully walking by the sea and thinking about my own problems I discovered my elder brother's girlfriend with another boy.</P>
      <P>At first I felt really annoyed and disappointed so I run to my brother in order to explain him what I had seen.</P>
      <P>Nevertheless, when I found him studying harder for his final exams I realised I would rather her girlfriend explained my poor brother the truth.</P>
      <P>But the thing is I needed to speak to someone about the fact so I could feel more relaxed.</P>
      <P>I didn't know who explain it to but actually I decided that if I needed to tell someone a secret I would trust an my best friend Pat.</P>
      <P>So, the next day, I nervously came to Pat's appartment where she had been living on her own since she was eighteen.</P>
      <P>After that, she felt completely sad because of the love she had been feeling for my brother for several years and she swore me that she was going to tell it to nobody.</P>
      <P>However, the truth was that not sooner had I arrived home than my brother asked me crying why I had told his girlfriend's affair to Pat instead of discovering him the truth.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
