<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR703*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Jones,</P>
      <P>I'm writting this letter to inform you about the disappointing evening I had when I visited the Circle theatre.</P>
      <P>Firstly In the advertisement you said that the actor would be Danny Brook but there was a different actor in the show and I was really disappointed, because I was really looking forward to seeing Danny Brook which I personally admire.</P>
      <P>Secondly the play didn't start at 19:30 as we were being told but it started with a delay of 45 minutes. Also when I visited the theatre's restaurant I found it closed because of renovation.</P>
      <P>Finally there were no discounts available in the tickets. All the above made my night terribly disappointing and I must say that the advertisement is nothing but a business fraud, so I'm in the unpleasant position to ask my money back. I'm looking forward to your reply</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Mrs Lemmings.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Technology is an essential part in people's life. It's something absoletuly necessary for every action people does It effects us both positive and negative. It's a part of our lifes. Firstly technology has created a bond between myself and my computer. I got used to spending 2-3 hours in front of the computer. My relationship with my family and friends doesn't even exist. I've end up being a T.V addict</P>
      <P>Also the need of doing simple things as a family is no longer the case. Why going to the countryside if you can sit there with a bowl of popcorns and watch T.V.</P>
      <P>Despite the negative effects, technology can effect with a positive way a person's life. Air conditions, watches, computers, and many other things have made my life easier. There's no need on going to the shops when I can order things by the computer. Air conditions also makes my life easier</P>
      <P>In addition technology has made my life easier but it's also an intrude in my life crating a distance between myself and my family. In my opinion technology is the least thing I could use in my life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
