<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR704*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Robertson:</P>
      <P>I'm writing you representing all the english class in order to let you know how exciting we are about the trip to London and to give you some ideas of other things we are interresting on doing in London while we're there.</P>
      <P>First of all, we'd like to thank you for the programme you all ready arrange it's wonderful, because it covers most of our interrests. But also we would like to visit The London Fashion and Leisure show that will be held at the Central kExhibition hall on Tuesday March 14 from 10:00 - 19:00. So we suggest to put it this way on Tuesday 14, in the morning go to the Science Museum and instead of shopping, we could attend the London Fashion show, because will be the latest fashion, leisure and sports wear, make up, and hair styles, and as you know us, we love all those topics, and it's a great opportunity while we are London.</P>
      <P>Thank you for your time, and We're looking forward to hearing from your opion.</P>
      <P>faithfully yours</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>IT WAS DANGEROUS, BUT I KNEW I HAD TO DO IT...BECAUSE</P>
      <P>Since always I'd gotten the idea of travel abroad and experiece others people's life and cultures, so I decided to go to Paris as soon as I finished university.</P>
      <P>I arrived in Paris for New Years Eve 2000 without a place to stay, not speaking any French, alone and with a little amount of money. But eventhough all of these desadventages above, I was folling my dreams and objectives and inspite of everything I was going to do it.</P>
      <P>So suddenly, a week later I found me a job as an au pair, taking care of two little girls that only spoke french at that moment. It took me three months to overcame the languages and after this time the whole familly falled in love with me, that when they decided to move to London, they invited me and now we all live here and I feel like part of the familly, eventhough It was very hard at the beggining.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
