<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR705*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr,</P>
      <P>I am a foreign student who is on holidays here. I am going to stay here a week. I went to your theatre three days ago and it was horrible. I'm sorry but I am very dissapointed with the musical show. I would like to explain you my experience because I want you to give my money back.</P>
      <P>The last Monday, I went to the theatre with two friends. We arrived on time but the musical show was delayed untill half-pass eight. Moreover, we hadn't any disscount for beeing students.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, the main actor was changed for another and nobody told us. When there was a restful we went to the restaurant which was closed because it was late. We couldn't have a drink. Well I believe that it was a bad day but I would like you to give my money back because on the advertisement there was some things that we hadn't in the theatre.</P>
      <P>Finally, it would be grateful if you could answer me soon.</P>
      <P>Yous sincerelly,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Our lives are changing. When I was a child I had different entertainments that the actually children hadn't. We could play with our toys, dolls and we could enjoy without a computer. We hadn't so many machines than they have.</P>
      <P>The technology is growing and growing.</P>
      <P>If you have a computer you will be able to have all the information that you want. It's very important but some times it is a wrong thing because the children can see it too. Moreover you can change the TV programme without getting up. We can find information about the weather, sports on our TV-text.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, the science is changing.</P>
      <P>We have more researchers than some years ago and we will be able to find the solution of lots of problems. Actually, we can cure illness which were very dangerous before. I'm sure that in a couple of years we will see cured some illness like cancer, UTH.</P>
      <P>The new technology is changing our lives.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
