<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR706*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I was one of your customers who had a very disappointing about Over the Rainbow show at your Circle Theatre yesterday.</P>
      <P>First of all, these starrings of the show were not Danny Brook and Tina Truelove. The only one reason I bought your ticket was because of Danny Brook and Tina Trulove, as your advertisement had shown. But your starrings were not.</P>
      <P>I bought a ticket for the 19.30 round and the show was very very late. It started at 20:15 and that waisted my time and made me feel bad about your service. And also the ticket discounts were not available. That was not your advertisement had shown. And finally, your restaurant was not available after the show.</P>
      <P>From every singular things I have complained, it was totally different from what your advertisment said. And because of this, I would like to ask for my money back. If you see that this is a good reason, please telephone me. My telephone number is 123-4567.</P>
      <P>Yours</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Thesedays we are living on a high-technology world. Modern technology has been growing rapidly and it has effected me a lot. Indeed, I have to save more money for upgrading my personal computer. Computer technology keeps improving all the time and consumes like me and you definitely have to pay our money to keep our personal computer up to date and able to work with new computer softwares that require more and more performance of computer hardware.</P>
      <P>Anyway, modern technology such as the Internet changes me a great deal of life-style. Using the internet, I can search for almost all information I want to know. And I can send e-mail to my friends via the Internet fastly and cheaply prepared to the old-style mail-services.</P>
      <P>Finally, I think modern technology makes me do my business faster, smarter with much more efficiency.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
