<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR707*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear sir,</P>
      <P>I'm writing you to complain about the disappointing expirience I had with your theatre.</P>
      <P>First of all, I arrived at about 19:20 because advertisement said that performance begins at 19:30, but it wasn't till about 20:15 that the begin of the show and I had to wait entire hour which was not very amazing.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I was supposed to have a discount but there were no discounts, although the advertisement said there are.</P>
      <P>Thirdly, the disappointment made me a bit hungry but the restaurant was closed without any sign saying why.</P>
      <P>And at last, the most disappointing point, the advertisement again said that there would be Danny Brook, my favorite actor, but there was someone else instead of him.</P>
      <P>So, the show was not good at all and my evening was spoiled in spite of all that advertisement promissed. As things went that way, I want my money back.</P>
      <P>Sincerely Yours,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>I shall have a look into the place I believe no one can avoid - the kitchen.</P>
      <P>How much effort and time it took about two decades go to chop vegetables or prepare coffee or how hard it was to deal with fridges! But today the mixer or some more complicated kitchen-device will chop and mix anything for you from fruits to meat, and modern coffee machines can make even cappuccino or whatever you want on their own. Those devices made our life easier like old fridges had to be defreezed to melt out and new fridges use different kind of cooling and will tell you if your forgot to close the door! The modern cooker will turn off itself if something goes wrong! Personally, my life became much faster and I have much more time for many other things during the day thanks to devices modern technology offers us.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
