<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR710*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms J. Clark,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you to thank for so good organisation of International Arts Festival, where I'd spent two exellent days recently.</P>
      <P>I would like to inform you whed the idea was great and I hope that so needful for people events would become a good tradition in our country. I think that providing such festivals could help people to be in the centre of cultural life of the world and to have enough information about the new art styles</P>
      <P>But I hope that next year visitores of festival would be able to introduce with more art groups from all over the world. I suggest it would be very intresting to meet artists from far and exotic countries.</P>
      <P>Also, if I were you I would make your concert halls a bit larger, because of too many people would like to spend their holidays with their families on your festival next year</P>
      <P>Event this year some halls, which I had visited were overcrowded and there were some problems with ventilation during some shows</P>
      <P>Finishing my letter, I hope what my notes could help you to make next-year festival more intersting and comfortable for public</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Want to be independent? Earn yourself.</P>
      <P>Everybody knows that common students are not the richest persons in the world. But then you are at the university you need money more, then anybody else want.</P>
      <P>It is so because you are young and need to make your life as intrestng as it can be now.</P>
      <P>All that discos, concerts, touristic trips have to be paid by a different sum of those small coloured pieces of paper, called money</P>
      <P>Of course, the easiest way to have them is to ask your parents for help, but a great number of young persons want to be independent. So thy need to get a job that is very difficult when you haven't any special education and experience yet.</P>
      <P>Most common way to earn is baby-sitting. Many young people earn their pocket money so, helping neighbouring parents to have a bit more spare time. Other students work as house or office managers, make promontion of different goods or even as a bouncer. Naturally, it's easier to get a job then you were good in foreign languagers or computers. When you can find yourself as a tourist guide or as a secretary.</P>
      <P>Sometimes small groups of students organized their own small business. For example, they can design furniture or clothes, make web-sites and so on. In two words, if the young man want to earn a bit of money by his own hands, the luck and success will find him</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
