<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR711*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Jane Clark,</P>
      <P>The reason I am writing this letter is to congratulate you for the International Arts Festival. I think the festival was fine but in my opinion there must be some improvements to make this festival better.</P>
      <P>Firstly, there were stars and artists only from six countries. This number may be increased to attract more and different people. Also some concerts holls were too small for this much people. In contrast with the halls, the concerts were great and I saw everybody enjoyed then. I must admit that you are very successful about finding good stars.</P>
      <P>The films and plays were not so many. As a result of this the kinds of films were not enough. In order to attract more people with different interests, the films and plays should be increased. I have nothing to say with the dance show, art exhibitions and talks by writers. They were excellent and they attracted any kind of people.</P>
      <P>Another paht is the tickets. The weekend ticket is excellent because it is not so expensive and it allows to see everything. But I was disappointed that there were no competition between the films performed I think there should be an Oscar-like competition in order to make people more ambitious to make better films.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Elinor,</P>
      <P>I'm so glad to receive your lost letter because I've started to think that you were angry about me for not writing for a long time. I promise I'll write more</P>
      <P>The school rules are horrible here. We are restricted to do nearly everything. The school is like a dungeen here. I don't went to be so evel about school but the rules are rules and they are limiting us with the borders of our school.</P>
      <P>We must wear the uniform-like clothes all the day and week They don't even let us to wear different sweaters - etc other than dark blue. It is boring. We are not allowed to compare our thoughts during the lessons becase the teachers think that we are chatting. How poor their imagination are!!</P>
      <P>However we are free at home. You could do anything you like as long as you have good grades. If you don't, you hear the same word every day, "Study, Study, Study"! Nobody likes to study but we have to.</P>
      <P>You can't imagine how happy I am and I'm looking forward to hearing from you soon</P>
      <P>Love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
