<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR712*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Swedish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>To the manager of the Circle Theatre.</P>
      <P>I went to see Over the rainbow Show, Friday evening the 16/6. The musical had been advertised to be London's newest and best musical, but all to my disappointment.</P>
      <P>I had been looking forward to see my favorite Danny Brook, but he had been replaced by some other actor. I was not too happy about that and why didn't the theatre start when it was suposed to start? (45 min late), and where were the discounts which were available? Your advertisement was ful of false advertising. In the end of the show I was looking forward to have a nice dinner in the restaurant together with my boyfriend, but it was closed, because you were short of staff. This was not my perfect evening out. I want to have at least half of my money back. I hope you preciate my letter and that you'll try to improve the disadvantages./ Sally Svenssen</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology Changed my daily life?</P>
      <P>The modern technology like internet for example has changed my life a lot both in good and bad ways. The advantages with internet are that I can do all my shopping from internet. I don't have to stress around in the supermarket a friday evening, when I'm tired from school, I just get all the groseries I need delivered to my door. Instead. I buy all my clothes on internet as well and it works brilliant, but I have to admit that there are some disadvantages with internet too. I don't get as much exercise as I used to get. Nowdays I spend 2 hours intent of the computer every day, shopping or chatting to people. I have got friends over the whole world now. I'll go to Japan next month to visit one of my internetfriends. The modern technology open new and exciting ways for us. I don't think that I had been going to Japan if it wasn't because of internet. Internet has opened a whole new world to me.</P>
      <P>Sally Svenssen</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
