<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR716*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Thank you for your answer. I'm happy I can join you at Camp California in the U.S.A.</P>
      <P>I'm sorry to say that I can attend your camp only on July because I just started my new job and I got one month of my holiday, which are on July.</P>
      <P>You wrote to me that I can choice my accommodation. I would prefer stay in log cabins because I have a problem with my back it is a reason that I can't lie on the ground. Beside that I'm alergic, that make me problem when I'm close to the nature.</P>
      <P>You wrote to me that I have a chance to do two activities, which I can choice. I'm quite good in paiting and I play tennis. I'll be very happy when you can give me a chance to use the camp's art studio and you'll be able to prepare some paiting's materials like oil paints canvas and bruches for me. The size of the canvas isn't so important.</P>
      <P>I have my own sports equipment to play tennis. I hope I'll have possibility to improve my ability in it. I'm champion of my town, so I think I can find a right person who can play with me.</P>
      <P>Could you write to me, because I don't know how much money I need and what type of weather do you have in this time of the year.</P>
      <P>Your sincerelly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim!</P>
      <P>Last month we had the pop concert of our favourite polish group "THE CULT" in Warshaw. I had the chance to help at the concert. You can't imagine how happy I was. I got money for that job and I enjoyed the work a lot. You know I'm good in mace-up and I have done many times scenography. They were pleased that I can do two of this job that's why I got the work. I was working like crazy but I enjoyed a lot. I didn't sleep two nights because I was preparing the stage where they made the concert.</P>
      <P>Could you imagine that they asked me to make the summer scenography. I heard, the atmosphere of their concerts is very hot but I didn't know they like to create this even by scenography.</P>
      <P>Could you believe that two nights I was cutting paper's flowers, grass, the sun and thousands of birds. I didn't have many people who was helping me that's why I was working 48 hours without stopping.</P>
      <P>I think the result of that action was marvelous. Everybody was very suprise that you can create such amazing things, using a sizors and papers. I like a lot the mountains which I made. From the distance they looked very real. I just rulled a paper and I painted a little white colours on the top. In front of the stage I put the grass and a lot of flowers. The light on the stage was very bright and very warm what's made the scenery very pleasent.</P>
      <P>After that I prepared the group. I done mace-up for them. I was very happy because on this time I had a chance talking to them and to know more about them. They are very nice people even Audrey who seems very stupid. She is very intelligent. I really don't know why she behave herself so badly during her interview. I got their address so we can visit them one day.</P>
      <P>I told them about you and they said we are very welcome any time. I told them you are full of live and they are yours favourite polish group. They like to know you a lot. We'll speak about it when I come to see you.</P>
      <P>I hope to see you soon.</P>
      <P>A lot of kisses.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
