<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR718*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writing with reference to your letter, which I have just received. I am very happy to hear that I have won the first prize in your competition.</P>
      <P>I am really excited to travel at Camp California in the USA because I like to know people of other countries.</P>
      <P>As I only have holidays on July I would like to travel on this month.</P>
      <P>I would prefer to have accommodation in log cabins because I like to be comfortable and I don't like to be lied down on the floor inside a tent.</P>
      <P>I would like to play basketball because I love this game. I used to play when I was at high school. I think that I am a very competitive player, as well or a technical player. Also I would like to do swimming. I think that I am very fast swimming but I don't have good style and technic.</P>
      <P>I would be grateful if you could send me more information about what clothes and money I must take.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>RAEL MEDINAH</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I have been helping to organise a pop concert in Dublin. As you know I love irish music so I was very happy when the organisers of the concert phone me to help them.</P>
      <P>The organisers paid for my acommodation and travel to Ireland.</P>
      <P>I arrived at Ireland on 2th July. On my first day I didn't work. On the next day I helped them to built the scenary and I had enough time to visit a museum in Dublin in the evening. On my third day I helped them to install the sound system. While we were installing the sound system we listened irish music and suddenly we saw to U2, which is my favourite group, going inside the stadium and they played music for us.</P>
      <P>I could speak to my favourite singer 'Bono', I could meet him and I helped him to repair his guitar because it didn't sound very well.</P>
      <P>The rest of the days I wasn't doing anything especial, just I helped to organise the rehearsals of the differents group who were going to play in the concert.</P>
      <P>Best wishes,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
