<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR719*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>41-50</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dears sirs:</P>
      <P>I would like to travel in July I'll have to finish my exams', the lastest of them will be on 30th of Juny.</P>
      <P>About my Accommodation I prefer the tents, I like them, every year I go 15 days out with my tent and some friends. I like to sleep outside on the grass. The weather will be no cold doesn't it?</P>
      <P>I'd like to play gold and tennis, I practis both since I was young, and I like them, but I don't have enough time to play, and my level isn't as good as I'll like.</P>
      <P>In order to know what sort of the clothes I have to take, please can you inform me about the normal weather for this periode? I'm not used to hight temperatures, I don't like so much the hot weather.</P>
      <P>How expensive the live is there? I have a Master Card, it's possible to use it in your country or it's better to take American Express or Visa? I wait your answer</P>
      <P>Your sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>One of the most important think we have to film is our bycicle classes, our school is now the best of the country in all ages We are prest with this, we can show what we do in order to be the best. If it sould be possible we can make an interview to the last winner.</P>
      <P>Should be good to show the swimming poole, the gim, etc.</P>
      <P>And an other hand we have also a very important museum, and very beatiful building in the school, bowls them!!</P>
      <P>We can also show one off de youngest classes and at the end one off de oldest, with this, the people who see the video will know the progres of our students.</P>
      <P>At the end of the video we can show, in front off the principal building all the students an all the teachers like a old photo.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
