<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR721*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>To: the manager of The Circle Theatre</P>
      <P>From:</P>
      <P>Subject: complaint</P>
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I was at the show of your theatre three days ago. Unfortunately, my expectations have not been realized because of many problems I had during the show.</P>
      <P>First of all, there was another actor instead of Danny Brook (as it was written in the advertisement). Secondly, the show was delayed and started at 20.15 so I had to wait 45 minutes doing absolutely nothing and wasting my time. No discounts were given and, what is more, your theatre restaurant was closed all the time. I was not able to have a dinner after the show. On the whole, I was very disappointed having left the Circle Theatre. All the impressions were destroyed by many problems.</P>
      <P>I ask you for returning my money back. Or I will have nothing to do except for going to the court.</P>
      <P>Faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Fashion of the Future</P>
      <P>Three hundred years ago fashion changed up one time in each hundred years. One hundred years ago it was one time in 50-25 years. And now we have to change some of our clothes every 6 months because they are not so fashionable any more. Fashion is one of the most important parts of our image and everyday life now. Fashion is becoming more useful, all the new inventions and technologies are going to play an important part in the fashion industry of the future.</P>
      <P>It is very difficult to predict but let us try to imagine what will clothes be like 100 years from now. With no doubt, the influence of modern technologies will be great. Future clothes will be very useful and incredibly comfortable, we can see the progress in the fashion even now. It seems that the decorative role of clothes will have disappeared by the year of 2050.</P>
      <P>So all the fashion industry will work to make clothes more useful, practical and comfortable. What will we have? Breathing jackets and shirts with air conditioning.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
