<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR722*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Miss Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am very glad received your letter, and very happy won first prize in your competition. I am writing to answer your question and ask further information.</P>
      <P>First of all, I am a high school student, so I only have four weeks vacation on July. I would like to travel on July. Secondly, for me, the best way to live in outdoor is in tents, because that will be a good chance to learn a lot of knowledge about planets and animals as well.</P>
      <P>Moreover, I am good at play basketball, in fact, I am the captain in basketball team which is one of the best teenagers team in my city, and I also like singing. I play piano very well. Two of my friends and I have a band, we sometimes perform in my school club.</P>
      <P>Could you tell me something about clothes and money which is I need to take with me.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Suitable lessons and activities</P>
      <P>To: Mrs Oliviar</P>
      <P>From: HUA TANG</P>
      <P>date: 13th June</P>
      <P>Introduction: The aim of this report is to summerize the suitable lessons and activities be filmed.</P>
      <P>Lessons: 1 Music</P>
      <P>Music is traditional lesson in our school, everyone in our school can play at least one instruments, so music lesson should be film and to express music is one of our school daily life style.</P>
      <P>2. Maths</P>
      <P>According to some survey which have done by another students. Every student in our school has one math class everyday. So, maths lesson would be filmed.</P>
      <P>activities. Basketball</P>
      <P>Our school basketball team is one of the best teenagers team in our city, and every afternoon students are all play basketball in playground. So, basketball should be filmed.</P>
      <P>Conclution</P>
      <P>Sum up, the daily life in our school should film music class, maths class and student playing basketball.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
