<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR723*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>I write to find out further information and give you some details about myself and the travel that I have won in your competition.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to inform you that I am able to travel only in July. Because, I am a student and in June, I will still have school. Also, in Augost I will be studying a summer English course.</P>
      <P>In addition, I would prefer to stay in a tent. Because I would like to stay somewhere which differs from my home and every days comforts, in these two weeks.</P>
      <P>However, in your letter is written some activities. I would choose Basketball and Tennis. Basketball I have been playing in a team, of my town for ten years. Also Tennis is my favourite hobby and I play twice every week with my friends.</P>
      <P>Finally, I would be grateful to you, if you told me about clothes and money. Will we need any special clothes and How much you would suggest me to carry for these two weeks?</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely </P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim</P>
      <P>How are you? I am very well I'm writing to explain my experience with the pop concert; last month.</P>
      <P>First of all, I think that I help them. Every day of that month I was trying to advertise this concert. I was going to markets to schools and I was giving information when and where the group was going to appear as well as where can they buy or book a ticket for this concert. I know, It was difficult and tired but I enjoyed a lot. Firstly, it was a good break from the routine. Because I did it for first time. Also, I felt wonderful when I saw, that the concert had succesed and every day was croweded. Because I believed that this was a result which came with my help. I would like to do again it in the future. It was a fantastic experience.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Best wishes</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
