<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR724*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter and congratulations! I have always been interested in visiting other contries. In fact it didn't want to ask my parents for money, and going on holiday with you would be an ideal solution.</P>
      <P>As regards accommodation, I would like to stay in tents, because I used to going on holiday with my friends and staying in tents. It is just wonderful.</P>
      <P>In my spare time I like to play basketball for a local team of which I have recently been made captain. I would now like to learn how to play tennis and golf, if it is possible.</P>
      <P>Could you please let me know what kind of weather will be there in July, what sorts of clothing I'd better take with me. Is there an extra charge for some trips, which might put them beyond my means.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>Raisa Sharapova</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>To: Dinara Safina</P>
      <P>From: Raisa</P>
      <P>Re: Daily life at our school.</P>
      <P>As requested, it has collected some information about the school. Below is a summary of the most important relevent points with some recommendations.</P>
      <P>1. The fully-equipped computer centre in the main building is extremelly good. Lessons are very interesting and full of fun. Our teacher is friendly and he encourages us to study well. However, there are no enough computers and sometimes we have to study in pairs. I suggest to increase the number of them, because it will be more exiting to film.</P>
      <P>2. The school arranges an amasing range of activities, such as excuintions, sports and different kinds of trips. Although there is plenty for us to do during the day, the most funny events happen while we are playing basketball and football. I must say, I think this is the best time for making a short video.</P>
      <P>Conclusion.</P>
      <P>Our school is an ideal place for making a short video. There are many interesting lessons and other activities. I do recommend, however, to make a short video about</P>
      <P>a) lessons in the computer centre</P>
      <P>b) basketball and football games.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
