<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR725*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I have just received your letter where you inform me I have won the first prize in the competition and now, I'd like to express my opinion about the questions you have written on it.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to travel only in the month of July, because during the month of June, I'm going to work and in September I have to study a lot, because school will start. Speaking about accommodation, between tents and log cabins, I woul prefer tents, because I love the adventure and also because I can be freer.</P>
      <P>I know I will have the chance to do two activities, so I have choosen two from your list: Basketball, because I have been playing it since I was eight and I have been taking part in a strong team for three years.</P>
      <P>The other one I have choosen is swimming; for the same reason why I chose Basketball. But, what about clothes, money, food?</P>
      <P>I hope you will take my answers into consideration. Thank you for now.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfuly</P>
      <P>Simone Pausini</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Many people "see" at shopping like an amusement, but I think it's not always a good translation to give it. In my opinion to do shopping is often funny, above all when you can enter without difficulties into a shop. For exemple, if the shop is full of people, is not enjoyable, because they will create too confusion, too noise with the risk of leaving time. Shopping is a funny thing to do, not when you are in a hurry, but when you have free time and when you can relax yourself. Another thing that regardes me, is that I enjoy my self more when I know I have to do shopping for me than when it's for my parents or for somebody else!!!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
