<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR727*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>41-50</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms Ryan,</P>
      <P>I was so surprised and delighted as well receiving from you such wonderful news! Thanks the God, you did me really happy.</P>
      <P>From your letter I was pleased to know that all accommodation and travel costs are paid for. But could you, please, let me have more details about my award. What kind of people will be invited at your Camp in this summer? I would like to know with whome I'll share sach a wonderful days with the sport activities.</P>
      <P>About sport... I must be honest: I'm not very keen on sport. But I will be glad to swimming and sailing for some weeks. I have been learnt to paint. And I would prefer to have a nice audience for my poetry as well, I'm a poet, yeas.</P>
      <P>I would be choose a month July, because I'm free in this time from family's duties.</P>
      <P>What about another camp conditions - it does not matter for me. I can stay in tents or log cabins, how you wish.</P>
      <P>Sent me, please, news about July.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Fu-Su Harp</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I hope that you still OK and now are preparing for me a new nice letter! I hope so!</P>
      <P>I have been written to you that my life in London was a little bit boring for me. It was true. But now all things became absolutly changed!</P>
      <P>I found the kind of activity what I looking for four ages. My Russian friend ivited me to set up a new exiting business. We established a firm which has a deal with musicians and contemporary pop stars. Can you imagine!</P>
      <P>First of all, in order of our firm purpose I wrote an inventation to my favorite idol - a poet and a singer Boris Grebenchekoff. We were renting for him a special hall near Piccadilly Circus. The hall was crowded. His one-week concert programme was so succsessful that we decided to invite him else, as soon as tickets would be sold. I had a nice expirience as manager too. I would like to be a professional in this stage, yeas. Do you share my idea, Kim? Is not it a brilliant idea?</P>
      <P>You know, Kim, I'm always looking for purpose of human being. Not only - to LIVE, but to have something to LIVE FOR. Now I did my choice.</P>
      <P>Good luck to you as well!</P>
      <P>P.S. Your present, a small toy, a white hose - I always keep with me, it helps me to pass my exams.</P>
      <P>With Love -</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
