<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR728*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>I am writting about this letter that I recently received from you, which is about a competition that I have won the first prize.</P>
      <P>I would like to know if is possible for me going on July, because I have school on the others months, and it is impossible for me going on December or January.</P>
      <P>About the accommodation, I would prefer log cabins instand of tents, because is safer and more confortable.</P>
      <P>The two activities that I prefer will be Basketball, because I had the experience to play in my school's big for almoust a year, and Photography, which is a hobby that I am good at and I practice since I was ten.</P>
      <P>On top of everything, I would like to ask how much money should I take, and which type of clothes are the best to wear in the competition.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Elisa F.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable</P>
      <P>If you are used to go to the Shopping very often, maybe is because you don't know about all the others good things you can do on your weekend.</P>
      <P>People are used to go to the shopping because it is easier and familiare, it is one place where you can have lunch or dinner, watch some movie after that, and if you want buy something at the shops.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, everything at the shopping is more expensive, because the people that buy on it usually don't compare prices or look for cheaper shops, because all they need it is already at this place.</P>
      <P>Instand of going to the theather, which is more cultural, or even do a picnic on the Ikurapiura park, people prefer spends all their money at Shoppings.</P>
      <P>So, why don't we try to change our customs and start to do knew things to enjoy ourselves.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
