<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR729*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Circle theatre's Manager: I am writting you because I felt dissapointed after seeing the musical show "Over the Rainbow". There were many things that were wrong in the advertisement I saw. First the actors who were suppoused to star in this show were not the ones put in there. So when I saw the show I felt horrible, because I was expecting to see Danny Brook. But the problems started while I arrived the place. I had a discount for it, but they refussed it and I had to pay the full price. Appart from this, the show started fourty five minutes later. I think this reasons are suficiently enough to ask for my money back. So I hope that you will understand my point. Please be comprehensive and realize that your show was not cheap. I'm a student, so I do not have a lot of money and I need it back. I also had to tell you that the theatre restaurant was closed because there were few people there and they take me out of the place, so I was very upset. I will go to your office this week. I hope to see you there.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Pat's secret</P>
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. He had talked to Caroline days before the secret was known. She had told him about the relationship with her boyfriend. Everybody knew that Caroline and her boyfriend John loved each other so much that it wouldn't be rare to find that they had have sex together. The point here is, that Caroline choosed the worst friend to told this. She was also concerned about being pregned, but she was afraid to told John about it. So she decided to ask Pat what to do. When she finally told him, Pat react in a very wrong way and told rapidly to John. He couldn't belived what Pat had told him, so he broke Pat's nose. Pat's father had to pay a very expensive operation. But as every story this has a happy final. John and Caroline still love each other, and she wasn't pregnant at all, it was just her fantasy. And Pat understood that secrets should die on your own.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
