<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR732*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Tito Torres Vargas</P>
      <P>ELIZABETH GASKELL COLLEGE</P>
      <P>Manchester, UK</P>
      <P>Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>Competition Organizer</P>
      <P>Dear Madam,</P>
      <P>Thank you for this great opportunity to travel with you for free! I entered the competition you organized but never expected to be the lucky winner.</P>
      <P>I could only travel on the first week of July because I have to join my parents on their trip to Italy, due to start on the 20th.</P>
      <P>The accomodation that best suits me is in log cabins, as the space in tents is very limited and I am not used to have all my belongings in order and packed at all times.</P>
      <P>In respect of the activities you offer, it is difficult to choose in such a hugh variety, but I prefer to do those I better know as climbing. I've been studying Photography on my own, and I am looking forward to practise new techniques and take pictures of new landscapes.</P>
      <P>Please send me a list of the items I many need there, including the most appropriate clothes for the american weather. I would also like to know in advance the amount of money I need to bring for expenses that will not be included.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable</P>
      <P>Most of us would agree on that. Who has never had a bad experience related with an unsatisfactory product? Moreover, who has the freedom to buy with an unlimited budget whatever they need? And finally who has all the time needed to do so?</P>
      <P>There are many things that can go wrong in the process of adquiring a product or service. And whenever money is involved, some problems are likely to happen. Thieves will try to put their hands in our wallets and purses, and even the so called 'plastic money' is not always safe.</P>
      <P>Hunting on the High Street, or the Shopping Malls, for the desired bargain - because we cant afford otherwise to buy - becomes often a desperate atempt to reach a living promoted by the new consuming society. And nobody can say they would rather go back to the caverns' age where money was not even invented.</P>
      <P>With more free time and more money to spend than ever, shopping is a great activity, but when this creates bad habits as overspending, could lead to serious problems.</P>
      <P>At the end all depends in our attitud to life, including shopping. I particularly enjoy making lists of the products before going shopping. But even without money to spend is fun to rush from time to time in the sales that seasonaly appear, or simply look at the superb displays that shops have in their showrooms.</P>
      <P>Shopping may be enjoyable or not at all!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
