<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR735*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writing to enquire about the competition that I won and give some details to you about myself and my interests.</P>
      <P>In the first place, I prefer to travel on July because my school will not be closed before this date. Secondly, a tent holiday is always attracted me so I would like to stay in a tent rather than in a log cabin.</P>
      <P>In my spare time, I enjoy playing basketball with my friends and I also like swimming. When I was in primary school, I was one of the members in swimming-school team. I am not really good at basketball but I think it is a good fun. Because of these reasons, I choose basketball and swimming from the list which were given.</P>
      <P>I would like to know what types of clothes I need and beside this, how much money I need during my vacation.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely, </P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>It's ages since I've heard from you. I hope you and your family are well.</P>
      <P>Last month, I had a great time at the concert of "Dragon" which is the most popular hard-rock group all over the world. They had a concert in my hometown that's why the organizators were looking for young people who can speak English. I applied and They took me on. I took part in the security department. The staff in that departnent are really friendly and helpful and they are also huge like giants. Basicly, I helped them connecting with the local police and getting some electronical equipments that they needed. They treated me as if I was the private secretary of the department, because of this sometimes I felt that the power was in my hands. By the way, I have already been invited their next concernt. They gave me two free tickets. Would you like to come with me?</P>
      <P>Looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
