<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR736*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear manager of the circle theatre,</P>
      <P>Two months ago I went to see your musical show. I got very angry because you are liars. It was one of the most disappointing evening of my life.</P>
      <P>The advertisement said that the actors were Danny Brook and Tina Truelove but the actor was different. Who can believe it? You are really a funny theatre.</P>
      <P>And the time too. You wrote that at 19.30 the musical started. I was waiting for 45 minute. the show started at 20:15.</P>
      <P>I paid 20 pounds without any discount. You said that some discouns was available. Nobody took a discount.</P>
      <P>When I went to the reastaure I was really suprised. It was closed and I steel don't know why?</P>
      <P>In the advertisemen you wrote "your perfect evening out", that's very funny. It was Just a disappointing night and I want you to return to me some of my money,</P>
      <P>a very angry man</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>The modern technology has changed my daily life in many ways. The modern technology help me when I do my homework, to some games e.t.c.</P>
      <P>First of all the computer. It helps me when I studie. I can find many things from the internet or to write my compositions on it.</P>
      <P>The car has changed my daily life, like everyone else. I can go from one place to other very fast</P>
      <P>Most of the machines which you have at home help me, too. I can find cold water in the refrigarator but 50 years before the didn't have the refrigarator, so our life is easier, today.</P>
      <P>When I stay home I can watch or listen to the radio e.t.c. so the modern technology help me to spend my free time.</P>
      <P>As you have seen the modern technology has changed my daily life a lot and I believe that it has changed it to the better.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
