<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR739*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear The Manager of the Circle Theatre,</P>
      <P>I went to the Circle Theatre to see the show, "OVER THE RAINBOW" a few days ago. I am writing this letter to tell you how I felt disappointed with it.</P>
      <P>There are some differences between the advertisement and the real show. With the advertisement, you mentioned Mr. Danny Brook and Ms. Tina Truelove were going to play but actually different people were playing, whom I have never seen before. And also it said it was going to start at 19:30 but it was not started until 20:15. To make it worse, neither discounts or restraurants were available at that night although they were said to be available. According to the owener of the restaurant, it was closed because the plugs of some lights were cut off.</P>
      <P>As I am writing, it was not a perfect evening at all but horrible, so I would like to ask for money back and compensate for my special 20th birthday.</P>
      <P>I am waiting for your reply as soon as possible.</P>
      <P> Faithfully yours,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Fashion Of the Future</P>
      <P>There have been already a variety of fashion style nowadays. Some are in formal others are in casual. Especially in big cities such as London, New York and Tokyo, you can see a lot of people in various clothes, so I do not think there will be such big differences in outlooking of clothes even 100 years from now.</P>
      <P>However, I think, there will be some diffences in quality and materials of clothes. For example, speaking of sports, a lot of remarkable progress has been made in especially swimming costumes and athletes' costumes for Olympic.</P>
      <P>In addition, I think the earth will be warmer and warmer than now and 100 year from now will be an Area of Space. So clothes for space will be necessary and clothes for warmer climates will be necessary.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, 100 years from now, I think, better quality in clothes will be created in every field, such as sports, office, leisure, building site, school and space. although outlooking such as, shape and color will not be changed so much in fashion.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
