<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR740*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writing to give you further information about the two weeks at Camp California.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to express my joy for having won that prize. I am very happy. Secondly, you would like to know when I will be able to go there. Actually, I have asked my boss and he gave me two weeks in July. We have a lot to do at work so it is not easy to have weeks off. Thirdly, I prefer staying in a tent than staying in a log cabin. I think it is more fun. Concerning the activities, I would choose tennis and sailing. I am very good at tennis. Last year, I took part in a competition and I did it well. I have also a licence for sailing but I have not done it for a long time. I need to know what kind of clothes I should take with me. I do not know if things are expensive there. Therefore, could you give me an idea of how much money I should bring with me.</P>
      <P>I am looking forwards to receiving more information.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Sofia Jordana</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>It is Saturday. The car park of the supermarket is full. No more trolleys for shopping. All the shops are crowded. Some people are in a hurry other are agressive and most of the other are very stressed.</P>
      <P>It is not always like that but we often see such a scene, even though shopping is becoming an entertainement not only for teenagers but also for adults.</P>
      <P>We have more and more shops everywhere and they sale everything. Because of that, people's need has increase a lot nowadays. It is also the reason why we have all these new supermarkets. In the one hand, it is very enjoyable to go shopping because we can find a lot of things. Sometimes we need them and sometimes we don't but it is fun to buy new clothes, furniture and so one. In the other hand, the service in the shops or supermarkets has decrease a lot those last years. The shop assistants are not always nice and sometimes they don't even know a bit about what they sell.</P>
      <P>In my opinion, shopping is not always enjoyable especially when there is too many people in there.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
