<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR741*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you to complain about the musical show "Over the Rainbow" which I went to see last week.</P>
      <P>First of all, the actors that played the show were differents to Danny Brook and Tina Truelove. Besides of this they were not good as actors, so I am quite disappointed.</P>
      <P>Then, the show had to start at half past seven and I had to wait fourty-five minutes because it started later. But it is not all because in the advertisement appeared the possibility of discounts available and it is false, I had to pay £20 for each ticket.</P>
      <P>Finally, I wanted to visit your theatre restaurant and have a good dinner after the show but it was impossible. The restaurant was closed because most of the employees was on holidays and there were not enough people to attend the demand.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, it was not the perfect evening that I expected, so I am therefore writing to ask for a full refund of the tickets. I will be looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets, and now my best friend knows that I will go to visit her next week.</P>
      <P>Alice is my best friend and we met twenty years ago. We went to the same school and we had the same hobbies. It was perfect because we always were together and doing interesting activities like snow board.</P>
      <P>One day her mother died and she had to move to Germany where her sister was living. But she was very sad because she knew that it will be very difficult to see eachother in the future.</P>
      <P>After that, we wrote letters and she phoned me once time a week but it wasn't the same. I couldn't explain all my problems to her and her voice had changed.</P>
      <P>Finally, I decided to visit her but I wanted that it was a surprise. I worked hard during one month and I could save money to buy a ticket for the plane.</P>
      <P>I decided to explain all my plans to Pat and she promised me that she didn't say anything but it wasn't true. Yesterday she phoned to Alice and explained all. In spite of this I am very happy because I know that Alice is preparing many activities to do together and to spend the best week in our lifes.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
