<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR742*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writting this letter to complain about the treatment that we have received when we went to the Circle theatre in order to see the musical show "Over the rainbow" whose actors were Anthony Keens and Tina Truelove.</P>
      <P>When we arrived at the Circle theatre in the evening, we were waiting during a long time, because that you advertisement noticed that the musical show would begin at 19:30, and eventually it began at 20:15.</P>
      <P>Moreover, the actors were not the same of the advertisement. Finally, after the show we went to the theatre restaurant but it was closed because they were on holidays. This evening was the worst evening of all my life.</P>
      <P>I would like that you give me back some money of the tickets.</P>
      <P>I look to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully.</P>
      <P>PEDRO REZ SORAN</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. She told our parents that we were going to get married in Brazil. Because of this, Sally's parents and my parents went to Brazil rapidly. Sally and I had bought a nice big house beside the sea in the outskirts of the city. It had three bedrooms, two bathrooms, one dining room and one kitchen. Indeed, it had a big swimming pool and a beatiful garden. When my parents arrived in Brazil and found us, our dreams were erased. We had to come back to Spain. Because of this, we had to sell the house and left our jobs. When we arrived in Spain, we had to explain our parents all our adventure.</P>
      <P>That day was the worst day of all my life. Nowadays, Sally and I are married, have three children, a marvellous house and both of us are working in a big company.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
