<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR744*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P> Dear manager,</P>
      <P>I am writing to tell you that I stayed very disappointed with the theatre. One of my reasons to travel to London, was this theatre.</P>
      <P>I knew that "Over the rainbow" was horrible! I thought that it was the best musical show that London had. I was wrong, very wrong.</P>
      <P>In the propaganda had written that Danny Brook and Tina Truelove are supposed to be the actors, and in the theatre had totally differents actors.</P>
      <P>I bought my tickets fuee days before the theatre thinking I will have discounts. But it happenned the opposite. I payed the same as who bought the tickets ten minutes before the theatre.</P>
      <P>Other thing I have to complement is about the time of the theatre. It was supposed to starts at half past seven, and it started only at fifteen past eight.</P>
      <P>After all this, I want to know if I will have some money back. I hope so.</P>
      <P>yours sincerelly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>It is true that science and technology affects our lives a lot. The technology is essencial to our life, we need it on each minute, on each second.</P>
      <P>It is rare the schools that don't have a multimedia centre with many computers to the students use. But it is good and bad in the same time. Good because you can have acess to a lot of informations, and it is bad because the computers are getting the people's work. Nowadays we have teachers, and tomorrow? Who have the certain that the computers will not get the place of the teachers? It is interesting to starts to think about this point.</P>
      <P>Another point is that the television is taking the childhood of the children. For example, our parents had time to played with dolls or toys, and the new generation don't have time for this, because they spend a lot of time in front of televisions that only shows silly programmes.</P>
      <P>We need this technology, but we have to know how to control this.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
