<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR746*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>31-40</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Cambridge, 13th June 2000.</P>
      <P>Dear Miss Helen Ryan;</P>
      <P>Thanks for your letter. I am very happy for the news. Also to know about the all accommodation and travel costs that is including in the first prize.</P>
      <P>I am going to give all the information that you need.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel only in July because I am free from my college and also it is a very good time for me. Regarding of the accommodation at the Camp California I would prefer in a tent, because I have very nice experience and I love to share with other people. In addition I would like to choose for singing and photography because I am good at singing and taking photographies.</P>
      <P>Please could you let me know if a need a especial clothes and also how much money I need to bring?</P>
      <P>Finally is it possible to have some map regarding of the area?</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>ELENA PANER (MRS).</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Cambridge, 13th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I hope you are fine together with your family. I am going to answer your letter just now.</P>
      <P>Last month I enjoyed a lot to help at a pop concert, really it was a very intresting experience, particularly to had deal with a young group of children from Latin America. It is increible!!, because I learnt some spanish words such us Hello, How are you? good bye?, What is your name, house, dog, cat, boy, girls etc, I am very happy that I promed to myself learn spanish this sommar at the Huntingdon College. Also another interesting things was to know about their culture, because all of them come from Peru, Bolivia, Ecuador, Chile and Uruguay. At the concert they were very susscceful because they were very confident and I helped with the sound system and our equipment was extraordinary and the audience were fantastic. I hope one day you and me can travel to South America because I would like to introduce you my new friends.</P>
      <P>Now I have to end this letter, so please call me if you want to see me next week.</P>
      <P>Take care!!</P>
      <P>Love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
