<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR747*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you to tell that I saw your musical show "Over the rainbow" and there were too many disappointing divergences between the advertisement for the show and the show itself.</P>
      <P>The main problem was that Danny Brook did not take part in the show. However, I bought a £20 ticket mostly because I saw his name in the advertisement. Furthermore, the show started only at 20:15, although, it had to start at 19:30. Moreover your theatre restaurant was closed all evening, I think you should know that ticket were sold without any discounts.</P>
      <P>It seems to me that all these failures were your falt, because you were responsible for the arrangement of the show. I think you ought to have postponed the show and have reimbursed me a ticket price. However, conserning that I saw the show, I would like to get a half refund.</P>
      <P>Please reply at your earliest convinience.</P>
      <P>I look forward to receiving your reply.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Modern technology changed my daily life completely. When I saw modern technology I mean Internet.</P>
      <P>For example, I live in Kursk, and I can get a letter from my friend after some hours since he has written it. My friend lives in Kresnodar. My grandmother lives in Orel, which is much closer to Kursk than Kresnodar. And it takes 3 days to her letter to get to Kursk. That is because my friend uses e-mail, but my grandmother uses post service. So with Internet I can make friends all over the world and it does not take lots of time.</P>
      <P>Another change in my life is that I use Internet as a library when I write my course papers. So that I can get books which is impossible to get in libraries of my town.</P>
      <P>That is why I think that modern techology helps me in my daily life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
