<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR748*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>June 5, 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Ms. Helen Ryan:</P>
      <P>I am writing this letter because I would like to express my happiness. This is the first time I won a prize in these kind of competitions so I would like to clear some doubts.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to travel on July because I have a lot of work and my parents wish to see me in this month, so if it is possible to arrange the date it would be very nice.</P>
      <P>Second, I use to go to Camps where they only used log cabins so I prefer if it is possible to be in tents, because it would be a original experience.</P>
      <P>Third, I love playing basketball, I am a great player and I play with my University and I like to be playing all the time so this activity I will not missed. The other activity would be surf. I think is very cool and I want to learn.</P>
      <P>Finally, I want to know what kind of clothe I will need and if have to take money for shops or markets.</P>
      <P>Looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerly,</P>
      <P>Jason Andre.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable. You have to be all the time walking, so your legs will feel pain, hurted at the final of the day, you will be very tired and you would want to hang around for two months.</P>
      <P>If I go alone is very fast and I enjoy it but if I go with my mother it would be horrible, I will have to do a sacrifice. I will have to be waiting until my mother decides which is the best place to buy her dress.</P>
      <P>She will see if it is pretty or not, if it is in discount at other store we will not buy the dress and we will have to go to the other store to see the other dress, but at the final of seeing all the stores and looking all the dresses she will decided for the first we saw. It is horrible.</P>
      <P>Is like a nightmare.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
