<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR750*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Jones:</P>
      <P>I'm writting you because I wanted to tell you what a bad experience I had during my holidays when I went to see the play on your theatre. To begin with, the actor you publised was going to perform, didn't. To make things even worse, the play didn't start at 19:30 as it was supposed to but instead it started 45 minutes late, at 20:15, and there weren't even your famous discounts available.</P>
      <P>As it wasn't enough, after the show, I took the risk of going to your restaurant and not very hard to guess I wasn't able to enjoy it, as for it was closed because it wasn't clean enough to sell food, the perfect ending for the perfect evening.</P>
      <P>Considering all this, and especially the fact that I didn't get a discount on my ticket, I think the least you can do is give me my money back to make it up to me, and so I can go an spend the money in a good play when they do what they've promised.</P>
      <P>Waiting for your to write back</P>
      <P>Yours</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Modern technology is, nowadays, not only a "tool" for every day life but also a lifestyle. People are getting more and more adicted to this, because helps every day life to be easier and more confortable.</P>
      <P>In my own personal experience, technology is something I can't live without. From a simple domestic appliance, a TV or a radio to a cell phone or a computer, my life is much better now than it was before. For example, whenever I go out by myself, my father gives me a cell phone, to call him in case I need anything. Another thing I depend on is the computer. Not only to play or use the Internet, but also to write my papers for school.</P>
      <P>I think that anything that can make our lifes better, should be done, because that way we wouldn't have so many things to be concerned about, and we would be able to live a happier and more relaxed life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
