<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR751*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I've been recently to one of yours musical shows called "Over the rainbow" in the Circle theatre in London thinking it might be a good idea but it was desappointing. I'm writting this letter to explain you what had happened and look for a solution.</P>
      <P>To begin, the organitzation of your collegues of the theatre was awful becouse of diferents problems. Despite saying it will start at 19:30, it done at 20:15 which I think is to much late for a good theatre like yours. After, you say in the advertisement to visit your restaurant, however it was close, how can you explain that?</P>
      <P>Secondly, there were some false information in your advertisement that made me angry. You say it would be Danny brook the man who was going to sing but it wasn't. And to sum up, there weren't discounts on the prices of the tickets.</P>
      <P>For all of that, I want my money back, at least 15 of the 20 pounds I'd paid. Looking for forward hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets, so without want I knew that it was going to be a concert on owr city of, from my point of view, the best group of the world, Oasis. And she had planned with my friends went there without me.</P>
      <P>At first I got angry with Pat more than with the others friends of the group, becouse Pat was and is my best friend. However, a couple of minutes later, I calmed down and asked she why. She answered to me becouse all this year I have been so irritated that I got angry with every person who tried to talk to me, and the others friend had convinced her to let me out.</P>
      <P>The I realised that she got reason, I was irritated becouse my parent was going to divorce, but Pat would always be my best friend so I told her that I wasn't angry with her and I was not going to go to the concert becouse I had to go to the court to solve my parent's affair.</P>
      <P>I asked her to look photos of Oasis for me and she accepted. If Pat had been good at keeping secrets, I wouldn't have known anything about the concert and I wouldn't have got angry for not being able to go.</P>
      <P>And that's the history of how I lose the oportunity to go to the only concert that Oasis had done in my city.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
