<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR752*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>On the behalf of all the students, I thank you for organizing our trip to London and for the really interesting programme you propose to us as well. It is likely to enrich our vocabulary and our knowledge of the English culture... However, we would like to suggest you something:</P>
      <P>A few days ago, we saw an advertisement about "The London Fashion and Leisure Show" which seems to be very attractive. Therefore, after having talked about it, we all concluded that we would be pleased to go there. Let me explain you what it is: It must be an exhibition which takes place in the "Central Exhibition Hall" on Tuesday and deals with the latest fashions, the different leisures, make up and so on...</P>
      <P>What do you think about our jobs? It would be all the more interesting for us as fashion is a great interest for people from our age. Moreover, you wouldn't have to worry about the price as it is free for the students. If you agree, we will only have to change the programme on Tuesday afternoon: I mean that instead of shopping, we would go to this exhibition. But I guess that neither us nor you would be against the sacrifice of a "Shopping-Afternoon" - that we can even put on Wednesday during the free-time - so that to enjoy the Fashion and Leisure Show...</P>
      <P>Please, Let us know.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>The respect of Famous people's private life has always been a hot topic... On the one hand, those people are equal to us in the way that they had a childhood, thy got married and built a family... The only difference between them and us is the kind of job they are doing which is literally a "public job". Therefore, why do we have to talk and gossip about them?! But on the other hand, the aim of a "public job" such as politician or actor is to be known and appreciated by the population. And here comes the paradox: Do we have to reveal someone's privacy to judge his work and appreciate him? Well, some people would agree whereas others would desagree. I guess this is an unanswerable question...</P>
      <P>As far as I'm concerned, I would say that famous people made the choice to be followed and tracked by journalists all the time, when they chose to be famous. That's as simple as this! Everyone is aware of the celebrity's consequences so, if they really wanted their privacy, why did they choose a "public job"?? Even if anyone deserve to have a private life, famous people know and might have made a mistake... However, I would add that journalists - being aware of that hard topic - should try to modorate what they write in order to respect altrui's privacy; since they would probably not be glad to have their own private life revealed!</P>
      <P>But to solve this problem, we may think first about its origin... "Reading the gossips": isn't it what anyone of us love doing?? Therefore we should try to educate ourselves so as to respect altrui in his privacy.</P>
      <P>Why not?</P>
      <P>To conclude, I would say that "privacy" and "celebrity" can't go together. It's just a matter of choice: being aware of that problem, everyone is free to become famous or not...!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
