<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR753*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>My name is ***. Recently I spent a week's holiday in London. read the advertisement and I found it interesting so I though that it would be nice to spent one of the nights I had in London at your musical show.</P>
      <P>But I was completely wrong. It was an awful experience. I had come with two friends on the 21st August, and one of the reasons was that we were big fans of Danny Brook and we were looking forward to watch his show. You can imagine disappointing was to find out that he was replaced by another actor not so popular.</P>
      <P>We were there at 19:15 as the show was starting at 19:30 for getting our tickets. We asked for the discounts you were refering at your advertisement but the counter told us that they were not available because it was Sunday.</P>
      <P>That was terrible but we didn't want to make a big deal of it so we went inside and waiting. The show started forty-five minutes later. We got really bored waiting.</P>
      <P>After the show had finished we went for dinner at the theatre restaurant but it was closed because the owner was ill.</P>
      <P>From all these reasons you can understand how unpleasant our evening. was We are asking you to return our money. Hope you'll understand</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. From the time she was a child she couldn't keep anything for herself, she always shared her thoughts with other people</P>
      <P>She was about sixteen years old when she moved to another city with her family. She went to a new school and she had no friends. She was not very sociable and she could not create relationships very easily. By the time she became close friend with Kim, who was really strange to other students and everybody disliked her.</P>
      <P>Pat was wondering why and one day she found out. Kim explained her that she kept the distance from the other students because her father was in prison and didn't want no one to find out.</P>
      <P>Pat Kept this a secret for two months but one day told it by accident to a boy from her class. In a few days all school was familiar with Kim's story. Kim was terrified because everyone was making fun on her and very angry with Pat.</P>
      <P>Pat had to make up. She had to find a way to make Kim forgive her.</P>
      <P>She had found the perfect way. She stand up infront of the whole classroom and explained that Kim's father actions didn't influence Kim. That she was a great friend to her and if someone owed to be punished that was her. Kim forgave her and all the students understand how wrong they were and were very sorry. They all got to know the real Kim know.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
