<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR754*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about the musical show. Over the Rainbow, which you advertised. I saw the show at your theatre with my friend on 6th June. However, I was disappointed with something which did not match your advertisement.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to have seen Danny Brook as I am keen on his play. He did not play in the evening. It made me sad. Secondly, the starting time has been changed from 19:30 to 20:15. We waited for ages because we had not been informed. In addition, although you advertised the discounts tickets available, they do not sale them any more according to your staff. Finally, we went to the restaurant in your theater after the show. It was closed because of the staff trainning.</P>
      <P>I am sure you can understand my disappointment. I must insist that you refund the cost of the show. Unless I hear from you within ten days, I shall have to take legal advice on the matter.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you in the near future.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>It is believed that our life style has been changed by mordern technology such as computers and washing machine etc. Especially for families. I have found very expensive to buy them but there are number of advantages.</P>
      <P>First of all, dishwashers are very effecient for me because I work full time and look after my children. It is very difficult to cook and wash dishes after working. Before buying my dishwasher I asked my son to wash them. He complained about a lot. Secondly, computers are useful for us as well, because we do not need to go somewhere if we want to have information, for example traveling.</P>
      <P>However my family's members do less communicate with each other than we used to, because my children are keen on playing computer games.</P>
      <P>In my opinion, the morden technology make our life style combinient. It is very good for us but I think we should think about more carefully when we buy something for our children.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
