<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR758*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear sir,</P>
      <P>I am writing to express my dissatisfaction with the musical show which the Circle Threatre has presented. I recently had a week's holiday in London and during my stay I came to your threatre to see the "Over the Rainbow". My evening was very disappointing.</P>
      <P>The play should start at 19.30 but it started forty-five minutes later, we were waitting over there with out doing anything. We got very bored and tired.</P>
      <P>After the show had finished I went to the theatre restaurand to hav something to drink and get relaxed but it was closed because the stuff was on holiday.</P>
      <P>Moreover the discounts were not available as you say in the advertisment and I paid £20.</P>
      <P>I would like some refand because It was one of the worst evenings in my life it if this matter does not solve I will go further. I hope that it will be solved properly</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat was not very good at keeping secrets. He and his friends got in trouble because of this habit, last week.</P>
      <P>As they were watching T.V at Nick's house last Sunday, Sally noticed that their cut Curly was hurt, she could not walk. The children were very unhappy and sorry about the pet. "Somebody had hurt her and had let her without help" Mourk said angrily. "We have to find him and make him pay for his action" Sally told them. Everybod agreed with her.</P>
      <P>Next morning as Pat was going to school met Bad Jon. and told him "Hey, you. We know what you have done and your dog will be sold". Bad Jon understood and talked immediately to his father. who was the school minister about the children' plan. Of course they were punished.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
