<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR793*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>Last night, me and my family visited your theatre, and we had a very disappointing evening</P>
      <P>In the advertisement the time when the show should start was 19.30 but it started 20:15. When I arrived to theatre and ask for the discount, it wasn't available. In your adv. starring was Danny Brook, and on the stage plaied different actor and his play was very poor. The whole show and acting was an profeccion like scholl theatre. When we decided to visit theatre Restaurant after the show it was clouse because same of decorating wasn't finish. It was last poin to get me angry. After evrything what happend we went to hotel tipped and very affect.</P>
      <P>It wasn't perfect evening out, how you did promise in your a advertisement, and I want ask for my money back.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Alexy Pasimov</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>For the last one hundred years science and technology did big step if we looking to back. Same thing more then 100 years ego the people haven't got the light. They were used just a candle. Nobody can thinking about the Telephone, and telegraph. From small village to town was very long way becouse the people used horse and wagon.</P>
      <P>And look at now. Evry family has now T.V., to travel for long distance we using not just car and elso train and airplain. Before we have phantasy about how people travel to other planets, and what we see now spaceship cruising in the open space.</P>
      <P>In the most part of our life entering computer. Before it was only emegination.</P>
      <P>New techology more our life more comfortable and esee. Evrything what we do now we do with: it help, looking after house, make very difficult operation, becose the computer can think much faster then human.</P>
      <P>And I can continue my list on this way... becouse science never stop on one place.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
