<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR794*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I would like to complain about the show which you presented on last saturday. It was such disappointing evening out with my friend during our a week's holiday in London. We have had a quite pleasant time except the evening. Actually it spoiled our time. So I would like to get back our money.</P>
      <P>These are some points I want mention about the differencies between the advertisement said and the realities.</P>
      <P>First, I had a great expectation to see Danny Brook plays his role, but he had never shown up that night. The main actor was an unknown actor. It was a such disappointing.</P>
      <P>Second, it started only at 20:15. It was 45 minutes later than it suppose to be. It was a such boaring to wait the show in a noisy and hot theatre.</P>
      <P>Third, there was no possibility of discount. The girl sold the tickets was laughing at me when I mention about the discounts availability was written in the advertisement.</P>
      <P>Forth, the theatre restaurant was closed. There was a not on the door saying that the painting was going on the weekend. How could you arrange work like that?</P>
      <P>Finally the sentence was written blow down on the advertisement was absolutely not true. It was most imperfect evening out I ever exprienced.</P>
      <P>I wish that you can provide a better service next time, and this time you need give back the money we paid.</P>
      <P>Sincerely</P>
      <P>Yu Phu Tung.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets.</P>
      <P>Since I moved to London to study English I have had a hard time to make intimate friendship with people around me.</P>
      <P>First it was because of the culture difference. It took quite long time to adjust in the multi culture in the language institue. Secondly the language ability was another issue. Even I could meet some friend, but I couldn't express my heat to them for we have different back ground and our first language were different.</P>
      <P>I really wished to have a friend can share everything is going in our lives. Finally I met Pat. She was a such wonderful person in our class. She tried to help others when they have difficult time at school. One day she realized that I was always been outside of circle.</P>
      <P>One day she invited me to her flat. Since then we have visited each other often and spent time together in weekend usally. We had a fantastic time together for three monthes. Even we could make a trip to Paris in the school holiday! We had many common interests in music, art and books.</P>
      <P>I thought that I found a good friend in my life. So I told her everything about my life. There were some stories I never told anyone before, but I had share with her all my secrets.</P>
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. Few days later I told her about my secret love story, it became a top gossip among my classmate. It was a nightmare!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
