<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR797*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>For the attention to the manager: I am writing to complain about the organization of the musical show that the Circle Theatre presented. Firstly, it was said that the stars who were invited to the estatement were Dany Brook and Tina Truelove. However, Dany Brook did not act and was replaced by another actor who was terribly disappointing on his performance. In addition, the event was supposed to start at 19.30 but we could not enjoy the show until 20.15. The advertisement for the show announced that we were able to visit the Theatre restaurant after the show but it was closed due to the Chef who leaded the Restaurant did not remember to bring the keys to open it. Also, the advertisement said that discounts for the tickets would be available, but it was not. To conclude, I would be grateful if the organization of the theatre bring my money back. yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets and she told her mother what had happened during the concert.</P>
      <P>Peter had a terribly problem with drugs. He started to consum the stuff at the age of twenty. He had problems at home because his mother wanted to settle down to Australia, but Peter was used to live in New York, overcrowded and surronded by people. Australia is a country too calm for him.</P>
      <P>We invited him to enjoy the concert of Texas but he started to make nonsenses because of the drugs. Firstly, he began to run around the crowd and also to hit the advertisements which announced the concert. A security guard saw it and put his attention on him. Pat stared at him and asked for help. The security guard heard her and agreeded with Pat that if Peter continued acting on this way he would obliged us to go out of the concert.</P>
      <P>He did it.</P>
      <P>When we arrived at home, Pat told to his mother what had happened.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
