<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR799*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you about the first prize I won in your competition. I am very pleased and I include the information you asked for.</P>
      <P>I prefer travelling in July because I am taking some important exams in September and I have planned to study in August. With reference to the accomodation I would rather stay in tent because I think it is the best way to socialize.</P>
      <P>For what concernes the activities I think that swimming and climbing are the most suitable for me. I have been swimming since I was three and I did a lot of courses. On the other hand I have never had a course of climbing even though I would like to take up this hobby.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask you something about the weather and clothes I should bring not to have to buy anything there. In addition I need to know whether meals are included or not in the accomodation so that I could decide how much I must have with me.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Mafalda D'Accatino</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I bet you want to know everything about my great experience at Luna Pop's concert last month. Before that I had never thought I would play with a famous group. But maybe you want to hear the story from the beginning.</P>
      <P>As you know Luna Pop is not my favourite group and I went to their concert only because Ake needed being accompanied. When we arrived she persuaded me to go the backstage because her boyfriend was the electrician of the band. It didn't sound very exciting to me but I accepted above all because I was curious. Unfortunately what I found wasn't what I expected. Everyone was upset, worried or angry and Lucre, Ake's boyfriend, explained that it was because their pianist had broken his arm and couldn't play. In that moment Ake exlaimed that I could play the piano. After that I tried to tell them I had just begun but within five minutes I was on the stage and I was playing that, luckily, easy tune.</P>
      <P>I think you can't believe in what I've told you but I won't forget this experience. This has been the first time I have realized that, maybe, playing the piano could be my future and, even though I was really frightened, I enjoyed staying on the stage with all those eyes on me.</P>
      <P>I wish you had been with me but I'm sure you understand what I felt.</P>
      <P>Love</P>
      <P>Mafalda</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
