<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR801*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>17th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I'm writing to complain about the musical show 'Over the Rainbow' I've visited it last evening in your 'Circle Theatre'. By the way I would enquire about some money back.</P>
      <P>I read your advertisement for the show and I decided to have a wonderful evening by visiting it. I believed in the phrase by which the advertisement ended: 'Your perfect evening out!' But nothing was perfect.</P>
      <P>The show should started at half past 7 pm but nothing happened. I waited and it becomes 8 o'clock pm - nothing happened. At quarter past 8 pm the show started and I was looking for Danny Brook and Tina Truelove. But I saw some foreign actors I didn't know. I was very wrong and afraid about it and I remember that this was the third problem this evening. By arriving at the theatre there were no discounts available. Now I asked myself if there will come another problem. The problem came. The restaurant, which I decided to visit after the show for eating something, was closed without any explaination and the perfect evening was completely unperfect.</P>
      <P>I think this are reasons enough for enquiring about some money back.</P>
      <P>I would be gladly to get an answer from you.</P>
      <P>Faithfully,</P>
      <P>Bergut Hunrtner</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>What will we wear 100 years from now?</P>
      <P>Fashion changed every year. Do you remember what people wore 100 years ago? And by the way do you believe that they also thought the fashion never changed? But the fashion changed.</P>
      <P>100 years ago the people wore long clothes and large robes. You can say they wore a lot of clothes at one time.</P>
      <P>Nowaday people wear lesser clothes. Often you causes very litte and short robes and tops. Often you show your skin because its popular and everyone do it. So it's possible to wear nothing in the future. A lot of thinks will be easier to do.</P>
      <P>But in the winter there's still a problem which is to solve. In the winter you'll freeze. But this problem is solving by itselfes. The sommers and winters get warmer. The season for this is the global warming, which is the salvation of the problem and another reason why this idea is possible.</P>
      <P>But by some situations you have to wear something. The clothes you'll wear will be very extraordinary because of their special kind of producing.</P>
      <P>So don't laugh about this idea. Think about this idea and perhaps you'll understand it. It's possible.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
