<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR802*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>17th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>On 14th June 2000 I went to see your "Over The Rainbow" musical show and I have a few points which I would like to bring to your attention.</P>
      <P>Your advertisement was featuring "Danny Brook and Tina Truelove" as the main characters but in fact some other people replaced them that evening.</P>
      <P>The time mentioned on the tickets was 19:30 however the show started at 20:15.</P>
      <P>As I came to London on holidays and purchased "The London City Guide" I saw your advertisement explaining that people could buy discounted tickets for £5 in advance. Well I tried to do so but the lady at the desk told me that they were quotas available at that price but were already sold out!</P>
      <P>After the show we tried to go to your restaurant but unfortunately it was closed for renovation!</P>
      <P>I was very disappointed of my supposed "perfect evening out" to your theatre and due to all the above-mentioned reasons I am asking for a complete refund on the two attached tickets.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>MODERN TECHNOLOGY</P>
      <P>"Technology" is an appealing as well as an interesting word for me. From ancient times up to now this science has allowed the world and human-beings to develop positively and negatively.</P>
      <P>Egyptians, Mayas, Incas, etc. were civilisations with great knowledge because they were mastering most of the science fields we deal with today.</P>
      <P>Back in the 30's the different governments invented guns, battleships and all kinds of weapons for their armies. The military technology has affected our lives more than what we think because most of the equipments we use were originally created by those people.</P>
      <P> The fast and growing computer industry is giving us less and less physical work due to a mechanical concept. Biotechnology is providing us with the latested discoveries to heal or improve the human body to its most efficient state. Transport means are also part of the overall technology and allow us to go faster, further than before with less effort.</P>
      <P>Besides all those improvements and confort I can't stop thinking where all this will lead us. I am keen on technology because I believe it should improve our lives however I dislike the idea that such a science might fall or had already fallen in wicked hands.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
