<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR803*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam:</P>
      <P>I am writing this letter I order to complain my unpleasant experience in your theatre. Two days ago, I went to see the musical show "over the rainbow" at your theatre. The advertised beginning time is 19:30. But due to some unknown reasons, the play didn't start until 20:15. The audience were anxious and bored.</P>
      <P>What made things even worse was that the leading actor Danny Brook did not appear at the stage at all. A second-class actor took the place of him. We felt totally disappointed and cheated. After the show, I was hungry and tired. As your poster suggested, I intended to rest for a while at your restaurant. But when I got there, it had closed. In addition, the conductor didn't offer me any discounts as you had advertised in the poster when I bought the ticket.</P>
      <P>I am sorry to say that I do not enjoy the evening at your theatre at all. I hope you can pay me the money back as compensation. I am waiting for your reply.</P>
      <P>Yours Faithfully </P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Modern technology has changed my daily life in two ways. First with a lot of advanced techniques being put into practical use, our living condition becomes more and more convenient and comfortable. When we look around in the house, it is easy to find things like these: microwave oven, TV set, computer, etc. All these equippments are the applications of modern science. When you are planning to travel, you can choose train, car or even plane as your transportation. Without the development of modern technology, it may take your several years to reach the destination.</P>
      <P>Second, Modern technology makes communication much easier and more enjoyable. With the spreading use of Internet, people living in different parts of the world can chat with each other through the web. And, we can also share important informations with other people. The development of information technology has changed the world into "an earth village".</P>
      <P>Modern technology plays an important role in our life. I am hoping to devote myself into the development of it.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
