<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR810*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P> Mr/Mrs... manager</P>
      <P>I am writing to you about your musical show "OVER THE RAINBOW". I have come and see the theatre but I am very disappointed. I have come to see a good theatre but I did not. Danny Brook was going to be the starring actor but he wasn not, actor took his place. That was very disappointing. The play was going to start at 19.30 but is was very delay It start at 20.15.</P>
      <P>And this is not all there is more. In the advertisement you write that there is biscount available but It was not. Also the restaurant was closed because there was not left any food.</P>
      <P>I think the next time you write an advertiment you write it with the right information.</P>
      <P>I did not have a perfect evening with so many proplems. So I am asking to retern me some money back.</P>
      <P>I hope to hear from you soon</P>
      <P>Yours fouthfouly </P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Techology is a bad or a good efection? What does it offer to us? How people use modern technology? Let see if we use the modern technology we may have good and bad results.</P>
      <P>In 18 cetury technology started to grow more and more 20 century named the century of technology. During that time technology made a great step.</P>
      <P>Thechnology helps people. It informs people, hospital use modern technogoly computer helps staders help people do their job.</P>
      <P>But modern technology do a lot of bad thinks. A lot of county buy gans for their safty as they say but they buy them do kill people.</P>
      <P>Modern technology is effecting people good and bad way. We have to be very careful with technology. Technogoly can't never stop going forward so people always go farward but with same effection of modern techology. Technology is in our life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
