<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR811*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Matthias Hähnel</P>
      <P>104 Mühlenstrasse</P>
      <P>09111 Chemnik</P>
      <P>Germany</P>
      <P>The manager of the Circle Theatre</P>
      <P>Dear manager,</P>
      <P>During my stay in London I went to your Circle Theatre to see the musical 'Over the rainbow'. In the advertisment you promised a perfect evening out, but it wasn't. So with this letter I want to ask for some money back. Now I want to explain the problems. It was very disappointing for me that the actor wasn't Danny Brook, how it was told in the advertisment. It was also told that the evening shows are starting 19.30, but it started 20.15. I had to buy a £20 ticket because discounts were not available. After the show I wanted to go to the theatre restaurant with my friends, but it was closed because of illness. So I want to ask for my money back, also because I had to pay for but cancel the arranged taxi because of the wrong starting time in the advertisment. I hope you will answer my letter and correct the problems in your theatre.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully Adolf Schmidt</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>At first you have to define what is meant by 'modern technology'. For me modern technology are things like personal computers, mobile phones, keyboards, video recorders, Hifi sound systems, television or even cars. But are they are usefull in every situation and everywhere? My oppinion is that modern technology can help you to save time. In my case for example my car is very time-saving. If I want to go to training I need not wait for the bus, and so I need not start one and a half hour before training I start a half hour before. So I save one hour, which I can use for other hobbies or for homework or something else. The same problem with mobile phones, if I got one I needn't go to the public phones, I save time. If I got Internet I can send e-mails, I needn't go to the letter box, I save time. In my daily life I can save time, but I think every body should use his saved time for things like hiking, walking, swimming, for a "natural life" and not for a life in a technical world with stress and sorrows because we are humans and not robots. We should also move our body and not only use our brain.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
