<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR812*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I recently visited your theatre to see the musical show "over the rainbow". I was very disappointed because the actors wasn't Danny Brook and Tina Truelove. Instead of them you had different actors. Then the show delayed, it started at 20:15, not at 19.30. I had to wait 45 minutes! Another point is that the discounts wasn't available although I could red it before at your notice.</P>
      <P>After the show was finished, I decided to drink something, but as I arrived in the restaurant it had been closed. But in your advertisement you wrote that people can visit the resaurant after the show. I can't understand such kind of mistakes.</P>
      <P>You wrote also that the evening would be perfect. For me it wasn't and because of that I ask you to give me my money back. If you can't give me all the money back then do it particularly.</P>
      <P>I give you my phone number, you can reach me from 8 o'clock till 12 o'clock: 08532143251</P>
      <P>Please call me back soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Carolina Schwitt</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed your daily life?</P>
      <P>Modern technology has changed my daily life in the point that all I do is becoming more comfortable. For example when I have to write a letter or do my homework, I always write it on the computer. If I search something like a telefonnumber or an adress I also look it up from the internet. I use also the internet when I need any informations for example I need them for school or private for myself. A few years ago I had to go in a library and look it up in many books. Most that took a long time.</P>
      <P>I think the advantage of modern technology is that all I do goes very fast and I have more time for my hobbys or for friends.</P>
      <P>Another important point for me is that things like listening music or watching TV sounds better and the pictures on TV are being impoved, because the machines become more better. And also a good intention for me is the Handy, because everywhere I go I can talk to other people.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
