<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR813*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear manager of the Circle Theatre,</P>
      <P>Last night, I cam to your musical show, "Over the rainbow" and I was very disappointed because it wasn't what you writed in your advertisement. For example, your advertisement said that the starring were Danny Brook and Tina Truelove, but at the show they were not them! They were Kevin Starr and Jessica Richmond. For me, this a big mistake. This event was not the only one because another problem was the respect of the time. Your advertisement said that the show will start at 19:30 PM, but it has started at 20:15 PM. I don't like to have such big change in time. The third problem was that it was writting that the discounts were available, but when I get there it was not true. The fourth problem was that the theatre restaurant was supposed to be open after the show, but once again it was a lie because the restaurant was closed for renovation. After that, I can tell you that I spend the worst evening in all my life at your show and that one more time your advertisement lied about "You will have a perfect evening!" After all these explanations, I am sure that you will understand that I would like to have my money back and that I was disappointed last night. So I wish to hear soon about you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerly</P>
      <P>Leia Beroni</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed your daily life?</P>
      <P>Modern technology, such as computer, car and other else, changed my life in many different ways like communication, traveling and working. For example, a car, which is used from everyone everyday, changed my daily life in the sens that I don't need my dad or my mum to go to ice-skating or to go to work. I can do it by myself and for me it is important not only because of the technology, but because I can show that I am responsable. With this car I can see the world, not exactly, but I can travel and visit other countries that Switzerland.</P>
      <P>Another technology that changed my life is the computer because you can do many things with it like homeworks, works, photos, but the most important at my eyes is the communication with my friends from different parts of the world by the web. This a big walk in the technology and I can say that it is the most important for me because I like to have a lot of friends. So I spend almost one hour every day on the web. At last technology that I would like to bring out is the TV. This is a good one because you can see what is happening around you and everywhere else on Earth. Naturally technology is everywhere even in the kitchen, for example a special plate or else, and I could talk a lot about them, but I think that the one here are the most important in the change of my daily life. </P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
