<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR814*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan</P>
      <P>Thank you for your information. I am very happy to win this prize but also I have some questions about this Camp.</P>
      <P>I would like to know if it is possible to travel to this Camp on July because for me it is the best time and I can not travel before or after according to my employer. While this two weeks I would like to stay in tents because you can be nearer to the nature as you are on log cabins. I like to go camping. From the activities I choose Basketball and Golf. In Basketball I am very good, because I have played in a Basketball-Team for ten years. But in Golf I am a beginner.</P>
      <P>I would like to know if it is necessary for me to take some clothes with me for the sport activities? Also I would like to know how much money I should take with me. If you could tell me this answers it would be very nice.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Aydo Ackermann</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable</P>
      <P>I think shopping is not always an enjoyable thing because there are a lot of things which are not good. For example: you need a lot of money each month for shopping, and a part of this money is only for buying the necessaryiest things like bread and other things to eat. I enjoy shopping when I can buy some clothes.</P>
      <P>Also a problem while the shopping is that most there are so many people and a lot of traffic in all shopping-centres. All the people are there most on the same day because there are not a lot of other possibilities for shopping while the week for the employees.</P>
      <P>I think one possibility is to buy your things on the internet, because then you have not to invest a lot of time for buying all this things, and they bring you the things at home In the end I think it is the best if you have the possibility to shop when there are not so many people because then you have enough time and you are not stressed.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
