<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR815*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>13 June. 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am so marvellous about winning the competition. I am answering what you would like to know some information from me.</P>
      <P>At first, I am able to travel only in July because I will have on holiday in July, furthermore I have a important exam in November. Secondly I would prefer to stay in tent as it will be natural life while I am at the Camp. Thirdly I keen on playing tennis and taking some photography.</P>
      <P>In spite of the fact that the weathe is bad, I play tennis. I collect strange photography by myself. Finally I am wondering that how much money I need for myself and what kind of clothes I need.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Bae Ki Seul</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Title: Speaking activity</P>
      <P>I like speaking activity while I am in the class. During that time I can talk some secret things or private with class-mates. After that we know each other more than before. In addition speaking activity include everything to learn English such as listening, speaking, grammer as well. Other lesson, the teacher teaches lots of things which are grammer, English culture... etc. It might be good. However all students are passive. So it can be boring. give a topic and then discussion about it. I know that what my friends think and like. It is real life who we are. Also the film must be funny. If a film is boring, nobody will see it. During speaking, there are lots of happening such as, some students can't understand what the other students say and their culture. Having fun and knowing new knowledge. It makes us laugh.</P>
      <P>So I think that speaking activity should be filmed as you can see and know real us and funny as well.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
