<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR816*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writing in reply to your letter that I have just received. I am very happy to win first prize in your competition. - two weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A. I am also very excited about it.</P>
      <P>If it is possible I would like to travel in July. This is the only month that I will be free. Because I am studying the Management and Finance at university and it will finish at the end of June. I will be in italy in August. Because I need to improve my italian and I am taking a very important exam next year.</P>
      <P>I would be appreciate it if I could stay in tents at Camp. Because I usually go on camping-site holiday, with my friends. It is great fun. I really like staying in tents.</P>
      <P>It is also written in your letter that we will have to chance to do two activities. I am really good at playing tennis and singing. I have been playing tennis for five years and I love it. I play the classicial guitar and I also sing songs. I have been playing the classicial guitar for three years. It is quite difficult but I like difficult things.</P>
      <P>I wonder if you could tell me about the wheather and what kind of clothes I have to bring with me. I would also like to know how much money I need.</P>
      <P>I look forward to receiving your reply</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>RIGHT TIME FOR SHOPPING</P>
      <P>Why do people like shopping? First answer is that they need shopping. Second answer is that the shopping makes everyone happy. If I get bored I can't stay at home and I feel going shopping. When I do shopping I don't think about any problems I have. It's very relaxing for me but if it is possible to do shopping. Sometimes it can be nightmare if you can't find something that you are looking for.</P>
      <P>I think the weekends are not the right time to go shopping. I went shopping last week with my friend she needed to buy a nightdress. We spent for three hours and we couldn't buy anything. It was incredibly crowded. We couldn't even move and the most people were just looking and were wasting of their time.</P>
      <P>If you are in a hurry, don't go shopping! It is not really good idea to go shopping if you don't have enough time.</P>
      <P>Imagine you have three children and you are going shopping with them. I can tell you how bad situation you are in because when I was a child I always had an argument with my mother about shopping. I can remember how upset I was if my mother didn't buy what I wanted and how much I cried. It was very ashameful for my mum. She was also very angry. Because she never managed to get me out from the toy shop.</P>
      <P>As you see shopping is not always enjoyable. Always make sure that is right time to go shopping.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
