<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR821*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about the musical show, which I have seen in The Circle Theatre on 6th June. On that date, I decided to spend one evening seeing a musical show as I was on holiday in London and was interested in musial show. But things started to go wrong from the beginning.</P>
      <P>The first problem was the price of tickets. I expected to buy ticket cheaply but no discounts were available. Another problem was that the show started forty-five minutes late. I found the theater rather noisy as I arrived very early to sit in the front row. Although I got a bit annoyed, I tried to have a good time.</P>
      <P>However, something wrong came up again. The actor 'Danny brook', whom you advertised in the brocher, did not play a part in the show. And I really disappointed from the different actor's performance. He kept forgetting his lines. Finally, I went to the restaurant to have something for dinner after show, but it was closed because it was refurbishing interior. I am not satisfied with your show as it was compeletly different from advertisement.</P>
      <P>I am therefore writing to ask for a full refund. I expect to receive a cheque for £20. look forward to hearing soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P> </P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>It's comletely different!</P>
      <P>Have you ever been to fashion show named "New trend, New Millenium"? 'It's completely different! How can we go our wearing thouse clothes?' This is what my friend said the other day when she went to see the show with me.</P>
      <P>These days, new designs and new trends are coming out every day, sometimes we are shocked by them in comparison with the days we were young. However, It doesn't seem to take long for most of young people to get used to it, so we can imagine what clothes will be like in the future.</P>
      <P>In my opinion, I believe that clothes indicate individual's creativity as well as social situation. We never know whether we might look like robots because it will be the electronic age. On the other hand, some people refuse to wear that sort of clothes so they prefre to wear nothing.</P>
      <P>Let's face it. Clothes are always changing. But the question no one answer is what is fashion in 100 year's time? </P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
