<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR823*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I would like to say that I am surprise to received the letter from you. I read the information as you gave to me, it is very interesting. It is very good due.</P>
      <P>According to Camp California in the U.S.A. I expect to traveling on July because I will have a long holiday break on that time and my children have to go to France with student's school on July as well. I think, it will be very good time to traveling by without worries.</P>
      <P>How is about an accommodation. I prefer to live in tents because I feel very natural. Can you imagine how exsiting when we stay in the dark and very quite and we can hear a sound of animal. How's amazing that?</P>
      <P>When I arrived there, I would to painting and take a photography because both of its was my hobby. I have been doing a lot of them when I have got a free time and when I feel empressted where I have been. I think I can do it very well.</P>
      <P>Fainally I would like to ask you about I have to spent any money over there without my shopping and how is the weather over there on July because I will prepare the clothes as usedful.</P>
      <P>By the way I have to say thank you very much for everything that you was offer me and I look forward the further information from you.</P>
      <P>your sincerely</P>
      <P>ZITA ZALAI</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>How are you? It was very long time as I didn't write the letter to you. I hope, you will feel better when you finished my letter.</P>
      <P>Today I going to write about the experience of helping at a pop concert as I went from last month, it has got a lot of thing to talk about.</P>
      <P>Firstly it is about the hall which they used for concert. It is very big hall including the sound system and the light at the. It was brillian.</P>
      <P>Secondly it is the super star as they came to show at concert. They are very cool.</P>
      <P>By the way I had done many thing in that concert. I had to connect with people who responsible about ticket. They had to check when people came in the hall and I was the one who checking the tickets as well. You know, you have to very strongly when you have to do that because when people came in they couldn't weait to go at frount and they are try to go over very quickly. So you have to explaining too many time to make people clamed down and standed in the row. It was very hard for me and I won't do it again.</P>
      <P>In the further more if you want to go there.</P>
      <P>miss you,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
