<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR824*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen,</P>
      <P>Thanks a lot for giving me the prize. I am so happy because of that. Thank you very much for treating me in that way.</P>
      <P>Appart from that, here you are the repplies that you asked me for:</P>
      <P>- concerning to the date: I can go in July because it's my holidays month. That was my boss told me.</P>
      <P>- About the accomodation, as I read, you can offer me log cabins or tents. From my point of view, I think tents are better than log cabins, so please, could you accomodate me in a tent?</P>
      <P>- Activities: I am very keen on surfing because, where I live, I can pactice it every day. I also want to "book in" singing because I love singing very much and I am always singing in my house.</P>
      <P>Thank you so much for your attention.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Javi Fernández</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Why don't you buy the green one? Oh, no! That's horrible, mum! This is one of a normal scene when a mother and her daughter are buying and getting clothes from the shelves. That is what most of the women love. They love going to a shopping centre and put lots of clothes on. That's so good when you have money for joy it but, appart from that, there are many problems.</P>
      <P>On the one hand, a big problem are the children. When they go to shopping with their mothers, they want to buy all the things that their sight reach: doors, little cars, films... but, when their mothers see a good thing that they want to buy, there are the children: crying because they are tired for shopping all the day.</P>
      <P>On the other hand there is a big problem: the mony. People buy and buy unnecessary things but, when they arrives in their houses, they can see an empty wallet.</P>
      <P>So, do you believe that a shopping bag like this one is an enjoyable shopping day?</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
