<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR825*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen,</P>
      <P>I would like to thank you for the letter I have just received. First of all I would like to point out that it is a great pleasure for me to take part in your competition.</P>
      <P>I would like to assure you that I would do my best to be the one of the winners in your competition. Now, If I would like to state some of the information that you may need.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I have to say that I can travel only in July this year. This is mostly because I have a job and I have made further arrangements for the other summer months.</P>
      <P>Secoundly, I would be very grateful if you can accommodate me in tents rather than long cabins. It is mostly because I like fresh air at night. From the list of activities in which I will have a chance to compete I have choosen: basketball and swimming. I am very good at those kinds of sports and think that I could be the winner.</P>
      <P>Finally, I would like to ask you how many clothes and how much money should I take with me. I will wait to hearing from you, soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Piotr Kaczmarski</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>I do agree with the opinion that shopping is not always enjoyable. Nowadays many young people like to do their shopping. But, isn't it a kind of entertaintment?</P>
      <P>In the first place, I would like to point out that to go shopping does not always mean to buy something. A lot of people, especially women, go to do their shopping only for fan. In such a situation they are looking for something that they might buy.</P>
      <P>But, what about real shopping. I mean shopping with a real purpose.</P>
      <P>For example, emagine that you are a bride and you have to buy an appropriate suit. It's a real nightmare when you try to match everything: from the size, the colour to the sawings of the suit that is acceptable for everyone.</P>
      <P>On the other hand it is a great achievement for you when you buy the suit that is perfect for everyone.</P>
      <P>To sum up, I would like to say that shopping is enjoyable when you are going only for fan. But, when you want to buy something special it's a real nightmare.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
