<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR826*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/madam,</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter and your congratulations. I never thought that I would win the competition. It is really wonderful. I can stay at Camp California in the U.S.A. for two weeks.</P>
      <P>I am a student at Portsmouth College and the end of this term is 23 June, so I can only travel in July. I wonder if it is all right for that time. And for my accommodation. I prefer live in a log cabin, because it is more comfortable. I like to relax there and enjoy the atmosphere when I live in.</P>
      <P>I like to do some activities in water and my favourite activity is swimming. Before I came England, I swam every weekend in my country even in winter, so I choose to do some swimming and sailing while I am at the camp.</P>
      <P>Actually, my mind has already gone there, I can't wait even for a minute. I want to go there now.</P>
      <P>By the way, I would like to know the shopping especially for clothes, I want to buy some for myself. And do you think I need to exchange money before I go there?</P>
      <P>I look forward to your letter.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>To: Mr Ted</P>
      <P>From: Meng</P>
      <P>Subject: About daily life at our school</P>
      <P>Introduction</P>
      <P>This report is aim to research the students about their daily life at school and give some suggestion about it.</P>
      <P>What do students do now?</P>
      <P>Lots of student normally have classes in the morning. And sometimes they do something in the library by themselves in the afteroon. For instance, reading, looking for some information or using computer.</P>
      <P>What do they think about it?</P>
      <P>The arts students want to learn another foreign language. Moreover, some foreign students hope there will be some English classes that aim to the examination.</P>
      <P>Most of them want to do more activities in the afternoon.</P>
      <P>Recommendations</P>
      <P>Open some foreign language classes at part-time for the students who is interested in it.</P>
      <P>Let foreign students do more excises about English to help them pass the exam.</P>
      <P>Using the equipment and area what we have to organise some activities.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
