<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR827*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear the Manager</P>
      <P>I am writing this letter to complane about the Circle Theatre. I went to the theatre last weekend to see "Over the rainbow'. I read your advertisement. However, it was different from the fact. I had a very disappointing evening.</P>
      <P>Firstly, Danny Brook did not act as you had said. A different actor acted in stead of him. it was disappointing.</P>
      <P>Secondly Discounts did not availabe. Even though I brought discount taken which I was given by travel agency.</P>
      <P>What's more, the theatre reastaurant had been closed, when the show finished. Because the show started 20:15. It should have started at 19:30 as you said at advertisement, or you should not have closed before the show finished.</P>
      <P>It was not perfect evening whatoever. I would like to ask for money back.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Fashion of the Future.</P>
      <P>My grandchildren will wear fish-liked-suit 100 years from now. As you can imagine, people will be lazier than now. Everything will be usefull and combinient, even fashion.</P>
      <P>More or less</P>
      <P>The clothes will be more comfortable but less decorations. People will put on fitted-suit such as diving suit. or perhaps nothing to wear. For instance, people would not care about what other people see. Or maybe we will not need to meet each other no longer.</P>
      <P>Male or Female</P>
      <P>Between male and female will be not important for clothes in 100 years time. The most important things is the fugure, such as long legs or pear-sharped.</P>
      <P>Traditional or Comtemporaly</P>
      <P>Even though the clothes become so, the traditional clothes will be continue. Because the fashion has repeated many times in the circle.</P>
      <P>In concrution, the clothes will more interesting than now. for everybody</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
