<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR829*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Tuesday, 13nd June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Ms Ryan,</P>
      <P>I've just received the letter telling me that I've won first prize in your competition. I guess you can imagine how happy and excited I am at this time.</P>
      <P>Here are the few information about my stay at Camp California, that you asked my to complete:</P>
      <P>For the date of the travel, I wonder if it would be possible in July because I'm going to pass a very important exam at the end of June. Two weeks in the USA would be a great occasion for me to relax after that.</P>
      <P>You asked my to chose my accommodation between tents and cabins. I prefer sleeping in a log cabin (I made a very bad experience with tents while I was camping with friends last year)</P>
      <P>The activities listed in your letter seemded to be all interesting. I choosed to do baskelball (I play in a club, I have a good level) and photography (there must be beautiful pictures to take in California).</P>
      <P>Talking about California, I suppose that the weather is hot there in Summer. Could you please tell me if I have to take special clothes with me. If it's not two much to ask, could you also tell me how much money I should take with me for food or evening activities at the camp</P>
      <P>Looking for you to receive,</P>
      <P>Dominique</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Last week I had planned to change my old basketball shoes. So I took the train to Lausanne (I live in Lavaux and it's impossible to find a corect pair of sneakers in this whole damned city!) to buy a new pair to play outdoor this summer.</P>
      <P>After having visited shops during 10 hours and tried at least 2,000 shoes, I finally found what I was looking for. The shoes of my dreams (well designed and not too expensive) So I went back to the station, very proud of me with my sneakers in a white plastic bag and a great smile on my face.</P>
      <P>I stayed that happy during the travel, thinking of how cool I would look on the playground with my brand new shoes on.</P>
      <P>As I jumped off the train, I met a friend of mine. I immediately wanted to show him what I had bought to make him jealous. I took the white plastic bag and... Oh my god! There was no more plastic bag, I had forgotten it in the train!</P>
      <P>How stupid I am! It seems like I will have to play with old shoes for one more summer...</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
