<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR760*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>13th June 2000</P>
      <P>Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>Competition Organiser</P>
      <P>Dear Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing in response to your letter, in which you told me I am the winner in your competition, and my intention is to try to give you all the information you may need according to your letter.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel in July because I had another trip to Spain in August, that is the perfect month for me, otherwise I would not travel to Spain.</P>
      <P>About accommodation, I would prefer tents instead of log cabins and the reason is I have never used tents and this could be a very exciting experience for me.</P>
      <P>The two activities which I find better for me are swimming and sailing. I love the sea, that is why I became interested in those activities since I was ten, therefore I have a lot of experience in both.</P>
      <P>Could you give me some advice about the weather in California?</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for everything.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>ION GAYARRE</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>13th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>Thank you for asking about my latest good experience, I let you know what the important details were.</P>
      <P>As you know I helped at a pop concert last month, I did things as unusual in me as cleaning instruments, organise people, and also look after the clothes of the artists. In fact everything was very easy, the instruments were already clean, and with the clothes my job was only wait there and give them what they asked for. Organise people involved, just a couple of things, say to people how to do the same as me and when.</P>
      <P>The most exciting thing was to be able to speak to the singers, the whole environment, and of course to the listen to the Concert in the very first position.</P>
      <P>All that I can say now is that I would do it again, I will never forget that day.</P>
      <P>Looking forward to seeing you,</P>
      <P>Best Wishes</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
