<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR830*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I received your letter last week and was surprised to see that I won a competition. It is the first time it happens to me.</P>
      <P>Unfortunately I'm free only in July. Actually I will be busy working abroad until the end of June and will be on holidays with my family in August.</P>
      <P>You asked me which accomodation I would prefer. It's ages since I have been sleeping in a tent and I would be happy to experiment it again. It will remind me some wonderful experiences.</P>
      <P>According to the activities, I would like to do some painting, which I am quite good at. The second activity I chose is sailing. I went two times on a sailing ship without doing anything, therefore have I got no experience at all.</P>
      <P>May I ask you how much money do I need and which sort of clothes do you advise me to take?</P>
      <P>I look forward to your answer and to the camp, naturally.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your last letter. As you asked me in your letter, I will try to explain my wonderful experience at this pop concert.</P>
      <P>First of all you have to know that it wasn't a common pop concert, but a real open air festival. It isn't the first year that I work there. However this year wasn't like last year.</P>
      <P>My job was as simple as selling ice-creams. You might say that it is quite boring, but it was so funny. Everybody was so relaxed; we were singing and dancing while selling ice-creams in our little van. Byran Adams himself bought me an ice-cream.</P>
      <P>It was amazing experience. What I particularly liked about it was that the staff was like a big family. Everybody was ready to help each other. I was really impressed by this solidarity and friendship which is quite rare in Switzerland.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you and wish you all the best.</P>
      <P>Love from</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
