<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR834*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>São Rafael, 13/06/00</P>
      <P>Dear Helen</P>
      <P>I'm pleased to receive your litter and realy happy that I won the first prize.</P>
      <P>I would prefer to travel only on July because it's when my vacations start. I could even think about skyping's school. July is also good because the wethear is warm and I could enjoyed mor the time that I will spend in the camp. I would prefer the tends because I'll be in touch with the nature and I could listen the sounds of the night. The two activities that I've chosen are Climbing and Photography. I've already climbed for four months on walls, indoor climbing. I think I can handde it very well. I've choosen Photography because I love to take pictures! I've never chose any classes or training but I think I can take very good pictures. I would like to learn more about developing films.</P>
      <P>I have some questions myself, I would like to know:</P>
      <P>. if I have to take special equipement to the activities that I've chosen</P>
      <P>. If I have to take lots of clothes or is there a service to wash them.</P>
      <P>. What kind of chosen do I have to take</P>
      <P>. If is there a phone, a fax or e-mail so I can be in touch with my familie?</P>
      <P>. If I have to take any money. If yes how much?</P>
      <P>I hope I've answered all you questions and I would be please if mine could also be answered.</P>
      <P>your sincerely,</P>
      <P>Sabrina Rodriguez</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>São Rafael, 13th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>How are you? What have you been doing there in New York? Did you find a girlfriend? Yesterday was Valentine's day here in Portugal, In particurely I had to spend it alone... again.</P>
      <P>I'm writing to you to tell you about a pop concert that happend here in São Rafael. Red Hot Chilli Pepers came here for a short time and they played at the "Chedicard Hall". It was realy cool because I did some backstage job. I helped with the clothing with some paperwork, with the microphones, with the computers. I was everywher. I was kind of a "handy girl". I did a little bit of everything.. The best part was when the band arrived. I took lots of pictures, asked for authographs and I even gave them my cel phone number! They promissed me that they would call me some day, what I particulary doubt. Some thing that was also great was to watch the show from the back stage. It's an unique experience. I wished you could be there with me.</P>
      <P>I hope you answer this letter as quik as possible with lots of thing to tell me.</P>
      <P>Lots of kisses and hugs</P>
      <P>Your pen friend</P>
      <P>Sabrina Rodriguez</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
