<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR836*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Mr Jon Stevens,</P>
      <P>Last month I have been in London for a week to visit your wonderful city and with the intention of seeing at your Thetre the famous musical show Over the rainbow but in all my life I have never had such a disappointing evening.</P>
      <P>First of all my cousin, who lives there, had had many problems with the tickets. The starring changed and this was the worst surprise I could have. My greatest wish was seeing Danny Brook's performance; you know it's the best singer. But instead of him there was a unknown young actor. What a pity, I thought.</P>
      <P>I arrived there in time, 19:15 in fact you wrote that the show would be starting at 19:30, but I had to wait until 20.15. What an absurd thing, don't you think so? The quality of the show wasn't as high as I expected. I hadn't tought for a restaurant to go to after the show, because if the advertisement had been right, there should had to be a luxury restaurant where I could eat. But it was closed because it was under construction.</P>
      <P>Because of the quality of the evening I spent, the only thing you can do is giving me back at least the half of the cost of ticket. To apologise and give the impression of being a serious theatre. I'd rather I had been at home seeing on TV my Italy!</P>
      <P>I hope that my wish is being accepted.</P>
      <P>Your Sinceraly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>We are in the ages of the technologic development it's out of doubt.</P>
      <P>What could be out of control of technology? Since the scientific revolution and the Industrial Revolution, between 17th and 18th century there have been sudden changes in our daily way of living.</P>
      <P>Nowadays especially in the west area of the world science and technology have done great, enormous steps in directions of the progress. Not only for the great nations, but also for every their inhabitants.</P>
      <P>Today it's absurd not knowing how a computer works, or how to use Internet</P>
      <P>I can buy, today, a book being comfortable at home, can communicate with other friends faster than before. I can have my homeworks done by a calculator etc. In future I wish I could fly on my own!</P>
      <P>For me it's very important to have my mobile and computer never broken. I think I should become crazy without them, not only me but the majority of us.</P>
      <P>But sometimes I'd rather to switch them off and think of what I could waste, like love and friendship. I wish all the world would do the same.</P>
      <P>Vico says that progress gives up when Man have noticed that he have been wasting those values.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
