<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR840*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>31-40</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>I received your letter which says I won the first prize in your competition - two weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A. I apreicate it and I thank you a lot that you have chosen me as a winner. I acxepted it and I want to inform you that I can travel only on July because I have booked my anual leave that period. Also, I prefer to stay in tents because I have memories from my childhood. Every years my parents used to sent me for holidays at Camps on the mountains so I would like to stay for a while in the same accommodation, and environment. Also, I prefer swimming and painting. I started to learn how to swim when I was 7 years old. My parents brought me to the sea side every weekend so I was used to be inside the water all the seasons. I have taken part in races twice in my life, where I was successful. Also, I like painting from young age, and I have taken part in a public exhibition, where I won the first prize. I would like to ask how much money I should have with me, where can I keep them? What about the clothes, you don't mention anything. Do I need something special or ordinary clothes?</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely </P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I would like to write about my experience that I had, when I enjoyed helping at a pop concert in my neighbourhood.</P>
      <P>I am a member in the council team so I decided to help them at a pop concert that was organized in the last month. I helped them to prepare the room for the bads and I decorated the place for the singers. Also, I assisted them to choose the right instruments and to test them. It took a long time to testifite the speakers and the microphones. Unless this preparation, I also took part to the concert. I helped them to the music and to the songs. It was a quite difficult assiment but I got very good experience. I understood it when the concert had finished. The audients was excited and I cannot discribe my happyness. It was some thing that I didn't expect. Also, it happen first time in my life. I still have the sound of the music in my ears and the voices of the young people who were accompaning our songs. I enjoyed very much and I want to tranfere my enjoyment to you though this letter.</P>
      <P>yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
