<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR841*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you to give some requiered information. First of all, I am glad to hear that I won the first prize in your competition. I am happy to visit the United States under your organisation.</P>
      <P>Actually, I would like to go to Camp California next July because I have got two weeks holiday then. I also will be pleased to stay in log cabins. My experience in camping is not so huge to stay in tents for 2 weeks.</P>
      <P>Therefore, you asked me what activities I would like to join. Surfing is something that I have ever wanted to try. As you can see, I have abosolutly no experience in it. Will it be possible to join a surf school? For the second activity I have chosen photography. I enjoy taking pictures of landscapes, I have also visited a photography course. So that my level is not beginners anymore.</P>
      <P>Moreover, could you please tell me what kind of clothes I should take with me? What kind of money is used?</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to going on holidays.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Mr Oliver Herre</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Brighton, 13th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>Excuse me that I didn't write you sooner. As you know, I was fairly busy with my studying for my First Certificate.</P>
      <P>The concert was absolute marvellous! So many happy people in the crowds, that the atmosphere was infectious. Anyway, what you wanted to know was what has been my job. Actually my job was not really stressful, but I had contact and access to all the famous Pop Stars. I had to bring them refreshments. That has been my dream since my childhood.</P>
      <P>I was a little bit disappointed about their attitude. They didn't really appreciate my service. Some of them were quite rude. Apart from that, it was an amazing experience. Whatever, if you ever will have the opportunity to do something like this then do it without hesitating. I liked to see their way of life.</P>
      <P>I hope you will write me very soon and I hope you know more about my concert experience in the backstage area.</P>
      <P>Lots of love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
