<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR842*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>To. Mr or Mrs Manager of Circle Theatre.</P>
      <P>Hi. My name is Taeron Jon. And I would like to inform you that something is not right and unfair about your theatre. I recently had a week's holiday in London. During I stay I went to your theatre to see a musical show and unfortunatly I had a very disappointing evening.</P>
      <P>The advertisement that you distributed through all the magazines wee totally untrue. Which so called "Rip off".</P>
      <P>First of all you said Danny Brook is in the play but different actor was in the roll. It was just unbelievably disappointing because the reason I mean main reason which made me to go was to see Danny Brook.</P>
      <P>Secondly about the time. If it's delayed you should have told us before. Not waiting there for almost 1 hour doing nothing. Due to late start it finished at 1 AM and my taxi which I booked just left so I had to wait out side for another hour to get a taxi. It was freezing out side and I got horrible cold for that.</P>
      <P>lastly about the ticket advertisment saids 'Discouts Available' but no way I had to pad full £ 20.00 and restaurant was closed because of rebuilding something. How ever the point that it am trying to say is you just ruined my hoilday. For me, It's not easy to have holiday and your play just blew my precious time away.</P>
      <P>Let me make it clear, you blew my time and money. I don't thing your play worth £ 20.00.</P>
      <P>Your advertisment was un fair. As you are a manager, you have resposbillity to justify this problem. and I have right to get a fair treatment as a costomer.</P>
      <P>So therefore I would like you to pay some money back. I am not asking for full payment but minimum 50% that it paid for nothing but the disappoint.</P>
      <P>Thank you.</P>
      <P>Yours</P>
      <P>Taeron Jon</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Fashion of the future.</P>
      <P>Fashion, what is fashion? Popular design of cloths. In particular time? Maybe. But I say fashion is Artistic insperation which expressed by fabric and all sort of material. In some way, fashion is combined with science as well.</P>
      <P>Now a days fashion play big roll in our daily life. Million kinds of fashion magazines and News paper tells you how much people are interested in fashion.</P>
      <P>What about after 100 years? I believe we'll be more into fashionable stuffs. As I said before, fashion is somehow influenced by science and insperations that we get from all sort of enviroment.</P>
      <P>Development of science produce new materials like water proof or fire proof fabrics. For example Castum of Astronuts.</P>
      <P>These days we are very intrested in space and millenium and things and many designers showed millenium looks recently. But we don't wear them. Frankly we can't because we think it's too odd or strange.</P>
      <P>But what about 100 year later? I expect human being'll live in the other planets and trevel around under sea.</P>
      <P>I think people'll wear those spacy and Ciber looking cloth after a centry. What do you think?</P>
      <P>Can you imagin you and your friends going picnic to the Moon with silvery skirt with Astronut boots with fire coming out at the bottom of your boots? It could be more facinating.</P>
      <P>Endless imagination and development of technology will lead us to future fashion.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
