<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR843*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>41-50</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs. Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter letting me know that I've won first prize in your competition. It came as a nice surprise.</P>
      <P>I would like to let you know that I can only travel in July because that is the only time I can take leave from work. I would prefer to stay in the log cabins as I would be afraid of insects or any crawling animals if I have to stay in the tent.</P>
      <P>For activities choices, I would like to choose Tennis and swimming. I used to play Tennis at tournament level and now I play it for enjoyment instead. Swimming is my best way of excercise and keeping fit.</P>
      <P>I've a few questions to ask. Since all accommodation and travel costs are paid for, Are there any other expenses that I have to pay? How much money I should have with me in order to cover all other expenses? Furthermore, what type of clothes I should bring?</P>
      <P>I would be grateful if you could let me know the above information as soon as possible. Thank you once again for giving me good news!</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>I find shopping is the most time consuming. If I want to buy a nice pair of shoe, I'll have to go into a city centre and browse around from shops to shops until I find the shoes I like. If I'm not lucky enough to find one, then I'll have to take a train trip to a larger shopping places such as London.</P>
      <P>Whilst in London; I'll be facing crowds and people will be rushing everywhere. To walk around London streets looking for a pair of shoe can definitely be a tiring task. As I'm a compulsive buyer, I'd probably ended up buying other things as well.</P>
      <P>At the end of the day, I would not only be carrying pile of shopping bags but also trying to squeeze in between other passengers on the train on my way home.</P>
      <P>By the time I get home, I would be completely exhausted. As you can see, shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
