<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR844*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>DEAR SIR</P>
      <P>I AM WRITING IN ORDER TO COMPLAIN FOR THE TERRIBLE NIGHT I HAD IN YOUR THEATRE.</P>
      <P>FIRSTLY I WANT TO COMPLAIN ABOUT WHAT YOU WROTE ON THE BROCHURE. IT WAS COMPLETELY WRONG!</P>
      <P>I WAS DISAPPOINTED TO FIND OUT THAT THE ACTOR WAS NOT THE ONE YOU WROTE I DISCOVERED THIS ONLY WHEN THE PLAY STARTED, AND IT WAS VERY LATE!</P>
      <P>SECONDLY, AS I WROTE BEFORE, THE PLAY STARTED LATE, AND FOR ME IT WAS TERRIBLE TO WAIT FORTY FIVE MINUTES.</P>
      <P>THIRDLY, I WAS VERY EMBARASED TO DISCOVER THERE WERE NOT DISCOUNTS AT THE ENTRANCE.</P>
      <P>FINALLY I COULDN'T EAT TOO. IN FACT THE RESTAURANT WAS CLOSED, VERY FAR FROM MY THOUGHTS.</P>
      <P>FOR THESE REASONS I WOULD LIKE TO ASK FOR MY MONEY BACK. BECAUSE FOR ME IT WAS NOT A "PERFECT EVENING OUT".</P>
      <P>I AM SURE THIS LETTER WILL RECEIVE YOUR PROMPT ATTENTION.</P>
      <P>I LOOK FORWARD TO HEARING FROM YOU.</P>
      <P>YOURS FAITHFULLY</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>UNFORTUNATELY, PAT WAS NOT VERY GOOD AT KEEPING SECRETS. THIS WAS LIKE AN ILLNESS FOR HIM. SO MANY TIME HE WAS TOLD: "PAT I SAY THIS SECRET ONLY TO YOU". PAT COULD STAND THIS SECRET ONLY FEW DAYS, AFTER THE SECRET COME FROM THE DEEP INSIDE, AND HAD TO BE SAID. THIS WAS TERRIBLE FOR HIS FRIENDSHIP: HE ALWAYS LOST HIS FRIENDS. HE WANTED TO DIE FOR THIS. THE WORST THING IS THAT HE COULD NOT IMPROVE THIS BEHAVIOUR. ONE DAY THE FORTUNE HELPED OUR POOR PAT. ON THE BUS HE SAW A ROBBER WHILE HE WAS STEALING A WALLET, HE WANTED TO SCREAM, BUT HE WAS ASTONISHED. WHEN THE ROBBER UNDERSTOOD HE COULD BE DISCOVERED HE SAID "IF YOU DON'T KEEP THE SECRET I WILL KILL YOU". PAT, AS HE ALWAYS DID, COULDN'T KEEP THE SECRET, EVEN IF HE WAS SCARED. EVENTUALLY THE ROBBER WAS CAUGHT BY THE POLICE, AND FOR HIS BRAVE AND HONESTY HE HAD A LOT OF FRIENDS.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
