<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR845*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear sir, I'm writing to express my complaint about the organization of the musical show I went to last Saturday evening. According to your advertisement, there should have been Danny Brook, starring all the scenes. Instead, you changed actor without any warning, so I didn't find my favourite Danny Brook, with my total disappointment, as his substitute couldn't catch him up at all. And what about the starting time? I had to wait for about an hour, as the show started at 20.15 instead of 19.30. Another thing that made me angry was that I couldn't have a discount. I was very annoyed about it: I only expected the discounts you had promised on the advertisement and, as I am a university student, I would have a right on it. At the top of everything, your theatre restaurant was closed because it was being restructurated, so I couldn't have my dinner either! It was a terrible evening out, so I ask you for a refund for all the troubles you caused me. Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Most people think modern technologies aren't so positive as they are often showed.</P>
      <P>My personal theory is completely different. I have always a good approach with all of the most recent invenctions or any other kind of modern applications.</P>
      <P>We live in the age of personal computers, of internet, of the mobile phones, and now for me it's impossible to think of a world without them. It' already four years since I bought my first cellular phone (then I changed it many times) and it is always very useful for me: everyone can speak with me wherever I am. When, for example, I go abroad I feel closer to my friend and to my family than before.</P>
      <P>Anyway, the thing that has most changed my daily life is the personal computer and, expecially, internet. For example, now I'm writing my thesis, but I use my pc everytime I have to write a document in a perfect form.</P>
      <P>Then, surfing in internet is becoming my passion: it's incredible how many unthinkable activities you can do with it. It's simply fantastic!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
