<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR847*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>I wanted to thank you for allowing us to have this great opportunity to visiting London.</P>
      <P>I have read the programme and I find it very appealing, specially because of the River trip to Greenwich. However, I have seen an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show and I was wondering if we could visit it. The show is going to be at the Central Exhibition Hall the 14th of March from 10.00 to 19.00. There will be shown the latest fashions, leisure and sportwear, some make up and also different hairstyles. The students are free so we won't have to pay for the visit.</P>
      <P>We all think this is a great opportunity to learn more about London daily life and what people like to wear.</P>
      <P>I suggest visiting the London Fashion and Leisure Show on Tuesday morning and visit the Science Museum on Friday afternoon.</P>
      <P>We all hope you would consider our suggestion.</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Almost everyone hates other people gossip in their private things. It's a natural reaccion to be angry with somebody you don't trust for gossiping and bothering your personal thoughts. So I think famous people, no matter if they are politicians or films stars don't deserve being followed by journalists every time they are trying to have a good time.</P>
      <P>I thing that journalit's only aim is money, be cause they know that if they publish famous people's private life they would earn lot's of money selling the magazine or the newspaper. But they don't consider the problems the romours may bring to the famous family or couple. Sometimes the journalit's aim isn't the money: there are some journalists who may try to spoil the politician's or film star's career only because they are jealous.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, no matter which or what the journalit's aims are, famous people deserve to have their problems, their affairs, their private life just as normal people have.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
