<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR848*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Manager,</P>
      <P>I saw your advertisment of your show in the circle theatre, over the rainbow. I went to it, but I was really disappointed about some thing.</P>
      <P>First the musical show, Over the Rainbow started at 20:15, and in the advertisement was written at 19:30, then also was written that the actor was Danny Brook, but in the show appeared a different actor, that was really disappointing. Also was written in the advertisment that some discounts were available, but there wasn't discounts. And because of the time that the show started I couldn't went to the theatre restaurant because it was closed.</P>
      <P>Mr, I was very disappointed with the show so I want my money back, and I am sure you will understand my reasons.</P>
      <P>Yours Faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets, and she went to her house to speak about the things I had told her. First she said to her father, then to her mother and finally to her brother, that I was from another planet called Orion, that was a billion kilometer distance of Earth and that I was so ashamed because I have been his boyfriend since I have came to Earth.</P>
      <P>My confession caused a disaster in the life of her and her family, and they called the police to take me out of the planet or arrested, so that I can't see her again.</P>
      <P>The police caught me, when I was peacefully in my room, and put me covered with something, in a car. After they caught me I think they brought me to the Area 57, were the police do experiments.</P>
      <P>Since then I live in Area 57, and this is my diary life. I don't now when I and going to be free, for going to my planet.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
