<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR850*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I received your letter congratulating me on having won the first prize in your competition. I am extremely excited about the opportunity to go to your camp in the USA.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I have to say that I am studying at University and I wonder if I could travel on July because of the exams I have on May. Apart from that I would not be able to travel there until the end of June.</P>
      <P>It does not matter to me whether I stay in tent or log cabin, but I would prefer tent to be much more in contact with wild life and nature.</P>
      <P>The activities I'd like to do most are playing basketball and Climbing. The first one because I have been played basketball since the age of twelve and the second one because there are not many places where to go climbing in my city.</P>
      <P>Finally, I would ask you if I have to take my own clothes with me or you will provide me with some, and the amount of money needed.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I received your letter last week in which you told me that you want to hear about my experience at the pop concert.</P>
      <P>It was terrible! We have a lot of problems from the beggining. The first one was the security. People in charge of security didn't arrive when they were supposed to. If it weren't a calm and quite public, we would have had troubles. Another problem was the band. They didn't want to play until the room were crowded. So that concert started an hour and a half latter.</P>
      <P>Everything was all right during the perform of the band, but at the end some espectators came up to the stage and made some damage to the band's instrument. The singer and the guitarist were so angry that they went out immediately leaving the public without the last part of the show.</P>
      <P>As you can see, hardly anything went well, but the lights and the sound - both in wich I helped carrying things - were appropriate for the concert. Althought all these things, I gained a lot of experience and I could be near one of my favourite pop stars, which was the better experience I've ever had.</P>
      <P>Looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
