<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR851*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Jane Clark</P>
      <P>I'm writing to express my dissatisfaction with International Arts Festival, which was organised by you last year. However I think that International Arts Festival is a great idea and I suggest you prepare it better.</P>
      <P>Firstly, it was written on the advertisment that there would be stars and artist from around the world I believe that it's difficult to arrange meetings with foreign stars but there were artist from only six countries and in my opinion there</P>
      <P>should be more. Secondly, the concerts took place in concert halls, which in my opinion were too small. That was the reason why some people were complaining.</P>
      <P>Thirdly, I suggest you should put more plays and films next year, because watching them is a very nice way of spending our freetime.</P>
      <P>Fourthly, I have to admit that a big advantage was your idea about giving one reasonably-priced weekend ticket for all events. That was excelent because it attracted peoples' attention</P>
      <P>Lastly, I'd like to give you a piece of advice. I suggest you invite some film stars, because they are very famous and people like them</P>
      <P>I hope you'll look into these matters and improve the festival next year.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you</P>
      <P>Yours sincerly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Nowadays everybody wants to earn money. Young people know that money make the world go round, so they always look for a job with big salary. Some people say that the young shouldn't be independent and earn on their own, but I am sure that it's better to work in your free-time than waste it. In my opinion the young should work rather than wait for their pocket money. There are a lot of possibilities to earn some money but of course the young are not able to get well-paid job, because they are not enough experienced and educated. They have to think about some season jobs. Firstly, the good way to earn money is, to help the old. They often are not able to do shopping or walk the dog. If you help them, they may give you some money as a reward. Secondly, you can find an easy job in a shopping centre. It's better paid and permanent job. You can work in storage, look after the goods or catch shoplifters. If you are good mathematic you can be a seller.</P>
      <P>Thirdly if you are good looking you can apply for a job in restaurant and become waiter. Maybe you'll not get a big salary but think about the tips, which in the posh restaurants are very high.</P>
      <P>Lastly, if you like playing instruments and you don't like working you can go busking. If you are good musician you will get a lot of money.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
