<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR852*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter. I'm pleased to that I've won the first prize at camp california in the U.S.A during two weeks.</P>
      <P>First of all,</P>
      <P>I would like travel on July because I am going to finish the college at the end of June and I will work the first of august.</P>
      <P>Second of all,</P>
      <P>About the accomodation, I would prefer a log cabin, I think that will be more safety about all my stuff.</P>
      <P>I'm very keen to have the chance to do some activities, I'm very attracted by the golf. I will be a beginner because I've never done this sport before but I will have a try. Also, I choose surfing, I love this sport. I've been practicing this sport since 5 years, so I'm quiet good.</P>
      <P>Finally I would like to know if I need a lot of money about this excursion and if we are going to visit some building. I've know idea what kind of weather it is in USA could you let me know what type of clothes should I bring with me.</P>
      <P>yours Sincerly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>Thank you for your last letter, I'm really envy you holiday under the sun.</P>
      <P>Last month was amazing for me, I was helping at a pop concert. All right, I wasn't able to do all the stuff like the lights the stereo, the sound but I've been helping to built the stage and the installation of micros. The stage was gigantesque the crowed could be all around.</P>
      <P>I really enjoyed to be next to the pop stars I got a lot of autographes, that was the first time I've seen like Jagger a lot of well know pop stars was there.</P>
      <P>I mean It's still inbelivable, can you imagine that was like a dream I was checking their hands.</P>
      <P>I keep a very good souvenir about this experience. I think I will go back the next year.</P>
      <P>Do you want join me?</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you as soon as possible</P>
      <P>Love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
