<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR854*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Jane Clark, the organiser of International Arts Festival</P>
      <P>I'm one of the citizen that enjoyed the last International Arts Festival. Most of attractions are excellent, but I'd like to point out that "quality isis!.</P>
      <P>First of all, the only "six countries" doesn't mean "around the world". I suppose you had difficulty to manage the schedule.</P>
      <P>Second, some concert hall were too small, so some audience couldn't concentrate to listen to the music. And others couldn't enter the hall.</P>
      <P>But "All in one ticket" was a good idea. In fact queuing up in front of every ticket office is wasting time.</P>
      <P>I pressume if the term becomes longer the festival become more excellent. Because it's easy to manage the artist schedule and audience can enjoy the live.</P>
      <P>I'd like to go to the Festival again!</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Thank you for your letter. And I'd like to answer for your question. AT first, in Japan, generally school rules are more strictly than home's. The gap between them is tremendously big! I can say the action which is prohibitted at school is no problem at home. Because the purpose of school rules is not only discipline but also unify.</P>
      <P>Here, I write down one of the rules at my school. "Whenever the students wear an extra cloth (because of cold or something) his or her (not students!) parents write down an application form with their authorized signatures".</P>
      <P>You will ask me why, the reason is the above..."unify". In addition "the students must not use any commercial paper bags (received at department store etc)". Now you know the reason!</P>
      <P>Needless to say I'd like to change such ridiculous rules, because such rules are not for us. They are for teachers'! Don't you think so?</P>
      <P>Do you have any rules at school that make you upset? If you have please tell me.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
