<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR855*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson</P>
      <P>I am writing to thank you for the good programme, especially on Wednesday, because the other student and I like Art Galleries.</P>
      <P>But, the last Friday, we have seen an advertisement for the "London Fashion and Leisure Show. Now, we want to know if it is possible to go to watch this Show. It is on Tuesday 14th March in the Central Exhibition Hall between 10.00 and 19.00.</P>
      <P>We think that it is a great opportunity because it is just one time per year and it is free for stundents.</P>
      <P>We suggest you to change the programme. We think that Monday and Wednesday are good, but we ask you to change the programme on Tuesday. If it is possible, we want to go to the "London Fashion and Leisure Show" and don't go shopping.</P>
      <P>We look forward to hearing from you as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>It was dangerous, but I knew I had to do it.</P>
      <P>Last July, I went to spend two weeks with my best in a beautiful village in the south of France, near Saint-Tropez.</P>
      <P>We lived in my aunt's house who was in the center of the village. In front of my aunt's house, there is a house with swimming pool, garage and garden. My aunt told me it was the famous French singer's house.</P>
      <P>One night, I heard a strange sound. I loocked outside and saw two men go into the house in front of mine. They went into the house through a window. I though it was some rubbers.</P>
      <P>I said to my friend that I wanted to go to see and he must phone to the police. I went near the house and waited to look what it would happen.</P>
      <P>After ten minutes, one man came out with a big bag and went into his car. When the other man came out, I caught him and fighted him. The first man went away, because a police car arrived.</P>
      <P>The policeman came to take the bugglar and thanked me to catch him.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
