<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR856*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I'm writing to complain about the show, that I have recently attended to at your theatre. During my visit there occurred some problems, that made my evening completely disappointing.</P>
      <P>Firstly, as I wanted to buy a ticket, I was informed that no discounts were available. However, the serious problems appeared later. Not only the play started 45 minutes after it was planned, but as the actors eventually appeared at the stage, have I also seen, that Danny Brook was replaced by a different actor, who was very disappointing in his role. To make matters even worse, the theatre restaurant was closed after the show, without any information given about the reason of it's closure.</P>
      <P>As you see, my evening in your theatre absolutely wasn't perfect. I hope I will get a full refund. I am looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Have you ever thought of a year 2100? Do you think, that world will be different from current world then? I would answer "yes" for both questions. And if I were asked, what will be completely different in year 2100, I would say: clothes.</P>
      <P>Most of the scientists, when asked about the Earth in a hundred years claim, that it is going to be absolutely scorching here then.</P>
      <P>In my opinion, if the weather is so good people will very quickly forget about any winter clothes. What is more, ground will be so hot, that going will only be possible in huge shoes, which should be massive, but not heavy at all. Another effect of the scorching weather could be, that people won't be allowed to get out of the building unless they wear specially designed caps or hats, made of materials, that aren't known yet.</P>
      <P>On the whole, we can only predict what clothes will be like in year 2100. But in case my predictions are right, maybe you should buy a new pair of shorts?</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
