<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR857*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Jane Clark,</P>
      <P>I am writing this letter to give my opinion on the last International arts festival.</P>
      <P>Firstly I found amazing the number of starts and artist who came to the festival although they where from only six countries around the world. The concerts and the dance show were incredable, except for the classical concert that halled to small.</P>
      <P>Secondly the plays and films were very good organized despide being short number. I suggest to do a couple more next year. The art exhibition and the talks by writers were great. The art exhibition showed us a new life style and society, it was totaly different from ours. The talks by writers were very tecnic but it could be understood by all the people who were in the festival</P>
      <P>In conclusion, I am impresed on all the good organisation, the service and the cost of the weekend ticket for all events. The price has been excelent because there wasn't any limit of hours.</P>
      <P>I hope that you organice this festival for all the following years.</P>
      <P>Your Sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Alice,</P>
      <P>How are you? I'm pleased to hear from you.</P>
      <P>As you already know I go to an English school, Bear House, in Spain. The rules in my country are standart, I mean, the rules are very similar to other countries in Europe.</P>
      <P>At school you aren't allowed to bring connected movil phones although there are more than one student that does it. Teachers will take it from you if it rangs during school hours. As well you aren't allowed to bring drugs or arms, to smoke or to drink alcohol inside the school. You have to respect other peoples opinion, teachers, school's material and people who works in the school. If you broke one of these rules you could be expulsed for a week, a month or for ever.</P>
      <P>At home I'm allowed to do what I want if I'm respectful with my parent's time table. I can go out at night once a week if I tell them were I'm going to be. In case I lie them or don't explain my plans that my friends and I have I want be able to go out. As well have the responsability to look after my brother in case they aren't at home.</P>
      <P>Answering to you question I won't change nothing because I think that these are the minimum rules that a theenager have to have to be responsable in a future.</P>
      <P>love</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
