<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR860*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson.</P>
      <P>I'm writing you about our journey which you have already orginesed.</P>
      <P>First of all, thank you for your good programme. We saw your details and enjoyed them. Especially River trip to Greenwich and visiting National Art Gallery.</P>
      <P>All the students in my class are excited about one more thing. We saw an advertisement about Fashion And Leisure Show. It will be at Central Exhibition Hall, London. The date is Tuesday March 14. The show can be seen between 10.00 - 19.00. This show is about latest fashions, leisure and sports wear, make up and Hairstyles. One more thing about show is, it's free for students. Isn't it a big opportunity for us?</P>
      <P>As you know, there is a free time in your programme if you don't mind, we can go for shopping in this free time. This changing, give us an opportunity to go to show on Tuesday afternoon.</P>
      <P>We hope you an accept our suggestion. It will make us so happy.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Sincerally,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>A PRIVATE LIFE</P>
      <P>All people have some difficulties about their job but some of them have more than the others. Reason for this; they are famous and everybody wants to learn about them.</P>
      <P>Having a private life is important for everybody. I think, people want this. if you are a famous person, for example singer, film star, politician or well-know footballer, you haven't get any choice. Because people want to learn about you everything. so journalists are following you all the time.</P>
      <P>I know, they are not like us. They are famous, but I think they need to be alone sometimes. They nead to be with their family in silence. This is important for everybody and I think this is important for them, too.</P>
      <P>I think media must be more understanding. We don't have to learn their every second. We have to remember that, they need a private life like us. We can love them without disturbing too.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
