<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR861*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you because of the latest musical show you played in Circle Theatre.</P>
      <P>I am keen on musicals and I have seen many of them in different parts of the world. Unfortunately the one I saw a week ago in the Circle Theatre was one of the worst.</P>
      <P>Here are some argeuments telling why me and many other people from the audience are so disappointed.</P>
      <P>First of all the musical should have started at 19.30 but unfortunately we had to wait forty five minutes. It is a wasting of time.</P>
      <P>Moreover the advertisement for the show says that the main role in the musical plays great Danny Brook. I must admit I'd been looking forward to see him. In fact at the stage appeared compleatly different person.</P>
      <P>Also discounts for tickets wasn't available.</P>
      <P>After the show together with my friends I went to the theatre restaurant to have a romantic supper, unfortunately it was closed without any sensible reason.</P>
      <P>At the end of my letter I would like to ask if it is possible to have some money back.</P>
      <P>I would be very pleased if you answered my request soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. Besides this little thing she is actually perfect. But to make everything clear I'll start from the beggining. It was two years ago.</P>
      <P>The school finished and we, I mean Pat, Tim and me, didn't know what to do with plenty of spare time. I didn't wanted to spend that holiday with my parents in the country. I was old enough to go somewhere only with my friends. Tim gave a proposition about going at the sea by his new car. It seemed fantastic but we knew our parents would never agree. We had to find another way out. We planned to tell them that we were going for a summer camp in the mountains where we would practise French. Parents were very pleased and happy we are so ambisious. Of course we didn't wanted to go there, it was just a "cover". We prepared tents and other relevant equipment and we were waiting. We promised to keep it in secret.</P>
      <P>Two days before going Pat was packing her luggage and asked her mother to help her. During chat Pat mentioned about sea and her mother found out that something was wrong. Pat started to cry and told about everything.</P>
      <P>As a result we were grouded for all holidays and all because our almost perfect Pat.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
