<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR862*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Clark,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you because, as one of the visitors of the International Arts Festival which took place two weeks ago in our city, I would like to let you know some of my opinions - and suggestions, as well - related with what I saw in the festival and what I could not see, but I would have liked to find.</P>
      <P>First of all, I must congratulate the people responsible of this good idea. It is known of all the lack of art festivals and cultural activities in general that shows our city. And what a belter thing to solve this than to give the festival an international character.</P>
      <P>But including only six countries in the festival does not seem enough, in my opinion. I think next year you should invite more different countries, because the festival would be more multicultural.</P>
      <P>Secondly, there were some problems of accommodation in the classical concerts because some concert halls were too small. Another important thing is that, despite the number and quality of films, there were, from my point of view, not many plays. In addition, I would like to talk about the success among most visitors of the weekend ticket, due to its economical price and because of its comodity in use.</P>
      <P>Finally, I would like to suggest that, in next year's festival, you include different kinds of music, as ska or ethnical music.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Who doesn't want to earn some money? The topic says that young people have a lot of problems, but without any doubt, money is one of the most important of them.</P>
      <P>If you still don't have economical freedom from your parents and your studies don't permit you to have a full-time job, these are some suggestions that maybe will help you.</P>
      <P>One possible thing is to display in a public place what you can do best, and, then, "sell" it to the people. For example, you can dance folk be Hamlet in the street, or even sing with some of your friends a nice song from you country. You must be aware, anyway, of the difficulty of this kind of things (bad weather, no attention from the people and so on)</P>
      <P>But maybe you are too shy to do this. In this case, you can cook some cakes and sell them near a school or in the centre of the city, as well as other traditional products: cheese, honey,chocolate...</P>
      <P>Another thing that can be useful is to make some pottery or do original paintings and sculptures. You don't need to be a Picasso, it's enough with a bit of imagination.</P>
      <P>If you don't feel like doing any thing of this, you have alternative solutions. If you like fishing, you can try to colaborate with the local market or some shops, in order to sell them the fish you can achieve by yourself.</P>
      <P>Finally, if anything of the above result, you can prepare the classical parties in discos or work as a babysitter It doesn't matter how, the aim is always money.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
