<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR863*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>41-50</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms, Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter to inform me for the prise I had won.</P>
      <P>I would like to answer to you question, please notice that I can travel only in July because only then I can take holidays from my work, after the busy time of month May and June.</P>
      <P>I prefer to staying in cabin because never before I when on holidays in tent., so I think is more corfotabel to sleep in bet instand of outside in tent.</P>
      <P>The activities I would like to do durring these two week it's basketball and swimming.</P>
      <P>Basketball I think I can playing well, because few years ago I was mamber of the scool team. Swimming it's not my favorite sport but I prefer swimming than golf or tennis. Please could you informy what do you meen when do you said all the accommodotion are paid for, that is including foods and drinks, so I know how mutch money I have to take with me, and what kind of wather it's during this period of the year so I know what kind of clothes I have to take.</P>
      <P>I look forward for this competition.</P>
      <P>Best Regards</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I would like to inform you about my experience of the last pop concert. It was very nice for me to help because I have seen so many people and I have goten a lot of experience of things that I never had done before.</P>
      <P>I was the assistent of the responsible person for the clothes and make-up of the pop-group, realy I was very nervous about that because was the first time with so famous people, but I am very happy that all the things went very well Kim what realy particularly liked was when I was asked to do the make-up on my on realy I was very nervous but at same moment very happy, but every thing when well and everyboby was very hapy with my work.</P>
      <P>Realy I think you have to tray to do the same things the next summer, I realy had enjoyed.</P>
      <P>Best Regards</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
