<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR865*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to thank you for the lovely programme you organised for our trip to London, especially because we will have both cultural trips and entertainments, like shopping. I can tell you that we are all looking forward to going there.</P>
      <P>However, I have been asked by the class to propose you another visit. We all would like to go and see the London Fashion and Leisure Show which will take place on Tuesday 14th March, from 10.00 to 19.00, in the London's Central exhibition Hall. This show is about the latest fashions, the leisure and sports wear, the make-up and the hairstyles.</P>
      <P>Everybody in the class is interested in this show, and it would be a great opportunity for us to see it, especially because many of us would like to work later in the fashion. Moreover, this show won't cost anything because it is free for the students!</P>
      <P>Consequently, I proposed to change the programme as follows; on Tuesday afternoon, instead of shopping, we could go to this show and we could go shopping on Wednesday afternoon, during our free time. What do you think about that?</P>
      <P>Hoping to hear from your decision soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>(class 3CD)</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>"Famous people, such as politicians and film stars, deserve to have a private life without journalists following them all the time."</P>
      <P>Nowadays, most people think that famous people have a so good life (lots of money, comfortable house) that they have to stop complaining about he media's treatment, because they have chosen to have this kind of life.</P>
      <P>On one hand, it is true because famous people have to do their jobs, that means being interviewed, giving news to the audiance, and soon. Moreover, especially for film stars, lots of people are hoping to see them on the Tv or in the newspapers, and this is really good for their fame.</P>
      <P>However, on the other hand, it must be so annoying to be followed by journalists or photographs all the time. You can't go outside quietly, and there is all the time a crownd of people who stands in front of your house waiting for you.</P>
      <P>The question you have to ask yourself is: would you like to have all the time people around your house who are watching at you or people who are following you everywhere? I am sure that nobody would like this.</P>
      <P>That is why I think that famous people deserve a private life, like everybody, and that journalists should not follow them everywhere.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
