<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR866*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>I am writing to tell you that my class is interested in going to the show which takes place in central exhibition Hall in London in 14th March.</P>
      <P>We have seen it in the advertisment and I would like to go to the show. I would also like to tell you that it is very interesting programme because it includes all the latest fashion about leisure and sports wear make up as well as hairstyles. It is great opportunity for us because the fashion is fashinating and free.</P>
      <P>I should be more grateful if you could change the programme so as to go to the show. For example we shall be able to putoff our visit at the science museums in Thusday morning for Wednesday afternoon. The fashion show starts at 10 oclock and finishes at 19 o'clock.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Yours Faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>All the people have the right to have a private life without others people to disturb them following all the time.</P>
      <P>The journalists follow the famous people, such as politicians and film stars, in order to take fotos and other information about them. After that journalist sell their information in the newspaper and magazines in order to earn money.</P>
      <P>I thin that it is very dangerous because the famous peple cannot have you private life and on the other hand they may suffer from deppresion and sadness which may be lead them to suicide.</P>
      <P>I think that the goverment have to protect them and their private life from the journalist, punishing them. I think that the government I responsible for the private life of the people.</P>
      <P>All the people have the right to live free without to be disturbed by other.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
