<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR867*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>June 17th, 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about the Musical Show 'Over the Rainbow' permormed on the Circle theatre last week.</P>
      <P>To begin with, there were no discounts available, and nobody seemed to be able to explain the reason. Second, the musical started forty-five minutes later! and, to make matters worse, the actor was not Danny Brook as the advertisement said. The new actor was not as good as Danny Brook, and he did not perform the show as he should have done.</P>
      <P>Finally, I found that the theatre restaurant was closed because there had been problems with one of the ovens.</P>
      <P>What was suppoused to be a perfect evening out turned to be disappointing one instead. I am afraid something should be done about this, and I urge you to refund my ticket.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to receiving your response.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>It is often said that technology has changed our lives in many ways, and that we live better now. However, technology has also brought many problems to Society.</P>
      <P>Technology brings me a lot of new possibilities every day, and it also makes everything easier. If I want to know how a friend is, I just have to phone him; I can see how the world is going on only by switching on the television, and I can cook in some minutes using the Microvelle oven.</P>
      <P>However, there are a lot of negative aspects in the way that technology affects my life. As technology develops so fast, there are always new things to buy, and it also reduces the amount of jobs available, so it is getting hard to find a job.</P>
      <P>In conclussion, I think that technology has two faces which affects my life as well as everybody else's life. I believe that we should try to change this bad aspects, or learn to live with them.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
