<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR762*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I'm writing to complain about my horrible evening at The Circle Theatre on 10th June 2000.</P>
      <P>Last week I was on holiday in London and I went to the theatre for entertaining but I wish I'd not go there because everythings went wrong.</P>
      <P>I bought a ticket at the box office but there were not any discounts for student like you said in the advertisement for the show and also the show had to start at 19.30 but on that day it delaied about 45 minutes. During the show I was expected to meet Danny Brook who is my favourite actor and Tina Truelove. There are Robert Alan and Jack Ruby instead of them. It really disappointed me. After finishing the show I wanted to visit your restaurant and I found that it was closed.</P>
      <P>It was a sign in front of the restaurant "sorry we closed because special reasons" and I was wondering what was the reasons for that.</P>
      <P>Finally I would like to have refund for my ticket back because it was horrible evening.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>Paya Chuaswee (Miss)</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets that why our great plan for horiday were not be real.</P>
      <P>It happened in last summer we planed to go on holiday in the Southen part of Thailand by motorbike but we couldn't tell our parents because they wouldn't allow us to go.</P>
      <P>We started our journey and we arrived at our purpose place by 6 o'clock in the evening. The sun was shining and wind were breezing like we had imaged. Whlile I was standing on the beach suddenly I heard someone called my name and said that I had to go home, that right, she is my mum. She told me Pat had phoned her while we were going and my mum followed us because it was so dangerous to went by bicycle. Eventhroughthough.</P>
      <P>From now on I don't want to tell something secrets to Pat because she always tell someone else but she still my best friend.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
