<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR868*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writting to thank you for your letter confirming the first prize that I won in your competition. I would like also with the present to give you some information about me in order to arrange the details for the trip.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to inform you that I will be able to travel only during July because in June I am going to give examinations for the First Certificate in English. Furthermore, in August I will be preparing for my course at the University which I am starting next September.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I would be grateful if you could arrange for me accomodation in log cabins as I am not used on living in the countryside and especially in tents.</P>
      <P>In addition, I would like to inform you that I prefer to do Surfing and Sailing while I will be at the Camp, as I am an active member of Sailing and Surfing Club of Manchester and it will be a great chance for me to practise my techniques and skills.</P>
      <P>I would be also grateful if you could send me information about the average living cost at California as I have to arrange the amount of money that I am going to spend, and some advice about the clothes that I need. I would like also to specify if the food is including in the prize.</P>
      <P>Please let me know if you need more information.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>As requested, I visited some classes during the lesson and some other rooms while activities were taking place.</P>
      <P>The aim of this report is make a series of suggestions on which lessons and other activities should be filmed.</P>
      <P>It's seems to me that it will be an extremely good advertisement for our school if you take plans from the lesson of Chemistry in the laboratory, because our laboratory is new, recognised as one of the best in the area as it has a huge amount of instruments and really some very good professors, and also many experiments are taking place in this laboratory</P>
      <P>Furthermore, I think it will be a good idea to take plans from a match of our school team in the football field as it is completely new and full equiped.</P>
      <P>In addition, I think you have to take also the school's Nursery as there are a lot of facilities for the children, and the parents can recognise that the teachers are very good.</P>
      <P>I think also that will be a good idea to take some general plans of the school area as there is a huge background.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, I have to declare that my myself and my fellow students will be available to help to this short video by all means.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
