<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR870*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Madam,</P>
      <P>First, I would like to thank you for offering me this wonderful prize. For a long time I wish I came to Camp California, and now my dream is about to become true.</P>
      <P>There is no much time left in my timetable in August since I will have to work then, so I would rather come in July. Concerning the accomodation, I would prefer to sleep in a log cabin, because to sleep in a tent would remind me of the bad experience I had in Ireland because of the weather...</P>
      <P>Since this stay at Camp California is a good occasion to discover new activities, I would like to sail and climb, but I am a beginner in both activities.</P>
      <P>Then, I would like to know what kind of clothes I will need there, and if I have to bring a lot of money. I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>Richard Amelin</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I apologize for not having written this letter sooner, but as you probably now, I was actually really busy because of the pop concert. What a great experience that was! I will remember it for a long time because of two reasons.</P>
      <P>The first one is that the band I have helped, although it hasn't met success yet, is really good. When they are on stage, during the repetitions, they are able to play a music that completely moves me. In a few months, when they are famous, I could say: "You know. I already know them, I have even helped them at one of their concert."</P>
      <P>Moreover, the work I've had to do, apart from carrying material, was essentially to sell tickets for the concert, which has allowed me to meet a lot of nice people and to become friend with some of them. Even though my entire body aches (material was quite heavy) and I am tired, I wouldn't call it a work! I am looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Richard Amelin</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
