<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR871*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan</P>
      <P>I'm writing concerning your letter about my win in your competition for two weeks at Camp California. I'm very happy to be the winner from your competition.</P>
      <P>Because I'm working in an accountant office, I'm very busy. The only month I could go to holidays is July, when we haven't got a lot to do.</P>
      <P>Moreover, because of the accommodation, I would like to be in a tent, because I want to spend my holidays different than usually. And in my opinion, when you live in a tent, you have more from the nature and the adventure.</P>
      <P>I like a lot from your list for the sport possibilities, however I will choose swimming. I used to be a member in a swimming club for about 10 years. Additionally I'm keen on taking pictures. But until now I only took pictures on holidays and some family celabrations.</P>
      <P>Lastly, I would like to ask if I have to take a lot of money with me, for example for the food. And also if the weather will be good at this time.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>I would like to begin this composition by saying that, not for everyone is shopping the same. For some people it's great fun, but for some other it's a "must".</P>
      <P>In my opinion, shopping is like relaxing. I like to go very often, to look around and to buy some new clothes. As long as I am not searching for something specific. When I must buy something, I usually can't find it and then the shopping become a nightmare.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, when you go with someone else shopping, and you both want to see and buy different things, it can also be boring and uninteresting. Then it is perhaps better, when you make an appointment in one hour and everybody enjoys the shopping alone.</P>
      <P>To sum up, I would like to say that for to have an exciting shopping, you have sometimes to plan it or just be in the right mood.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
