<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR873*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to give my opinion about the musical show called "Over the Rainbow".</P>
      <P>I recently had a week's holiday in London and during my stay, I went to the Circle Theatre to see "Over the Rainbow". To tell the truth, it was a very disappointing evening. When I read the advertisement first, I thought that it would be fun.</P>
      <P>In the advertisement, it was written that the show was London's newest and best musical show. Well, it might be the newest one but certainly, it was not the best one. I thought that the actor of the show was Danny Brook, but he was not playing in the show. The actor was somebody else and this was something disappointing.</P>
      <P>The show should have started at 19:30 but, it started at 20:15. Which means, I had to wait there for 45 minutes. And also, it was written that the discounts were available but they were not.</P>
      <P>After the show, I decided to visit the theatre restaurant but it was closed. On the door, there was a note saying that the restaurant was closed because of the illness of the cook.</P>
      <P>I had given £20 and now, I would be pleased if you give some of my money back. It was a terrible evening out for me. I hope the next musical show would be a better one.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>MODERN TECHNOLOGY</P>
      <P>In the past, everything was very different. People had completely different life-styles.</P>
      <P>People were using candles to see around them. In winter, they used to fire some woods to keep warm, "Computer" was a word that nobody had known the meaning of it. As my mum told me, when she was young, only a few people had televisions in their houses. And of course, they were black-and white. Their hobies were listening to the radio, reading books or sitting on a chair without doing anything.</P>
      <P>Modern technology has changed our daily life a lot. We are using mobile phones so it doesn't matter if we are in a crowded city or on a desert. You can communicate with other people any time you want. Nearly 90 per cent of people know how to use a computer and computers are used in every section of our lives. We also have "internet", by which you can learn something about the world in less than a minute.</P>
      <P>Modern technology is very important for all the countries. It has a very big role in developing a country. When you look around, you can easily understand that modern technology is used in everything.</P>
      <P>I think, we are all very lucky people that we aren't using candles or black and white televisions anymore?</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
