<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR874*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Jane Clark,</P>
      <P>I had a wonderful time at the International Arts Festival. I think this festival is a great idea to enjoy arts from around the world, but I also have some complaints.</P>
      <P>First of all, I got disappointed when I found that there were no artists from Indonesia. There were stars and artists from only six countries.</P>
      <P>Secondly, the concert halls. The performances were great, but some halls were too small to accomodate so many people there were that day. A crowded hall is not good to enjoy musics.</P>
      <P>Overall, however, the festival was definitely a great success. I liked plays and films, and want to see more next year. The special tickets were excellent because we could enjoy arts without worrying about money. So all you need to improve is to have larger concert halls. I also suggest that you should make it easier to find out where and what is being held using more notice boards.</P>
      <P>I have no doubt that you will succeed in next year's festival.</P>
      <P>Sincerely Yours,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>I would like to recommend the job, a home teacher. It is a job that you become a teacher and visit your student at his or her house.</P>
      <P>The best advantage of this job is the payment. It is very good considering how less time we spend on it. It's about 3,000 yen per hour in my district. It is also attractive that this job rarely affects our university studies. Students who want home teachers are usually primary school, junior high school, or senior high school students, and it means they take lessons after school, not in a daytime. So, in a daytime, we can focus in our studyings.</P>
      <P>It is not so easy for every student, though. Because teaching requires a lot of knowledge. You have to be much smarter than your student, and you also need to prepare for lessons, for it is your responsibility to provide your student right information.</P>
      <P>As you see, teaching is a hard work in some respect. But I am enjoying it and getting a lot out of it.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
