<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR876*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms Jane Clark</P>
      <P>I am writing to you because I have some suggestion about next year festival, and if it is possible I can give you some opinions about this year festival.</P>
      <P>Firstly, in your advertisement states: stars and artist from around the world, and this year one only from six countries It would be great if there was more artist not only six.</P>
      <P>Secondly, the concerts are fantastic, especially rock concerts. I very enjoy on it, but some of the halls are too small. I saw that a lot of people were unsatisfied.</P>
      <P>Another thing, plays and films. I saw only 2 plays and 3 films. For me it is too little. One of the reasons that I have visited your art festival was to saw a lot of plays In future I supposed to be an actress and that's way I want to learn something from professionalists. I hoe that next year I will.</P>
      <P>The last thing is that I was very surprised when I read that you have weekend-priceprice. This is excellent idea because during the week people don't have too much time to go to the festival. Now they can visit it by whole family at the weekend and see all events in reasonaby-price</P>
      <P>I believe that you consider my opinions. If you can't consider all of then, I would like only one: more and once more plays!</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Annabel</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter, and I'm sorry I didn't write. I have examinations, but now I have plenty of time and I can write a letter to you. In your letter you ask me about rules in school and home I have. I think that they are the same as yours, but I'm not sure at 100 per cent so I vrite:</P>
      <P>Rules at school are: we must be on time at lessons, always have make homework. Everybody must be present at lessons. If someone is ill must bring a paper from a doctor. And the main rule is that everyone must be nice to teachers At home I must clean my room and vacuuming home. I often go shopping and help my mother clean windows. I like clean my home, and I like when there is clean and fresh. However I'm the only child and I don't have do too much but I want and I like it. There is one thing I like to change, the treatment students by teachers. They want too much forstudent and are unkindly for them.</P>
      <P>That's all, I hope that I give you answers for all questions you have.</P>
      <P>Give my best wishes to your family</P>
      <P>Bye</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
