<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR878*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan</P>
      <P>I am writing in connection with the competition I entered a month ago. I received your letter, and I was delighted to know that I won it. As requested, below are some further information and some enquiries.</P>
      <P>I would be able to travel only after the end of my exams which are taking place in June. So, I think that July would suit me best.</P>
      <P>As far as accomodation is concerned, I would prefer sleeping in a tents. I have been travelling every summer since I was eighteen years of age and this type of accomodation is part of the ritual.</P>
      <P>I would enjoy a lot playing tennis because it is a sport I love and I am really good in it. In addition I would love to follow the photography classes eventhough I have never tried to take a picture before.</P>
      <P>I hope I gave you all the information you needed. From my part, I would just like to know what sort of clothes should I bring with me and also how much money.</P>
      <P>Thanking you in advance, I am looking forward to your prompt respons to my enquiries</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim</P>
      <P>I got your letter yesterday and I was really glad to hear from you... it's been ages since you last wrote to me! I've done so many thinks and between them I went to Glastonbery (as you know)!</P>
      <P>It lasted three days and I've had the best fun of my life. I went as a voluntier staff in order to go for free. I had to help the Green Peace teems to recycle everything we could.</P>
      <P>We were more or less two hundred students doing the same job. Our duty was to work eight ours each day and then we were free to enjoy the rest of the day as we liked.</P>
      <P>The accomodation and the food were part of the contract... everything free. They provided us tents and also a VIP pass in order to get food.</P>
      <P>Oh my God!!! It has been the best experience you can Imagine. I met lots of nice and cool people, and what I most enjoyed was the crazy atmospher of the hole thing. No matter how hard we had to work, everyone had always humor and a positive mood.</P>
      <P>So, I'll sign off now and I hope you'll write soon.</P>
      <P>Lots of love</P>
      <P>Irene</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
