<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR879*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am very glad to hear that I have won the first prize from you. I appreciate all about this.</P>
      <P>I am writing to you about my information which you need. Firstly, I am afraid that I am just available to travel only in July because it is difficult to get my own holiday from my work a the moment.</P>
      <P>I prefer staying in tents to log cabins because I have really been interested in making tents and staying there.</P>
      <P>Finally, if I have any chance to choose activities, I will choose Basket ball and Sailing with no doubt because I would love to make friends from these kinds of sports. Both could be exciting for me.</P>
      <P>I would like to know more about clothes and money. I have got not idea about them. I would be grateful if you could send me some information of them.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you in the near future.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>KANG OFF WOO</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I am happy to write a letter to you. What I really want to say is about my recent experience.</P>
      <P>Last month, I helped at a pop concert by chance. I have just as a normal worker but I have met so many famous singers who I ever seen on TV. Of course, I could listen to all their music which were so cool. After the concert I had got an opportunity to join them to the party. The best thing was that I have learned how to control their expensive instruments and I have sung my favorite songs with them.</P>
      <P>Especially, Mike who is a member of Metal Potato told me I had got a talent to play the electric guitar. It is impossible to explain all my experience without this word, "Brilliant!!!".</P>
      <P>I would like to invite you to their next concert and share my experience with you. Please let me know if you want to come as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Best wishes,</P>
      <P>KANG OFF WOO</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
