<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR880*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Hello,</P>
      <P>Firstly I would like to thank you for your prize. This travel enjoys me because I never go to USA.</P>
      <P>Secondly I am going to answer your questions. I can travel only July because I study in an ingenior's school in France and in Summer we have holidays since July.</P>
      <P>I prefer to live in tents, where it is easier to make contacts with other people than in log cabins. When I travel I don't often sleep in hotel, I prefer tents and also I can meet people, who lives in the country.</P>
      <P>For the activities I would be very happy if I could play golf. That is a sport that I always want to practise but in France it is to expansive. So if I have this opportunity, I don't want to fail it. I would like to photograph too. There are so much monuments in California and so I will remember these holidays with my photographies.</P>
      <P>Could you send me more informations about clothes to take with? Finally I would like to ask you, if I need some money because you say all accomodation and travel costs are paid for.</P>
      <P>Thank you for your answer.</P>
      <P>Charles Dumaux</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Hello Kim,</P>
      <P>Last month, I enjoyed helping at a pop concert. It was marvellous!!!</P>
      <P>I was in the backstage, so I could speak with the singer before the concert. During half an hour he explained me, how he feel in France.</P>
      <P>I had to serve glasses of water to the group before and during the concert, so I had a lot of contact with them. They are very gentle. After the concert, I went to eat with them in a restaurant near the stadium, where they had played.</P>
      <P>What I particularly liked about this experience is that I saw that famous people are like us and have the same interest.</P>
      <P>I think that this experience is something that you have to live too. Perhaps in the next concert we will go together. I will give you news about it.</P>
      <P>I hope you will answer my letter and say me if you are interesting in my proposition. I send you with my letter a photo of the singer, what he give me.</P>
      <P>See you later.</P>
      <P>Charles</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
