<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR881*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for letter which I received last week. I was delighted to heard that I won the prize for two week at Camp California in the U.S.A.</P>
      <P>I would be able to travel in the first week of July 2000, because my college will finished on 28 June 2000. I needed 1 - week to prepare all I needed to take with me, It said that about accommodation I would prefer to stay in tents to log cabins. Staying in tents more interesting than in log cabins and I always dream of sleeping in tents so my dream coming true!</P>
      <P>I always interested in sport, so I am very happy to do sport activity particularly Basketball and tennis. When I was at secondary school I used to play for a school team and I am very good at them. The last reason I love to watch basketball and my favourite team was Chicago also my favourite player was Michael Jordan!</P>
      <P>I would like to know more information about clothes and money. Do I need to take a special clothes such as, warn clothes, jumper. Finally, How much money to I need to take with me? Is there any cash machines nearest where we staying?</P>
      <P>It would be very grateful for you to give me more details as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>I looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Your sincerely,</P>
      <P>Alak Liyana</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear, Kim,</P>
      <P>How are you? I haven't heard from you for such a long time. I hope everything is alright with you. Sorry! I haven't written to you since last two months, because I have been very busy to helped and organizing the pop concert which took place near my town. Let me tell you more about what I have done last month.</P>
      <P>I have had a wonderful experienced with helping pop concert last month. My duty was helped them cooking for all of them during the concert, as you know I'm very good at cook and everybody loved my good I cooked! Secondly, I helped them to prepared the clothes and the custom during the concert, although I never experience about clothes and art before, but I enjoyed it very much.</P>
      <P>What I liked most about my experienced from the concert was a great atmosphere behind the state and live music made me felt great and happy, what's more, I have opportunity to meet a singer who I loved and I dream about. He also gave me his adress and telephone number if I need help from him in the future. I'll show you when you come around to see me.</P>
      <P>Anyway, I'd better go now. I have some homework that needs to be done. Write to me soon when you have time. Give my regards to our parents. Take care!</P>
      <P>Best wishes,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
