<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR882*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I saw your advertisement yesterday. I have visited the circle theatre. I would like to say that I am not satisfied of it.</P>
      <P>First of all, there were any different actor. I was disappointed. The other point is that the organization was very bad. For example, it is said the show starts at 19.30 but it started at 20:15. I have waited around one hour. Now I have a cold because it was so cold evening. Thirdly, I would like to enquire is about the tickets. Firstly, twenty pounds are a lot of money for such a organization, on the other hand it is said that discount is available. It is false, I have paid twenty pounds.</P>
      <P>What other I would like ask is that why it is said this is the London's newest and best musical show. I can mention it is the worst musical show. And I was invited to visit the theatre restaurant after the show. But it was closed because there were not anything to drink or to eat. Finally it was not the perfect evening out.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, I really did not like it. I want to ask if it is possible to give me money back.</P>
      <P>I look forward to your letter.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Modern technology has changed my daily life very much. At the present, the technology develops rapidly. In my opinion, World can not do without it.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I would like to mention is that in our daily life we always use some technological machines. For instance, TV-set, stereo, microwave oven and others. Another point is that with the help of the technology we can communicate with the whole world. Without doubt, discovering of the computer is the most important technological event. It is very useful. Almost everything is connected to the computers. For example, education, researching of the Universe and others.</P>
      <P>Another thing I would like to say is that modern technology help us to go anywhere rapidly. The most suitable examples are the planes. What other I would like to mention how important the modern technology is. We research our plant, other planets and many other things with the help of it. Finally I think that at the present the life is more comfortable.</P>
      <P>In my opinion, no one can do without modern technology. It go on to develop and always will be the most importand think in our life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
