<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR883*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>The Circle Theatre</P>
      <P>17th Jun 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Sir and Madam</P>
      <P>I am writing this letter to want you to know that what I think about the musical show which you (The Circle Theatre) present.</P>
      <P>I bought group ticket for the show. Because we were 7 people. I saw "discount available" in the advertisement. When I asked something about stafis. I ignored it. Becouse I wanted to see this show. Becouse my favorite actor plays in it.</P>
      <P>We went to the theatre bulding at 18:30. We waited to start the show about one hour and fourty-five minutes. The show started late (about 45 min.) We were bored and we wished that this is last mistake</P>
      <P>During the show, we couldn't see Danny Brook who is my favorite actor. An other one played in the show. We were really angry. Becouse you said lie to us. If Danny Brook does not play, you have to say something about this to people who there are in the theater This is your unforgiven mistake.</P>
      <P>After the show, w were still angry, we wanted to eat something in your theater restaurant. When we came to the restaurant, we saw that it was close. I was sure that we can visit it after the show is writing on the advertisement. We were hungry and angry in this time.</P>
      <P>This is too bad evening for us. We were bored to waiting. We couldn't see Danny Brook in the show. We were hungry after the show. But we couldn't eat something and we couldn't use discount.</P>
      <P>They are your mistakes. I hope that you can understand me and you will do something about mistakes. When you do something, I went to see your new shows. But, now, I want to ask that you could pay my money back. Thanks for reading this letter</P>
      <P>Yours faithfull</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>CHANGING LIFE</P>
      <P>When I went to school, I wrote a letter to my friends. Becouse I hadn't got a mobile-phone. Now I have got a mobile-phone and I always use it. It's fast and easy. But sometimes I miss the letters. I miss to wait the postman every morning.</P>
      <P>Before we had a computer, I played game with my friends in our garden or in their garden. We played a lot of games during day. When we had a computer, I started to play computer games. I didn't want to play outside games with my friends. Becouse the computer was more interesting than my friends.</P>
      <P>I use internet now. I don't buy newspaper. Becouse I can read my newspaper in the internet. I can buy something from internet. for example, I send a flower to my mum in mother's day by internet order.</P>
      <P>My daily life is changing. Everthing is easy now. I can send a mail to my friend who lives in Canada. I never forget important days. Becouse I have got a data-bank. When the important day is coming, it says to me.</P>
      <P>Life is really easy. You need to learn how you can use the technology. But, sometimes I miss past days. I miss to play in the garden, post a mail to my friends, forget the important day. Sometimes I want to go to somewhere without technology.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
