<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR884*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>31-40</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>BRASILIA (DF), JUNE 17th 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Manager,</P>
      <P>I'm writing this letter to express my disappointment with "Over the rainbow", the musical show which I watched last evening.</P>
      <P>First of all, according to the advertisement, one of the main actors would be DANNY BROOK who I love. Instead of this, I had to watch the performance of a different and unknown actor who wasn't so great as I expected.</P>
      <P>Secondly, the show started one hour late and I hate waiting in a queue more than it's necessary. I felt very upset and my enjoyable night became a stressed and very expensive one, too.</P>
      <P>There wasn't discount avaiable for the tickets and I went to the theatre with my three cousins from Brazil. In addition to this, after the show, we looked for the theatre restaurant which has been closed for repairing since one month ago.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, last night definitely was the worst experience about entertainment I've ever had in my life and that's why I ask you my money back as a compensation.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to your reply</P>
      <P>faithfuly,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Modern technology can affect our daily life transforming our relationship and the ways to comunicate to other people as well as our life expectancy. With the introduction of the computer in our civilization we can access Internet to comunicate with our relatives and friends living abroad or far from ourselves. Despite of the distances, we can keep our friendship closely and with a cheaply way. Besides of this, the information goes faster than it used to know and it's avaiable in the same time to every part of the world. On the one hand, our time is taken to learn how to deal with the new technologies. On the other hand, we can feel more comfortable with them providing us support to our hard tasks and letting us free to apply our attention and efforts to more important things. For instance, we can research new manners of improving our quality of life. In conclusion, we are able to feel or to recognize the benefits of the modern technologies but we should be aware about how they are introduced in our lives to avoid the dangerous side of the TECHNOLOGY.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
