<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR885*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear sir,</P>
      <P>I'm writing to you, to complain about the musical show "OVER THE RAINBOW", that I came to see during my holiday in London, at your theatre. Unfortunately that evening wasn't as good as I expected.</P>
      <P>First of all in your advertisment for the show you wrote that Danny Brook and Tina Truelove were taking part at the show. And I was so excited about it! But I was very disappointed when I realised that another actor was taking part. And the worst was that he wasn't so good in his role!</P>
      <P>Another thing was that the show I went to was starting at 19:30 but it started at 20:15! The people who were there to watch the show were very ungry and they were shouting because they were waiting for too long, And I absolutely agree with them. Also in the advertisment you wrote that discounts were available, but they weren't, And also that people could visit the theatre restaurant after the show, to eat some thing or to have a drink. But when I went there, it was closed. I don't know why and I'd like you to tell me, the reason.</P>
      <P>Finally, you said that it would be our perfect evening out. Well it wasn't and I ask for my money back. I'd like you to return them to me.</P>
      <P>I'll wait to hear from you soon...</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. So, the next day Pat went and told to his sister Sally that her friends were organising a suprise party for her birthday. When Sally heared that, was very suprised and very excited. But because she didn't want to disappoint her friends, she was acting as she didn't know anything. She let them to organise it! But although she was acting like this she was very ungry with her brother Pat, because he didn't keep the secret.</P>
      <P>The party was on Saturday at Sally's house. All her friends were going to meet there, while she was at her swimming lesson. When that day arrived they all went there as they planned. When the clock showed 8:00 they hide themselves under the tables and the furnitures. After a while the bell rang. It was Sally! Suddenly they all shouted "suprise!". Sally although she knew it, she seemed very suprised! So her friends didn't understand that she knew about the party and they were very happy because they believed that the suprise party had succeed!</P>
      <P>But although Sally knew about it, they had a really great time. They danced a lot and they had pizza for dinner. It was an unforgetable night!!!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
