<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR887*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>A few weeks ago, I went to London, and I decided to go to the theatre and see a musical show, called "Over the Rainbow."</P>
      <P>I'm very sory to tell you that I had a very disappointing evening.</P>
      <P>First, I got there at 7:00 pm, because the show was about to start at 7:30 pm, and I need some time to by the tickets, I by two tickets of £20 and when I ask for a discount, they didn't give it to me, then I keep waiting for the show to start untill 8:15 pm.</P>
      <P>Then when the show finally started I got very disappointed because, I really wanted to see Danny Brook, but instead of him there was any other actor.</P>
      <P>Lately when the show finished, I planed to go to the restorant and get some food, but I was close, because it was being repaired.</P>
      <P>I will be very thankfull if your could return me half or some of my money, or even to make the corresponding discount.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets, every time I tell something to her, finally everyone knew about it. But this time it was something more important that any other time. I was in love with a friend's boyfriend and we were about to have an affair, but when I made the big mistake of telling me little and terrible secret to Pat, everithing started going wrong, Katrin my friend, and the one I was being bad with, was very upset with me, and she was right, but I really don't know what to do, I was in love with Brett, but I love my friend too. So I decide to talk to Brett. We both decided to finish with all this stupid affair. It was difficult, but I was the best for everyone. Then I decide to talk to Katrin, I was very sory of all I have do, so I apologize with her and promise her that this will never would happen again. Now I'm very happy because I learned that friends are the most important thing in the hole world.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
