<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR888*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Swedish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>41-50</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Manager Date 17-06-00</P>
      <P>xxxx</P>
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I'm writing to complain about the performance, Over The Rainbow at The Circle Theatre on the 14th of June. It is always a great opportunity to enjoy a musical when you go on your holiday to London. London is one of Europe's biggest centre and you can always get the best in show business. Rescently I decided to watch Over The Rainbow, a very famous and wellknown show.</P>
      <P>Firstly, the night performance was 45 minutes late and there were no discounts available as the advertisement told.</P>
      <P>Furthermore, I was shooked when one of the main persons entered the stage. He wasn't Danny Brook, one of the resons for my choice.</P>
      <P>Finally, the Theatre Restaurant was under reparation so we had to find another one for the evening supper.</P>
      <P>This wasn't "my perfect evening out", as said, and I'll make a claim for half the money back. I'm looking forward to receiving you reply as soon as possibly.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>Kim Nissen</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed my daily life. A century ago, when a farmer took the horses out of the stable and put the plouge behind them, we've got the word "time". Why not talk about the social life just sitting around a table without no rush.</P>
      <P>In modern days we have to wear a mobile phone. I visited an airport some days ago and in nearly every crowded corner, I could see those busy people always on their way. I heard the different phone signals, and what a miracle you can change them on the train when you are restless. A new word has appeared in those days, a technical proof of this is the computer. I can send and save information and the possibilities are uncountless. In nearly every home you can find it and the users now and in the future are the new generation.</P>
      <P>I must say a few words about the new electrical cars which surely will have a central role, exspecially today when fuel is so expensive. Watch out highly advanced technologies are appropriate and helpful for me and others if we only remember the importance of time to be together.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
