<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR889*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you to complain about the differences between what the advertisement of The Circle theater said about the musical show called 'Over The Rainbow' and the things I noticed when I was there.</P>
      <P>First of all, the most annoying thing for me was the absence of Danny Brook because in my country I don't have the chance to enjoy his excellent performance. Another actor standed for him, without any advice.</P>
      <P>Another thing was the confirmed hour of the show which it started forty-five minutes later without any factual reason.</P>
      <P>In addition to all this, there was no discount in the price of the tickets, for students either, contrary to what I was told by phone when I asked for more information.</P>
      <P>Moreover, as I had read the advertisement carefully, I had planned to invite some friends to have dinner at the theater's restaurant. But for our surprise, it was out of order. At the end of all these circumstances we were so puzzled and disappointed that we decided to make a complaint.</P>
      <P>So, due to the things I have mentioned, I think I shoul be given some money back.</P>
      <P>I look forward to recieving information from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>"How has modern technology changed your daily life?"</P>
      <P>Owing to the great speed of technological development, people need to lead a faster life.</P>
      <P>When this technological aspect changes so quickly, I obviously feel that my life changes too in many fields.</P>
      <P>I would say that the worst thing of this development for me is that more and more I experience stress in almost every aspect of my life. There is no enough time to do a lot of things; and if I want to do them, I realize that my life passes devoted in my duties without time to pleasures.</P>
      <P>Apart from this, another disadvantage is the pollution we all live with in the majority of cities, being able to breath fresh air several days a month when we go to the country.</P>
      <P>In addition to this, there is less comunication between members of my family, because when we arrive at home after an exhausted day racing with the time, the only thing we want to do is lying in the sofa while watching television.</P>
      <P>Apart from this, computer's advanced technology allows me to contact anyone at the moment that I want to, while five years ago when I did not have a computer, I had to write letters which was a slower way to contact with people.</P>
      <P>On the other hand and as a conclusion, I think that this development has made my life more comfortable living sourrendeddifferents.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
