<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR890*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Manager,</P>
      <P>I am writing in order to complain about the Musical Show, OVER THE RAIN, I went to see to the theatre.</P>
      <P>In the advertisment for the show you said that one of the starring was going to be Danny Brook, and to my surprise it was a different actor, and it realy disapoint me. Then the show was suppost to start at 19.30 hours but it started at 20:15, more than half an hour later. I cuold read in the advertisment that there were some discounts available but there werent. And the restorant of the theatre was being pait, so I could not go as you said in the advertisment.</P>
      <P>As you may undertand it was not a perfect night and I am not pleased with the show on eaven with your services. That is why I am going to ask you my money back. I am look forward to hearing from you as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Tecnology, are we prepeared for those advances? It change every days and I do not know if we will be able to understand it.</P>
      <P>Tecnology improves our lives, we have tecnology for cook, for work, for study, well hardly for everything. Mostly all of us, today know what is internet about, but one or two year ago we did not. And when we understand internet, we thought that meeting people from other countrys and could "chat" with them, was the top of the tecnology. But now we can eaven watch his face, Internet is amaizing. and now of courese there will someone trying to improve it.</P>
      <P>Tecnology change our daily life, it makes our life easily to live and of courese more confortable like with computers, televitions, radios etcetera and some times more secure like in medicine.</P>
      <P>Definitly we should try to understand tecnology, if we know how to use it, tecnology will improve our way of life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
