<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR892*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing in connection with the musical show your theatre company has presented recently, and, I want you to know, it has really disappointed me.</P>
      <P>To begin with, the actor the advertisement showed did not come, which I found it in very bad taste, disappointing. Moreover, the show started at a quarter past eight, forty-five minutes later than it might have been. I paid twenty pounds for my ticket because, as you may know, there were not discounts available. It is for this reason, I think you should return me some money back.</P>
      <P>To sum up, I would like to make my point about what happened in the restaurant after that.</P>
      <P>It was closed because its owner had decided to go on holiday. However, nobody told me. I think you would have to take it into consideration to avoid it happens again.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. If I had know it before, I would have never told her, because then, that was really important for me, but, anyway, presently, it doesn't really matter me.</P>
      <P>By the time, Pat and me had a close relationship. I explained her everything it happened to me and vice versa. We had many points in common and we knew each other as if we were sisters.</P>
      <P>However, one day our friendship was broken down. I told her I was falling in love with my best friend and she decided to explain it everybody in our group, despite knowing that must be a secret. When I met Caballos, my best friend, I felt embarassd and disappointed and I couldn't say anything. I was at a loss. Now I wish all of this had never happened, while I try to forget it laughing with Caballos and Pat.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
