<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR893*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen,</P>
      <P>I was very glad to receive this great notice. I am very excited about it. I entered in this competition because I have always wanted to do these kind of things.</P>
      <P>In your letter you asked me when I would rather travel, I will be able only on July because I have to work and I can take some days off on this month.</P>
      <P>If it is no problem I would rather stay in a lab cabin because I do not like much sleeping on the floor, but if you can not put me there I will be fine anywhere.</P>
      <P>About the I have to choose I would like to tell you something. I am very good at tennis and photography but I would prefer to practice new ones, if it is possible. I am keen on water and risk sports so I would choose climbing and surfing, I think it would be great if I learn them while I am there.</P>
      <P>Finally, I would like to ask you if there is any place where I can buy some souvenirs, so to take some money with me and I would be very grateful if you could send me a list of clothes.</P>
      <P>Thank you for everything. I am looking forward to travelling.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Every woman in the world likes the word shopping. It is like if they lose their concience while they are shopping.</P>
      <P>You can do shopping alone, with friends or with your kids, but the best thing of it is that you feel that you have all the power while you are buying things. May be it is not for you, may be it is a present, but buying things at least for me it is the best.</P>
      <P>But all this power and all this excitement could turn into something that you could start to hate.</P>
      <P>When you go shopping and there are a lot of people in the same place, all trying to find the best prices and not carying about anybody, this could get crazy to anyone.</P>
      <P>The long queues, close places, hight prices, sales, all these things conbined could make shopping an enjoyable thing for people who like doing it.</P>
      <P>But my advise for people, who like it so much that can not help doing it, is to try shopping in the afternoon, at this hour no-one do shopping and if there are some shops that are closed you can always go to a shopping mall.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
