<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR894*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am so glad that I have won this competition - two weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A. I would like to travel in the middle of July because my summer holiday starts in the middle of July. Is it possible to travel in July? And also I like to camp in a tent, because it will be more interesting than log cabins. You need to do everything by yourself.</P>
      <P>Taking a photography during the holiday is very good memory for me, and I can share my adventures to my friends. So while I am at the Camp I like to take many photographies and climb a mountain. Fresh-air. By the way, I wonder if I need a lot of money and what kind of clothes I should bring. Finally, thanks for giving this opportunity to me I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>13/06/00</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable</P>
      <P>Shopping sounds very enjobleable and fantastic for women. You can find a lot of interesting things which you unexpected. Some people enjoy window shopping, but some people enjoy spending their money on their clothes or shoes. Nowadays in a family shopping isn't women's job.</P>
      <P>In other hand, after shopping you'll get tired and maybe you can't afford your credit card. For instance, you want to buy everything which you saw, and after that, you don't know how much you have spent. If you are going shopping someone can easily steal your wallet which you are looking at some interesting things. It will be very awful.</P>
      <P>However, shopping has pros and cons, it depends on personal thinking. I enjoy shopping very much, it can let me know what's going on in the world. But it is a good idea to have a break during the shopping, you won't feel so tired.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
