<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR895*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms. Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your letter with reference to the competition. Here are the information you required.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I would like to travel in July, because it is the only month that I am free.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I prefer cabins. The main reason is that I love wood. In addition, due to my height (185 cm), I think cabins may be a better choice.</P>
      <P>Thirdly, from the activity list, I chose swimming and tennis as my favourite ones. Although I have played tennis only twice, I really enjoyed it. With contrast to this, I can swim when I was six. Furthermore, I once have been trained in a swimming centre, so I am quite confident with it.</P>
      <P>Lastly, could you please tell me what kind of clothes and how much money I should prepare and do I have to buy insurance myself?</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>The aim of this report is to suggest lessons and some activities which should be filmed in the video from my school.</P>
      <P>In my opinion, maths, politics, chinese, English and painting lessons are the most interesting ones. They are also the lessons which English and other foreigners are particularlly curious in.</P>
      <P>As far as I know, English people are really surprised about Chinese students' advanced level in Maths, as well as the knowledge in politics. This is a good oppertunate to see how they learn in class. As it is expected, painting lesson is an amazing one. You can find students use traditional chinese ink to draw and write.</P>
      <P>In spite of lessons, there are all kind of activities such as sports meeting, racing competition, and countryside activities. Some are held once a year and some are held every term. You will experience a different life in them.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, besides all mentioned, I highly recommond you video students' daily life and interview them. That will make it defenitely a successful video.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
