<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR897*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>13th JUNE 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Miss Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am really glad for reciving the first priec in your competition, I will be very plesant joining the holliday.</P>
      <P>According to your first question, I would like to travel only at July because it is my school holliday so I would not miss any class.</P>
      <P>I rather prefer to stay in tents because I like to stay as closest as possible to nature, it makes me feel better.</P>
      <P>As a regard for activities I would choose singing and surfing, surfing because it is my favourit sport, I have been surfing since I was a child so I am pretty good on it, and singing because I really love it, I am not as good on singing as I am on surfing but I like doing it.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask about somethings which might be necessary for me to take with, like what kind of clothes should I take, should I take my own surf board, and what about money, should I bring some with me?</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hear from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>13th JUNE 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Kin,</P>
      <P>As you know, I had a great experience last month giving a helping hand for the band called RAMONES.</P>
      <P>It was a breeze to help them and was very cool as well, those guys really know how to play rock.</P>
      <P>I had only to stay behind the drummer suppling them with water whenever they wanted.</P>
      <P>When the band had just started to play, lots of girls started to jump the faints getting very close to them, some of the girls started to take their clothes of, which was the best part for me, but some of securities went there and took them away.</P>
      <P>Afterwards, the Ramones had a short break and when they went back from their break they've just went of.</P>
      <P>I had a really nice time with them even tought I would've prefered to stay at the front with the others people, but anyway it was a great experience for me, I holp to be able to help them next year.</P>
      <P>I holp you've enjoed my experience, and I hope to hear from you soon.</P>
      <P>See yah mate</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
