<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR898*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I received your letter and would be glad to travel two weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A. but I will only be able to go in July for in June I will be in Austria with a friend and in August I have rented an appartment with my family.</P>
      <P>I would rather be accommodated in a tent because I already have the necessary material for camping. While I am at the Camp I would like to play tennis and do photography. I play very well tennis since I have played it since I was a child but I am a novice in photography and I would like to try it as I have always been interested in it.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask you a few questions:</P>
      <P>What kind of clothes should I bring?</P>
      <P>Will you give clothes for activities?</P>
      <P>How much money should I bring there?</P>
      <P>Faithfully Yours,</P>
      <P>Pascal Fritz</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Although many people enjoy shopping, shopping is not always enjoyable. You can fall on a very disagreable sellor and if you find what you wanted, you will not want to pay him or her for it.</P>
      <P>Sometimes the seller might even ignore you as he or she is talking to another sellor.</P>
      <P>For example, you walk into a shoe store. Two sellers are talking and although they saw you enter, they continue their discussion so you have to interrupt them. Then, one of them serves you but half listens to you because he or she is still talking to the other sellor. There is nothing more disagreable than that.</P>
      <P>Also, when you find a nice sellor and he shows you lots of objects, when you don't find what you want, you feel sad for him or her because you made him or her lose his or her time so you feel obliged to buy something. All this to say that shopping may seem enjoyable but often is not.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
