<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR899*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>Further to the umpleasent fact that took place last week I am in my right of complaining about the musical show I saw when I was in London.</P>
      <P>First of all, when we arrived we went to pay and we gave a discount ticket. It was not available but the worst thing was that nobody explained us the reason.</P>
      <P>The show had to start at 19:30 and it did not start until 8:15, then I felt dissappointed because the main actor had been changed. It had not been such a terrible thing if the new actor would have acted as well as the other one.</P>
      <P>If it does not seem enough, after the show by boyfriend wanted to invite me to eat something in the theatre's restaurant but the umpleasent surprise was that it was closed because all the waiters were on holiday.</P>
      <P>After explaining you my complains I hope you to send me some money back.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. It was our last school year, so we decided to organize a trip to celebrate we had finally finished it. We knew that our parents wouldn't let us to travel alone so we had to invent a story to avoid they could realize what happened. Kim, Kate and Pat told their parents they were going to travel with the school and so, did I. We were excited and we started to organized everything. We booked some rooms in a hotel, next to the beach and we bought all the useful things we were going to need. It seemed the perfect holiday but it wasn't. Pat was in love with my eldest brother whose name is Jon (I have never got on well with him). Pat told him our idea. Pour Pat, she didn't know my brother, she didn't know how he was. Jon told my parents what we wanted to do. We lost our holidays.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
