<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR900*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>31-40</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>To Competition Organiser</P>
      <P>Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>Thank you for choosing me in your competition for first prize. I feel very happy a I answer immidiatly to your letter.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel only in July, because I will have holiday that time. I'm always having holidays in July it is my favorite time for holidays.</P>
      <P>For accommodation at Camp California I prefer tents, because I use to go tents holidays, I like it.</P>
      <P>From activities which you offer to me I choose swimming and tennis. I am very good in swimming. I do this sport since I was child and I really enjoy it. I'm not so good in tennis but I would like to play it for practise. Also I find that it sport is very usefull for my health and does me feel better. It is all about me.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask you something.</P>
      <P>At first, which kind of clothes I need take with me, because I don't know anything about the weather in California, and at tend how much money I will need.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>Some people likes to do shopping. I hate it. I never liked shopping. It always was trouble for me.</P>
      <P>I don't like to have many things in my house, I don't like to have many clothes and shoes, and I don't know what else. Just nesseccary.</P>
      <P>I think the people who are enjoying shopping they are greede for materialistic things and they havn't interests for spirit (?), intelect life. They are loosing time of their life for nothing. In my opinion we must spend more time for more interesting than shopping things like sport, reading, chating about ideas which make our lives better. We must do something for help other people to feel better and usefull.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
