<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR903*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Swedish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear director of the Circle Theater!</P>
      <P>Last week I was in London. On Friday we, my friend and I visited your Theater to see 'Over the rainbow'. It should has been my best evening that week, unfortunatly it wasn't. The first thing that happen was that the show didn't start on time. Instead of 730 am as your advertisment said, it started 815 am. In the meantime we tried to get our money back to do something else, but that was impossible. When the show started Danny Brook was not acting, witch was a great dissapointment for us both. We are both big faan of him</P>
      <P>When the show was finished we went to the resturant to have something to eat. But then it was cloesed because of reparations.</P>
      <P>Due to all this troubel I think we should have our money back. We both have £15 tickets. And to an other time, make soure that your advertisment is correkt!</P>
      <P>Yours Mrs Anna Schulsson</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. She was my best friend for several years as a child. But I haven't seen her since we were 10 years old. When were nine years old and were in thired grade we had a 'House' where we used to play all afternones. In fact it wasn't a realy house, it was some stones between the trees in the littel forest neear our house. But we used to call it 'Our House'. It was a secret place and we had promissed each other not to tell anybody about it. Useally we were cooking flower-soup, and talking secrets.</P>
      <P>One day when I were there alone, I heard some other kids aproting, I sat down behind one of the stones so they shoulden't see me. One minute later, Pat and half our classe stod in 'the House' looking and laufing at me and my flower soup.</P>
      <P>Maby she did it to get friends. But in fact that day she had loosed my friendship.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
