<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR95*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helene Ryan,</P>
      <P>I have just received your letter and I am glad to know that I have won first prize in your competition. Now, I am writing to you to ask some details about these two weeks at Camp California and giving some answers to your questions.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to know if you have some vacancies in July because it is the only month where I am in holidays. About the accommodation, I would prefer staying in tents as I used to during summer holidays when I was a child. Furthermore, you asked me to choise two activities I would like to do. Firstly, I will be happy to play tennis because I used to play this sport with my village club for five years and earned a few competitions. Secondly, I am very interesting in photography because my father is a photographer and we are used to spending time each other. We had a lot of fun during our last holidays and we took a lot of pictures. As the instructions about clothes and money were not enclosed in your letter, I request about it and ask you to include in it.</P>
      <P>Thank you very much, I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>A lot of people like doing shopping but most of them might tell you that sometimes is not always enjoyable. And nowadays people must do shopping either they like it or not.</P>
      <P>For people who used to do shopping, going in big stores, I think they like it and they are always looking for fashioned-clothes. But when these stores are full of people, crowded, like the sales period, I am sure that the same people who like doing shopping may think it can be boring.</P>
      <P>In my opinion, I think people have to do shopping even though they don't appreciate it very much. If these people have a family with children, they must buy some food to feed them even if a supermarket is full of people. And now for them shopping can be considerated like a contrariety.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
