<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR96*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>41-50</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/madam</P>
      <P>I am writing with regard to your advertisment. During my 2 week's holiday I would like to attend a musical show. It was my favorite play. I was very hopefull that I was going to have a good time. But there were many things which went wrong.</P>
      <P>Firstly, I have had no discount at paying. secondly there was delay which got me into trouble, After the show I couldn't catch my train. Because I didn't have any plan I decided to have a lunch in theatre restaurant. But it was closed. The worst thing is that I couldn't watch my favorite actor. I was so dissapointted with that. I couldn't consentrate on the play any more.</P>
      <P>Contrary to the advertisment everything was disapointing. I regret to demand all my expenses. I hope you are going to be take into consideration my terrible situation.</P>
      <P>I am waiting for a satisfactory answer</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Azami</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Technology has developed increasingly in recent years. As a result of this our society has changed a lot.</P>
      <P>On the one hand technology has made our lives more comfortable and easier. On the other hand we have faced some problems, such as social and environmental problems.</P>
      <P>Nowadays students have much more facilitis in education than before. Although in those days the only way of learning was reading. These days we can use computer, television and some sophisticated equipment. which were unusuall before. Than to technology we can reach any place in the world easily. We can get some information more quickly. Technology has a huge effect on our spare time activities as well. Children play wit computer instead of usuall plays.</P>
      <P>Despite the huge facilities technology has affected our lives negatively. There has been change relatinships between people. People are getting more and more lonely. We have noticed the environmential damage in recent years.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
