<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR97*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Robertson,</P>
      <P>I am representing an English class, which is going on a three-day London tour.</P>
      <P>We would like to thank you for organising our programme. We really appreciate your attention. The programme you suggest is versatile and full of interesting activities. We are eager to attend National Art Gallery and Science Museum.</P>
      <P>But we would like to make our suggestion, if you don't mind. We have seen an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show and would like to go to this exciting show. It will take place in the Central Exhibition Hall on Tuesday on the 14th of March from 10 a.m. to 19 p.m.</P>
      <P>Our students will have a great opportunity of seeing the latest fashion, as this unique show is held only once a year. What's more, new hairstyles and leisure and sports wear are presented there. And apart from it, this activity is free of charge.</P>
      <P>We would be very grateful if you could change our programme for Tuesday afternoon. We are thinking here particularly of the fact, that we can go to the show, instead of shopping.</P>
      <P>We sincerely hope that you will consider our suggestion.</P>
      <P>Faithfully yours,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>We tend to think that famous people, such as politicians and film stars are very happy and satisfied with their life. But such an attitude is wrong. It is quite obvious, that celebreties can't lead a normal life, as they are constantly followed by reporters, what makes their life miserable.</P>
      <P>The first point I would like to make is that a private life of a celebrity is open to public. I am thinking here particularly of the fact that every event and action is wildely discussed in the mass-media. It is common knowledge, that such an attention inevitably tells on relationships in the family.</P>
      <P>Another aspect is that children of famous people suffer a lot from this attention. They can't communicate with ordinary children and attend ordinary schools.</P>
      <P>And last, but not least is the fact that famous people can't express their emotions, show their real feelings to public. And it tells on their attitude to life and on their character. I would like to stress that very often famous people become reserved, bad-tempered and angry with the world for interfering into their lives.</P>
      <P>I would like to sum up by saying that every person, either famous or not, deserves to have a private life without being followed or disturbed.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
