<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR98*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you to complain about the show which I saw last Friday at your theatre. The show was called 'Over the rainbow' I was not pleased with the way that was set out.</P>
      <P>First of all, when I went and bought my ticket, there was no discount but in your advertisement it said clearly that discounts are available and as a result my ticket was bought more expensive.</P>
      <P>Secondly, the show I went was the evening one, which was supposed to start at 7:30 p.m. but it had a 41 minutes delay and ended up starting at 8.15 p.m.</P>
      <P>Furthermore, the original actor was Danny Brook but it changed to a different actor which acted terribly and was very disappointing. Last of all, it said in your advertisement that there is a theatre restaurant after the show but it turned out to be closed because it was redecorating and no annocement was made.</P>
      <P>I didn't have a perfect evening out and instead I had a awful evening out. Therefore I would like are refund of my ticket and I would like a apolygists. Thank you from you</P>
      <P>Your Sincelery, </P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>What will clothes be like 100 years from now? What do you think modles will wear in cat walks? Will they wear anything? Who know? Nowaday, people look at fashion-magesins or get opinions from their friends to decide what to wear in different occasions</P>
      <P>Will they still do the same 100 years later?</P>
      <P>In my opinion, I think clothes will be a lot differente 100 years later compare to now. As new materials are made and new styles are created either by designers or people themselves which leads to changes in fashion but on the other hand come materials will probably still be used such as jeans, which was invented ages ago in America. and people nowadays still use jeans as a common material. If you walk out to the street now, you will probably see more than half the people wearing clothes that are made with jeans which is incredibly surprising!</P>
      <P>From my point of view, I think people will wear more clothes that are see-through in particular. As people are wearing thinner and thinner clothings to show off their figure They might as well just wear clothes that are see through to give it a better effect! so if you want to know what clothes will be like 100 year later, the only thing you can do is to WAIT!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
