<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR101*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Satomi Fukao</P>
      <P>12 Dover Street</P>
      <P>AS3 7GH, London</P>
      <P>13, Jun, 2000</P>
      <P>Mrs. Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>Competition Organiser</P>
      <P>Dear Madam</P>
      <P>I have received the letter which tells me that have won first prize in your competition. I am going to write about information which you want to know.</P>
      <P>First, I would like to travel in only July, because I have got a job and only July is the time I can have a vacation.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I would like to choose a tent for accommodation, because I have never spent time in a tent, that's why, I think it is a good oppotunity for me.</P>
      <P>I would like to choose swimming and photography for activities. I have a planty of experience and knowledge of both aspect of part.</P>
      <P>Lastly, I would like to ask you two questions. One of them is that what kind of clothes suitable on this camp. Another one is that how much money I have to prepare.</P>
      <P>I will be greatfull if you could inform me.</P>
      <P>Your sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Hi! How are you doing? I had a wonderful time last month. I helped a pop concert as a charity. My jobs were collecting a ticket, saling goods and refreshment, guiding people to a right seat and cleaning up the concert hole after finish a concert. I wasn't allowed to help a heavy work, even though I wanted to do, because I'm woman. What I particularly liked about the experience was the concert had achived by our supports. It seemed that all people, audience, the band and stuffs were delightful. If I have chance, I want to help a concert again. I have never felt such as satisfaction. I really recomend you to help them, I think this is a good oppotunity and I want you understand my feeling well. I've got lots of things about the concert to talk to you. I want to know your openion.</P>
      <P>If you have time, drop me a line, please.</P>
      <P>Bye</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
