<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR104*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam;</P>
      <P>Yesterday I went to the theatre play called "Over the Rainbow" which I saw the advertisement in todays Guardian. I want to tell you that I am very dissapointed about the play.</P>
      <P>In the advirtisement it is written that Danny Brook was in the starring. However I didn't see him all the night. There was another actor instead of him. And also it should be started at 19.30, as I saw in the advirtisement, which has started at 20.15! And so far there wasn't any discounts available which is written to be "available" in the advirtisement. I went to the theatre restaurant after the show but it was closed because of the re-decoration progress inside. You should have written it in the advirtisement. And after all no one can say that I had a perfect evening out! Absolutely it was very dissapointing. so I want my money back.</P>
      <P>I hope you understand me and correct your mistakes in the next advirtisement and send me my money soon!</P>
      <P>Yours Faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Simple Solutions</P>
      <P>It is over 50 years since the production of the computer and television. Our lifes changed since then</P>
      <P>Today every 5 out of 10 pupil can use computer basicly. And almost everybody has a television in their homes. These 2 devices make my life easier. I can't go out all the time or be with my friends to have fun. So I watch Tv at home instead of sitting in a chair looking out of a window. I play computer more than watching Tv when I get bored.</P>
      <P>The internet is the world's largest communication system ever made. I can do anything I want such as buy Cd's watch film or even buy food. It is really enjable when I chat with pupil. Internet brought a new way to my live since I started to use it. It is easy and very useful. I can reach any knowledge that I want to. Techology is also important in one subject for me. Transportation. I can't have to walk to school everyday for 8 months, Cars, busses and trains are very useful in daily life.</P>
      <P>Lots of thing would be hard and boring in my life I was living in a different time than now. I can easily do what I want. Technology brought simple solutions to my life.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
