<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR106*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>Unfortunatelly I have to complained about musical show in your's Circle Theatre last evening.</P>
      <P>When I become your's advertisment concerning the show "Over the Rainbow" I thought that I'll have a great evening, but unfortunatelly it was a big disappointment for me. Maybe I start for the beginning. First of all, Danny Brook - the main actor in this musical - was abbsend. The show had a 45 minutes delay - what a shame! You also offered discounts, whot kind of discounts? I haven't seen any! I was with my son (11 years old) and I had to paid a full-prize for his ticket. Becouse the show was very long, we were getting hungry but of course your's theatre restaurants was closed because of holiday.</P>
      <P>Hereby I have to ask for money back or another discounts for me.</P>
      <P>Waiting for you replay.</P>
      <P>With best regards</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. The stay has begaun last year, when I stated my summer holiday. I had not any money for travelling but my parents were able to give me them if I only had a concret plans. I started talking with my parents that I will be travelling with my friends through West-Europe for one month. I had really a good plan but any good friends. I become quite a lot of money and I left home. During one week I was really travelling with my friends but then I was getting boring with them and I started to travel alone. Now I don't think that it was a good idea. Sometimes I had to sleep on a railway-stations or under a bridges. After one mounth I came home back and explained my parents how a lot of fun had I with my friends - I don't know why I was such a lair. My parents belived my word's untill my younger brother Pat told them the true. Now my parents' don't belive my words. But I think, this was a good lesson for me and I lair any more.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
