<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR108*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms. Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writing to thank you to send me all the details about my prize and I'd like to give you a complete information about the journey will be done by myself.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel at the beginning of the month, could be between first and fifteeth of july, because afterwards I have several business meetings and it would be difficult for me to take a trip.</P>
      <P>Related with accommodation, I'd prefer to stay in log cabins. Although I like camping and sharing with different kind of people, I'd prefer a confortable and private place (if it's possible) where I can sleep, or be quiet.. I am not a teenager!</P>
      <P>Really, this prize is wonderful to have a healthy life. I want to do two activities; painting and tennis. The first one is for my mental health, I need a break in my style of life. the second one is just because I'm fanatic of that sports (really I'm not martine hingis).</P>
      <P>Eventually, I'd like to request to have special food, because and vegetarian person, besides I try to eat just organic food.</P>
      <P>I hope my reply has been suitable.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>How are you doing? It have been a long time since the last time I wrote you... I'm sorry. However the reason is absolutely amazing. I was training to be a personal assistance to Madonna herself. Maybe, you don't believe me, but it's true.</P>
      <P>I applied to the job and she selected me between hundreds of candidates (I don't receive salary). My work is to help her during each concert. You know, she has a brilliant performance where she must change her customs, make up, scenery, everytime; so she needs a lot of people near.</P>
      <P>My first job was in the Hillsborough's concert (I think, you heard about it). I was running all the show, my responsability was to get dress her. I wasn't alone, I worked with a staff of ten people. We had to take of some clothes and then to put on others ones completly different, in just few minutes (similar to Formula One).</P>
      <P>I was exhausted when the concert finished, anyway it has been one of my best experience and I'll remember for life.</P>
      <P>Finally, I send you all my positive energy and I am looking forward to receiving your letter back.</P>
      <P>all the best.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
