<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR109*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>To:</P>
      <P>From:</P>
      <P>I spent two days at annual international arts festival from 21 to 22 of November.</P>
      <P>This festival was well-orginised. There were a lot of activities for everyone. I relly liked exhibitions. I had a chance to see amazing pictures with painted by Russian painters. There was an excellent jazz concert. The Band "Three Kings" apresented new stily of music. I would like to notice that a dance show was absolutelly marvelous. What's a greit idea to invite writers there! I relly liked to speak with them.</P>
      <P>From my point of view I can complain only on a small concert hall and there were artist from only six countries. Nowadays many people fond of classical music, but this concert was too small that's why many people had to miss this classical concert.</P>
      <P>You wrote an advertisment that people from more than 15 deferent countries were going to visit this concert, but there were artists only from 6 countries. It was relly pity because I expected to see artists from France and Italy.</P>
      <P>The International Arts Festival was organised quite well. I would only recomended you to have more artists and a classical concert should be in bigger hall than it was.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>One man and one woman lived in small house beside the sea. There names were Ivan and Maria. They were so pour that somitimes they hardly had something to eat.</P>
      <P>One day Ivan caught a fish. It wasn't usual fish, it was Gold Fish and it asked him as human; ' Please, let me go and I can do for you anything you want'. But Ivan was so kind person that he let Gold Fish went without any condition.</P>
      <P>Afterwards he came back home. He told her wife about this story. She was angry and she said that Ivan was just foolish man. She persuide him to go to the sea to ask a lot of things for her. Ivan had to do what she said. Gold Fish did everything what Ivan asked.</P>
      <P>When he come back home, he was surprise because Maria was more angry than before. She said that it wasn't enough what Gold Fish had done for her.</P>
      <P>Ivan had to beg Gold Fish again and again. In the end, greedy Maria wanted impossible thing. She said that Ivan should bring Gold Fish to home and Ivan could leave this house because she didn't need him anymore. Maria wanted too much and Gold Fish returned everything at the beginning. Maria and Ivan were again poor.</P>
      <P> This story happened a long time ago.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
