<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR111*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>13.06.2000</P>
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your letter. You would like to have some further information from me. I am writing to answer your letter.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel only in July because I have been working in a bank and I can only go on a holiday in July.</P>
      <P>I would prefer to stay in a tent because I used to go camping and stay in the tent. Therefore I would like to try some kind of experience.</P>
      <P>I am interested in tennis but I am not so good tennis player. However I would like to attend tennis activity. In addition swimming would be good activity for me. While I was studying at the high school and the university, I was in the swimming team of the school.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask you about clothes and the money. Could you tell me what kind of clothes I should bring? When I go there, can I use credit card or should I have cash?</P>
      <P>I look forward to your answer.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely, </P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>I think all people like shopping. When you ask some people to learn their opinions about shopping they can tell you they don't like shopping but I suppose it is not true. For example me, when someone asked me about shopping I would say that I hadn't liked it. However now if someone asks me the same question my answer will be "yes, I like it". When people hear this word shopping they only think about to go some stores and try new clothes or shoes and search for their size and so on. They don't think about other kind of shopping which are liked by themselves. Maybe they like shopping on internet or window shopping doesn't matter what kind of shopping they like. There are a lot of shopping style on the world I am sure everybody prefer one of them.</P>
      <P>In my opinion, even though people say shopping is not always enjoyable, there are always some fun you can find. You only need to discover what you like, and how you can have fun with shopping.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
