<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR112*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Olivier Peissaud</P>
      <P>The Manager</P>
      <P>Circle Theater</P>
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complaint about a very disappointing evening I recently had during a week's holiday in London.</P>
      <P>My girlfriend and I read an advertisement about the show "Over the Rainbow" which is very popular. She is fond of the actor Danny Brook so I decided to buy two tickets, provided there were discounts available. When we asked for discounts tickets, we were said there never were discount offers and that we had to pay the highest tickets - £20 each - because we were not English students. We were annoyed about it but we paid off. We took our places, and began chatting with other people. We had to wait 8.15 pm before it started whereas the show was supposed to start at 9.30 pm! Moreover, we were astonished that another actor we did not know was playing the role of Danny Brook. My girlfriend was very upset and so was I.</P>
      <P>After that we thought we could have a drink in your theatre restaurant but it was closed because the decorations were being changed. Finally we had the worst evening I have ever imagined, it was definitely not the "perfect evening" as written in the adverstiment.</P>
      <P>So I want my money back for these two tickets - I have included a copy - and I hope you will pay more attention to the way you treat your customers, and avoid false advertisement.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Your children clothes in 100 years</P>
      <P>How interesting it is to imagine what kind of clothes people will wear in about a hundred years from now. Fashion is changing so quickly that all our dreams about clothes can become true. But let's see my point of view. In a hundred years, clothes would certainly be totally differents than ours. Materials, textures and colours change, and are minds too.</P>
      <P>So I think people will wear clothes made of recycled things, like bottles of aluminium. And I hope colours won't be dark and sad but very bright and enjoyable to see.</P>
      <P>I think men will still wear pants and jackets but maybe not in jeans. Syntethic materials have grown up and become very popular so it would keep going on. But maybe the shape of the clothes will changed: large pants as "baggy", or trousers with many pockets as we see today. For women, clothes change more than for men's. It maybe because they are more likely to try new ways of clothes. I guess they will wear a sort of tunique upon a shirt and a skirt, or more male clothes because they want to change. Finally it's very difficult to say that.</P>
      <P>Maybe Luc Besson's "Fifth Element" movie is quite a good example. The clothes were designed by the famous Jean-Paul Gaultier. And it really is an interesting point of view.</P>
      <P>To conclude, in the end clothes won't be what we think about today, and it's a good thing because we can only imagine and follow the trend of fashion that makes us feel pretty and happy.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
