<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR764*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you because I went to The Circle Theatre some days ago and I regret to inform you that it was not a good experience.</P>
      <P>According to the advertisement Danny Brook was the male actor. However he did not act, and his sustitute was not very good at acting.</P>
      <P>Secondly I had problems with both tickets and time.</P>
      <P>The play started at 20:15 instead of 19.30. Furthermore I could not get a discount although I think I was entitled to it. (I have a special youth card).</P>
      <P>In addition the theatre restaurant was not available because of the waiters' strike.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, not only my evening was horrible but also expensive. That is why I ask you for refunding my money, or at least part of it.</P>
      <P>Faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="5a">
      <P>Best Detective Stories of Agatha Christie (Accident)</P>
      <P>Dear Nigel,</P>
      <P>I was pleased to hear from you last week. Now I am writing to you because a story of Agatha Christie is going to be read on the radio. Its title is "Accident"</P>
      <P>I know you are interested in the author and I think you'll like the story.</P>
      <P>Firstly the main character is Evans, a retired police captain. He is not as well-known as Poirot or Miss Marple, but his personality it quite interesting. I am sure you'll agree with me.</P>
      <P>Secondly the plot. It is about a woman who poisoned her first husband. At least this is Evans' opinion. Not only is the plot interesting but also it catchs your attention since the first moment.</P>
      <P>Finally, you should pay attention to the ending which is surprising.</P>
      <P>I hope you will spend a good evening listening to the radio. The story is going to be read next Friday at 8.00 p.m. Have a good time and write soon.</P>
      <P>Love,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
