<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR905*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Robertson,</P>
      <P>The trip that you planned for us, students, it's a great chance to meet new people and visit a beautiful city like London. Your programme is excellent because it tries to offer to the students the best way to spend our time without wasting time in silly places or events. We'd like to thank you because the kind of happening shows how you are dedicated with our school and the students that study there. It's great to visit especially the Science Museum because of its expositions.</P>
      <P>But there's something that I'd like to ask. The London fashion and Leisure Show will start on Tuesday. It's a great opportunity for us because there will be expositions of the latest fashions, of the new hairstyles, of the new leisure and sports clothes and people teaching how to make up.</P>
      <P>Our suggestion is that you could change the day of the leisure time to the shopping in the afternoon. By this way, the leisure time would be on Tuesday and we would be able to go to the London Fashion. Thanks for the attention and we're waiting for your answer.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Famous People x Media</P>
      <P>Famous people are special for the rest of the society. They form opinions and invent new fashion styles. Nowadays, the media is expanding its ways of communication so they need more information. The media is starting to get into the private life of these famous people.</P>
      <P>It's important to respect other people lives because it can cause serious problems in the family of the person or in his life. If the famous person doesn't mind in being filmed in his personal life there's no problem. But if the politicians or the film stars ask for privacity the media has to respect. Everybody likes to be with your family without any reporter or photographer.</P>
      <P>In summary, the best thing to do is try to extract from these people their best qualities and not try to find things that could irritate them like familiar problems or personal problems. The respect is essential. They deserve to have a private life like any common person.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
