<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR908*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Manager of The Circle Theatre.</P>
      <P>I'M WRITING TO YOU TO EXPLAIN MY DESAGREABLE EXPERIENCE IN YOUR THEATRE THE LAST SATURDAY, IN YOUR SHOW "OVER THE RAINBOW".</P>
      <P>FIRST OF ALL, I WANT YOU KNOW THAT THIS SATURDAY WAS MY HUSBAND'S BIRTHDAY AND I WAS PLANNING THIS DAY DURING ONE MONTH. MY INTENTION WAS TO SPEND AN SPECIAL NIGHT WITH HIM. AND IT WAS REALLY SPECIAL!!!</P>
      <P>YOUR SHOW STARTED ALMOST ONE HOUR LATER AND WITH ANY DISCOUNT FOR US ON THE ENTRY. BUT IT WASN'T THE WORSE, BECAUSE I CAN UNDERSTAND THE TROUBLES TO PLAY ON THE THEATRE. BUT WHAT CANNOT I FORGIVE TO YOUR COMPANY IS TO CHANGE THE START AT THE LAST MOMENT, MY HUSBAND IS A DANNY BROOK'S FAN AND HE FELT REALLY DISSAPOINTED.</P>
      <P>IT ISN'T ALL. WHEN THE SHOW WAS FINISHED, WE WANTED TO GO TO DINNER, AS YOU PUBLISHED ON THE PROGRAMM, BUT THE RESTAURANT WAS CLOSED BECAUSE IT WAS ON PUBLIC WORKS!!!</P>
      <P>YOUR ORGANISATION WAS A GREAT DISASTER. NOBODY TELL US ANYTHING ABOUT THE CHANGES, AND WE WANT THAT YOU GIVE US BACK THE MONEY. I FEEL YOU LIE ME AND YOUR COMPANY IS NOT SERIOUS.</P>
      <P>I WAIT YOUR ANSWER, AND OUR MONEY BACK AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.</P>
      <P>Your's faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets.</P>
      <P>Pat wasn't the most popular boy in the school. He was shy, reserved and a very closed person. He enjoyed himself reading, playing piano at home.</P>
      <P>Despite his way of live, his best friend was Anna, the most popular girl in the school. She explained everything what happened in her live to Pat.</P>
      <P>When Pat was 16, he decided to change his way of live, spending more time with friends, but what he could do to have some friends?</P>
      <P>Definately. He started to "sell" the secrets of Anna to all the boys of the school who were interested in her. All the boys of the class went to Pat to know what Anna was doing in every moment, and Pat was becoming 'friend' of all the boys.</P>
      <P>He was very happy, because he felt that everybody loved him. Everyone, less Anna. She didn't tell him anything more, and Pat didn't have any secret to sell to his "new friends".</P>
      <P>At least, Pat didn't have any friend, because he didn't have anything to sell about Anna.</P>
      <P>Is it moral, to get some friends destroying and hurting another people? I think NO! And you?</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
