<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR909*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam.</P>
      <P>My name is Veronika. And I visited your theatre to see a musical show "Over the Rainbow". I am writing to you to say that it was a very disappointing evening. And I'll try to explain why.</P>
      <P>First of all, there were the different actors in a show, but you didn't say anything about it before the show.</P>
      <P>The other point was the beginning of the show. It started at 20:15, but it was said that it starts at 19:30. As a result I missed my train.</P>
      <P>The third problem was the discounts. There were no ay discount at all. But I am a student and I know that I can get tickets with the discount.</P>
      <P>And the last disappointment was your restaurant after the show. It was closed because of the lack of stuth</P>
      <P>Of course I want to get my money back, but I know that I will never get it. So as a conclusion I want to give you one piece of advice - try to organise your shows more carefully.</P>
      <P>With the best wishes</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed your daily life?</P>
      <P>We know that everything is changing. And of course the technology is also changing. Not so long ago we had to do many things by our hand, but now there re a lot of machines to do the same. And it makes our life easier. Now we have free time to do anything else, while machine is doing our work. It's connected with our house, our workplace and e.t.c.</P>
      <P>For example, earlier I used to wash my clothes by hand, but now I have the last version of wash machine and now there are no any reasons to do it by hand. Earlier it took me 3 hours, but now it is my free time and I can go for a walk with my friends.</P>
      <P>Another example is that earlier we had to rewrite some documents by hand just to make a copy. Now we have a scanner and a printer to do it. And it takes bout 1 minute to make a copy but not 1 hour.</P>
      <P>So, I think that modern technology gives us a lot of opportunities to do the really important for our life things.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
