<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR910*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson</P>
      <P>Thank you for organising the trip to London. It is very fantastic especially the programme on 13th March that we are having a river trip to Greenwich. The purpose that I am writing due to the fact that my class has seen an advertisement for the London Fashion and Leisure Show. It is worth visiting exhibition and we would like to go there.</P>
      <P>The show is established on Tuesday March 14th at Central Exhibition Hall London from 10.00 to 19.00. In the hall, there are four important themes; latest fashions, leisure and sports wear, make up, and hairstyles. This is great opportunity for the student to learn the changing in fashion and leisure and it is free.</P>
      <P>That all I would like to recommend you. It would be greatful if you could consider our suggestion and please inform us about your decision as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>The discussion about whether or not the famous people deserve to have a private life without journalists following them all the time is the controversial one. There are people from both side of agrument who have strong feelings.</P>
      <P>There is evidence that these people's life should be advertised by the media. Obviously, they have a lot of fans and their fans would like to know what happened to them. In addition, their life may be the good example for other people to follow. Sometime, many people don't know what to do and they should the person who they admire to immitate.</P>
      <P>However, there is other disadvantages that we should consider. Firstly, the famous people would like to do anything they want without being concentrated by media. I think it is annoying if you did something and tomorrow your performance would be known by the public. Eventhough, the famous people can be the good example, they should be the bad habit for public. A lot of people try to be like people who they admire, For example, buying the clothes that famous people wear. The reason that they know what kind of clothes that famous people wear is these people have a public life. To Prevent many people from copying too much we shouldn't inform all aspects of life of famous people.</P>
      <P>I agree that the famous people life should be in private. It is the benefit for themselves and the public.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
