<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR912*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Austria, 13th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Mrs. Ryan,</P>
      <P>I refer to your letter in which you informed me that I have won the first prise in the competition. You asked me for some further information and hear are my "desirs":</P>
      <P>I would like to travel only in July because in August I have to study for an exam. Further I would prefer to live in a tent at the Camp, because I am already used to that, because I often spent my holidays in tents. I would like to do painting, because one of my greatest hobbies is silk-painting and so I think I can improve my abilities. The second activity, which I choose is playing basketball, because I love this wonderful sport. We always play it at school and I am very good at it. I am in our school-basketball-team.</P>
      <P>I hope that you are now well informed and I would like to ask you which clothes and how much money I should bring with me.</P>
      <P>Thank you very much, I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Your sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Austria, 13th June 200</P>
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I hope you are fine. You know, last month I helped at a pop concert and I am sure you want to know some details.</P>
      <P>My first task was to open the doors to let in all the fans of Britney Spears. I stood at the entry and theire I had to check the tickets. Two girls came together and they wanted to go in with only one ticket for both! I had to tell one of them, that she had to leave. She started crying. Such a poor girl. At this moment I didn't like my position.</P>
      <P>My second task was that I had to look in all the bags of the fans to collect "dangerous" items, I saw really funny things like teeth-bruches in the bags. This part of my work was really funny and I enjoyed it.</P>
      <P>Summing up I can say that it was a fantastic day, because Britney sang so beautiful and the performance was also super.</P>
      <P>I hope you can imagine how a wonderful day it was for me.</P>
      <P>Yours</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
