<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR913*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson</P>
      <P>I am writing, on the name of all my English class, to thank you for the opportunity you give us to spend three days in London, but also to suggest some modifications in the programme.</P>
      <P>The programme you has already organised is very interesting, especially because it provides a good combination between cultural visits and more relaxed activities.</P>
      <P>But, in another hand, we have seen an advertisement for the "London Fashion and Leisure Show", which includes a range of different stands. The only day we can attend to this show is the Tuesday 14th March from 10 am to 7 pm in the Central Exhibition Hall.</P>
      <P>We are really interested in visiting this unhabitual show and the main advantage is that the entry is free for students.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, I suggest that we go directly after the Science Museum to the show. We all agree that we have enough time in Wednesday for shopping.</P>
      <P>I hope that you will agree with this suggestion. I am waiting for your answer.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Famous people, such as politicians and film stars, deserve to have a private life without journalists fellowing them all the time</P>
      <P>Famous people have always been the center of interest for number of people. Their wedding, their holiday, their new haircut and so on. But do we think enough about the right to have a private life?</P>
      <P>We can watch this problem from two different points of view. From one side, this people chose to become public people. If we don't want to be in the newspapers, we don't do politics or movies! But from the other, everybody has the right to have a secret garden, the right to be with his/her family without be disturbed by journalists and photographers. The case of the Princess Diana showed how this problem can reach such extremities.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, I would say that both parts, famous people and journalists, have to respect some rules. As public people, stars and politicians have to accord some time to their public but fans and press people have to respect their private life and to stay polite and respectful.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
