<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR914*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Robertson,</P>
      <P>I am writing you to thank for your program which will be for us in the next three days in London. Especially, sightseeing by bus in the morning and river trip to Greenwich in the afternoon are exciting activities.</P>
      <P>On your program of Tuesday is very interesting. Fortunately, there is the London fashion and leisure show which is held once a year. This show give us a lot of informations about current activities, fashion and what is happened here in London for example lastest fashions, leisure and sports wear, make up, hairstyles.</P>
      <P>It is a great opportunity because we will be able to learn london culture. We can be part of this show and be up to date with style and fashion.</P>
      <P>The admission is free for students. The show starts at 10.00 and finishes at 19.00 so we can change our afternoon program to go to the show at Central Exhibition Hall instead.</P>
      <P>If you agree, after Science Museum, we can have lunch at restaurant near the musuem, then we go directly from the restaurant to Central Exhibition Hall. We will be on time for the second show at 13.30 P.M and we can enjoy the show until 19.00 P.M.</P>
      <P>I'am looking forward to hearing your opinion on my suggestion.</P>
      <P>Your sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>The Home of the Future</P>
      <P>"Home" has so much meaning to the people. It doesn't mater who they are, where they are coming from, which color of their skin they have.</P>
      <P>Home is institution that create human and make them as a person and a good member in their communities.</P>
      <P>When I think of "the Home of the Future". I want to have a home which is built with a new material. Home made out of plastic also windows made out of plastic therefore we can have our home for a long time. The door it is broken, we can replace it rapidly and it is not expensive when it is plastic.</P>
      <P>We have more time to stay together at home, watching TV, playing games, etc.... because we can access to internet at home we can have all informations from internet. I think it is the best way of education and working when we can stay and learn or work from home. We have more time for the family who need mostly care and love.</P>
      <P>It will be a numer of Developments in Technology in the future, which can make our life easier to live but what should remain the same is feeling of being together and love.</P>
      <P>This 2 feelings can not be replaced by any Technology but we can use them to make a better home of the future.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
