<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR916*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you and reply the answers from your letter.</P>
      <P>I was glad to hearing the news from you and thank you very much! When you mentioned the period of my travelling I'm afraid I only free in July. Because I go on holiday in July naturally, and I have two terms in June and August. Therefore, I hope that you could make suitable arguement between you and me. Furthermore, I would like to stay in log cabins which I could feel more American style of the accommodation. In addition, there should not too hot inside during July.</P>
      <P>If I get two choices, I would like to go swimming and take photographs. Because I grew up in my home town that is a seaside city. I was starting trainning since 1996, and I have never give it up. Esepically, it is really good for my healthy during the growth period. Photography is my hobby that is taken in my spare time. I can remember that I used to take photographs on the exhibitions or during the holidays. It must be nice for my memories when I am older. In addition, it could showed people how nice the places are and the views I have got. Therefore, I would like to do those two activities.</P>
      <P>Finally, I would like to know the weather in California. Do I need take too much clothes? Could you tell me that the amount of money I can bring during the holiday?</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you!</P>
      <P>Your sincerely</P>
      <P>SHE DUNES</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable</P>
      <P>Shopping is concerned that people exchange from money to their demands. There are more and more retailors are opening to customer. Therefore, people used to shopping weekly or monthly.</P>
      <P>In my opinion, women are really enjoying shopping. It seems a human activity during their spare time. However, we are going to change traditional system to the "e-shopping". It is new for customers by technology they can switch on the computer and click everything they want. Therefore, it looks like a service and also boring for customer. I think most of gentlemen dislike shopping. They are always waiting for a long time after women finish their shopping.</P>
      <P>I believed that most of busy people want go shopping by the easy and quick way. Because they don't like waiting for payment and waste time of life. Therefore, they would like to use "e-shopping" which is getting better for their time.</P>
      <P>The life style has change already from past. Shopping is common activity in their life. We must focus on the specific life style, which will make us enjoyable.</P>
      <P> In conclusion, I believe that shopping only waste time for human life. And you couldn't get back any more.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
