<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR918*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>Last week, I had a week's holiday in London, where I haven't been for 2 years. I prepared everything for my family and wanted to enjoy it, we were happy all the time, but, unfortunately, the last day was the worst thing we have got, which was your musical show. At first, you said that, if we had bought 5 tickets, we would have had a discount, but we didn't have anything. Secondly, we booked the show at 19:30, but it started at 20:15, what's wrong with your clock?. Thirdly, someone on stage was very strenge for me, because I expected to see "Danny Brook", but I didn't. The last one, we wanted to have a dinner in your restaurant after a terrible musical show, but we couldn't have it, because a waiter said your chef had gone home. I have no idea what your business is, I have never seen something like this.</P>
      <P>By the way, I want you to pay my money back for the waste time, and I think that you understand.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Have you ever been in the Countryside? Try it, it doesn't need to take a long time to live in that place, but it will give you many things, which are different from your lifestyle in city. Nowadays you wake up in a morning, go to school or work by the sky-train, start your lessons with the computer, go for shopping in a store which has an air-conditioner, watch cartoons on TV, or cook by a microwave oven etc. Do you really enjoy it? Althoug the modern technology gives you many comfortable things for living, can it gives you natural, peace and fresh air? How much the technology gives to you, it take from you more. Have you heard about the environment pollutions, the healthy problems and the moral problems? These all happen. </P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
