<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR919*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Mr Soren:</P>
      <P>Let me express how disappointed I feel at this particular moment, or I should say angry, better sad. I would never expected that I could be so decepted. This is not the firt time I have been in your theatre and I have to tell you I have enjoyed many other plays, but be sure "Over the rainbow" will be the last one. As I am specially fond of musicals, I even travel abroad to see what's new, I am probably one of the most devoted customers. I know this word is not the best but you have demostrated that the theatre can be just as cold as any other business. We both know this is not true, or shoudn't be. When someone comes specially to see Danny Brook acting, one of my favourites singers, whose career I have been following since the begining, and never appear, and nobody give any reason to the audience, how should one feel? There was no reason either for the delay. Almost an hour! Can you imagine how many things one can do instead. Even listening some music to help us take it easy would had been better than nothing! None an announcement, not an invitation...oh, yes, I forgot. The bar was closed. Well, I will not comment that point. That terrible place definitively needed a renewal.</P>
      <P>Well, this is not my idea of a perfect evening out, as you can realise. Each time I see the advertising I get mad.</P>
      <P>Of course, you shoud make a refund of the money, not only to me but to all the public. But I can say that you will never be able to give my appreciation for your theatre back, at least till you continue as its manager.</P>
      <P>Expecting your news,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>It is almost true to say that fashion is one of the most exciting human activities nowadays. How can we define this crazy and continuous change of colours, shapes, patterns, and uses? New fabrics create new textures, all kind of accesories are added to create new versions, to refresh old ideas, to make new proposals that will last, like always, just some weeks. All in fashion pass away in a couple of months and has to be created again.</P>
      <P>Fashion is a part of our lives, even for those who will never reconize it. Have you notice that all the classic gentlemen wear same tipe of suit? And what about this kind of intellectual and progressive people, don't they wear all the same model of ugly but confortable shoes?</P>
      <P>I am sure that fashion will survive for ages, even it will change to become easier to use and clean, because we all need to feel a part of our society, comunicate our way of living and thinking, be part of a group and, at the same time be different.</P>
      <P>The future will bring to us new concepts, adapted to our lives.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
