<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR920*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr/Mss</P>
      <P>I'm writing you in complain about musical show, that I have visited last evening. I had a week holiday in London, so I wanted to spend my last evening with great pleasure, however it was the worse evening in my life.</P>
      <P>First of all, the actors were different from those who were advertised. Second, the show started at 20:15, althoug I read that it started at 19:30! More over after watching a show I wanted to visit your theatre restaurant, but it was closed, it really disappointed me.</P>
      <P>It was my dream to see Danny Brook and Tina Truelove, so it is still my dream because of your show.</P>
      <P>So, I had no perfect evening out and I want my money back. I hope you'll understand my situation and if you want other people to visit your show, you should return my money.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfuly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern techology changed my daily life. Fifty years ago people even didn't think that after 2000 years they would have another life. When Thomas Adison invented an electric light, it was the greatest invention for people of that centure. And nowadays modern technology can change all our life. I mean, almost everyone has now a car, a computer, a mobil phone and even an airplane. My life is changing too. First of all now I can phone my friends and parents from every place, I can chat with other foreign teenagers with the help of the internet. Second modern technology helps me in the kitchen. Coocking became faster with the help of the microwave. What is more Modern technology prevents different illnesses. Further more, yesterday I've heard that every man could fly to the space without any experience, it is great, from my point of view in 2050 year everybody will fly to the space.</P>
      <P>On the other hand people can atrophided of all this inventions. He become lazy because they know that they can seat on the sofa and turn the chances on the TV by pressing a boton.</P>
      <P>In conclusion I want to say that inspite of this, I hope that in future we will have more and more new inventions and they will stop our disasters and problems.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
