<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR765*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>17th - June - 2000</P>
      <P>Auda. Lolas 44</P>
      <P>MADRID 23456</P>
      <P>SPAIN</P>
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about the show "Over the rainbow" taking part the 15th of June</P>
      <P>The last week I have been to London for a holiday. There is saw the advertisement for this show and I decided to go there.</P>
      <P>I went to buy the tickets but when I paid there was not any discount avaible. In the advertisement you told me I would have discounts.</P>
      <P>This was not the worst thing because when I arrived at the theatre I was waiting fourty five minutes because the show should start at 19:30 and it started at 20:15. When it started the main actor Danny Brook was not in, another worse actor was taken his part. In my opinion when the main actor can not do the show it is better not do the show than do it with a horrible actor.</P>
      <P>When it finished I arrived at the theatre restaurant but it was closed because they are going to do a new better restaurant.</P>
      <P>In my opinion you should refuse my money because the evening and the show were so terrible.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets.</P>
      <P>But I did not know it, and I told her my secret: I have fell in love with Paul a friend of us. No one know it else her.</P>
      <P>The wendsday Pat phoned me and told me that Sally also love Paul. I had also told Sally my secret. The thursday Sally phoned me, because we are also friends, but she did not tell me anything about Paul.</P>
      <P>The weekend started and this Friday we went to the dyscoteque. I spent there a good time but at the end, when we were going to come back home, I saw Sally kissing Paul!! It was terrible!!</P>
      <P>When Sally came out the dyscotheque I was very nervous and I started to shout her. She hit me and I decided in this moment that I never should speak with her.</P>
      <P>Paul ask Pat what had happened and she told him my secret. One friend of mine told me that Pat had told Paul my secret and I went to speak with her. Now we are friends but I know that I can not tell her any secret.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
