<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR924*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson</P>
      <P>First of all I would like to thank you for the good programme you organised for our trip to London. Especially the sightseeing by bus seems to be very interesting.</P>
      <P>But we would like to suggest you something: There is a trendy event about the latest fashions, leisure and sports wear; make up and hairstyles on the 14th of March. It is called "The London Fashion and Leisure Show." This would be a great opportunity because we are all intrested in clothes, sports and fashion. I have almost forgotten to mention that it is free for students! Unfortunately we realised that on the 14th we will already visit the Science Museum. The show lasts nine hours, from 10.00-19.00, the whole day! Our question now: Could we go to this show? We could maybe change Tuesday's programme to Wednesday. We all prefer the show, free time is not so important for us.</P>
      <P>Please think about this and give us an answer. Thanks.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="5b">
      <P>Dear Jack</P>
      <P>Thanks a lot for your letter. I am fine but quite busy because I have my German exams. Therefore I read Agatha Christie's "Best Detective Stories of Agatha Christie". I can really recommend you this book, it is fabulous. It is also a suitable present for your cousin, I think. One story is about ten persons who stay together in a hotel on a lonely island. There is a storm and they can not leave. Suddenly a murderer happens! Believe me, you would never guess who the killer is! There is also Hercule Poirot, the famous detective and he finally solves the mistery. But I will not tell you more. You have to read it yourself. And if your cousin likes crime stories it is a perfect book!</P>
      <P>Unfortunately it is quite expensive, £32. But do not worry about the price because your cousin will love it!</P>
      <P>Okay, I hope to have news from you very soon. Have a good time.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
