<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR925*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Robertson,</P>
      <P>Thank you for your effort, which you have made to organize this three days programm in London and I am sure that we will have a great time there especially in the National Art Gallery.</P>
      <P>Nevertheless, the students in my class have some suggestions for you how to make it even more interesting. The thing is that we have seen an advertisment for the London Fashion and Leisure Show. It will be held in Central Exhibition Hall in London on Tuesday, 14th of March, from 10.00 to 19.00. Naturally, all the students are interested in it because the latest fashions, leisure and sports wear, make up and hairstyles will be shown there. Futhermore, students can enter free!</P>
      <P>We are concerned that this is a great and the only opportunity for us to see this show, as it takes place only once a year and only in London. Certainly, we do not refuse to take part in other activities in London. Probably, you will agree just to put London Fashion and Leisure Show instead of Science Museum and shopping on Tuesday.</P>
      <P>Thank you for your attenlion and understanding.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>The Home of the Future</P>
      <P>Dear Reader,</P>
      <P>I have decided to describe my home of the future or, in other words, the place where people will live in 100 years.</P>
      <P>Well, I suppose that almost everything in future house will be automatic and will obey to what people say. Perhaps, there will be personal computers, which will control every thing, every item of furiture, light, temperature. Moreover, they will be able to create a special climate for each room. But, on the other hand, people will still have to programm them, as they have to do nowadays. Maybe children will not have to go to school, they just will stay in their rooms and study from computer, some kind of on-line education. All the rubbish, dust, dirty dishes, plates, caps will be washed and cleaned automaticly. It is possible that only one computer will do this all and it will have its own personality, voice, eyesight..</P>
      <P>This will be your home, another member of your family and your house or flat together.</P>
      <P>This is my opinion of the Home of the Future and I wish I could live in it.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
