<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR926*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>41-50</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>17th JUNE 2000.</P>
      <P>DEAR SIR,</P>
      <P>I AM WRITING TO COMPLAIN ABOUT THE PROBLEMS WHICH OCCURRED IN THE LAST MUSICAL SHOW OF THIS THEATRE.</P>
      <P>FIRST OF ALL, DIFFERENTLY OF ADVERTISED, THE MAIN ACTOR WAS NOT DANNY BROOK, BUT OTHER UNKNOWN PERSON.</P>
      <P>TO MAKE MATTER WORSE, THE SHOW DELAYED STARTING AT 20:15.</P>
      <P>AS IF THIS WERE NOT ENOUGH, I DID NOT OBTAIN A DISCOUNT IN THE PRICE OF THE TICKET, ALTHOUGH THIS WAS POSSIBLE ACCORDING TO YOUR LEAFLET.</P>
      <P>ON TOP OF EVERYTHING, I COULD NOT VISIT THE RESTAURANT OF THIS PLACE, BECAUSE IT WAS CLOSED AFTER THE SHOW.</P>
      <P>I AM VERY DISAPPOINTED, BECAUSE THAT EVENING OUT WAS NOT PERFECT AS I HAD PLANNED.</P>
      <P>SO, I WOULD BE GRATEFUL IF YOU COULD REFUND OF ALL OR PART OF MY MONEY WHICH I PAID FOR THE SHOW.</P>
      <P>I LOOK FORWARD TO RECEIVING YOUR PROMPT REPLY.</P>
      <P>YOURS FAITHFULLY,</P>
      <P>MARCOS ALMO BRAS DE BARODO.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>IT'S UNDENYABLE THAT DURING THIS CENTURY OUR WORLD HAS BEEN CHANGING. NEWS INVENTS HAVE BEEN INVENTED AND THE SCIENCE HAS BEEN IN QUICK PROGRESS. AS A RESULT OF THIS PEOPLE'S DAILY LIFE HAS BEEN CHANGING AS WELL.</P>
      <P>AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED, I FIRMLY BELIEVE THAT, IT'S WORTH TO POINTING OUT THE FOLLOWING:</P>
      <P>FIRST AND FOREMOST, IT'S IMPORTANT TO REMEMBER THAT TODAY IT IS EASIER TO TRAVEL AROUND THE WORLD BECAUSE NOWADAYS THERE ARE LOTS OF GOOD AND FAST WAYS OF TRANSPORT.</P>
      <P>IN THE SAME WAY, WE CAN TRAVEL INSIDE OUR COUNTRY QUICKLY AND SAFELY. CONSEQUENTLY, WE'VE GOT FACILITIES TO KNOW MANY DIFFERENT PLACES AND TO CONTACT DIFFERENT PEOPLE, TOO.</P>
      <P>SECONDLY, WE CAN'T FORGET EITHER THAT ALL OF US HAVE CONDITIONS TO COMMUNICATE WITH PEOPLE BY MOBILE PHONES, BY INTERNET, WHO LIVE NOT ONLY IN THIS COUNTRY, BUT ALSO ABROAD.</P>
      <P>FINALLY, WE CAN CONSIDER, TOO, THAT THE TECHNOLOGY HAS BEEN PROVIDING US WITH IMPORTANT DISCOVERIES, MAINLY IN MATTERS ABOUT HEALTH, ENVIRONMENT AND SO ON.</P>
      <P>IN CONCLUSION, I REALLY BELIEVE THAT OUR DAILY LIFE IS VERY DIFFERENT THAN IT WAS IN THE LAST CENTURY AND EVEN IN THE BEGGINING OF THIS CENTURY. THE SCIENCE AND THE TECHNOLOGY ARE THE MAIN RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
