<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR927*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Manager,</P>
      <P>During my visit to London, I had the opportunity to visit the Circle Theatre and to see 'Over the Rainbow'. To my dismay the musical was nothing compared to what I had expected, as it completely contradicted to the advertisement.</P>
      <P>Firstly, despite the advertisement stating that Danny Brook was starring, another actor was starring in the actual show and his performance was literally horrible, and disappointing.</P>
      <P>Secondly the starting time of the show was far from punctual. I had gone to the show which according to the advertisement was supposed to begin at 19:30, but the show did not start until 20:15.</P>
      <P>In the advertisement, it said that discounts were available. Despite this the ticket vendors explicitly told me that there were no discounts to be offered.</P>
      <P>According to the advertisement, the audience were free to go to the theatre restaurant after the show. However by the time the show had ended the restaurant was closed.</P>
      <P>I was further humiliated by the irony of the advertisement stating that it would be my 'perfect evening out', when it was totally the opposite.</P>
      <P>I hope you understand my disappointment. In addition, as a way of compensation, I would like to have a refund, and justification for such a show.</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology change your daily life?</P>
      <P>During these past few decades, or rather, the 20th century, there has been a significant developement in modern technology.</P>
      <P>One of the essential developement is the form of transportation. The invention of cars planes, trains and other similar forms of transportation have enabled us to go from one place to another with no time. This enables us to save great deal of time and effort. Quite recently, in my country electrical bicycles have been invented. This compared to the traditional bicycle is less physically painstaking and less time consuming and therefore lets me travel to my destination in small amount of time with hardly no effort at all. This has made my life easier. On the other hand, I feel as though I am becoming lazier and exercising less.</P>
      <P>Another significant technological developement is the creation of electrical appliances. There are many indispensable electrical appliances such as television, radio, fax machines, and microwaves. What changed my life most is portal computers. They are particularly useful for someone like me who travels often. Before I used computers generally, It took so much time for me to looking up words in a dictionary and looking up for information. With a computer however, all this is done in the matter of seconds. This again enables people to save time.</P>
      <P>The modern technology helps people in many ways and is indespensible. However if we rely on it too much, we could become lazy and apathetic and as a result, would not be able to live without them once they are gone.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
