<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR930*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>I am replying in response of the competition I won. As you asked in the letter, I will write everything I need to know about the travel.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to travel on July, because during the other months, I will be studying, preparing myself for other exams or I will be out travelling somewhere else with my relatives.</P>
      <P>I have been thinking and I decided I would prefer to stay in tents, simply because it's a new experience and I would like to try everything new. Also, it seems more dangerous. For the two activities I have to choose, I decided to choose a new activitie that I have never done before, which is Sailing, so I am a totally begginer at this. The other activitie is Photography, I am not an expert, but I know how to use a camera, all I want is to improve my knowledge.</P>
      <P>Finally, I need to know what kind of clothes and how many I should pack. Is there any place that I can wash my clothes? I also needed some information on the money I will take. Do you have any kind of souvenirs that I can buy? Do I need to take any money at all?</P>
      <P>I will be waiting a reply.</P>
      <P>Your sincerely,</P>
      <P>Sara Todi</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I'm sorry it took so long for me to answer your letter, but I've been too busy with my school, papers and everything. But now I found some time to tell you everything about the pop concert I helped.</P>
      <P>There were about a hundred people that wanted to help, but only two would be chosen. When they said my name, I couldn't believe it! All I could think was "Oh my god, I'm gonna be talking and helping the most famous pop bands!" I was so excited that I couldn't believe.</P>
      <P>When I arrived to help them, they welcomed me and were so nice with me that it seemed we had known each others in ages! They weren't those kind of people that think they're gods.</P>
      <P>I helped them organizing the stage, cleaning everything, fixing what was broken and they even let me play with their guittars! That was so great!</P>
      <P>I don't know exactly how I felt, sometimes I wake up and think it was nothing but a dream. I hope you liked everything I said and I hope an answer as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>Best wishes,</P>
      <P>Sara</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
