<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR931*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>JUN 17th, 2000</P>
      <P>Dear MR SMITH,</P>
      <P>My name is Volencia Vardez. I am writing to complain about the services that you are offering during the shows at your theatre.</P>
      <P>Last May, I had a week holiday in London, and during my trip I decided to buy tickets for OVER THE RAINBOW, the MUSICAL SHOW. I was really excited with the idea of seeing that show.</P>
      <P>First of all, when I arrived, I met a note stuck on the front door that informed about changes at actor's staff. Danny Brook was ill. He was replaced by another actor whose abilities were bad.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I want to tell you that the show started forty five minutes later.</P>
      <P>In order to the tickets, I want to say that they are very expensive. I had put some money aside for a month, thinking about the discount, but when I want to buy them they said that discounts were not avaible.</P>
      <P>To sum up, the restaurant was closed.</P>
      <P>I will appreciate if you could send me my money back. Looking for your repley.</P>
      <P>Yours Faithfully.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat was not very good at keeping secrets. That is why she could no be a spy.</P>
      <P>When she was a girl, Pat used to play spies and detectives games. Her mother gave a book about how to become a spy for her birthday. She had watched all Mission Impossible and gadget, the inspector series.</P>
      <P>When she finished the school, she went to study to the Agent Trainning Agency where she learnt about guns, clues, agencies, etc. She was the best student they have ever had.</P>
      <P>But things changed during her first mission. She was sended to New York to discover how some people from government gave money to the merchants because they want to build a Trade Center there.</P>
      <P>At first she walked around the bayside market looking for all the people who were there. When she saw a man, different for the rest, talking with one of the sellers. Immediately she interrupted and told to the man that she was a secret agent. Obviously the man realised that she was looking for him and said that she was really crazy!</P>
      <P>You can imagine what had happened with her cover as a spy.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
