<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR932*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am very pleased about the prize I just won in your competition. Thank you for choosing me. Here is some further information about myself and a few enquirement.</P>
      <P>First of all, I am sorry to say that I could only travel in July. As my family's new restaurant is about to open in August, I need to help with the restaurant, which is expected to be rather busy.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I would like to live in log cabins while I am staying at the camp. I had bad experience last time I lived in a tent. I was terribly attacked by a been and it still gives me nightmares!</P>
      <P>As for selecting two activities, basketball and surfing are definitely on my list. I spend one third of my spare time playing basketball. As a result, I have an important position in our local basketball team. Surfing was a fresh sport to me which I took up recently. It is really fasinating to challenge waves. I wish I could learn more so that I could enjoy it more in the future.</P>
      <P>In addition what kind of clothes shall I bring with me? How much money is appropriate to carry?</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I really wish you were there with me at that one of the exciting nights in my life. Now I can't wait to tell you every detail. Are you ready?</P>
      <P>That was a pop concert of Steps in M.E.N Arena. And I was initially employed to be an entrance assistant whose job was to keep the queue under control as well as keeping the area clean.</P>
      <P>A few minutes after the concert began, a backstage assistant called in sick who was responsible for checking wether everything is going well according to the timetable, if something comes up, she should inform other staff. I was then taken in to cover her job. I couldn't find my feet at first as I was so nervous. I was given lots of paper with many different time on it. I did manage to "study" them though, thanks to other staff. They were very helpful and nice. They patiently explained to me my job even so they were fairly busy themselves. Then I found it was not as complicated as I though before. And I guess I did a good job as everything was getting on quite well.</P>
      <P>I saw all the members of the band backstage, how did they change their make-up, hairstyle etc. They were even talking jokes with me and other staff. I was impressed when they kept saying "thank-you" to the staff. Indeed, they can not succeed without their help, can they? I was lucky to have this chance and able to know how they work behind the scene. All in all, it was a once-a-lifetime experience.</P>
      <P>Yours,</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
