<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR933*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>31-40</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I'm writing to complain about the musical show named OVER THE RAINBOW. Regarding your advertisement, it is the LONDON'S NEWEST AND BEST MUSICAL SHOW, but I was deeply disappointed at it.</P>
      <P>According to your advertisement, the starrings were DANNY BROOK AND TINA TRUELOVE. I decided to go to see this show because of its starrings, but at the day I saw it, a different actor played. He was not DANNY BROOK.</P>
      <P>Moreover there was no discount ticket. They were all sold out. You should have said they were very few. I had to buy a £20 ticket.</P>
      <P>To make matters worse, the time that the show started was delayed. It started at 20:15, fourty five minutes later! That's why I couldn't have a dinner at the theatre restaurant after the show. It had already closed, when the show finished.</P>
      <P>I'd like to ask for a full refund for this awful night. Could you give me a satisfactory reply as soon as possible.</P>
      <P>yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Modern technology has changed my life.</P>
      <P>Especially, a computer has made my daily life change dramatically.</P>
      <P> It is only two or three years since I have used a computer at home, but now I wonder how I can live without it. I open my e-mail box every night. When I find a new message, I'm very happy.</P>
      <P>Before using e-mail, I used to write letters and sometime telephon. However I've found e-mail is better than them. Because as soon as I send my message, they can receive it. In the other word, I can also receive their reply soon. It's really useful, when I need quick reply.</P>
      <P>Overmore when I send e-mail, I need not worry about the time. I can send them anytime I like.</P>
      <P>Thanks to modern technology, I enjoy chatting with my friend in other countries and my family in Japan almost every day.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
