<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR935*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Mr Manager,</P>
      <P>I'm sorry of writing you for such a bad thing, but my evening at your theatre wasn't as perfect as you announced: it wasn't perfect at all! I was pleased to see Danny Brooke, he's my favourite actor, so you can easily imagine how disappointed I was when I saw a different and unknown actor on the scene! By the way, what really upset me was the time of starting. According to your advertisement it was at 19:30, and, what a surprise when I had to wait almost an hour until the show started at 20:15! Now let's talk about the tickets. You had promised discounts on the cost which was from £10 to £20, but despite my thoughts I had to pay £20 without chance. In the end, I thought I could enjoy myself visit the theatre restaurant but it was closed because of something they didn't explain to me.</P>
      <P>As you can see it's not a perfect evening, isn't it?</P>
      <P>I'm asking you my money back, you can do it, can't you?</P>
      <P>Wondering your comprension</P>
      <P>your sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="5b">
      <P>THE OLD MAN AND THE SEA - Ernest Hemingway</P>
      <P>As I see it, the Old Man and the Sea is a really exiting book. It describes a challenge, the challenge of life. The major characther is the old man who has to fight against the sea to keep alive. It could be his last adventure. This old man with his old boat goes too far away from the coast to try to fish something good. By surprise he comes across the biggest fish he has ever seen, a beautiful marlin. The man keeps immediatly in contact with it. They are going to be one thing linked together. They're fighting for the same reason with the same strenght, the man has to kill a brother, as he calls the fish. I think they're really brothers, they feel the same pain and fear during the battle.</P>
      <P>If the marlin could speak it would have told the old man's same thing. When the old man won the fight he felt sorry but pleased. He respected and still loves it. But, afterwards, the life's rule is MORS TUA VITA MEA and that's the most difficulty to face to.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
