<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR937*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Ideas to improve the Festival</P>
      <P>Dear Jane Clark,</P>
      <P>I went to the International Arts Festival and saw some interesting things, but many points could be better. That is why I write to you, to give you some suggestions that you can take into consideration or not.</P>
      <P>Firstly, it is a good idea that the Festival is International. But in the advertisement it was written that the artists were from all the world and I saw only six nationalities.</P>
      <P>Secondly, the classical concerts were excellent and the halls were so crowded that nobody could walk. In my opinion, it would be important to rent bigger halls next year.</P>
      <P>Thirdly, I noticed that the plays and the films were a good entertainment. It attracted a lot of people and they were really joyous after that.</P>
      <P>Finally, the reasonably price of the tickets for the weekend was a good point, because all kind of people an afford to buy it. I also think that you should put a Snack-Bar or a little restaurant so as the people are not too hangry and morever you can realise big benefits</P>
      <P>In conclusion, in the whole the Festival was a success, but these suggestions can maybe help you to improve.</P>
      <P>I hope you will not take this letter as a complaint and I look forward to going to the next festival.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Home and school rules</P>
      <P>Dear Andrew,</P>
      <P>I receive your letter and thank you for it. I am very happy to hearing from you and I hope that you are fit. As expected, I want to talk at first about my school and then about my home.</P>
      <P>As you know, I finished school two years ago. This year, I started a private school in Dijon. So the rules are clear, you need to participate to the lessons and also be successful at the exam of June 2000. In our class, we don't have problem with students who dislike to work, because we are all there for the same reasons and nobody wants to say there years and years. It is also expensive and I can't afford to stay there too long.</P>
      <P>In my sweet home, my parents let me do what I want, because I am an adult now. But when we are in society, we have to be careful not to disturb the other persons. It is the same in our family and for example my parents dislike hearing music in the whole house or that I let dust everywhere. When I go out, they don't give me an hour to be at home, because I don't exagerate.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, I don't want to change something in my house or at school, because I totaly agree with the few rules that I have.</P>
      <P>I hope these few information can help you and I look forward to hearing from you</P>
      <P>Best wishes</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
