<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR938*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>17th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing with reference to Over the Rainbow musical show which I went to see at the Circle Theatre last night. Being a theatre lover, I am always looking forward to seeing new musicals, but unfortunately, this particular one was very disappointing.</P>
      <P>First of all, Danny Brook was not starring, even it was stated in your advertisement, but the main role was played by an unknown actor. Secondly, I had to wait for forty five minutes for the show to start, and it was 20:15 (not 19:30) when the curtain went up.</P>
      <P>Another disappointing thing was that I could not get any student discount, even that your advertisement promised them. To make things even worse, the theatre restaurant was closed after the show, because of the roof repairs.</P>
      <P>As you can see I had a very disappointing evening - the worst one during my week's holiday in London. I would like therefore to have my money back, so please send me a cheque for £20 to pay the address above.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>Katja Menan.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Fashion of the Future.</P>
      <P>Almost everyone is trying to be fashionable and look modern. Every season we can see arrival of new styles, fabrics and proportions. Let's try to imagine, what will clothes be like 100 years from now?</P>
      <P>I think in the future people will express themselves by wearing appropriate clothes. There will be mixture of styles from different times of the past, so if you feel like a medieval princess, you can dress like one. A new technology and science will change fabrics, so they will change their colour during the day.</P>
      <P>In the future people will be even more concerned with pollutions and harmful UV-rays. So their clothes will have built-in protective filters to help them keep healthy.</P>
      <P>With so many choices shopping for clothes is going to be even greater fun than it is now. Fashion of the future will not be the same as today's, but it will be more exciting and fun!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
