<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR939*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I am glad that I have won first prize in your competition. I have been very surprised winning. You ask me in your letter when I would like to travel. The answer is the following one: I only can travel July because I have to work all August. I can take holidays only the month of July. You ask me if I prefer to sleep in tents or log cabins. I prefer the tents because I never use such kind of accommodation. I have choosen the two following activities. First one is Tennis and second one is sailing. I played tennis for many years. I have even done competitions. I like a lot this game. I have choosen sailing because I would like to try a new sport. I love water but I never try this sport before.</P>
      <P>I would like to ask you two questions. How much money do I have to take with me for these two weeks and what kind of clothes do I have to bring with me? I'll be very happy to see you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerly.</P>
      <P>Yves DUTEIL</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable because of different problems.</P>
      <P>The first thing is the place of shopping. Sometimes you have to go far away from home to do your shopping and it takes a lot of time. The second thing is that you need to go shopping when the supermarkets are open. Many people work late and they do not have enough time to go for shopping. The third thing is the trouble of full shops. Everybody do their shopping at the same moment and often in the same place. It is almost a battle to buy different things and to go paying those things. People are often nervous and agressive. Sometimes you can see fights between two men or women.</P>
      <P>There is one more thing. When you are a man and your wife asks you to come for shopping, be patient! Because women loves shopping and you have to follow them everywhere and always giving your opinion about clothes, music, parfums...</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
