<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR940*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan:</P>
      <P>I am writing to give you the information it was ask in the letter you had sent me.</P>
      <P>Firstly, the best date for me to travel will be the second week of July because I will be very busy in any other date for reasons of work.</P>
      <P>Secondly I would prefer sleeping in log cabins because I fell much more comfortable. One reason is the cold, and the other is that I cannot sleep on the floor because I have problems in my back.</P>
      <P>Finally, the two activities I would like to do while I am camping are Singing and Basketball. The first one because I think I am good at it and also I love singing loudly with other people. The last one I have never tried it but I think I can do it well because I am very tall and that could make things easier.</P>
      <P>I would like to know if I must take some money and what kind of clothes I will need.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>your sincerily</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim:</P>
      <P>I'm very sorry I haven't written you for such a long time but I had to make a travel to my parents house because my mother was operated on; don't worry she is all right now.</P>
      <P>Last month I went to help at a pop concert where Rolling Stones were playing. It was a wonderful experience but at the same time I had to work very hard. The things I did were: Prepearing and controling the equipment, I had to clean all the stadium, make sure that all the lights were in perfect condition, that the singers were confortable and relaxed, etc.</P>
      <P>The most exciting thing was talking with the band, asking questions to them and of course listening the music and enjoying the incredible show.</P>
      <P>It was the most exciting experience I've ever had in my life.</P>
      <P>Best wishes.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
