<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR943*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam, I recently went to The Circle Theatre in order to see Over the Rainbow, and it has been quite deceiving. I am writing to you to complaint about five or six utterly outrageous facts. In the advertisement for the show, which I have picked up in the hall of the theatre, are there about five points which were not respected. To begin with, as far as the starring is concerned, Danny Brook should have performed the main character, and I saw at the very beginning of the show that he did not. Insofar as I came here especially to see him play, I have been very deceived, and this could be the understatement of the year, inasmuch as he is my favorite actor. Apart from it, the show should have begun at 19.30 and it started at 20:15! Could you explain me the reasons of such a huge late? Thirdly, the ad mentionned possible discounts. Personnaly speaking, I didn't saw it and even didn't heard of it: I have asked about it, but nobody seemed to know anything concerning discounts. On top of that, the restaurant was closed for renovations! How can you dare putting an advertisement for a theatre restaurant if you obviously know that is closed? To put it in a nutshell, and quite honestly, I would like to emphasize on the fact that I did not spent a "perfect evening out" at all, as it is mentionned in the ad. For all these reasons, I would like, dear Sir or Madam, that you give me my money back. I am looking forward to hear from you. Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. If only Paul had knew it before...</P>
      <P>Everything had begun when Paul went downstairs of the Heavy Sleep. As he closed his eyes, he started to travel across the dark paths of his councience. He went through valleys, plains and mountains of the Dream Landscape. He finally arrived in Faerie, a country of elder elves and strong white-bearded dwarves</P>
      <P>While he was wandering in the depths of the forest he felt a little tired and sat on a grey huge stone, on top of which he could stare the whole woods.</P>
      <P>All of a sudden, a weird creature popped into his dream. She was taller than a dwarf and as thin as a dying tree. Paul was wandering wether this beast could be offensive when the creature said these words "I am glad to meet you, Paul." The boy could not beleive to what he was hearing. How did the beast knew his name? "You see, I am a mere product of your mind, but I would like to go out of the Heavy Sleep. Please, bring me with you, in your reality!"</P>
      <P>At these words, Paul suddently awoke. Relieved, he thought that bringing the creature in his world would have revealed the existence of Faerie, and with it, threatened the ecology of the Dream Landscape, when he heard a creepy sound under his bed. He jumped out of his room, locked the door and found his brother, Pat. He told him about his adventures and asked him not to repeat it.</P>
      <P>Unfortunately...one our after, a local zoo arrived and caught the creature in order to put her in a cage. There she died because of not having Faerian food necessary to her survival.</P>
      <P>This is how human destroys what is good and burns the Woods of Dream. This is how mankind can't be relied on. This is how secrets are betrayed, and the result of it.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
