<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR944*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about the show, "Over the Rainbow" which I saw in your theatre last week. I was really disappointed because the show was far from what I expected.</P>
      <P>First of all, I was really expecting to see Danny Brook, my favourite actor. However, he was not on the stage that day. Secondally the show started late and I had to wait for 45 minutes without doing anything. It was a waste of time. I also thought that there should have been discounts for students, which in fact was not available and I had to pay for normal price. Furthur more, the restaurant in the theatre was closed after the show because of the delay. I had to go home without eating a dinner, though I was really hungry.</P>
      <P>I have to say that the evening was terrible. If I had known all of them, I would have changed my plan and could have a better time.</P>
      <P>I strongly suggest you should give us right information. I also would like to claim some refund for the evening.</P>
      <P>I hope this matter will receive your prompt attention.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Fashion in 100 years</P>
      <P>If you compare the fashion now with that of 100 years ago, you'll notice that there are incredably big difference between them. People have become more informal, casual and practical than before. But how about the fashion of the future, for example, 100 years from now?</P>
      <P>I think it'll also be very different from now. But in which way?</P>
      <P>First of all, people might think more about the function of clothes than the design. For example, they'll wear a cloth which protect themselves from air pollution, sunshine etc.</P>
      <P>Imagine that all the people have masks on their mouthes and noses like we have sun-glasses, and that all the masks are designers brands, which are made of special material to prevent us from breathing in polluted air. It's like a joke, but a bit scarely.</P>
      <P>Imagine that all the people have hats with big edges to protect their faces from sun-burn, and it's the most trendy fashion of the year!</P>
      <P>It's funny. But we never know!!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
