<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR945*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Madam or Sir,</P>
      <P>During my recent holiday in London I visited one of your shows in the "Circle Theatre". The show was called "Over the rainbow" and should be, in refer to the advertisment, London's newest and best musical show. But I was very disappointed. I was very pleased that the main actors listed on the advertisment were Danny Brook and Tina Truelove. When I saw that you had changed Danny Brook to someone else I was very disappointed.</P>
      <P>Moreover I would like to tell you that the show should begun at 19:30 but it started with a delay of 45 minutes. I do not think that this delay is acceptable. Furthermore you have mentioned some discounts in your advertisment, but I had to pay the full price although I am a student.</P>
      <P>Even your theatre restaurant was closed for repairs. The perfect evening you promised in your advertisment was the complete opposite and that is what I want to get some money back from you.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to an early answer.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Herman Ruter</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. Pat and I have been friends for a long time. We have had a lot of fun together because we had the same interests. When we were 15 years old we decided to drive with my mother's car on a day when my parents were absent. I told Pat to keep in mind that my parents would be very angry if they got to know that. Pat promised me to tell nobody about our purpose. Two days later my father asked me whether I had thought at any time to drive a car without a drivers license because he had heard that from some parents of my friends at school. He told me two hours what could happen if I would do that. I was very surprised because Pat and I were along when we decided to do that.</P>
      <P>The next day Pat told me that he wanted to be admired by some girls and so he had to tell them our secret.</P>
      <P>I felt very disappointed in this moment but I have learned something new about humans; is you can only trust yourself. Pat and I have still been good friends but we have never had an other secret together.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
