<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR946*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Sir,</P>
      <P>I have seen your musical show "Over the Rainbow" in London. I have been very disappointed when I had read your advertisement, I was keen on your show, but I have not seen the same show, I have seen one which it looked like, but not be.</P>
      <P>First of all I have been attracted by the actors - Danny Brooks and Tina Truelove - and not by the actors who played effectly that evening. This actors appeared with fourty-five minutes later refering which is written on your advertisement. This late forbid me to dinner in your restaurant because it was just closing!</P>
      <P>For all this reasons I do wish that I would not have been gone see that show, for which the tickets were not available. And as a conclusion I want you to give me my money back, (I have still the advertisement if you want the prooth what I say). You have the choice, either you make what I want, or I attack you in justice.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerly</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="5b">
      <P>"The old man and the sea" E.H.</P>
      <P>When I have read this book, I have been fascinated by the will of the old fisher. This will is so amazing, he has all the elements against him. His boat is so small and poor, he is old, it is hot and he is alone without any chance to meet someone who could help him.</P>
      <P>But I don't think he would want to.</P>
      <P>He doen't want because he wants to prove the little and himself that he is not really old, even if he has a big age.</P>
      <P>I think this are the reasons of his will. Although the fish is eaten by the sharks, he is the winner, the winner of himself. He could have triumph othe fish because of his knowledge of the sea but principally because he has known research in the deeper of his mind.</P>
      <P>To conclude I think the difficults situations allow us to discover ourself getting out of ourself.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
