<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR947*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan,</P>
      <P>I have just received your letter with congratulations and I am writing to you in order to provide you with information you need.</P>
      <P>First of all, I would like to start with the time of the travelling. I would prefer to go to the Camp on July. The reasons for my choice are that I am having my graduation exams in June and my entrance exams in August.</P>
      <P>As regards accomodation, I would rather choose staying in tents. That is because I am keen on hich-hicking and I amused to living in tents. It is quite romantic, I think.</P>
      <P>As to the activities offered I would love to go in for swimming and photography while camping, although I am not quite good at the last one. Actually, I would like to take up photography as a hobby and if you can provide me with an opportunity to study in this area, I will accept it with pleasure. As regards swimming, it is my passion from the very childhood and I have been going in for this kind of sport for five years now.</P>
      <P>In the conclusion I would like to ask you if you could send me some additional information. I wonder what kind of clothes I should take with me. I don't know much about the weather down there, in California, so I am rather puzzeled about what to wear there. Besides, I would like to know how much money will I need and which expensies will I have to pay for by myself.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>XAVA SURGANOVA</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Subject: to suggest what should be filmed for a short video about daily life of our school.</P>
      <P>Introduction.</P>
      <P>The aim of this report is to find out what are the most important things people should see watching the short videofilm about the daily routine of our school.</P>
      <P>The Area Around the School:</P>
      <P>I have made a little survey on the subject of my report and I have elucidaded that most of the pupils of our school consider that the region and the area around school should be filmed first. Personally I agree with their statement and think that it will be interesting for viewers to learn about the surroundings of the school. We should film our gardens around school and a pitch with the playgrounds for volley-ball and tennis at the back of the school in the very beginning.</P>
      <P>Classrooms, Lessons and Breaks.</P>
      <P>Next things to be shot, by the majority of students was said to be the teaching process and the breaks. Obviously it will be interesting to find out what methods are used by our teachers to help pupils understand their subject better. Here I should also mention the decoration of our classrooms and atmosphere in them. People should see all the renovations that have been made during the last years and all modern conveniences that were made for both students and teachers.</P>
      <P>And as regards breaks student consider them being a very important part of school life, despite all their mess and noise.</P>
      <P>Outdoor Activities</P>
      <P>And the last but not least thing we should include in the film are the outdoor activities, which our student are provided with in our school. We can make some short shots about the school theatre and it's performances and also about the sport-clubs and their competitions and awards.</P>
      <P>Conclusion</P>
      <P>In the conclusion of my report I would like to say that the suggestions were made according to the survey made among the students of our school. I hope you will consider this information.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
