<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR950*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>Thank you for your letter 2nd of March. I am writing to give you some information about myself. I am very keen on joinning Camp California in the U.S.A.</P>
      <P>I will have graduated from university by the end of June and I will be available for this travel only in July because I will have to start working with my parents in August. I m always been intents when I went with the university camps so I prefer log cabins at Camp California because it would be a new experience for me and I would also learn how to live in there.</P>
      <P>According to your activities at the Camp, I would choose singing and painting because I am a lead singer in the university band and I think I will be good at this activity. Also painting is my hobby because I have always been painting when I have a spare time. I would be grateful if you could tell me some details about what type of clothes and How much money I should bring.</P>
      <P>Once again, thank you for giving me a good opportunity. I look forward to going with your camp in the near future.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>(THONGCHAI ENPHENO)</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Most people enjoy going shopping every weekend but some think that shopping is not always enjoyable because of different reasons and places.</P>
      <P>In the first place, some housewifes don't like to go to the supermarket because it is not fun to go shopping with a long list and decide which one is the first and the second. To make matters worse, you forget to buy something when you get back home. It is very frustrating. Moreover, if you go with your children, you will have to control them and remember things on your list at the same time and sometimes they cry when they want something in the supermarket. It is a tough chore!</P>
      <P>Another point of view against shopping is a lack of the items that you really want. Sometimes when you meet a nice dress and you think you are going to buy it tomorrow but when you come back it is sold out or there is no your size left. I cannot imagine anything worse.</P>
      <P>The other disadvantage is that you enjoy going shopping too much and pay everything buy credit card. When a bill comes to £1000, you would be shocked and regret what you had done.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, I believe that shopping is not always enjoyable if you accidently meet a bad situation or you can not control your expenditure carefully.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
