<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR952*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>51+</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>13.6.00</P>
      <P>Dear Hellen,</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your letter that I received yesterday. I am very happy that I won the first prize in your competition - two weeks at camp California in USA. Also I am pleased, that I don't have to pay any expenses.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel end of July. In June I have other arrangements, such as my school exams and my birthday. It is convenient for me the last two weeks of July. After my school exams I will have time to prepare myself for the trip.</P>
      <P>During my time in California, I would love to have the chance of some leisure activities such as swimming. It is my favourite sport. I am good and fast at swimming. Another sport I love is basket ball. Hopefull I will meet some other girls in the same sport. So we all play as a team.</P>
      <P>My final question is this. Can you let me know if there is any facilities for washing my clothes If not I will bring with me enough to last for two weeks. Please give me a rough idea how much spending money I will need.</P>
      <P>Please write soon</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shoping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>As a housewife I have a good idea about it. Once a week I go shopping. Sometimes I go two days We all have to do our shopping. It is unavoidable Sometimes it is pleasant, and sometimes it's not.</P>
      <P>I often shop with no problems, but on Saturday is not the same. Shops are so crowded and it takes long time to find what we want and what we need. Also we got to face a long queue in order to pay. Spending long hours shopping it is tiring for some people. I find it very tiring sometimes.</P>
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable because we spend money. Usually much more money we spend than we expect. We can't do anything about is. We have to face it - it has both sides. Sometimes shopping is very enjoyable but not everyday.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
