<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR954*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms. Ryan, I am writing to you, in reply for your letter. Firstly, I would like to travel in July, because it is summer season, and it is nice weather to enjoy in California. Secondly, I would prefer my accomodation to be in log cabins, because I am alergic to some insects that might go in the tent. In regard to the activities, I would like tennis, because I have some experience playing, and my spin and volley are very good, and painting, because I have some techniques, that I would like to put on practise. Lastly, I would like to know if I need to bring any special clothes, and where can I change my money to American dollars cheaper. I would ask for your prompt reply, so I can start organizing myself. Thanking you, Yours sincerely, Carmen Dolores Rossell</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I hope you are doing fine, I am writing this letter, to tell you about my experience of helping a pop concert.</P>
      <P>Firstly, you need to know, and be counscious of what you are doing. I spend two weeks preparing all the stage, speakers, background, michrophones, everything with all the staff, and every night, the artists came to rehearsal their show, I could see how they really improved, and how nice they were with the staff. The day of the concert, everyone, including the artists and managers were nervous and were tired, however, when the concert started, we saw that all our efforts were worthy, the crow and artists thanked the staff.</P>
      <P>What I personally liked the most was all our teamwork. I could see the staff, managers, artists and even the director, all like a big team, working together. That was what made it mostly special. Try it, I recommend it.</P>
      <P>Write back soon,</P>
      <P>Love,</P>
      <P>Carmen Dolores Rossell.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
