<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR956*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr. Smith,</P>
      <P>I am writting you about an enjure that I had in your last musical Circle Theatre. I went to see "Over the rainbow" last Saturday and I had a very disappointing evening.</P>
      <P>First of all, I was surpprising that Danny Brook and Tina Truelove did not played. Anybody told us why they wasn't there.</P>
      <P>I read on your advertisment in Friday's edition of the Times that the show should start at 19.30 but the representation started at 20.15. I was waitting 45 minutes for anything!</P>
      <P>I am studiant and I didn't find any discount's ticket. I don't understand the problem between your advertisment and the reality.</P>
      <P>And finally, after the show, I wanted to drink a coffee but the theatre restaurant was closed!</P>
      <P>Like mentioned in the newspaper I didn't have a perfect evening out and I ask you to give me back my money.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Your sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed your daily life?</P>
      <P>My life change everyday with the modern technology. For exemple, if I don't have time to do my shopping after school because I have to do my homework, I am going on Internet and ask for what I need. The day after I get everything at home by post.</P>
      <P>In my point of vue, Internet is the most important discover of the 2000 centery. You can book tickets for theatre, sport, etc., you can find all informations you need for yourself. You have a lot of things to do, to see, to learn. It is too big to tell everybody about what you can do!</P>
      <P>I use all the time Internet for my homework and in the futur, I hope, I will be able to use it for my own work.</P>
      <P>Technology will not stop to grow up and help people in the futur. I hope I will help them, I am sure I will!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
