<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR957*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>41-50</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I'm writing to complain about your musical show "OVER THE RAINBOW", which I recently saw at the Circle Theatre. It was the only disappointment during my holiday in London, since several points didn't worked out as promised in your advertisement.</P>
      <P>First of all, there were no discounts available, and having payed £20 I had to wait 45 minutes longer than expected since the show began at 20:15 and not at 19:30.</P>
      <P>As a second point, the actor was not Danny Brook, as displayed, but someone else I've never had heard of before. His acting and singing was horrible.</P>
      <P>At last, after all these disadvantages, I was not able to have diner in your theatre restaurant. It was closed of some reason I still don't know.</P>
      <P>You see, it was not the "perfect evening out", as you had promised in the advertisement. Therefor, I would like to ask for at least half of my money back.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to hearing from you soon,</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully, Ewe P Meier</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>The pressure of secrets</P>
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. And if he had been able to keep one, the following story wouldn't have happened.</P>
      <P>Pat was a teacher for english as a foreign language. Sometimes he had liked to surprise his class with a test to see how good they would be when they could not have learned for it in advance. And always, every body made it surprisingly well.</P>
      <P>What was the reason? Pat used to show the test to his friend Nick, when he had finished it to get his opinion. Nick now had taken a copy of the test to archive it. And the girlfriend of Nick happened to be in Pat's class. She was quite clever and had known everything about this, so she had taken copies for her classmates and everybody was prepared.</P>
      <P>You see, each little secret is a kind of pressure to Pat, and he only feels free if he can tell someone about it. And this is the same for everybody, isn't it?</P>
      <P>Or can you keep a secret?</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
