<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR958*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr....</P>
      <P>It wasn't the first time for me to visit this show in your theatre, but it was the worsed one.</P>
      <P>At first it was a great plessure for me to get a ticket therefor becauses I'm one of the greatest fan of Danny Brook. It's not that problem that there was no more discount available - but I had choosenalowed.</P>
      <P>When musical started at 20:15 (not at 19:30 as showed) I was realy shokked when I realised that a different actor was playing. I couldn't stay any more and had to leave the theatre.</P>
      <P>You have to know that I am very sik because of my blood presure and so I was laying down the hole weekend. In my opinion it's a simple way for you to pay me the money I left back. Otherwise I have to contact my lower.</P>
      <P>I am waiting hearing of you.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>For me as an scientist it's a main problem to show how the inovations of the last century goes the environment and natur.</P>
      <P>In past new technologies mostly followed by ground-, water- or air pollution.</P>
      <P>A nowadays simple thing like a computer include so many possible ways to destroy different environmental compartiments. On the one hand there are the materials from which the PC's are made of, on the other hand is the uge waste problem situated.</P>
      <P>Now I try to show, in my daily work, how the airborn chlororganics, which are degased from plastics, will be seperated and damaged by green plants.</P>
      <P>Sometimes it seems to me like joke if I remember all the daungerous materials I need to do my job. Nevertheless, in my opinion, the only way to find a better kind of living with the nature is to check out the problems we have. Therefore it make sense to use the inovation which are standing for environmental destructions.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
