<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR959*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen,</P>
      <P>I am writing to answer your letter, which I have recieved yesterday. First of all, I would like to thank you for accepting me and I am very appreciate that all costs are paid for. I could travel only in July because my exam will be finished in the beginning of that month and it would be great if I could set off my journey on 15th July.</P>
      <P>I would prefer to stay in log cabins because the weather is going to be rainy according to the forecast. Therefore, I have chosen golf and tennis from the list. I have been playing them for more than 3 years in which I have been trained, 3 years for tennis, 1 year for golf by the professional coaches. I'm enjoy playing both of them regularly.</P>
      <P>In addition, it would be nice if you could send me an address which I am going to stay, so that I can keep in touch with my friends and family. Finally, thank you again for everything and I am looking forward to accompanying you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>"Shopping is not always enjoyable". I think this statement is true. In my opinion, shopping is not suitable for children whose age is under 18! This is quite a strong opinion, but I know it from my real-life experiences of shopping.</P>
      <P>When I was 15, I was starting to look for new clothes, shoes, and everything I could find now unneccessary.</P>
      <P>I'm not dare to culculate how much I have spent for those things without thinking. However, it was not bad, my mom always told me that I hadn't have earned enough money so that I shouldn't have spent it in the wrong way.</P>
      <P>Therefore, people who is over 18 can think of more reasons than young children for shopping and buying such tempting objects. To sum up, shopping is not a wrong thing to do as long as you can earn money yourself and know what you are spending it for!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
