<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR767*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam.</P>
      <P>A few days ago I went to your theatre to see a musical show. Unfortunately I was very disappointed with it, I was expected opposit.</P>
      <P>First of all the advertisement where you have advertised your program and what the theatre was providing for you is totaly wrong.</P>
      <P>A came to look at my favorit actors Danny Brook and Tina Truelove, but whom I saw were another people. Another thing is that I took a particular amount of money to buy a tickets and when I apeared infrant of casses I found out that the cost of tickets on your advertisement and real price wasn't the same, real price was much higher. Also show started very late compere to what was writen on the advertisement. And I think you know how it is just sit and wait for 45min. befor the beggining?</P>
      <P>So, after all of that, I wanted to have a nice relaxing diner in your restaurant, I was very angry when I apeared infrant of closed doors and there was a notice, that the restaurant wasn't working.</P>
      <P>In fact writing to you just with one main reason. I'll be really delightful to resive back the money for my ticket.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forword hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Faithfuly yours</P>
      <P>Lena Jarova</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Begin at the begining. Look at historical books 400-600 years ago, or even in time of First and Second World War, how are sociaty changed, just because we did step up in the science and technology.</P>
      <P>In one hand scientist discovered a lot of medisent from different illneses, but in an enother hand they discovered many illneses about which we haven't herd before. I think this side of the question is balanced because before effect on our health was less than it is now. More and more people died from some illness wheres long time ago less people died from illneses, dispite that fact that they had less medisent.</P>
      <P>However technology nowerdays impoved so much and it changed our life a lot. Today we can't even think how we could possibly leave without computers or without airplanes. Computer it is our way of with outside world comunicat, wheres with airplanes we can rich our parents, friends easily and much faster, then if we would use bouts or trains. Everyday scientist and technologyst discover and produce more and more new things and it is good, it has to be like that, we have to do forword not behind from the point where we are now.</P>
      <P>Society has to go forword not to stop on one place.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
