<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR961*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I am writing to you in reply to your letter.</P>
      <P>First of all I want to give you the thanks for this prize. I am very excited because I have never won a prize. I have never been in the USA, so I think that this travel will be an unforgetable experience.</P>
      <P>Secondly, I will like to tell you that I can only travel in July because in June I have to take my final exams at school. In August I have to be in Madrid because I am going to work as a trainee in a travel agency. After august I must return to school, so I can only go to California in July.</P>
      <P>I would prefer to stay in a tent because I like very much the nature and camping, so I think that I will be better in a tent than in a log cabin.</P>
      <P>Although all the activities that you mention are very interesting, I prefer swimming and tennis. I think that I am very good in swimming. I won a local competition when I was seventeen. I am not so good in tennis because I began to play only two years ago. Finally, I would like to ask you how the weather will be in July and which kind of clothes I have to wear. Furthermore, I would like to know the money that I have to take and which amount of money is normally spent in the camp. I look foward to receiving your reply.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Silvia Torroja.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>In my opinion the statement 'Shopping is not always enjoyable' is totally true.</P>
      <P>An argument in favour of this statement is that shopping is very tiring. You can be walking for hours and finally you can't find anything that you like.</P>
      <P>Also, you can spend hours trying to decide between a wonderful blue trousers or a beautiful black dress, for example.</P>
      <P>I think that shopping is even more boring when you go with a friend and you have to give her some advice. It can be a very stressful situation because in some moments you don't know what to say.</P>
      <P>In my opinion shopping could be a 'dangerous' activity because you may spend more money in some clothes that you can afford. I know people who are overdrawn because of shopping. Despite shopping is boring I think that it is necessary because it is important for people to have several clothes and also suitable clothes for a very important meeting or appointment.</P>
      <P>So, shopping is not enjoyable, but necessary.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
