<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR964*0100*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P> Mr. Robertson:</P>
      <P>First of all our class would like to give you our special thanks about the programme you gave us yesterday afternoon.</P>
      <P>After reading the hole organized programme, we all agreed about the sightseeing by bus around London wich will give us the knowledge about this fantastic city we all want to meet since time ago.</P>
      <P>The main purpose of our letter it's to explain about the London Fashion and Leisure Show. We found the advertisment in a local newspaper article and have been thinking it could be such a good opportunity, because the show consists on these topics:</P>
      <P>. Latest Fashions</P>
      <P>. Leisure and sports wear</P>
      <P>. Make up. Hairstyles.</P>
      <P>On the other hand, and the most important, it is free for students.</P>
      <P>After being discussing, we want to suggest how we think the programme should be re-arranged. Instead of going to the science museum, we could go to the London Fashion and Leisure Show wich is opened on Tuesday, march 14 from 10 am to 19 pm. After that we could continue our trip as it had been arranged previously.</P>
      <P>Yours sincirely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="5a">
      <P>Best Detective Stories of Agatha Christie - Agatha Christie.</P>
      <P>A good book should interest, amuse or teach the reader something.</P>
      <P>Agatha Christie always was my favourite writer. Not only because she's famous or wrote lots of books, but she knows how to introduce caracthers or how to tell a good story us though decieving the readers.</P>
      <P>One of her most interesting and famous work is a novel called "The Orient Express". It's a detective story, like all the stories written by her. In our words the story is settled on a train wich tooks the orient. On the train, all the passangers seem to be involved in a crime.</P>
      <P>This is such a fasinating story or it's the way Agatha Christie tells it. The mistery is kept until the last page of the book. I read it and I have really enjoyed it. It has been fabulous experience so if anybody would like to read a good detective story, try to read Agatha Christie's detective story and you wouldn't regret it at all.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
