<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR965*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mr Smith,</P>
      <P>I'm terribly sorry but I would notice you about a very disappointing evening. I'm sure you'll read this letter, with the intention of explaining the problems had during the musical show of his theatre. One of the causes of my disappointing was the different actor that played the show.</P>
      <P>I like very much Danny Brook, and his unaspected absence caused on me a big sadness.</P>
      <P>Then, musical show had to start at 19,30..why at 20:15 there was also the light on? You'll be agree with me that 45 minutes to waiting for the starting of the show is a too long time.</P>
      <P>The advertisement for the show indicated discounts available and open restaurant after the show but it wasn't in this way. The restaurant was closed 'cause of illness.. of who? It's strange thing! For those reasons I ask you for some money back, sure of my good reasons.</P>
      <P>Greetings</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets.</P>
      <P>It's for this reason that now I'm in this terrible situation. I can't believe she said that, I was at the Maria's party and 'cause of my distraction, I said Pat that I had lost the Jon's shirt. I was agree to buy another one, of the same style, but now he's angry with me, 'cause I didn't say anything to him.</P>
      <P>I don't know how to do. He's my best friend and so he wanted from me all the truth I can give him. It's all right, but I also think that he's too exagerate. I don't think of having done a so bad thing to broke our friendness. I feel sad and shocked. I like his company, and we are happy when we are togheter. I can't finished 'cause of a girl that can't keeping a simple secret.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
