<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR966*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Italian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>DEAR "CIRCLE THEATRE" MANAGER,</P>
      <P>I AM WRITING IN ORDER TO EXPRIME MY DISAPPOINTMENT AT THE SHOW "OVER THE RAINBOW" PERFORMED 2 WEEKS AGO; FIRST OF ALL, I READ ON THE ADVERTISEMENT THAT DANNY BROOK WAS TO ACT IN THE SHOW, BUT THE ACTOR THAT REALLY PLAYED WAS DIFFERENT, AND THIS WAS VERY DISAPPOINTING. THEN, THE SHOW WAS TO BEGIN AT 19:30, BUT IT BEGAN ONLY AT 20.15!</P>
      <P>AS REGARDS THE TICKETS, I READ THAT DISCOUNTS WERE AVAILABLE, BUT IT WAS NOT SO, AND I HAD TO PAY THE WHOLE PRICE. MOREOVER, AFTER THE SHOW, I HAD INTENTION TO VISIT YOUR THEATRE RESTAURANT, BUT IT WAS CLOSED AND THERE WAS NO EXPLANATION FOR THAT. EVENTUALLY, YOU PROMISED ON YOUR ADVERTISEMENT A PERFECT EVENING OUT; AS IT HAD NOT BEEN SO, I WOULD LIKE TO HAVE MY MONEY BACK.</P>
      <P>I HOPE TO HEAR FROM YOU SOON,</P>
      <P>BEST WISHES</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>FASHION: THIS TERM EVOKES TOP MODELS, STYLISTS, COLOURS AND THE GREAT EUROPEAN CAPITAL CITIES, LIKE ROME, LONDON AND PARIS. BUT IT IS NEARLY IMPOSSIBLE TO DEFINE IT OR TO FIX THE RULES WITHIN WHICH IT DEVELOPES; NOWADAYS THE FASHION WORLD INCLUDES (AND IS CREATED BY) STYLISTS FROM ALL OVER THE WORLD, EACH ONE PRESENTING A DIFFERENT MODEL OF BEAUTY, SOMETIMES ONE OPPOSITE FROM ANOTHER. I THINK THAT FASHION IN THE FUTURE WILL DEVELOPE ACCORDING TO VERY DIFFERENT LINES: THERE MAY BE A RETURN TO THE FASHION OF THE PAST, AS WE CAN NOTICE YET NOW, OR A MORE FANTASCIENTIFIC AND TECHNOLOGICAL DEVELOPEMENT. SURELY, ORDINARY PEOPLE WILL NOT FOLLOW ONLY THE MODELS PRESENTED ON TV, AS REGARDS EVERYDAY LIFE, I THINK THAT IN THE FUTURE ATTENTION WILL BE FOCALIZED ON COMFORTABILITY MORE THAN ON ELEGANCE. BUT IF IT IS DIFFICULT TO FORECAST THE DEVELOPEMENTS OF THE FASHION WORLD, IT IS NEARLY IMPOSSIBLE TO FORECAST THOSE OF THE COMMON PEOPLE, THAT IS A TOO VARIOUS CATHEGORY.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
