<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR967*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Madam,</P>
      <P>I am very happy to have won first prize in your competition and want to thank you for that very interesting competition.</P>
      <P>I am only available in July because I am studying in an engineering school and I'll work until the end of June. But no problem for July!</P>
      <P>You asked me which accommodation I would prefer between tent and log cabin. I am used to spend summer holiday in tent and I like it, but why not try log cabin? But it doesn't matter if there is no log cabin available... Now let's speak about the most interesting activity: sport. I would be very pleased if I could practice tennis and surfing. In fact, I soon practice tennis and I am quiet good at, and it will the occasion to train myself surfing is completely unknown for me and I hope that I will like it. But if I don't try it I will never know if I like it or not!</P>
      <P>Finally, I wanted to know if I need money and how many, and if there is a dry cleaning.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Anis LACOSTE</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>We know all what shopping is. Sometimes it is necessary and sometimes not and overall it is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>When you got to the supermarket because you want a particular thing and have driven a long time only for that, you look for it but there is no more of it. You think that shopping is not enjoyable at all.</P>
      <P>Sometimes it is necessary but you spend four or five hours in the supermarket because there is too much people. You don't like shopping but you must go shopping to eat!</P>
      <P>But sometimes you go shopping for pleasure and you have all your time (the girls know what it is). finally, when it's for pleasure shopping is enjoyable, but most of time it isn't enjoyable!</P>
      <P>To conclude, if you don't want to go to the supermarket to spend four hours there, send your girlfriend and it will be more enjoyable!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
