<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR969*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen,</P>
      <P>I have received your letter this morning and I'm very happy for this first prize.</P>
      <P>It's a great opportunity for me participate in your Camp California because normaly I work a lot and I can't spend money to travel, moreover, I have to maintain my big family because I'm married and I have three children.</P>
      <P>I would like to travel in July because before I have to work with my father because he's ill.</P>
      <P>For de accommodation I prefer a long cabin because it's more comfortable. I recognise that I would like to sleep in a tent but in this moment I have a little problem with my right leg and it's better for me to sleep in a bed.</P>
      <P>I know that I have the chance to do two activities during this time. I have to choose painting and the photography therefore. I would prefer surfing or climbing but I have to think in my helth.</P>
      <P>In your letter you explain me that all accommodation and travel costs are paid for but I need to know if the life in Camp California is expensive or not because I have to bring money. The weather I hope will be good so I suppose I have to bring short clothes.</P>
      <P>I'm very enthousiastic and I attend.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>In our society the money is one of the most important aspect to have power.</P>
      <P>If we thing about, we will realise that we need money all the day. Not only for the basic needs but also for the rest of the activities.</P>
      <P>There are a lot of people who spend a lot of money because they like shopping. Sometimes, they have to buy something that they need but frequently, they buy only to spend money. This is a big problem because a lot of families haven't money, however spend going shopping.</P>
      <P>We have to teach to our children the value of the money, to explain the difficulties to earn money in a job, because we have to work eight, nine or ten hours a day, for example. It's a first step to educate the youngest and to help our society.</P>
      <P>The money is important but we have to know how to spend it: shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
