<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR970*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>AUTHORITIES OF THE CIRCLE THEATRE:</P>
      <P>I'M WRITING YOU BECAUSE I WANT YOU TO KNOW WHAT HAPPENED LAST WEEK, WHEN I WENT TO THE CIRCLE THEATRE AND I SAW "OVER THE RAINBOW". IT WAS REALLY DISAPPOINTING.</P>
      <P>FIRST OF ALL, IN YOUR ADVERTISMENT SAID THAT DISCOUNTS WERE AVAILABLE, BUT I COULDN'T FIND THEM ANYWHERE. SECONDLY...THE PLAY STARTED AT QUARTER PAST EIGHT: FOURTY-FIVE MINUTES LATE. WHEN IT STARTED I COULD SEE THAT DANNY BROOK WASN'T IN THE PLAY, AND NOBODY TOLD US WHY. THE ACTOR WHO WAS ACTING HIS PART IS THE WORST I HAVE EVER SEEN, REALLY TERRIBLE. HE HAD BEEN IN A PLAY BEFORE? I DON'T THINK SO.... FINALLY, WHEN THE PLAY FINISHED, WE WENT TO THE THEATRE RESTAURANT TO HAVE DINNER BUT IT WAS CLOSED. I DON'T KNOW THE REASON...</P>
      <P>AS YOU CAN SEE IT WASN'T A "PERFECT EVENING".</P>
      <P>I WANT YOU TO GIVE ME A COMPLETE REFOUND. MY ADRESS IS IN THE ENVELOPE. I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO HEAR FROM YOU IN A VERY NEAR FUTURE.</P>
      <P>YOURS SINCERELY.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>UNFORTUNATELY, PAT WASN'T VERY GOOD AT KEEPING SECRETS....AND WHEN SHE KNEW THAT MARIA WAS GOING OUT WITH TIM (A CLASSMATE), SHE TOLD IT TO EVERYONE SHE MET. IN FEW DAYS MARIA'S FATHER (WHO IS VERY JEALOUS) HAD HEARD THE RUMOUR. HE ASKED MARIA IF IT WAS TRUE AND SHE COULDN'T LIE. HE GOT VERY ANGRY AND HE DIDN'T ALLOW MARIA GOING OUT FOR A PERIOD OF TWO WEEKS. MARIA TALKED TO HER FATHER AND TRIED TO EXPLAIN HIM THAT TIM IS A GOOD PERSON BUT HER FATHER SAYS THAT SHE IS TOO YOUNG TO HAVE A BOYFRIEND.</P>
      <P>MARIA MET TIM AT NIGHT, WHEN HER FATHER WAS SLEEPING. WHEN MARIA COULD TO OUT SHE TOLD TO HER FRIENDS WHAT PAT HAVE DONE. NOW NOBODY TELLS HER NOTHING. MARIA IS STILL GOING OUT WITH TIM. HER FATHER ACCEPTED WITH THE TIME.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
