<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR971*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>51+</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear...</P>
      <P>Thanks for your letter. I am very happy that I have received the first prize in your competition.</P>
      <P>I am looking forward my holy day begins on first of july to twenty-first july so it is possible to take the travell in this time. I like to sleep in a tent under the free sky since I have done the military-service therfore I would prefer a tent as my accomodation. My favourite activity are swimming and singing. It is important for my health that I swim an hour a week because I am overwight. I like to singing a song when I am alone. Singing is good for my emotion. Also I choose singing and swimming as my activity. I am a beginner in swimming and also in singing.</P>
      <P>Can you say me which cloths I take away for two weeks. Which kind of weather have you in this time.</P>
      <P>Do I need a lot of money etc. for different excursions</P>
      <P>Thanks for your answer.</P>
      <P>Your sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable</P>
      <P>What does meansworld I live and I need different goods for survive. I need material for drinking and eating, that is the basic fact that I must go shopping for food.</P>
      <P>It is not enjoyable to see that the prize for food are going more and more higher. My salary are going lower than lower. When I have enough money the price isn't important, then I can buy a lot of goods whitout take care on my money. Despite I have enough money shopping is not always enjoyable too, because I don't know which goods I will buy in the future. Also I will buy goods which I don't need.</P>
      <P>There are many goods which quality is bad in this way the environment pollution will be more and more increase.</P>
      <P>This is the fact that shopping is not enjoyable.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
