<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR972*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I recently had a holiday in London and had been to your musical show 'Over the Rainbow' but found it very disappointing.</P>
      <P>It is said that the singers are Danny Brook and Tina Truelove in the advertisement. However, there was a different unknown actor in that. The show started later at 20:15 which was very different in '19.30' as shown. There was no discount at all which is in contrast with 'Discounts Availabe'. After the show, I wanted to have something in the theatre restaurant and found it was closed because of no reason.</P>
      <P>The real show on it owns is really very different to what are mentioned in the advertisement. I am unsatisfied and would like to ask for some money back. Please would you also change the advertisement to the level of the actual facts.</P>
      <P>Thank you for your attention.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully, </P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>What will clothes be like 100 years from now? It is a very hard thing to predict.</P>
      <P>The fashion of nowaday clothings is just keep on changing. Although some may appears again after few years different styles are developed.</P>
      <P>For the fashion of the future, I think it depends on the people's own personalities and develope their own styles which suits them the most. They can wear different kinds of clothing, like they design for themselves or those like history can wear those of victoriantime.</P>
      <P>For the colours, I think the metalic colours, especially silver, will be the most popular. As different kinds of farbics will be invented and. Maybe paper can also be a farbic use for make clothings and for those who like to wear new clothes everyday. They can be thrown away after wearing it and light enough to be carried around whenever you want to change your wearing.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
