<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR973*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Japanese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to let you know our unbelievable experiences which we had when we went to the theatre to see the musical show 'OVER THE RAINBOW.'</P>
      <P>First of all, I am a fan of Danny Brook but he was absent because of sick. It made me disappointed very much. Moreover, he made many mistakes.</P>
      <P>Secondly, although we had booked the tickets 3 days before we went to the theatre, we could not be given any discounts only because we had done at a travel agency.</P>
      <P>Finally, I am going to write about the theater, the Circle Theatre. The show supposed to start at 19:30, but it started at 20:15. Because of that, we missed the train and we had to stay one more night in London. It was your responsibility. We would like you to pay back the fee of the show and pay us that hotel's fee as well. I would recommend you to show that the restaurant is closed on Monday. I could not have dinner.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Fashion of the Future</P>
      <P>If you asked the young people what they spend their money the most in, most of them would answer 'clothes'. In these days, new fashions have been passing very quickly.</P>
      <P>From my point of view, young people tend to wear the clothes which they can show their skin. For example, short skirts and tops like an under-wear. I think young people would wear smaller clothes which they look like almost naked even in winter. I suppose that a scientist could invent new kinds of materials which are warm and thick. It could be happened that people wear the clothes which ancient people used to wear, like skirts made of leaves.</P>
      <P>Next, I predict about patterns of clothes. The animal-pattern is catching up now. It might be possible that the fish-pattern come up in 100 years.</P>
      <P>However, fashion changes too fast to predict. I think fashion changes very quickly so that people are interested in those changes.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
