<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR975*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Elise-Lune 48</P>
      <P>1093 La Conversion</P>
      <P>17th June 2000</P>
      <P>The Manager of</P>
      <P>The Circle Theatre</P>
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>Last week, I went to London in your theatre to see "Over the rainbow" and I had a disappointing evening.</P>
      <P>There problems were; Firstly, the famous actors Danny Brook and Tina Truelove weren't there for your musical show, I was unhappy to constat that it was different actors this evening. Secondly, the show of 19:30 only started at 20:15; Thirdly, your advertisement said: "Discounts available"; but it wasn't the case. Fourthly, the restaurant was closed for renovations and you don't have to propose us to go.</P>
      <P>Like you can see, I'm very disappointed for this evening out and I think it was a waste of time and money. That's why I ask you to give my money back. I ask you give me £20, back by check.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to hearing from you.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology changed your daily life?</P>
      <P>The technology is the future, and the present. For instance, internet. All the world is now connected on it. Internet is the "new" revolution of the communication and knowledge. It is now ten years that Internet exists, but we only used it for army and government. Now, everybody who work in commercial companies use every day Internet.</P>
      <P>The technology means too, every electrical machines, which don't stop to be developped. Another example, computers, every six months, something better is discovered.</P>
      <P>The modern technology has changed my daily life in every day. For instance, the meats, we don't cook our meals, everything is already done. Five minutes in the micro-waves and it's ready. The machines have replaced the work of the humains. We use every day technological machines without to know.</P>
      <P>All our life is symplifying by the machines for not waste the time to work on their developpment.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
