<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR976*0102*2000*02" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Ms Clark,</P>
      <P>I write you this letter because I want to tell you my experiences of the festival. I have spent two days at the "International Arts Festival" and I have to say that it was a good event but I think some details could be better the next time. For example, on the leaflet it was written that there will be stars and artists from around the world but they were only from six different countries. That was disappointing! Some concert halls were really small so that there was bad air and not enough place for everyone and you could not enjoy anything! What about plays and films? It was a small offer; I hope it will be larger the next time.</P>
      <P>But do not worry! There have also taken place very good attractions like dance shows, the art exhibition and listening to talks by writers,</P>
      <P>The reasonably-priced weekend ticket was a very good idea. This was a clever way to attract people's attention</P>
      <P>At last, I would like suggest a "pony-ride" for children, to attract families. Please tell my your opinion about this.</P>
      <P>Best regards</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>I think there are some possibilities for earning money. I would say the simplest way is to give lessons to pupils, for example, maths or english. There are also some schools which offer such a job. To teach pupils is not easy, of course. But I think that after some lessons the pupils will see that it is better if they sit down and learn their stuff. So it would be easier for the teacher! It is also not a dirty work, I mean you do not have to clean rooms or toilets of other people! And you do not need to carry heavy things or have stress with customers if you are working in a shop. To be a good teacher you especially need patient and good nerves! Not everybody has the ability to understand everything at once. And the money you get is not less</P>
      <P>So, if you like to b with people and help them and if you have talent to explain good then it would be the best, if you offer your help to the people!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
