<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR977*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan: Thank you for letting me know about my prize to Camp California in the USA. Here I will answear all the questions that you ask me, and I will ask you other things that you dind't mention. I'll like to organize my trip in July because is when I have vacations, also because is summer time in U.S.A, about acomodation at Camp I'll prefer tents, because it's a new expirence for me and I'll like to sleep in tents to have a great time at my new adventure. In my free time I like to play golf and swim, so I think that I'm good playing golf. I play every saturday and Sunday after that, I usually go to the pool because I love swimming, I think that those sports I will like to practice at the Camp. Helen I will like to ask you how many money we have to take to the Camp? What kind of cloth we have take? Thank you very much for your colaboration. sincerely Teresa Reina</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable</P>
      <P>Most of the time when we go to the shopping Center we have a lot of fun, we go to stores to see cloth, we also eat something like ice cream or French Fries, but not all the time shopping is enjoyable.</P>
      <P>Sometimes when we go shopping with someone who is not a good company, we usually don't have a great time, or when we know what we want to buy, but when we get to the store they don't have what we want, in that momentneatchristmasevery where is very crowd so we can't find what we are looking for with calm because everybody is pushing you to the other place that you want to go</P>
      <P>In that cases is when we don't enjoy shopping because we can't find what we are looking for and we have a bad time in the shopping center.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
