<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR978*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs. Ryan.</P>
      <P>I'm glad to receive your letter. I'm very happy to know that I have won the first prize. It will be great to spend two weeks at Camp California. First of all, I would like to say that the only month available from me to travel is July. I finish my classes on the 25th of June and August is for going with my parents to France. This has been scheduled 3 months ago.</P>
      <P>About accommodation, I would prefer the log cabins because I think they are more cleaner than the tents. While I'm stayin there I would like to practise tennis and basketball, as I have been playing both sports all my life, and I have to say that I am very good at both.</P>
      <P>There is one question I would like to ask you about the Camp. I would like to know if there are any washing machines or a place to wash our clothes.</P>
      <P>I hope this letter contains all the information you need from me. I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>From my point of view, the real question is: Who said that is enjoyable? Maybe for women, but not for me. I know that this sounds horrible, but sometimes it's what really happens. For men, sometimes is hard to go shopping with their partners. Sometimes that means a complete tour around all the fashion shops in town. And of course, we are not allowed to stop in a place that we like. The Sports Shop. You cannot lose the time because all the other shops could be closed when you arrive. And that is allways what we want. That's men's intention.</P>
      <P>Another point is to go a big area. Specially week-ends. Everyone pushing a trolley and crashing around. People should have to take a license to drive those things. Someone could be injured. And of course, the time to pay. A huge que that lasts half an hour or more and finishes with you completely freaked out. In conclusion, for me to go shopping is not enjoyable at all.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
