<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR979*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Spanish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I'm writing to you inform you about the dissapointing evening I had when I went to your theather to see the play called "OVER THE RAINBOW". According to the advertisement you gave, there have been some important differents.</P>
      <P>Firstly, the play started almost an hour late, and I went there to see Danny Brook, but there was a different actor on stage.</P>
      <P>Secondly, in the advertisement the discounts are available but in the tickets I bought they were no discount. Furthermore, I had planned to have a great dinner with my family in your restaurant and it was closed because the people who work in were on holidays. In addition to this, I have to tell you that it was the most horrible evening I had out and because of this I want to ask you if you could send me a refound of a part of the money I wasted there. I would be grateful if you do it.</P>
      <P>Finally, I want to tell you that it is not useful for you and your theather to cheat to your customers. If you do it, there will be no bussiness for you and no satisfaction for them.</P>
      <P>I look fordwad to hearing from you</P>
      <P>Your sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How has modern technology change my daily life?</P>
      <P>Nowadays, technology is the most useful tool that human beings have. It affects everyone who live in this planet and every activity made in it.</P>
      <P>In this case we are going to focus on me. Emilio Almodar, 18 years old, University Student, and the career I have choosen is Internacional Commerce or Market. I use technology every moment but I did not realise. For example, when I come back home from university and I call my friends, I am using it because at home we have very modern phones and fax and almost everybody in my family has a cellular phone and thing like that.</P>
      <P>We also have five computer, the latest versions of them, because they are useful for my father to work and for me to do some special works for University. This machines are connected to Internet, and it gives to my family too much facility to get every information we want, from how to prepare son drink to what was the result of the Sunday's football match. In addition to this we use the net to comunicate with some friends we have in U.S.A. It's really amazing.</P>
      <P>Apart from this, I don't spent my free time in technology. I prefer playing rugby and going out with friends, because technology is not all life, but it is only a little part of it.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
