<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR768*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Monday, the 5th of June 2000</P>
      <P>To the Circle Theatre's manager</P>
      <P>Dear Mister,</P>
      <P>I recently had the opportunity to see "over the rainbow" which was played last week in the Circle theatre.</P>
      <P>I'm writing to you because I'm very disappointed by the bad evening I spent there. Actually, I read the advertisment for the show and there were a few mistakes on it.</P>
      <P>In fact, Danny Brook didn't play or appear on stage last Tuesday, the role was played by another - a quite bad - actor, less famous than Danny Brook.</P>
      <P>I'm also sorry because I had to wait 45 mn before the pieces started. I can't accept waiting so long for the result I had. I was in London with some friends (we were students) and no discount was proposed or made for us. We had to pay £15 each for seeing a miserable pieces.</P>
      <P>After the piece, we waned to eat at the theater restaurant but we couldn't. It was apparently closed and I'm asking you why.</P>
      <P>As you can see, there are some (volontary?) mistakes on the advertisment you made. We didn't have a "perfect evening out" at all. That's why I'm asking you for giving us money back.</P>
      <P>I'm sure we'll find a compromise and I'm really looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>An unusual part of life.</P>
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets, and half a week later, all the school knew about me.</P>
      <P>I had a strange feeling then because it was just amazing to notice how money can attract so much people.</P>
      <P>I started to have a lot of new friends, they all wanted to be my best friend.</P>
      <P>Actually, my best friend would still remain Pat, even if he failed me. It's not easy to keep such an enormous secret and I couldn't keep it inside of me.</P>
      <P>I became quickly bored by this hypocrital attention they had for me. They didn't stop giving me advice or telling me what to do with my money. I always has been involved in many differents associations, which are fighting against AIDS or cancer. I knew at this moment what to do exactly and finally, I could refind my ordinary life as an unpopular student.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
