<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR980*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir/Madam:</P>
      <P>I am writing to ask about your advertisement and theatre show. I am a student in Liverpool, and recently I had a week's holiday in London. First day in London, I saw your advertisement which was very interesting to me. But I was really disappointed it.</P>
      <P>First of all, there was only one actor that was different from your advertisement. Also, it was certain to me to bought a discount tickets cause I am a student. But, it was not availiable.</P>
      <P>Second, I went to the theatre exactly seven thirty in the evening. However the show started 45 minutes later. I wasted time too much for waiting. It was not good to me, cause I had only one week holiday in London. Moreover the theatre restaurant was closed with the word "Stuff vacation" on the front door after the show. It was absolutely different from your leaflet.</P>
      <P>On the whole, I was really disappointed at that time. Could you do me my half of money back. I enclose my phone number and address.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
      <P>Lo Son Lin. </P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Fashion of the Future.</P>
      <P>Have you ever seen the film star wars?</P>
      <P>And did you notice something about fashion of the future?</P>
      <P>I think the people will wear convenient clothes with simple design in the future. Because the people will stay at home more than now with their computer. And they will use soft cozy cloths like cotton and silk.</P>
      <P>However, if they have some special day when like important public day or special day of their life, they will wear very different kinds of clothes which was you never seen before. Some of that will be very strange to our eyes, but some of others will be familiar to us. And they will use the most kinds of things like small stone to diamond etc. Maybe some peoples are nakid.</P>
      <P>It will be very interesting...</P>
      <P>Just imagine the way of future people's life. And you can see the their clothes also. </P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
