<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR984*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen</P>
      <P>Thank you for my prize! I never been in the USA and I should be glad to spend two weeks at Camp California.</P>
      <P>I can only have some holidays in July from the 3rd to the 17th with my husband at the same time, that is why I would like to travel during those two weeks.</P>
      <P>For the accommodation I would prefer to have tents because I used to travel in Campsites and I love it during summer, just to change the customs!!</P>
      <P>Concerning those activities I have choosen two of them. I enjoy swimming and anytime I have opportunities to swim I go. My second activity is painting because I love art and art history and I think that is better to join one sport and one and I do not really want to involve myself in a new activity that I don't know for my holidays.</P>
      <P>Please could you tell me about the weather if I need special clothes and about the money for the change if you don't mind. See you soon!</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>"Shopping is not always enjoyable" "Shopping today!" You decide to go in town or during holidays to move in a "shopping destination", that is mean that you need something special for you or someone else. You have the money and the time as you want. That's why it should be a great day! Save some money to go for shopping in Paris or Roma and see how is the French or Italian fashion on yourself! and after that you can make a stop in the Duty-free and buy some chipper souvenirs. Singapoor and many places in Asia are famous for the shopping, and it is really nice to go there with money to buy that you always wanted to. But even if shopping can means dream it can be boring sometimes. If you have no money and a friend ask you to come for shopping, it should be boring! and you become jealous against him and want him to do that quickly! or you are going to get nervous! And you can find too much people in shops, it is too hot or you can not have your right size or the right colour or flavour -- - then you get angry! or you decide to not spend money in shopping today, but in front of the shop. What is going on??</P>
      <P>So, you'd better to stay home today...</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
