<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR985*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>German</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Madam and Mister</P>
      <P>I am writing to you about your theatre: 'over the rainbow'. I went to a performance and I am very disappointed. Firstly, your advertisement said the actor would be Danny Brook, but it was not. It played an other one who played very bad. Secondly, the musical should start on 19.30, but we had to wait until 20.15! It was boring that nothing happend such a long time on the stage. Did you know that you have no discounts on your tickets? I could not believe that. Why do you write things on your advertisement when nothing is true? And finally, I would had my dinner after this disappointment musical and thougt I go to 'Theatre restaurant'. But how can it be, it was closed!</P>
      <P>This are too many negatives points for one evening. I am afraid, but I want my money back. I hope you do not disappoint my in this point.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully</P>
      <P>Pica Landen</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>'Fashion of the Future'! This is not a tabu by me and my friends. We have discussed about it a lot of times. I think it is important and necessary to think about it, because our children will live in the future.</P>
      <P>I have dout when somebody said, that the fashion of the future would be different. I think it is very difficult to change the clothes and the fashion so much again. We have so many kind of clothes and fashion behind our old generations. Maybe, the skirts will be shorter and the colours brighter, the shoes moderner so that you can not walk in them anymore.</P>
      <P>Maybe in 500 years, some people will live on the Mars and then, they have to wear other kind of clothes. But I don't think this clothes are going to be a fashion on the earth. They just look funny!</P>
      <P>See you in your next life!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
