<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR986*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan</P>
      <P>I am very happy and excited because I have won first prize in our competition. It is a pleasure for me. I am writing to enquire you about some doubts and to give information that you need about me.</P>
      <P>I have been working hard here in Portugal and I will be on holiday just in next july. Because of it I believe it is the best date for travel You asked me about accommodations or Camp California. I would prefer to stay in tents because I suppose I will have more contact with natural things than in log cabins.</P>
      <P>Another question that you asked me was about two activities I will have the chance to do there. I would love play tennis and basketball that I've been playing for six years. About tennis, I just started to play last year and I need to increase my technique too much.</P>
      <P>I would like to know something about money and clothes. Are they inclued in the prize? How much money I can spent during this time? I'd prefere if you give me this information as soon as you can.</P>
      <P>I am look forward to hearing from you</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
      <P>Rui Veloso</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>I am very happy with your letter that I received last week. I'm too excited and I have to tell you about a fantastic experience that I had last month.</P>
      <P>I suppose you know about "Portugal Pop Concert" that happened here in Rio de Mouro last month, aren't you?</P>
      <P>It was a marvellous concert and there were about 100,000 people there. I worked as a receptionist in the Vip room and I needed to look very happy during all time, what wasn't very difficult. You will can't believe how many famous people I known. I met Madonna and could talk with her for ten minutes. It was a dream and she was amazing with me.</P>
      <P>I didn't tell you, but I helped in this concert just by a chance. A friend of me gave up one week before and asked me if I would like to go in his place. I said "yes" and I am sure it was the best decision of my life.</P>
      <P>Of course I was very tired at the end of five days because of some stressed situations. However, these days were unforgatable to me.</P>
      <P>Hope to hearing from you soon</P>
      <P>With best wishes,</P>
      <P>Rui</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
