<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR989*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Portuguese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Saturday, June 17th, 2000.</P>
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about the musical show "Over the Rainbow" that has been presented in the Circle Theatre. As I was very anxious to see that show, I planned to go to the theatre in the last holiday, and I am completely disappointed with that.</P>
      <P>First of all, I have to say that the advertisement was totally different of what I saw there. For example, the actors that were announced to take part in the show were not Danny Brook and Tina Truelove, the discounts were not available and the principal point: it started forty five minutes later. Then, to complete this terrible night, the restaurant was closed. I wonder you could explain me why.</P>
      <P>Due to my huge dissatisfaction, I would like my money back, as you do not make what was advertised.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully,</P>
      <P>MANUELA REVES RAVERNO</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>The influence of modern technology</P>
      <P>Every day, the growth of the modern technology increases in the whole world and it is becoming essential in everybody's life. Today, almost no one can live without, for example, a television, a radio or electricity in their homes.</P>
      <P>The huge growth of technology has brought lots of good aspects to my life, like the facility to be informed about everything that is happening around the world with the best image in my cab TV and in my computer. Without leaving my bedroom, I can go anywhere using the Internet. On the other hand, the excess of comodity can led us, in the future, to a completely "cold" world, because of the distance between people that can be caused. Another bad points can be mentioned, like the polution for example.</P>
      <P>Despite the bad aspects that the modern technology can bring, in my opinion, if the governments tryed to do the best, and if everybody contribute with a little bit, we can solve the main problems and only take advantage of the benefits to our lifes.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
