<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR991*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Dutch</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thanks for your letter. I have reading the letter and I was very surprised that I have won the first prize.</P>
      <P>About the time when I like to travel is only July, because in the summer is it very busy at work. People where I working with they are going on holiday in Juni and August. So hey need me at work in that months.</P>
      <P>Further the accomodation I prefer at Camp California is the log cabin. Because, at first when I was a little child we were staying every holiday in a small house and I like that. At second, I don't like tents and I don't get used to it, so I prefer log cabins.</P>
      <P>About the different activities we like them all, but If I choose two I take sailing and tennis. In the summer I'm sailing races almost every weekend and I have my own sailing clothes. I'm not very good in Tennis but I can practise on my travel.</P>
      <P>Finally, I have one question about the money. Which things I must paid for on my travel?</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Dear Kim,</P>
      <P>Thanks for your letter. How are you? With me is everything fine and the pop concert was great.</P>
      <P>I enjoyed helping at the popconcert, but it's very stressful work. You always walk from side to side to move things and there's no break. Some other work what I have done was to lead the people to there places. We have worked the whole day and luckily at least we had some food.</P>
      <P>The most beautiful things were that we saw famous singers and I spoke with Robbie Williams. He's friendly and very handsome off course. If you see the famous singers in reality they are different and the most singers they haven't time for you.</P>
      <P>Another thing I have done was the make up only for about fifteen minutes. That was very nice, because I didn't expected that. There were some people they gave me some advise to clean the face and etc.</P>
      <P>Finally, it was a very nice day with great experience.</P>
      <P>Loves</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
