<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR993*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>To the manger of the Circle Theatre Mr Smith</P>
      <P>Caen, Saturday June 17th</P>
      <P>Mr Smith,</P>
      <P>I have recently been to London on a holiday trip so I decided to spend my free-time going to the musical show you were advertising for. It seemed very attractive and the different informations on the ad pushed me into going to it.</P>
      <P>Unfortunately, I've been really disappointed. I'm not keen on liars Mr Smith and I think that you've lied to such naive tourist like us: some brilliant actors were supposed to play the part and we only had different and pityful ones. Moreover the show was expected to begin at 19.30 but it was delayed of forty-five minutes. It is a shame! I ought not to talk about the restaurant closed for no apparent reasons</P>
      <P>You had promised a perfect evening but I spend an horrible one and you ruined my holiday!</P>
      <P>What are you mistaken us for, Mr Smith? Foolish idiots? We did not deserve such bad show. That's why I want my money back! Now! Otherweise I'll have to put some others ads in London saying that your show is just a fake!</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>How modern technology changed your daily life!</P>
      <P>To begin with, I'd like to underline how the place of technology has increased since a couple of years. With the end of the Second world war and the economic prosperity many goods like TV, washing-machine, etc. became cheaper and available. Nowadays, the Internet and the mobile phone with the developpment of satellite seem to take the lead. Do they affect my daily life?</P>
      <P>As far as I am concerned, the first way modern technology influence me is in my work: the internet has become such an incredible tool, I can make research about everything I want, find informations for lectures for example or exercices. The internet is really the widest source of knowledge.</P>
      <P>Nevertheless, new technology has made me become more lazy. I spend a lot of free time watching TV, or surfing on the Internet or playing the computer. Maybe it change me into a kind of self-centered person, a loner.</P>
      <P>But the positive way new technology have changed my life is in way to communicate. It made it possible to discover, to talk with new people on the Internet but also to join and to be joined by my friends or parent. I can send e-mails or use the mobile phone. But we should not forget that it's only tools and emphazise human relationships.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
