<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR995*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Catalan</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>&lt;16</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Mrs. Ryan</P>
      <P>Before answering your letter (which I have just recieved) about the prize of the competition I recently won, I'd like to tell you thank you very much for giving me the chance of gong to the USA. It is just a dream come true!</P>
      <P>I have been asked to say when I would like travel. There's only one month for that: July (as I am working all the year round and I am not available to leave my job).</P>
      <P>About the accomodation; I rekon I would prefer to be in a log cabin instead of a tent, since it is more comfortable.</P>
      <P>During my two week sat Camp California, I'd like to practice climbing and surfing, whose basics I know perfectly well.</P>
      <P>I am quite good at both because I do usually practice them. Furthermore, I love to go through such sports!</P>
      <P>In addition to this, I would like to know the ammount of money I should bring, as well as the kind of clothes that i could need and the sort of people that I will find there.</P>
      <P>Don't hesitate to contact me if there's any problem, and thank you very much again.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely,</P>
      <P>Bola</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Hi Kim!</P>
      <P>How are you?</P>
      <P>It has been so long since I wrote to you for last time...</P>
      <P>Hey, guess what: I gave a hand to a friend at a pop concert!</P>
      <P>It was great, and I got my entrance for free!</P>
      <P>It happened by chance: I was walking down the street when I bumped into Jane, my old friend, who asked me if I wanted to join her and a couple of mates to help at the concert.</P>
      <P>I agreed unwillingly, as I couldn't imagine how a pop concert looked like... but when I came in I changed my mind!</P>
      <P>None of the groups were known nowadays, but I belive they are well on their way to becoming famous bands.</P>
      <P>My tasks were serving drinks and some other stuff, and stay there after the concert to clean everything. This was the best part because when everyone was gone, Billy Joel arrived to give his support to the beginers!!! What was a fella like that doing in such a place? I couldn't belive my very eyes... Jane took a photograph of us toghether. I'll send you a copy as soon as I can.</P>
      <P>Lots of Kisses from</P>
      <P>Bola</P>
      <P>xxx</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
