<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR996*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Thai</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>17 June 2000.</P>
      <P>Dear Sir and Madam</P>
      <P>I am recently spending a week's holiday in London, and I have just visited your theatre to see a musical show and I would like to complain with couple of things.</P>
      <P>First, I like to complain about the main features which is an actor, he might have been well known in England, but on the night, he performed abysmally. Secondly a lot of people were not very impressed with the time, because all of us at least have to wait for almost an hour until the show start.</P>
      <P>Also, a lot of people were enitieising about the facilities which said to be serve in an advertisement. For example, the discount for the tickets were not available, and especially a lot of people were disappointed that they can not visit the theatre restaurant because it was closed, due to the cleaner forgotten to clean up the mess from the previous party.</P>
      <P>Lastly, I think I could not call this as my perfect evening, so I would like to ask for a refund, and I hope as a Manager of London's newest theatre, you would handle the situation favourbly.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully.</P>
      <P>Seung Phittikhun.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets, although he's one of my best friend, but sometimes, he's a real pain in a butt.</P>
      <P>Pat and I knew each other very well, because we are neighbours, so since we've met, Pat and I always got on very well. We always go to the same school, and he's often make more friends than I do, and everytime he's always introduce them to me. Even though Pat has got a great sense of humour and wonderful personality, he'll never be able to keep any secreats for anyone, even himself.</P>
      <P>Although, we are great friends, but sometimes people can make such a stupid mistake, and so there was one time when Pat and I had a fight, it all started when once I accidently, took the wrong bag back to my house, and there was lady's knickers inside, I was so nervous and embarassing, so I tell Pat and there he goes, he tell every single students in the school that I've stolen girl knickers, and everyone started to call me a pervert.</P>
      <P>So that's when we had a fight. Anyway Pat eventually apologized to me and we still being best mates as ever.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
