<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR997*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Korean</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir</P>
      <P>I am writing to complain about a terrible performance in your theatre. I had expected to see the fantastic musical show. However, everything was not performed as you had advertised.</P>
      <P>Firstly, there was a different actor/actress who I have never heard their name before. Even though they performed their parts excellently I was very disappointed about your incorrect advertisement.</P>
      <P>Secondly, the musical was not started on time. It was going to start 19.30. However, It was started 45 minutes later. Afterall, I lost my find return train after show.</P>
      <P>thirdly, there was no discount about my ticket and the theatre restaurant was closed because of being repaired.</P>
      <P>Finally. It was perfectly terrible evening out. So, I want you to give my money back to me. If you don't do that, I will tell public what you are wrong in your advertisement.</P>
      <P>Your sincerely.</P>
      <P>Yeung</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>When I was a yong child, I used to be interested in reading a scientific fiction. Interestingly, nowadays, I live in the scientific world which I read in the book.</P>
      <P>Probably, I started useing mobile-phone 5 years ago. Before using mobile-phone, if someone wanted to talk to me immediately, they couldn't find me where I was. However, nowadays, it is easy to find me because of mobile-phone.</P>
      <P>I used to write a letter to my friends. However, After appearing Internet, I've sent e-mail to my friends. It takes just a few minutes to send e-mail to some one. I just check my e-mail before going to bed everyday.</P>
      <P>In conclusion, Because of modern technology, I'm very comfortable and do something effectively with computer and mobile phone.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
