<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR998*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P> Mrs Ryan</P>
      <P>When I received your letter, I was very surprised and happy because I don't remember that I did this competition.</P>
      <P>First I can travel only in July because, I will finish school at the end of June and I will pass my exam in Septemeber; so I have to repeat it a lot during the month of August.</P>
      <P>To answer your second question, I choose the accomodation in tents because I like to sleep outside.</P>
      <P>For the activities, I choose the Golf and the Surfing (that wasn't easy to decide which activities I will do, cause almost choice interested me)</P>
      <P>I tried the golf twice, I'm really bad but I hope to do much progress.</P>
      <P>I never did surfing, but every time I see surfing on television I find this magic.</P>
      <P>I have just two questions.</P>
      <P>Can I wash any clothes there?</P>
      <P>How many money will I have to take with me?</P>
      <P>Please phone me to answer my two questions.</P>
      <P>Thanks for all</P>
      <P>Mar</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Hello Kim</P>
      <P>I'm sorry I can only write now because last week I have too much work.</P>
      <P>As you asked me I will tell you about the pop concert of last month.</P>
      <P>With my friend Miko we looked for a little job during a week-end and one evening we met a guy who wanted to buy some drinks in the pop concert and so we told him that we were agree to help him at the bar.</P>
      <P>It was a wonderful week-end: we were opposite to the singers and we have seen every concert without buying any tickets entry! (we were include in the staff of the concert)</P>
      <P>At the end we have 1200. - of benefice and each us take 400. - for himself</P>
      <P>I particulary like seeing all this people, and I meet a lot of new friend there.</P>
      <P>For next year we search for a new barwoman.</P>
      <P>Write to me soon and tell me if you want to join us for 2001.</P>
      <P>Love Mar</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
