<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR769*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Chinese</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Kowloon, Hong Kong.</P>
      <P>July 17, 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Sir,</P>
      <P>I am writting to complain about a musical show last weekend when I was in London.</P>
      <P>I felt very upset about you advertisement was totaly different between the musical show. Firstly, I could not buy a discount ticket as you mentioned. Secondly, the show started at 20:15 p.m instead of 19:30 p.m. Thirdly, a theatre restaurant was being closed. But the worst thing is the actors were not Danny Brook and Tina Truelove., It was really let me down!!</P>
      <P>How dared you could show "You perfect evening out" in you advertisement. It was very rediculous!</P>
      <P>To be honestly, I would like you could return the money back to me. And explain what had happened.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing you return back.</P>
      <P>Thank for you patience.</P>
      <P>Your faithfully,</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. Although, Pat is very smart and intelligent. She like to talk with other people. She has a open-mind. So, she got many friend</P>
      <P>Lily was one of her best friend before three year. She enjoyed sharing everthing with Pat whatever what it was. Nick was Lily husband. Her husband was being fried last year. Lily felt very nervous about their financial problem and their future. As they went to getting a baby. She told to Pat about what had happened in her family. And what she was worried. Of course, she knew Nick didn't like her to tell other what about his private. She told to Pat that she didn't want other people know it except her. Pat also promised not to tell other people.</P>
      <P>But in one gathering party, their friend want to show their concern, they went to ask about Nick and send him sympathy. This let Nick very embrassed and got hurt. Finally, they got seperated.</P>
      <P>Today, Pat and Lily still are friend. But Lily never tell her what she really want and what her really thought the thing. Pat felt very sorry about that was too late.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
