<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR999*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>French</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>. I would like to travel only July because I would be in schools holydays and the weather is hot and the sea's temperature is less cold than in winter. I would like to travel in July to be sure it would not rain during the trip which is boring?! And when the sun is shining you are relax and you feel good.</P>
      <P>. I would prefer tents to sleep at Camp California because it is fun to sleep in tents to compare in a house. You are in communication with the nature and you can hear the insects. And we only need to sleep and not to cook or watch T.V... It is very nice to stay in tents wich are strong and confortable.</P>
      <P>. From the list below, the two activities I will choose are Tennis and sailing. Tennis because I play Tennis and I am classed 15-5. I like very much Tennis because it is a technical and physical sport. And you need strategie to win the match. It is nice to play tennis outside in the court when the weather is hot. But you can't play if there is too much wind, the ball becomes incontrolable!</P>
      <P> Windsurfing because I pratise it for a long time. You can do it alone. I like windsurfing because it is a sport of speed and slide like skiing, surfing. you need technics to move the windsurf. You must know how to use the wind and you have great sensations!</P>
      <P>I would like to ask you questions: Must I take with me my clothes?</P>
      <P>Is there a washing machine at Camp California?</P>
      <P>Do I need some money to pay the meals!</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>you have recently had a class discussion about shopping. Now your english teacher has asked you to write a composition, giving your opinions on: "shopping is not always enjoyable"</P>
      <P>In fact, shopping is not always enjoyable because sometimes you want to buy articles but you don't have enough money!</P>
      <P>You don't find anything interesting in the shop.</P>
      <P>You can hesitate to choose an article. Which is the best article to take? The seller can be not very nice and watch you all the time. You don't find your size or the good color in the article. The article can be too expensive.</P>
      <P>It looks fragil and it could break easily.</P>
      <P>Your must test several shops and compare the price, the quality of the articles. So you must walk all the day or go by car. And the weather must be fine if you walk in the town.</P>
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable if there is a lot of people in the shops because you can't move and choose the article and be cool!</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
