<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1000*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Polish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Madam,</P>
      <P>I am very glad that I have won first prize in your competition and I can go to the United States. It has always been my dream to go there and to be able to see that beautifull country. Now my dream will come true.</P>
      <P>I will try to give you some information about me. The best time to travel for me is July because I am working and only then I can have holidays. I would be pleased if it is possible.</P>
      <P>About accommodation, I would prefer a tent because I have never slept in the tent and I would like to try it. It will be very interesting for me because normaly I have not a lot of time to do activities. I would prefer swimming because I very like it and I am trying to swim anywhen I have got some time, and painting because I have finished painting course and I have some practice with this.</P>
      <P>That is very nice that every costs are paited for but I would like to ask you how much money I should to take with me because I do not now anything about prizes in the U.S.A. and please to tell me if I need anything to paint because it would be difficult to take it with me, so if I will need to take everything I will just change this activite.</P>
      <P>Thank you for the letter and I am looking forward an answer.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="4">
      <P>Hallo Kim,</P>
      <P>Thank you for answer on my last letter, I hope your sister's health is better than on last time and she is all right.</P>
      <P>My life is a little bit changed after that concert on last month. I will try to explain you why.</P>
      <P>As you now I was helping to make every decorations before and during the concert. It was realy wonderfull new experience for me. I have never before met so many people and I didn't now that is so hard to keep everything in order during the concert. Now I now that everything need patient, time and hard work before someone will sing any record on scene. The people were wonderfull, they was helping each other with everything and it was a lot of easier to do. It is very nice feeling when you need help and is so many people which want to help you. I will never forget this concert and those people. It was good experience which I will never forget. I hope I will be able to do it again.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
