<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1002*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Russian</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Helen Ryan!</P>
      <P>This is just a note to confirme you, what I had recive your letter.</P>
      <P>I am so happy to have won this first prize in your competition. I will be happy to be for two weeks at Camp California in the U.S.A.</P>
      <P>I am understud from your letter, what all accommodation and travel costs are paid for me, including transport to and from the airport.</P>
      <P>To answer your questions, I would like to tell you, what my travel can be possible only on July, because I will have the Cambrigge exam till 1 July.</P>
      <P>Would it be possible to have accomodation at Camp California in a tent, because I didn't have chance to sleep into it.</P>
      <P>And would it be possible to do swimm and surf. I am very good swimming. I done it since I remeber me. In surf I am not good at all. I have been driming about this activitie since I had 10 years old.</P>
      <P>I would like to know about how many peopl will stay with me into the tent, and have a take with me special clothes for doing serf.</P>
      <P>I will contact you, if I will have more questions.</P>
      <P>I look forward to beeing at Camp California in the U.S.A.</P>
      <P> Your faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>I like shopping. I love to do shopping. But if only I have money!! Ore some money. Shopping can't be enjoyable if you don't have money to spend. It is better to stay at home and read a good book.</P>
      <P>I'm thinking do shopping in the big spaise like Harrodss it's not plesure. Because it's crowding of people. I'd like to be in small boutiques, and I would rather go to shopping along and during the weekand time. Because I don't like to give some advisewilly. And go to shopping at the end of weekand it's not for me. I don't know what I can tell you more? I'm sorry. Drop me a line or give me a call if my writing will not so good for you. Because I'll be out next week. And I'll mees your lessons.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
