<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1004*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Turkish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>26-30</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Mrs Helen RYAN</P>
      <P>Competition Organiser</P>
      <P>USA</P>
      <P>13th JUNE.2000</P>
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>I received your letter in this morning and thank you very much for your kind letter and chosing me.</P>
      <P>I can only travel in July because I had already booked and fully paid for a middle-east holiday, from 25th of July till end of August. If you can arrange my departure time from 1st of July it should be convenience for me.</P>
      <P>I would like to stay in tents because I had much great times in tents during my previous holidays, if it is suitable for you.</P>
      <P>I want to do this two activities while I am at the camp: Sailing and photography. I have great experience for sailing. I used to work for a sailing company in Turkey. And I have done certificate for using radio (VHF). I have knowladge about navigation, engine, ropes and knots and sails as well.</P>
      <P>My other passion is photography, especially I like black and white photography. I have a camera which is a called Minolta X300. That is a manual camera. I know to develop films and print them.</P>
      <P>I have doubt about clothes, money and immigration rules of the USA. please could you write me how is the weather like there, what kind of clothes I need and how much money I should have.</P>
      <P>I look forward to hearing from you.</P>
      <P>Yours Sincerely.</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>I like shopping but I had a bad experience about my recent shopping. I went out for shopping and to get some ideas about new brand computers and products. First of all I went to a local shop but I couldn't find enough selection of products.</P>
      <P>Then I visited another one, in Cambridge Street. It was very crowded, I could hardly walk in the shop. I decided to by a CD room driver for my old computer. When I approached to the cashier I suddenly noticed my wallet had gone. My money, travel card and credit card. It was a nightmare there were pickpokets in the shop. I went to the shop assistance but it was useless.</P>
      <P>As soon as possible I phoned to my bank for cancelation of my credit card but they had already used it. it costs me about £500. This experience has changed my shopping habit, now I do all my shopping on the internet. But I'm not sure how it is safe. But you must be always award against to pickpokets.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
