<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1006*0100*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Greek</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>21-25</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>13th June 2000</P>
      <P>Dear Mrs Ryan,</P>
      <P>Thank you very much for your letter. I was really surprised and very happy when I read that I have won the first prize. First of all because I have never been to California and second because it's the first time I have ever won something.</P>
      <P>The only time that is possible for me to travel is July, because I am working for a bank and this is the only month I can go on holiday.</P>
      <P>For my stay in California I would prefer the accommodation in tents because this gives me a feeling of freedom and adventure and it is quite different to my live here in Greece.</P>
      <P>The activities I would like mot to do are climbing and surfing. In my free time I have climbed a lot of mountains in the surrounding area so I can say, that I am quite good in climbing. But I have never 'surfed' in my live, so that is an activity I have to learn.</P>
      <P>Last but not least there are some things I would like to know: What kind of wheather do you have in California? Is it very hot? What kind of clothes should I bring with me?</P>
      <P>And what about money? How much money Should I take with me? Are there any activities which are not included? And my last question: how many persons are going to stay in each tent.</P>
      <P>I'm looking forward to hearing from you soon.</P>
      <P>Yours sincerely</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="3">
      <P>Many people, especially women, love shopping. If you go to the centre of every big town you will see people walking from store to store searching for something to wear or to buy to eat. But shopping is not always enjoyable.</P>
      <P>First of all because of the big variety in the store. Very often you don't know what to buy because we don't have only three or four different sport shoes to choose from, not, we have to choose out of twenty or thirty such as Nike, adidas or Fila.</P>
      <P>And very often you have to pay a lot of money for the product you want.</P>
      <P>Another cause is that shops and stores are often overcrowded. Very often you can hardly move because of the crowds of people.</P>
      <P>And many people are in a hurry, so don't wonder if other people have not tolerance and patience to wait and hit you with their shopping cars.</P>
      <P>Of course there are a lot of other causes why shopping isn't always great fun, but the last cause, which is very important for me is that shopping is becoming more and more impersonal. That means that there are more and more big supermarkets and big stores, where noone has time for you to show you or explain things to you such as what kind of bicycle is the best for me, no one to talk to and noone to complaine. That is the most important reason why I only like to go shopping in little stores, where I have peace and quiet and very often nothing to complaine about.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
