<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<HOO version="2.1">
  <HEAD sortkey="TR1008*0102*2000*01" sourcetype="FCE">
    <CANDIDATE>
      <LANGUAGE>Swedish</LANGUAGE>
      <AGE>16-20</AGE>
    </CANDIDATE>
  </HEAD>
  <BODY>
    <PART id="1">
      <P>Dear Sir or Madam,</P>
      <P>I write to you to complain about the dreadful evening I had when I went to see your show at the Circle Theatre the 9th june.</P>
      <P>To start with the famous actors Danny Brook and Tina Truelove didn't perform as told. They were replaced by some unknown actors who had certainly never performed a musical. If I had only one reason to ask you for my money back; it would be the latter.</P>
      <P>But to add to this I had to make a long queue to get a full price ticket when instead I had brought my student card on the purpose of getting a discount which had been advertised but didn't in fact exist.</P>
      <P>The show which was to start at 19.30 only began at 20.15 and therefore me and my friends weren't able to find a restaurant when we had to because the theatre restaurant was closed on sanitary reasons.</P>
      <P>For this deceiving and uncorrect advertisement and for all the given reasons, I ask you for an average refund of five pounds per ticket.</P>
      <P>Yours faithfully</P>
    </PART>
    <PART id="2">
      <P>Unfortunately, Pat wasn't very good at keeping secrets. This feature didn't allow you to tell him much about yourself. He wasn't really wicked, he merely didn't understand to keep his mouth shut, especially at school where every little unimportant thing about your so called "private life" runs three laps around the schoolyard before you learn it although you are the most concerned about it and didn't even know.</P>
      <P>Well, some people just don't care, some are bothered and feel ill at ease. But small drama can grow up as children are very sensitive.</P>
      <P>There is one point I want to make clear, I don't begrudge Pat anything. I believe this is a rule of society, it's a sort of group behaviour, and belongs to the childhood and the teenage. We all speak or have spoken of our neighbours, family, classmates, workmates, friends in bad terms. That is only human.</P>
      <P>According to me what is more to regret is when now we full-growns continue to act with this bad habit. The criticism spirit has to be preserved but we must keep our secrets. What allows us to reveal parts of someone others privacy, nothing.</P>
    </PART>
  </BODY>
</HOO>
